I like you.
I don't care what others think about us.
I like you just the way you are, Hyun Ji.
[Episode 10]
What brings you here?
Are you Professor Joo Hye Sung?
Yes, I am.
Do you know Bong Pal?
Park Bong Pal.
- Yes.
- Ah.
I'm like an uncle to him.
I heard his professor worked here,
so I decided to stop by and say hello.
Is that right? It's nice to meet you.
You seem very familiar.
Have we ever met before?
Come to think of it, I think we saw
each other around the neighborhood.
No.
It was a very long time ago.
I'm not sure.
- I don't remember.
- I see.
Hello.
- We got lunch.
- Go ahead and eat first.
I see it's lunchtime. Forgive me
for taking so much of your time.
- Not at all.
- Please enjoy your lunch.
Please take good care of my Bong Pal.
Yes.
Excuse me then.
Ah, Monk.
- I'll see you next time.
- Yes.
- This looks so good.
- Eat slowly.
Don't worry about anything.
Got it?
Monk Myung Chul.
I guess he's not here.
I guess so.
What did he watch again?
Bong Pal, is this you?
You are so cute! When was it?
This was my middle school graduation.
Why was Monk Myun Chul
watching this all of a sudden?
He kept mentioning
my graduation earlier.
- Come on, let's watch a little more.
- There's nothing to watch. Forget it.
I'm curious about your childhood.
Forget it. Just watch it next time.
When next time?
Just next time.
Who recorded this?
Oh, my father.
He used to work as
a producer a long time ago.
So it must have been a copy of his.
Did your father record all
those videos in that room too?
Yes.
- What did he film?
- I don't know. Random stuff.
I've never watched them.
I was wondering...
Why do you live
seperately from your dad?
It just... happened to be that way.
I'm going to wash up.
Okay.
There's something
suspicious about that punk.
- Is it good?
- It's totally good. Sit down.
- Should we go inside?
- No, it's not cold at all.
Goodness, goodness.
Let's turn it off.
- I'm going to bed.
- Oh, yeah.
Good night.
Okay.
Why isn't it turning on?
Why aren't the lights turning on?
There we go.
One, two, three.
Who are you?
Where is the manager?
What brings you here instead of him?
I saw something.
- I think it was a ghost.
- A ghost, you say?
Ghost. Ghost... G...
G... a ghost, you say?
Wait a minute.
You've got bags under your eyes.
Okay, give me your right hand.
It's okay, it's okay.
His pulse is so weak.
You're able to see ghosts because
there's darkness surrounding you!
We can shine light upon you.
Then what do I have to do?
We will take care of everything.
You, sir...
You just have to prepare the cash.
Up front. Yes, over there.
The right side, the right side.
Bong Pal, this ghost has been
seen all over the school.
But the way it looks is very peculiar.
Is this the right place?
Bong Pal, do you see something?
No, it's not here.
I think it left this place.
- No.
- What about you? Do you see it?
There's no ghostly energy.
Ah.
What is that?
- Ah, that scared me!
- It's here! It's here!
It's here! Wait for me!
- Something is strange.
- Yeah.
What the heck!
- Get it! Get it!
- Bong Pal, we caught the ghost!
We caught the ghost!
- I'm not afraid of ghosts!
- I'm not a ghost, I'm a person!
- No, you're not!
- Hold on! Hold on!
Senior Hyun Kyu?
It's you, isn't it?
Senior?
Let go! Let go!
Senior.
What... what is this?
Geranium helps with breathing
and strengthens your immunity.
This bracelet is made from geranium.
You can't take it, okay?
I've counted all of them.
Senior, what happened to you?
Life is tough.
Senior, that guy earlier.
He must've been hiding
in the school for a very long time.
Yes, it seems that way.
Getting hired must really be hard.
I heard he was a genius
when he was attending school.
What the heck is a geranium pyramid?
He's being chased by
debt collectors because of it.
What is this?
Why are you carrying this?
This is not... this is not
the exorcism fee, is it?
You catch on real quick!
You know, I was listening
to that senior's story
and this bath mat is
made from natural geranium.
It helps with breathing, builds
immunity, and... produces endorphins.
I can't stop laughing ever
since I put this bracelet on.
Bong Pal, this geranium
bracelet is for you.
Here, try it on.
You keep the healthy stuff.
I want money.
I have to go to class. See you.
Why did you accept this?
He has no money!
What was I supposed to do?
Ah, how about we give
this to your grandma?
My grand...
What's this?
Yeah, what is this?
Are these mosquito bites?
Hold on...
There's nothing to look at.
The alcohol level has
been confirmed from her blood.
She cracked her skull and broke
her collarbone and femur from the fall.
There's visible injury
to her head. That's all.
I see.
She killed the person she loved
and killed herself because of the guilt.
- It's like a novel.
- Let's not go that far.
It's just a suicide.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
This case is not your concern.
Why are you interested in it?
Someone is making me interested.
Who?
That professor?
- Yes.
- Senior.
The chief wants us to hurry up
and take care of the Wooyongdong case.
Get going. You must be busy.
Yes, thank you.
Are you going to head
straight up to Seoul?
You have the address of Professor
Joo Hye Sung's mother, right?
Yes, but why do you ask?
You're not thinking of
going there now, are you?
Get in.
The chief is going to
throw a fit if he finds out.
I'll go by myself then.
Let's go.
No!
Dad, where are you?
He's at it again!
When are you coming?
Come quickly! Mom's not home either!
Dad, come quickly!
Brother!
Brother. Brother.
You're injured! Oh no!
Brother! Brother, wake up!
- Brother!
- Move... Move!
Brother, what's the matter with you?
Don't do this. You're scaring me.
Brother.
Brother!
- What are you doing? What are you doing?
- Don't!
"Hyun Ji, I don't know when
we'll ever meet again..."
Now you're writing love letters?
It's going to get wrinkled.
It's going to get wrinkled!
- Are you okay?
- Did you just hit me?
You shouldn't have
taken it away from me.
Did you just hit me because of a ghost?
It wasn't intentional.
Let me see, let me see. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
My eye.
- I can't see.
- You can't see?
I can't see.
I can't.... Shim Chung!
Shim Chung! Shim Chung, where are...
- You can see.
- You're right.
You... You... I'm going to
put you in a mental institute.
Do it.
Yes, this is Blood Sausage Soup,
your 24-hour exorcism service.
I'm Choi Chun Sang, how may I help you?
[Notice]
Professor, there's no lecture today.
You're not sick, are you?
- There's no lecture today.
- Perfect! Should we go somewhere?
All you want to do is have fun.
At least I study hard.
[Senior Chun Sang]
Hello. Are you
Professor Joo Hye Sung's mother?
Oh, thank you.
What brings you here from Seoul?
I apologize for the sudden visit.
We came here to ask you a question.
- Is it about Hye Sung?
- Yes.
Has your son come to visit you recently?
He does visit often.
Do you remember when that was?
- Excuse me?
- The day your son came to visit you.
By any chance, do you remember?
Well...
I don't remember the exact day.
- What's the matter?
- Senior.
- What?
- Over there.
You drove quite a distance.
So, did you confirm everything?
I don't know. You should
ask your mother directly.
Sorry to bother you.
Goodbye, ma'am.
He hasn't returned.
My mom is looking for him
but it's been over an hour already.
Soo Kyung was looking at me.
- You saw a ghost?
- Yes.
Do you think she'll hurt Hyun Bin?
Is there a place he usually goes to?
My parents probably already went there.
What about a place
Soo Kyung would go to?
Over there.
He probably went here.
He scattered her ashes here.
Over there!
Bong Pal, over there.
- Senior, drive faster.
- I'm going as fast as I can.
Step on it! Step on it more!
Step on it!
We're almost there.
- What the heck?
- What's wrong with this thing?
There's smoke!
I hope it doesn't explode!
I'm going to go first.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Why are you trying
to kill him when you should save him?
What are you talking about?
Why would I kill Hyun Bin?
- I'm trying to save him right now!
- Soo Kyung.
I'll see you soon.
No!
Hyun Bin, please don't do this.
Soo Kyung.
It's brain cancer.
At most, you have
three months to live.
What about surgery?
Surgery is possible,
but it's not guaranteed.
I...
That's dangerous.
Who are you?
Ow, that hurts.
Are you determined to kill yourself?
- It not like it's the end of the world!
- It is the end of the world for me.
Ah, I see. I didn't know.
Did you think I was going to say that?
Look, I don't know what your story is
but why are you giving up
already? You're too young.
No one knows the future. You have
to live each day to its fullest.
Carpe diem. Don't you
know what that means?
Something good might happen.
So be strong, okay?
- Be strong.
- You can do it! Fighting!
I can do it! Fighting!
Go home safely.
People follow traffic signals, got it?
Oh, I have to go now!
- I'd like to buy these, please.
- Yes, sir!
You made the right decision.
Coffee is much better than alcohol.
Here you go. Goodbye... wait! Here!
- Take this.
- You can drink that.
Oh, and...
Hi!
- You're here.
- Did you wait too long?
No... well, I waited
for a really long time.
- Be careful.
- I will.
Be careful!
I need to go somewhere for several days.
I'll be right back.
All right.
- Don't take too long.
- When I return...
I'll come straight to you.
Okay, have a safe trip.
Doctor.
The surgery will go well, right?
I will do my best.
I...
I want to live.
- Have a good night.
- Thank you.
Oh my, Hyun Bin called me.
I'm sorry.
I might not be able to return to you.
That's why I wanted
to tell you the truth.
The truth is, I...
Soo Kyung, I miss you.
Hyun Bin, are you okay?
Can you think clearly?
I'll go get Mom and Dad.
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Can you answer the phone, please?
Hello?
What did you say?
No... No!
No! No!
[Shin Soo Kyung]
Shin Soo Kyung... Soo Kyung.
No...
I'm sorry, Soo Kyung.
If I hadn't called you then...
No, it wasn't your fault.
So please don't try to die.
I tried that so I could come see you.
Why did I have the surgery done?
So I could be with you
and live with you.
If you die and get to be with me...
I wouldn't like that.
It would make me more sad.
Soo Kyung, please...
I was very happy that I was with you.
Now I will leave with our happy memories.
I'm asking you.
- Soo Kyung.
- Hyun Bin.
Please promise me that
you won't hurt yourself again.
You promised me, right?
- I love you.
- I love you too.
I will always love you.
Soo Kyung...
He'll be all right, right?
He will be okay.
Senior, I will
return the clothes tomorrow.
Sure. You did well today.
Bong Pal, wait a minute.
Well... can you give this
to Hyun Ji for me?
Tell her it is from my heart.
- In Rang.
- Yes?
- About Hyun Ji...
Hyun Ji...
- In Rang.
- Yes?
- About Hyun Ji...
She already likes someone.
What?
See you tomorrow.
It hurts...
You fool.
What is it?
We will also have to separate
like them some day.
Probably.
So what? What matters
is that I'm happy now.
Worrying about the future
won't change anything.
Hey, you're the one
who told me not to worry.
You're right.
By the way, In Rang will be okay, right?
He will be okay.
This is why you should've listened to me.
How can you be in love with a ghost?
I agree.
,If I had known it would hurt this much
I wouldn't have started.
I wrote this letter for her personally.
Such a fool.
I will let you go, Kim Hyun Ji!
I don't think I can go on, either.
I will go see her. I will.
- Hyun Ji, I will come see you!
- Hey!
- Let go of me!
- No!
If you die,
how am I supposed to live?
I want to see Hyun Ji.
I want to see Hyun Ji,
Chun Sang. I really do.
It really hurts.
It really does, Chun Sang.
What should I do?
Are you sure it was the same man?
I'm not so sure,
but I have this bad feeling.
When I shook his hand,
my whole body was in pain.
If you felt such a thing
when you're such a lousy monk
he must be extraordinary.
By the way,
what brings you here today?
Perhaps you want me to...
No way! I can't handle such a man.
It's not my specialty either.
I've seen In Hyok go down like that.
Don't even think about it.
You're being a chicken.
- That's not why I came.
- Then what is it?
You know the weapon that I used
on Bong Pal when he was little.
Can I get the same weapon again?
- Didn't it break?
- That's what I'm saying.
It's so rare that
it will be hard to find now.
It will make me feel better if I have it.
Can you ask around to see?
I will.
And can you make me an talisman?
I will have Bong Pal carry it.
But I don't know if it will work.
I will go back now.
Do that. It's getting late.
Drive safely.
Are you hurt?
It's not serious.
I will go now.
Hey, who was that?
Was it your son?
He's very handsome.
He's not my son.
He is...
Is anybody here? Someone fell!
- What are you doing?
- Me? Studying.
You're already studying this early?
I have to study hard. I don't have
much time until the SAT.
- Aren't you going to eat?
- After I finish this.
- Why did you do that?
- I want you to take it easy.
If you work too hard now,
it will be tough on you later on.
No, don't look.
I already saw them.
- When?
- A while ago.
Let me see them. Come on.
Gosh, you drew all over
on Seo Yeon's face.
What? Give them back
if you're going to tease me.
Gosh, you made her look ugly.
- Are you jealous of her?
- No way. What jealousy?
Then what is this?
If you're going to tease me,
give them back.
I can't even take
a single photo with you.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't personally like photos.
I prefer seeing things in person.
It is better to see
you in person like this.
- You're so ugly.
- What did you say?
- Say what?
- Stop it.
- I will keep doing it.
- I said stop.
Hey.
- Neener!
- Hey!
Hey, what now?
Hey, it hurts.
- Hey!
- It sounds like Bong Pal...
When did he start to laugh like that?
Hey, why?
- He didn't even lock the door.
- I'm really sorry. Hey.
- It's so low of me to hit me there.
- Okay, I got it.
I'm late. I have a class at 11:30 a.m.
- How about breakfast then?
- We will eat at school.
Bong Pal.
Monk Myung Chul.
Who were you talking to just now?
I asked who you were talking to just now.
By any chance...
were you with that female
ghost from last time?
- Why are you getting up already?
- I will make more sausage.
It's not for you.
There is a stray cat around.
Bong Pal!
Did you get this toothbrush
for me to use?
You've been living with
that female ghost all this time?
What do we do?
- Don't worry about it.
- What do you think you're doing?
Are you in some kind of love
with that ghost?
- I said don't worry about it.
- Your mom died because of a ghost.
But you're with a ghost?
We will fix your eyes immediately.
I will look into it.
Also, stop going around exorcising!
- I will take care of it.
- I don't think so, punk!
- Let's end it right now!
- I don't want to!
By any chance...
do you have feelings for that ghost?
Yes, I do.
- So please stay out of it.
- You punk...
Fine. I will stay out of your business.
Did your mom die because of a ghost?
You're trying to save
money to fix your eyes?
- Don't worry about what he said.
- It's true, isn't it?
I didn't even know, like a fool.
I said don't worry about it.
Let's go to school.
I will stay home today.
You go ahead.
When we have no idea
what's happened to his dad... seriously!
Let me see. According to
the lunar calendar, today is...
Oh my goodness.
It's Bong Pal's birthday today.
Why do I care about
this stubborn punk who doesn't listen?
Bong Pal! Bong Pal!
What am I going to do?
I can't just leave the cake here.
By any chance...
He should've cleaned it
a little bit before he left.
I know you're in here.
Don't leave and hear me out.
I don't know why you're stuck here.
Leave Bong Pal.
You don't seem like an evil spirit.
Please leave Bong Pal for his sake.
When he was little
an evil spirit entered his body.
It was all my fault.
If only I had been stronger,
I would have been able to get rid of it.
Monk Myung Chul.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
When the evil spirit came
out of Bong Pal's body
I couldn't finish it off completely.
It is my biggest regret in life.
That evil spirit got so angry...
it killed Bong Pal's mom
right in front of him.
I learned that he started to
see ghosts from that moment on.
Energy from that evil spirit
somehow stayed in his eyes.
Since that time, he's been
suffering from seeing ghosts.
He's been an outcast from his peers
because of his eyes.
Do you think a ghost and a human
can possibly be together?
So please leave Bong Pal,
for his own sake.
Do you think a ghost and a human
can possibly be together?
So please leave Bong Pal,
for his own sake.
Hyun Ji.
Hyun Ji...
[Bong Pal, happy birthday.]
Hyun Ji.
Yes? You're back?
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm good.
You didn't run into
Monk Myung Chul again, did you?
I saw him briefly,
but I disappeared on him.
- Good.
- By the way, it's your birthday today?
Monk Myung Chul came back with a cake.
Yes, it is.
Why didn't you tell me?
I had no idea.
Actually, I forgot.
- I don't usually celebrate my birthdays.
- Why not?
I can't buy you anything
but is there any place you want to go?
Let's spend your birthday together today.
Wow, it's so pretty.
It is pretty.
It's my first time on a cruise.
I might have been on it
when I was alive, huh?
I also haven't been on one for a while.
You haven't?
But I like it more
because you're with me now.
Me too.
It's about to start. Let's go see.
- It's better to see it here, isn't it?
- Yes.
- Bong Pal.
- Yes?
I want you to be happy.
I'm happy now.
To be honest, I haven't
celebrated my birthday before.
I never liked it either.
But I like my birthday now
because you're here with me.
I'm sorry.
About what?
- About everything.
- What do you mean?
- I can't do anything for you.
- It's fine.
- Happy birthday, Bong Pal.
- Thank you.
Bong Pal, I'm thirsty.
Wait here then.
I will go get some drinks.
Where did she go? Hyun Ji!
Excuse me.
Hyun Ji.
I'm sorry.
Hyun Ji!
Kim Hyun Ji!
I'm sorry, Bong Pal.
[Lets Fight Ghost]
- Hyun Ji.
- Let go of me.
- Let's go home.
- I said let go of me!
You think you and I make sense?
Being with you makes it hard for me.
Where is the stuff you wanted to give?
I don't know what you're planning.
But it's not going to go your way.
Bong Pal!