This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[LET’S FIGHT GHOST]
Bong Pal.
I'm alive...
Hyun Ji.
She's going into cardiac arrest!
Is it cardiac arrest?
- Vitals!
- There's no pulse!
- It's charging.
- Clear! Shoot!
Shoot!
Clear!
Hyun Ji.
Bong Pal.
Hyun Ji... Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji!
[EPISODE 12]
I told him to lie still on the bed! Where
did he go? Gosh, he sure doesn't listen.
He shouldn't be moving around.
- Bong Pal!
- Hey, Bong Pal!
- Bong Pal! Bong Pal!
- Let's carry him.
- Hold on.
Hold on.
Hyun Ji, wake up!
Mom. Dad.
Hyun Ji!
Why am I here?
Why are you crying?
You don't remember the accident?
An accident?
Me?
You've been in a coma for five years.
You don't remember?
Doctor, why doesn't
she remember anything?
Don't worry so much.
It's a minor aftereffect of being
in a coma for such a long time.
Your memories will return in time.
Let's make sure your condition is
stable first and do a physical exam.
Let's just be thankful
that she's awake now.
Congratulations, Hyun Ji.
I'll see you again.
Yes.
- Thank you. Thank you, Doctor.
- Thank you.
- Hyun Ji.
Do you remember me?
Continue to follow up on Kim Hyun Ji.
There might be
a problem with her memories
so set up a consultation with
the neurology department.
Yes, Professor.
[KIM HYUN JI]
You really don't remember anything?
Yes, I don't remember anything.
My head just hurts a little.
Don't try too hard to remember.
Those memories aren't important.
Not when you came back alive.
I'm so happy.
It's okay.
Why are you crying if you're happy?
Don't cry.
Not you too, Dad.
You've been through a lot.
Thank you for staying alive.
- Don't, Mom.
- Thank you, Hyun Ji.
Doctor, are his BP and OP okay?
He's not going into
cardiac arrest, is he?
Don't you need to intubate
him or give him an EPI?
You've watched too many medical dramas.
That's not necessary
and his x-rays are fine.
But it seems like he's
overworked himself lately.
He's exhausted and his
nutritive condition is a mess.
I've prescribed him vitamins. He can be
discharged after he rests the whole day.
- Yes, Doctor.
- Thank you.
I guess he eventually
collapsed after Hyun Ji left.
Bong Pal was struggling? Why?
Huh?
Well, I guess Bong Pal
and Hyun Ji were kind of an item.
An item...
Hyun Ji has feelings for Bong Pal?
I think Bong Pal has
feelings for Hyun Ji too.
That's why he's in
this state after she left.
You know, getting hurt from
a painful breakup is every man's fear.
So that's what happened.
Hyun Ji and Bong Pal were...
I see.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, I'm okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
And don't try to hurt Bong Pal.
[FLOWER VIRGIN SHAMANESS]
Is it true that there's one more weapon?
I heard the head monk prepared one.
Hong Myung Hee met the head
monk before she passed away.
I heard she asked him
to prepare another weapon.
One more?
By any chance, do you
know where that weapon is?
He passed away and that's all I heard.
There's one more weapon.
She had it made for the sake of her son.
I'm sure having that made was not easy.
Do you maybe think the personal item
Bong Pal's father went looking for....
It was the weapon.
Then the reason why that evil
spirit is hanging around Bong Pal...
It's because of that weapon.
That's his lifeline.
That's why the bastard is chasing him.
I have to go.
- You're leaving already?
- Yes.
Watch out for yourself.
If that punk is serious,
he won't go easy on you.
Thanks.
I'll call you.
[KIM HYUN JI]
What should I do with you?
Oh dear Buddha.
Bong Pal.
Where did he go?
Is this rascal in trouble?
- Hello? Who is it?
- Hello...
Isn't this Park Bong Pal's cell phone?
Yes, it is.
In the hospital?
Which hospital is it?
Yes, I understand. That punk!
Who is it?
I don't know.
Hello?
I told you already.
What the heck?
Bong Pal.
What happened?
He's not seriously injured.
He just passed out from exhaustion.
The doctors says he'll be
fine after a day of rest.
Goodness, he must've been
seriously heartbroken.
But who are you?
Yes... we're Bong Pal's seniors
as well as business partners.
Business partners?
- With Bong Pal?
- Yes.
Ah... this...
- Thank you.
- It's nothing great really.
We're running
a 24-hour exorcism business.
- I'm CEO Choi Chun Sang.
- I'm Manager Kim Il Rang.
What's the matter?
Who are you?
He's a monk.
You punks...
You're the punks I met at Gampo.
So, you punks are using Bong Pal
to catch ghosts, is that it?
We're not using him.
This is a mutual and beneficial
partnership we both agreed upon...
- You punk!
- Don't do this.
Don't you know how
dangerous exorcism is?
It does look a bit dangerous,
but this is the 21st century...
Why you little punk!
- I was wrong!
- Are you going to continue or not?
If you ever use Bong Pal
again, I'm going to...
The same goes for you too!
Goodness, you rascal.
You get sick because of that one ghost.
You guys stay right next to Bong Pal.
Don't go anywhere.
I'm going to meet the doctor.
- Yes, sir.
Goodbye.
I thought he was about to
rip my ears off. Seriously.
- Who is that monk?
- I don't know. A relative, maybe?
Aren't you hungry?
Should we go eat something?
I'll go and buy something.
Stay here, I'll be back.
She woke up after five years.
Okay, try closing your hand.
Open it up again.
Put more strength into it.
Fortunately, there is
nothing wrong with her nerves.
You need to continue to exercise
your hands to relax the muscles.
Practice using a spoon
or chopsticks often.
- Writing is fine too.
- Yes, Doctor.
Walking is too much for now,
so use the wheelchair.
And the hospital prepared this
congratulatory gift for you.
Congratulations once
again on waking up.
- Thank you.
Congratulations.
Who is it, anyway?
It's the girl who woke up after
being in a coma for five years.
The girl from the car accident?
I'm glad to hear she's awake.
Hyun Ji...
[KIM HYUN JI]
Is she really...
Hyun Ji.
Hyun Ji... Hyun Ji!
What's wrong?
Hey, hey! Hey.
- I have to find Hyun Ji.
- No, no. Wait a minute! Sit down!
Wait. You're burning up. The doctor says
you have to be calm. Stay still, okay?
Chun Sang, Chun Sang,
Chun Sang! Bong Pal!
I'm so glad you're here, In Rang.
He's frantic to find Hyun Ji.
- I saw Hyun Ji!
- What?
You saw Hyun Ji?
Yes, I saw her at the
hospital ward on the way here.
What nonsense are you spouting?
How can you see a ghost?
No, she looked exactly like Hyun Ji...
No, she's Hyung Ji for sure.
The name tag next to her
room says Kim Hyun Ji too.
Come here.
You're burning up too,
so get a shot while you're here.
No! People are saying that she
woke up from a five-year coma!
Hey, Bong Pal! Bong Pal!
Move! He was just getting stabilized!
Why did you have to bring up Hyun Ji?
- It's that way!
- Bong Pal!
Where did he go?
Bong Pal.
[KIM HYUN JI]
Hyun Ji.
You're alive. I thought you disappeared.
I was so worried about you.
What are you doing?
Hyun Ji.
Who are you?
You... don't recognize me?
I'm... Bong Pal.
Don't you remember?
Look... I don't know
how you know my name.
But I really don't know who you are.
Please leave.
- Hyun Ji.
- Mom.
Who are you?
Do you know him?
No, I don't know him.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I must've mistaken you for someone else.
What the heck?
Hey.
It's Hyun Ji, right?
What did she say?
What did Hyun Ji say?
She... doesn't remember me.
- What?
- She doesn't remember?
Yes.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Are you sure that's Hyun Ji?
- I'm sure.
Look at her. There's no one prettier
than Hyun Ji in all of Korea.
- In all of Korea?
- Yes.
She is pretty, I guess. I don't know.
Hi.
Oh no, she must not remember me either.
How can she remember you when
she can't even remember Bong Pal?
But why can't she remember?
- She was in a coma for five years?
- Yeah.
Then you're saying Hyun Ji
was a soul, not a ghost, right?
I guess she was in limbo.
She came back into her own body and
forgot everything that happened with us.
What do you want me to do about it?
Excuse me... beautiful nurses.
- Yes.
- We have some questions to ask.
Sure, go ahead.
- Who are you? Do you know him?
- No, I don't know him.
Bong Pal. Bong Pal!
Mong Myung Chul.
Who says you can leave the hospital?
- I've been looking all over for you.
- How did you find me?
Your seniors or whatever told me.
I can't believe you're
friends with idiots like that.
They're of no help to you.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
You need to take better care of yourself.
Let's go. You have to
eat well at a time like this.
Let's go and get you something to eat.
Taxi! Hurry up.
Over here.
Stop!
Wow, the quality of this oxtail is good.
- Monk, I'll do it.
- Go away.
I can do this better than you.
I'm fine. I'll do it.
Listen, will you?
Go and get some rest.
Okay.
Monk Myung Chul.
What is it?
I'm sorry for yelling at you last time.
That rascal even knows how to apologize.
He's all grown up.
Let's see here.
Bong Pal.
Bong... Bong Pal.
Bong Pal. Bong...
Bong Pal.
- Senior.
- Here.
Ah, you came here to bring me this.
- I could've come and gotten it.
- Well, we need to talk too.
- What is it?
- The thing is...
So, you're not the only one
that Hyun Ji can't remember.
They say she can't remember
what happened five years ago.
Hyun Ji was a victim
of a hit-and-run accident.
I think she has problems
remembering because of trauma.
The amnesia is only temporary.
Her memories will return in time,
so don't be so disappointed.
We should be ecstatic
and grateful that Hyun Ji is alive.
And at times like this, you should
be by her side, don't you think?
You punks!
Who came back alive
from a hit-and-run accident?
Hello, sir.
What?
Bong Pal left his bag behind
and we brought it for him.
We'll be on our way now.
Goodbye.
See you later.
Bong Pal, is Hyun Ji alive then?
Yes, she's in the
hospital I was staying at.
That child was not a ghost.
Unbelievable.
He should be jumping up and down
with joy. Why does he look so down?
We should be ecstatic
and grateful that Hyun Ji is alive.
And at times like this, you should
be by her side, don't you think?
Are you okay after
saying all that to him?
About what?
Well, you're trying to get
Hyun Ji and Bong Pal together.
Have you completely
given up on her then?
Hyun Ji's happiness is my happiness.
I'm good as long as she's happy.
Plus, there something
more important than that.
What is it?
We have to catch
that punk and get revenge.
Who?
The bastard that put her
in a coma five years ago.
It's my life's mission
to catch that punk.
- Chun Sang.
- Yeah?
Do you have
that detective's business card?
Business card?
The business card we got
from that detective...
The business card we
got when Sadako died.
Ah!
I have it, I have it, I have it.
I do have it. Here it is.
Let's go.
To the police station.
Let's go! To the police station!
Goodness, it's not even a case.
Why did you come all the way here?
There's something I need
to find out personally.
This is old news.
It's a simple accident.
There's nothing to look over.
Is the scene of the crime still there?
Why? You want to go there?
Yes.
Okay, he fell right here.
Anyway, he was already
dead when we arrived.
I think he died from internal bleeding.
One of the residents discovered
the body while passing by.
She said she didn't see him fall.
That's what happened.
Is anyone there? Someone help!
A straight fall from the 15th floor.
What? You want to go
up to the 15th floor?
- Hello.
- Who are you?
- We called you earlier.
- Ah, yes.
- We're from the police station.
- I see.
- Please excuse us for a moment.
It's nothing really.
This detective is from Seoul and he
just wants to take a quick look around.
- It'll only be for a moment.
- Sure, go ahead.
Thank you.
There was no self-defense whatsoever.
It's hard to say it was manslaughter.
And there was no letter or statement
left behind to indicate it was suicide.
It was written on the autopsy
report that he drank a lot.
So he drank, smoked, and did this.
He lost his balance.
He tilted over and lost his balance.
Do you remember who
was there at that time?
When I went up...
the wife was there.
She didn't know that her husband fell.
Was the son at home by any chance?
His name is Joo Hye Sung.
He was 13 years old at the time.
Yes, the son was home.
- Yeah, what is it?
- Senior.
- Where are you right now?
- Did you get something?
The chief is looking all over for you.
- You need to get back immediately.
- I'm on my way.
Why are you so concerned
with a simple freak accident?
- Did you find something?
- I don't think it was a freak accident.
What?
The railing is about one meter tall.
Joo Hye Sung's father
was 173 centimeters tall.
Even if he stood by the railing, it'd be
hard for him to fall over on his own.
That's unless someone
pushed him from behind.
The only people who were home
were the wife and Joo Hye Sung.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm going to reinvestigate
Professor Joo Hye Sung.
Slowly.
Very good. Pull a little more.
- Are you comfortable?
- Yes.
I'm going to increase
the speed just a little bit.
Hello?
Yes.
- Let's stop right here for today.
- Okay.
Be careful.
You're doing very well.
The muscles are responding well,
so you should be able to use crutches.
Even though it's hard,
you have to keep it up.
I will.
Where did my mom go?
- Should I take you to your room?
- No, I'll do it.
- This is considered exercise too.
- Okay then.
- Thank you.
- Good job today.
- Hello.
Hello, Doctor.
- Hello, Miss Hyun Ji.
- Hello.
This is a piece of cake.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Are you okay?
Yes.
You look tired. Where is your room?
I'll take you there.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It must be your first time
in a wheelchair.
You looked very clumsy.
Ah, yes. I've only been
using it for several days.
You should be careful.
It's actually quite harder than it looks.
- Are you a doctor here?
- No.
I used to volunteer at a hospital,
which is when I tried one out.
I see.
I hear you were in
a coma for five years.
Oh, how did you find out?
What kind of accident was it?
A hit-and-run accident.
But the truth is, I don't remember.
Not even remotely?
Yes, the doctor says
it's because of the shock.
But he says my memories
will return with time.
What a relief.
Hyun Ji.
It's my mom.
Mom.
Where were you?
I was looking all over for you.
Who is he?
Ah, this person escorted me.
Really? Thank you.
- You're too kind.
- Not at all. I'll be on my way now.
- Good luck.
- Yes, thank you.
Who is he?
He is so good-looking.
He's exactly my type.
Oh.
A present for you.
What is it?
This is mine?
- Yes.
- Thank you!
Nice.
Come in.
What the heck? He's here again.
I'm not a strange person,
so don't be afraid of me.
I want to apologize for last time.
I didn't know you lost your memories.
What are you doing?
It's my student ID.
I'm a sophmore business
major at Myungsung University.
Call the school if you doubt me.
Why did you come again?
You're going to regret treating me
like this once your memories return.
Regret, my butt.
Just who are you to keep
bothering me like this?
Park Bong Pal.
Park Bong Pal?
That's right, Park Bong Pal.
Your boyfriend.
- Granted, you don't remember.
- What?
Boyfriend?
Yes.
We were an item? I dated you?
No, it's more like we lived together.
That's a more accurate expression.
What are you saying?
Why would I live with you? When?
- When you were a ghost.
- What? A ghost?
- You've lost your mind!
- I'm perfectly fine.
- You chased me around.
- No way.
You're not my type. Get out.
You don't have to remember right away.
I'm grateful that you're alive
and well and haven't disappeared.
You bought a new cell phone.
What are you doing?
I'm giving you my number.
Call me if you miss me.
Get out. Get out!
- I came back to return your stuff today.
- Today?
- You're coming again tomorrow?
- Yes.
Don't ever come again. I swear I'll call
the cops on you if you come tomorrow!
I'm coming tomorrow
and the day after tomorrow.
I'm going to come every day
until you remember.
Every single day.
See you tomorrow.
Ah... and call me if you
want to hear my voice.
Wow.
[MY LOVE BONG BONG]
What a crazy bastard!
What is it?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
- Did you buy this?
- No!
Just throw it all away. The books too.
It's the exact same
thing you used before.
- Really?
- Really.
You always used
a pink cup and toothbrush.
- Did I?
- You did. Ever since you were little.
You threw such a fit
if I bought you a different color.
Mom, wait.
What is it?
Just leave it there for now.
You're so wishy-washy.
Here.
Let's see here.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
This looks like my handwriting.
Hey, Kim Hyun Ji.
What is it? Are you in pain?
My head hurts.
Hyun Ji.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
For a patient who was in a coma for five
years, your recovery speed is amazing.
- You're in great condition too.
- Really?
When do I get discharged then?
It's so stuffy in here.
At this rate, you can start receiving
outpatient treatment in three days.
Yes!
Is he not here today?
It's strange not seeing him.
No, what am I talking about?
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
I am going to introduce
you to a new friend today.
This fellow's name is Happy.
- It's that guy from last time.
- And he's three years old.
What is he doing?
What are all of your names? Can you
please introduce yourself to Happy?
- Yes!
- You go first.
- Hi, I'm Ji Woo.
- Hi, Ji Woo.
- Hi, I'm Hyun Soo.
- Hi, Hyun Soo.
- Hi, I'm Seo Woo.
- Hi, Seo Woo.
Now that we've introduced ourselves,
how about we get friendlier with Happy?
Yes!
All you have to do is
gently pet him, okay?
Yes.
Gently. Happy might get scared.
- Hi.
- Be gentle.
He's so cute.
He's so soft and cute.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Yes, goodbye.
Bye, see you next time.
You look much better.
I see that you can walk now.
Yes.
He's so cute.
You said you do volunteer work.
Do you volunteer here as well?
- Yes.
- What did you just do now?
Pet therapy. It helps patients recover
from or better cope with health issues.
It's a type of pyschotherapy.
I probably need it too.
Of course.
- Do you want to hold him?
- Yes.
Here you go.
- His name is Happy.
- Hi, Happy.
Excuse me, is this Kim Hyun Ji's room?
Yes, that's correct.
How did you get here?
- Did she go somewhere?
- Yes, she left for physical therapy.
Who are you?
Kim Hyun Ji and I don't really
know each other very well.
By any chance, are you her mother?
Yes.
Congratulations on
your daughter waking up.
This is my gift.
- Thank you.
- I'll get going.
Wait, sir.
Who should I say came to visit her?
Tell her a mean monk who once
said some harsh words to her came.
Please tell her I'm sorry.
Have a good day.
Ah, so you're a professor.
No wonder.
The school you're teaching at
is the school I wanted to attend.
I was going to apply to Myungsung
University before the accident.
I'd probably be graduating by now.
Come visit the school
once you're discharged
and attend one of my classes.
- Really? I can do that?
- Of course.
I get discharged in three days.
Can I come then?
- Yes.
- Yes!
Why is that punk here?
Monk Myung Chul.
Hey, Bong Pal.
What are you doing here?
Oh, just because. Just because.
Why are Hyun Ji
and the professor together?
Hyun Ji?
Ah, the girl next to that
professor is Hyun Ji, huh?
Yes.
Monk Myung Chul.
It's nothing. I'm going to leave first.
You scared me.
You look like you're
in a good mood today.
I was in such a good
mood before I saw you.
I was wondering why
you didn't come today.
- Were you waiting for me?
- You wish!
Wait... Do you remember anything?
Go to a mental institute
and stop bothering me!
What about lunch? Did you eat?
What's it to you if I eat or not?
It's boring eating
hospital food every day.
I packed a lunch today.
Let's go eat it together.
No thank you. You eat it.
I bought jangjorim and meat.
Meat?
Yes, meat.
Here, dig in.
Just because I'm eating this doesn't
mean that I've opened up to you.
I'm only tasting it out of courtesy.
Okay, just give it a taste.
Shall I then?
It's kimchi stew.
- You have to put tons of meat...
- You have to put tons of meat in it.
You have to put tons of meat
in for it to taste good.
I did. Eat it.
You're pretty good.
Here, rolled eggs.
You like this.
You've been stalking me, haven't you?
How can you know everything I like?
- You chased me.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Don't lie!
Here.
How can I like all these dishes?
You're a pretty good cook.
Whether you're a ghost or human,
that hearty appetite is still the same.
It's meat.
I don't know what you're up to.
But it won't go your way.
- Hello.
- Goodness, hello.
Hello.
Is Professor Joo Hye Sung in?
He's not here right now.
What brings you here?
I just wanted to say hello.
- When will he return?
- He'll be back in about an hour.
- Should I give him a call?
- No, that's not necessary.
I'll come again.
By any chance... may I use the bathroom?
Of course! The bathroom is downstairs.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Kim Hyun Ji.
Why is her student ID here?
- You're back, Director.
- You came back early.
Yes, the appointment was canceled.
- Everything's fine?
- Yes.
Ah, Director.
Someone is here to see you.
- Who?
- The monk who came last time.
He's in the bathroom right now.
Goodness... the professor is here.
This is not the bathroom.
- I think you're lost.
- No kidding.
I went into the wrong room.
I'm full.
Since I ate all your dishes
for you, I'm going to leave now.
Already? Stay a bit longer.
I'm bored.
I wish I could, but visiting
hours are almost over.
See you. Hand me my crutches.
Hey!
- I'll walk you to your room.
- It's fine. I can do it myself.
- I said it's fine!
What the heck are you doing?
You were falling.
We almost kissed!
I haven't had my first kiss yet.
That's... not true.
Then...
You pervert!
Hey, hey, hey!
Do you want to die?
Ow!
Hey!
My first kiss what?
I told you not to mess around with me!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Jerk.
She's good at fighting.
It feels good to hit him.
Where have you been?
- I went for a short walk.
- Let's go in.
- Thank you.
- Be careful when you walk.
I will.
The professor is off today,
so I came in his place.
- Are you comfortable.
- Yes.
Oh, I don't see
Doctor Kim Jung Woo either.
Pardon? Who?
Doctor Kim Jung Woo.
You know, the really tall guy.
We don't have a doctor by that name.
- Rest up then.
- Thank you.
Rest up.
My cell phone.
I must've dropped it on the roof.
She's so clumsy.
Kim Jung Woo.
Kim Jung Woo?
I've heard that name somewhere.
Do you know a Kim Jung Woo?
Kim Jung Woo?
He used to work at our hospital.
You know him?
You don't know him?
About 10 years ago,
that doctor died in our hospital.
That doctor killed a patient
in the operating room.
Not only in our hospital, but also
in the previous hospital where he worked.
He killed patients during surgery.
Look at him.
Right behind you.
- There's blood all over him.
- I can't believe it.
Once the police started to investigate,
he killed himself in one of our offices.
Bong Pal!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[LET'S FIGHT GHOST]
Pull it tight!
What are you doing?
Joo Hye Sung is a professor
at Myungsung University.
I'm sure you'll find something on him.
- Is it a gift for your girlfriend?
- Yes.
- You may leave now.
- Where's Bong Pal?
You don't know what kind of
person he is. Don't get too close.
Professor Joo will be in charge
of Miss Hyun Ji's psychotherapy.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
He said he'd come, but he's not here.
Are you sure you have it?
All the evil acts you committed
will come back to haunt you.