This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let’s Fight Ghost]
Bong Pal!
Hyun Ji!
Are you okay?
Hyun Ji, are you okay?
Wake up.
Hyun Ji.
Someone help!
Is anyone here?
Hyun Ji.
[Episode 13]
Kim Hyun Ji?
Why is her student ID here?
- Director, you're back.
- You came back early.
Yes, the appointment was canceled.
Everything's fine?
Yes.
Ah, Director.
Someone is here to see you.
Goodness, the professor is here.
This is not the bathroom.
- I think you're lost.
- No kidding.
I went into the wrong room.
Excuse me then.
Monk.
- Did you not come here to see me?
- Ah, yes.
I came to ask if Bong Pal
was doing well in school.
Is that so?
Yes. Bong Pal is doing very well.
I'm glad to hear that.
That rascal is not very social,
so I was a bit worried.
Monk.
Would you like to hear
something interesting?
Several days ago, I went down to
the countryside to rescue a cat.
I went to the site, and that cat was
trapped inside a small ventilator.
There was noise coming from it, so it
probably went inside out of curiosity.
But...
it went in so deep that
it couldn't get out.
Despite all the pain, that cat...
kept going inside deeper
and deeper to follow the noise.
So do you know what happened?
Ultimately, it couldn't breathe...
and died a painful death.
That's not a interesting story.
You think so? I thought it was.
And there's a lesson to be learned.
I shouldn't be the one
to give you any advice...
but I'll say some words
of wisdom from Buddha.
"He who delights in evil will never
be free from his grudge and hatred."
If you have a heart filled with anger,
karma will come and get you someday.
- Thank you for the words of wisdom.
- You're welcome.
Please keep them close to your heart.
You see, nothing and no one
is an exception to the rule.
Whether that's an animal or a ghost.
Director.
Yes?
- You have a guest from next door.
- Ah, I see. I'll be right there.
Yes, sir.
Monk.
I'll keep your words in mind.
Goodbye.
- I'm sorry for coming so late at night.
- That's okay.
- What's going on?
- Ah, well...
I want to ask you some questions
about what happened 18 years ago.
Is it true that
your husband died from an accident?
It's all in the past.
Why are you asking?
I know the case is closed.
There were several things
I noticed that I found strange.
You were inside the house with
your husband at that time, correct?
Yes.
How could you not know
about his accident then?
- I thought he went outside.
- Ah.
I went to the site of the
accident during the day earlier.
Your husband and I are
about the same height.
When I was standing
out on the veranda
I noticed it would've been difficult
to fall over the railing even by mistake.
What do you think?
I think someone pushed
him over from behind.
Professor Joo Hye Sung was also inside
the house at the time, wasn't he?
What was he doing at that moment?
Ma'am.
Please leave now.
I have nothing more to say to you.
Ah.
Well...
If I can ask you one more question...
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Excuse me.
How is she doing?
Her breathing is stable,
so there's nothing to worry about.
- She's fine, right?
- Yes.
She just had a temporary mental shock.
She'll wake up once she's stable.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You may leave now.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
This is Hyun Ji's cell phone.
I'll be on my way.
Kim Hyun Ji? Why is her student ID here?
Just how is she connected to that punk?
[Kim Hyun Ji]
Please go home now! Let me work!
- Please help us, Detective.
- Yes, please help us.
Seriously, you two are driving me nuts!
- You're here.
- What's going on?
Excuse me, sir.
Detective, please help us.
Please catch the punk that
hurt our friend Hyun Ji.
Who are these kids?
They've been here for hours begging me
to catch a hit-and-run criminal.
- That's enough.
- Wait.
You guys are the kids
from the cyberbully case.
He remembers us!
But we were not the cyberbully.
We called you in the afternoon too.
Were you the ones
who called me 11 times?
- Yes.
- Tell me what the case is about.
- Yes, so....
I have a really beautiful friend.
She's like an angel.
Nothing like that. What's her name?
Her name is Kim Hyun Ji and she
was a victim of a hit-and-run accident.
She was in a coma for five years
and woke up not too long ago.
She's awake,
but she doesn't remember anything.
I feel so bad for her
and Bong Pal, Detective.
It's very important that you catch the
criminal. Please catch him, Detective.
It's the hit-and-run accident that
happened five years ago in Seokjongdong.
I contacted traffic control
and there were no witnesses.
- The case was suspended.
- It was suspended?
The case was suspended?
My friend is in the hospital
struggling to regain her memories--
Okay, I got the gist of it.
You can go home now.
No, I will not go home!
Detective, I request
a reinvestigation...
If you guys keep this up, I'm going to
charge you for disruption and detain you!
We'll wait for you to call us.
Please promise us that
you'll reinvestigate the case...
Look, that's not up to us, okay?
There's no proper witness!
I swear, how many times
must I repeat this to you?
Come here and get them out of here!
Go.
- Just a moment please.
- Il Rang, that's enough.
No, wait a minute! Detective,
you have to catch that punk! Please!
I request a reinvestigation!
Detective, I request a reinvestigation!
Please reconsider.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
By the way, the chief
wants to see you tomorrow.
- Why?
- Why do you think?
You keep digging stuff up on
Professor Joo Hye Sung and he's noticed.
Nothing is going my way
and I keep getting complaints.
Bong Pal.
Bong Pal!
Why did you drink so much?
Well, I just wanted to.
- Bong Pal.
- Yes?
Come here and give me a kiss.
What's the matter with you?
You're grossing me out!
You gave me so many kisses when
you were this little. Come here.
Forget it! I'm not a child anymore.
- What?
- I'm not a child.
Come and lie down.
Goodness, you've gotten big.
- You're all grown up.
- I'll get you some tea.
No, that's okay.
No, tea. How about a cup of water?
Get me a cup of water.
Oh goodness.
I'm sorry.
Bong Pal, I'm sorry.
Mom.
- You're awake?
- Yes.
- And you're fine?
- Yes, I'm fine.
You mean it?
Speak up if something
doesn't feel right, okay?
Okay.
What happened?
Why did you suddenly pass out?
I don't know.
I saw something scary and I think
I fainted from the shock of it.
But what about Bong Pal?
Did he leave?
Hey! You don't know what kind of
person he is. Don't get too close to him.
- Why? He's a good person.
- How do you know that?
The world is a scary place.
Mom.
- You weren't mean to him, were you?
- What?
- What would I possibly say to him?
- Don't be mean to him.
He has nothing to do
with me passing out.
If anything, he helped me.
Let's not talk about him anymore.
I'm going to go see the doctor.
Can you be alone for a moment?
Yes.
- Bong Pal!
- Are you okay?
What did I see that time?
Was it a ghost?
Why did I call for Bong Pal?
Did we really know each other?
Oh, I don't know.
[Amnesia]
[Are you okay?]
Are you okay?
When did he change his caller ID?
Yes, I feel much better now.
That's a relief. I was worried.
Yeah right.
Thanks for saving me earlier.
Did you get hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm glad to hear that,
but what did I see?
I'll tell you later.
Okay.
I'm being discharged tomorrow.
You can come if you want to.
Okay, I'll come.
[Good night]
Good night.
You too.
Do you know what time it is?
Hurry up and go to bed.
- Okay. After I send this.
- That's enough.
I'm not a kid. Give it back.
You're not a kid,
but you're still a patient.
If I see you messing with your
cell phone late at night again
I'm really going to confiscate it.
Fine.
Good night, Mom. Bye.
Good night.
Bong Pal, are you sleeping?
- No, not yet.
- What were you doing?
I'm just here. Aren't you sleeping?
It's after 2:00 a.m.
I'm going to sleep in a little bit.
When are you being discharged tomorrow?
In the morning.
[You too. Sleep well.]
[Sleep well.]
Monk Myung Chul.
I made some bean sprout soup. Eat it.
Where are you going this morning?
To the hospital.
Hyun Ji is being discharged.
I see.
That's good to hear.
- Tell her congratulations.
- Sure. I'll see you later.
Okay.
I'm not sure if it's okay for
those two to continue to see each other.
Welcome.
- Is it a gift for someone?
- Yes.
Your girlfriend?
Yes.
Would you like to see this product?
- Yes.
- Sure.
Here you go.
It's a necklace designed to have
the meaning of destiny behind it.
- I'll take it.
- Okay.
Student.
Hello.
By any chance, did you
come to see Hyun Ji?
Yes. I heard she's
being discharged today.
I'm sorry, but just go home.
- Excuse me?
- I don't know what your relationship
is with her,
but I don't like you coming here.
Hyun Ji passed out while
she was with you yesterday.
It's been five years since she woke up.
Yesterday's incident
can never happen again.
- I'm sorry.
- Please leave.
The results... are very good.
- You can leave.
- Yes!
Mom, I can go home!
But will she be okay
from fainting yesterday?
That's called a vasovagal syncope.
Hyun Ji was in a coma
for a very long time
so it's hard to say
if she's mentally stable.
In instances like that, when
a sudden emotional change occurs...
something like yesterday can
happen due to sensory overload.
What should we do if something
like that happens again?
Vasovagal syncope occurs frequently
in even normal young adults.
I wouldn't worry so much.
As long as you continue your treatments,
something like yesterday won't occur.
You must come twice a week for
mental and physical therapy.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- I'm a little late.
- You're here.
Professor Joo will be in charge of
Miss Hyun Ji's psychological treatment.
- Hello.
- Congratulations on your discharge.
Thank you.
He's a veterinary professor who helps
us out in the psychology department.
He's very popular in
the animal therapy field.
- Oh.
- He's quite a busy person
but he personally volunteered to take
Miss Hyun Ji on once he heard the story.
Thank you.
You also helped us out last time.
I can't believe
we're meeting like this again.
- Not at all.
- Do you two know each other?
That's perfect.
What about her father?
He's busy, but he'll
be home later tonight.
What should we do with
all her belongings?
I'll help her since
she's also my patient now.
That's great then.
Your recovery will be faster
the sooner you get to know one another.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Well, you don't really have to do that,
but if you insist on helping us out...
- Mom.
- What?
He said he'll help us.
It would be rude to refuse him.
- Isn't that right?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Thank you for everything.
- Thank you.
- We're going to get going.
- Take it easy.
- Goodbye.
- Let's go.
What the heck?
He said he would come.
What did you say?
It's nothing.
Okay, I'm going to drive now.
You're home.
Yes. Are you leaving?
Yes, I'm going to step out for a bit.
I thought you were going to the
hospital. Why are you back so early?
Just because.
Isn't that Hyun Ji's discharge gift?
I'll give it to her next time.
- Did her memories return?
- No.
I don't think she remembers
the time when she was a ghost.
Bong Pal.
I shouldn't say this for your sake.
But it might be better if
her memories don't return.
What?
What good is it to remember
her time as a ghost?
She would be so scared if
she knew she was near death.
I'm sure every day was a nightmare
being near those dangerous ghosts.
It's better not to remember.
She's human now.
She deserves to have a normal life.
You don't know how it will affect
her if she finds out the truth.
It will be difficult for you
but I don't think it's a bad idea
for you to help her live a new life.
In order for Hyun Ji to move on,
you need to let go of her hand first.
I'll be back.
I'll see you later.
- Have your memories returned?
- No, not yet.
I can't believe you went there.
- Where?
- Someone asked her to do a favor.
She went to some unknown academy and got
into a car accident right in front of it.
Just from whom and what kind
of favor did you accept?
I don't know. I don't remember.
Anyway, I don't know who it was
but it was all for nothing
and that person ruined your life.
It's your fault too!
You're too kind for your own good.
You're always helping people out.
Why did you go all the
way to Seoul to do that?
It's good to be kind.
Oh please!
Anyway, that's another story, but the
hit-and-run criminal is even worse.
I hope that evil jerk
gets what he deserves.
I'm going to leave now.
Thank you. We were able to come
home comfortably because of you.
I would love to treat
you to a hot cup of tea.
- I feel so bad.
- We can do it next time.
I'll call you to
schedule our appointments.
- Yes, goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Drive safely.
Wow, he is one decent guy.
- I told you he's pretty cool.
- I know.
- Is this place our home now?
- No.
We lived here temporarily
because of you.
Let's pack up and leave soon.
Your father is by himself too.
Okay.
- All the boxes are still here.
- Of course.
How could I unpack when you were
lying in the hospital like that?
Go to your room.
I made sure it is in perfect condition.
- It's on the second floor.
- Really?
Wow, it's exactly like my old room.
Oh my, what's all this?
It's so pretty.
Mom.
- What do you think? Like it?
- Yes.
We bought all these
one by one on your birthdays.
We prayed you'd wear them
when you wake up.
- Thank you, Mom.
- What do you mean?
I want to thank you more.
- Organize it and come out.
- I will.
Thanks, Mom.
You must have worried
so much because of me.
I will be a very good daughter.
I will study hard and go to college.
I will get a job and give you money too.
I don't need you to do any of that.
Just don't get sick.
That's all I need.
No, I will do everything for you
that I couldn't do before.
I will kiss you this much too.
You're too big to do that.
I know you like it.
Stop it.
It's now clear that
you had it all this time.
What? Reinvestigation?
It's been years
since the case was closed.
You two have a lot of time
on your hands, huh?
When you have time for this,
why don't you do other work?
Do you understand?
Don't even say a word.
I can't stand you right now, so leave.
Get out!
How could you tell him that you'd
reinvestigate the case out of the blue?
Well, he wouldn't let me
do it even if I ask nicely.
It works the same way.
I only did that
because he asked me to report.
Then will you continue
to investigate the case?
I should. Two people,
including No Hyun Joo, were killed.
We can't just let it go.
What happened 18 years ago
is also suspicious.
I understand, but we don't have
any circumstantial evidence.
So we will investigate
until we find evidence.
He's so stubborn.
[Hyun Ji]
What are you doing?
Why isn't he responding?
What are you doing, huh?
You should be studying at this hour.
What have you been doing
since last night, huh?
If your grandma knew about this,
would she be happy?
Don't you feel bad for
Bong Pal and Hyun Ji?
I feel bad. I do.
If you write on a website,
would someone read it?
It's been read.
- It's been read by one person.
- It was me just now.
I should do something.
How about you?
Do you have a plan?
I do. I do have a plan.
I have a delivery.
Is Choi Chun Sang here?
Perfect timing.
Wow, it's amazing.
Now we don't have money
since we can't exorcise.
You ordered something.
Then you'll wipe with your hands
in the bathroom because you're broke?
There are bare necessities in life.
This is toilet paper and tissues.
Wow, these are some bare necessities.
They are for our leisure.
Anyway, that's not what's important.
Where could it be?
Here it is.
Hey, hold this.
- Hold it.
- What is it?
Walk three steps backward.
One, two. One, two.
Do it right. You will be
surprised when you see it.
Ta-da!
[Looking for a witness!]
Usually witnesses of hit-and-run cases
travel the area of the accident.
Posting online like you did won't work.
We should hang this where people walk by.
We will mention the reward money too.
I already printed several more, so
- we will go and hang them all over.
- Wow, Chun Sang.
- You're so cool.
- You punk!
It's me, Chun Sang, punk.
Bong Pal.
Are you on your way to class?
Yes, where are you two off to?
- To hang this.
- What is it?
It's a banner looking
for Hyun Ji's hit-and-run driver.
Chun Sang got this all ready.
- Have you talked to her?
- Yes.
- She doesn't have her memories back yet?
- Not yet.
I wish she'd get her memory back soon...
I'd love all four of us to
hang out together like before.
That's Bong Pal.
Park Bong Pal.
Ah, it's Hyun Ji.
- Wow, she's so pretty.
- Why did she come here?
- Did she get her memory back?
- I don't know.
- Why are you ignoring my text?
- Sorry. I didn't see it.
By the way,
what brings you here to school?
I came to sit in on
Professor Joo's lecture.
Professor Joo?
- "Animals and Society"?
- Are you also taking that class?
Amazing. Where is the classroom?
Come with me.
- I will go first.
- Do that.
Hi there.
Hello.
She doesn't seem to
have her memory back, does she?
No. By the way, why is Bong Pal
acting that way with Hyun Ji?
I want my Hyun Ji to be happy.
My heart started to beat fast...
Who are they?
- They are my seniors.
- I see.
They're not my type,
but they look familiar for some reason.
By the way...
how do you know Professor Joo?
He's helping me with
my psychotherapy treatment.
- I met him at the hospital.
- Did you?
- You're here.
- Hello, Professor Joo.
You found the classroom.
- Are you okay to come out today?
- Yes.
Even my doctor told me to go out more
rather than staying home all day.
He told me to practice walking.
I didn't realize it at the hospital
but you sure look like
a college student now.
I do?
By the way, you two know each other?
Well, we know each other a little bit.
I see.
- Then shall we go in?
- Sure.
About my lecture today...
- Hope you like the class.
- Thank you.
- Bong Pal, hi.
- Senior.
Who is she?
- She's sitting in today.
- Ah.
- Hello.
She's just sitting in?
Didn't he say
I was his girlfriend last time?
Are you hurt?
What happened? Are you hurt?
I just got a tiny scratch.
It doesn't look tiny.
It's okay.
Did he get injured because of me?
Animals also have the right
not to be tortured.
Let's take an example with a toy.
If you step on a toy
and break it by accident
you will apologize
to the owner of the toy.
But you don't feel sorry for the toy.
Until now, we didn't give
animals proper rights.
We considered animals
the same as toys, rocks, and plants...
Lift it a bit higher.
Higher.
Tie it a bit tighter.
Come on.
Shall I pull it tighter?
- You tied it?
- I did.
Pull it now.
Excuse me. What do you
think you're doing here?
You can't be doing this, seriously.
Did you get permission
from the police station?
Are we supposed to get permission?
- No.
- This is just too much.
What's all this, huh?
Are there too many?
Can you please try to investigate?
How can I just take
your word and investigate?
You will find something
only if you investigate.
Joo Hye Sung, a veterinary professor
at Myungsung university.
- You will find something.
- Please leave.
Conduct an investigation.
You will find something. Please!
Hello.
You're the detective
who released Bong Pal last time.
- How are you?
- Hi.
We've met before.
By the way, what is it?
[Joo Hye Sung, veterinary
professor at Myungsung University]
How do you know Professor Joo?
Do you also know him?
Are you saying Professor Joo
has Kim Hyun Ji's belongings?
I'm saying he does.
That's why he's the one.
At the scene of the accident,
her belongings weren't found.
It was because he took them all.
Even so, we can't start the investigation
without any evidence.
Go home. We will contact you.
It's better to start
the investigation soon.
Hello, detectives.
What's with them?
We got a call about them
hanging banners illegally.
The vendors caught these students.
They said they knew you,
so I brought them here.
Good work. You can go.
A banner? What is it about?
A hit-and-run case?
Go home.
This case is proceeding
in an interesting way.
Go get the case file
from the transportation department.
Yes, sir.
- We will get going now then.
- Wait!
- Anything you want to tell us?
- You are going to Myungsung, aren't you?
- You rude punks!
- Why are you doing this?
- Do you know Professor Joo Hye Sung?
- Professor Joo Hye Sung?
Ah, he's a veterinary professor
at our school.
Then can I ask you to do me a favor?
We'll wrap up for today. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Hyun Ji.
How did you like my class?
Did you like it?
- Yes, I liked it.
- Did you?
A lot of students were dozing off.
Were they? I thought it was fun.
I'm glad you liked it.
If you have time,
can we go out to eat?
We can also schedule
our next appointment.
Can we do that next time?
I just have things to do today.
Do you? That's too bad.
- I will call you then.
- Sure. Thank you.
Professor Joo.
Well, I have something
to talk to you about.
You said you wanted to tell
me something. What is it?
It is...
I'm graduating after this semester.
So I won't have much time to see you.
That's why...
Go on.
I like you, Professor Joo.
I've liked you ever since I met you.
I'm sorry.
I wonder if I led you on.
If I acted inappropriately, I apologize.
No, I'm the one who started to like you.
I will just appreciate how you feel.
Then.
This.
Hey, why did you leave
without talking to me?
You were talking to Professor Joo.
- Are you mad at me?
- No.
- No?
- Bong Pal.
- Yes?
Have I been here before?
I told you that you followed me around.
I still can't believe that,
but this place is familiar.
Ah, I need to go now.
- Where?
- To see my friends.
- Your friends?
- Yes.
Some of my high school friends
live in Seoul.
They will help me take the GED.
- Will they?
- Yes.
I will get really busy then.
After taking the GED, I will need to
take the SAT and get a job.
Take it easy. Why rush?
I'm five years behind
compared to everyone else.
I will have to try five times harder.
I want to get my life back together.
I lost so much all those years.
There are a lot of things I want to try.
Hi, Min Ji. Are you here already?
Okay. I will be right there.
- Bong Pal, I will go.
- Have fun.
See you next time. I will text you.
It will be difficult for you
but I don't think it's a bad idea
for you to help her live a new life.
In order for Hyun Ji to move on
you need to let go of her hand first.
Let's get together more often.
Seo Yeon.
Hi, Bong Pal.
- Did something happen?
- No, no reason.
Stop drinking. You've had enough.
- I'm okay.
- Stop drinking.
I'm okay.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. I will go to the bathroom.
See you next time. Bye.
- Where are you?
- Hello?
Hello?
This is Bong Pal's cell phone.
Senior, get up. I will take you home.
- Hyun Ji.
- Hello.
Hello. There is a cab outside
that brought me here.
Take it home.
Let's go, Bong Pal.
- What's with you?
- What do you mean?
You said you liked me
and that you were my boyfriend.
Then why do you keep changing your mind?
It bothers me.
- It bothers you?
- Of course it bothers me.
- Really?
- Yes, it just bothers me.
You being with another girl bothers me.
You're smiling? How can you smile now?
When a man loves a woman,
he should stick to his feelings.
You shouldn't do this.
Even if I don't remember you
you should find a way to try anything...
You pervert!
Don't ever call me again!
Hey.
You should at least apply
the ointment before you leave...
I can't believe you asked
me to apply the ointment.
Ouch! It hurts.
What do you mean it hurts?
I'm applying it so gently.
- All done.
- Ouch!
- You're grateful, right?
- I'm grateful.
It's late, but I wanted to congratulate
you on coming home from the hospital.
What is it?
It's a necklace.
I will put it on you.
Then are we now going out?
Well, it depends on how you behave...
I will behave.
See what happens
if you're seen with another girl.
It won't happen again.
You're the only one for me.
Get home safe.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
You have a good night too.
- What took you so long?
- I told you I'd see friends today.
- Can you stay home alone for a little?
- Sure.
I'm not a little kid. Why ask?
I'm going over to your uncle's.
- Lock up, okay?
- I will.
- Wait, Mom.
- Yes?
- Pick up ice cream on your way home.
- You got it.
- See you later.
Sir, what are you looking at?
I'm looking at the record
of the cars Joo has had.
It was a white car that was seen
at the hit-and-run scene, right?
Yes, it was a white sedan.
No other information was available.
Joo drove a white car five years ago.
- He did?
- On August 25th, 2011
- he scrapped it.
- Hold on.
- That's two days after the accident.
- True.
The timing is interestingly coincidental.
[Kim Hyun Ji]
Bong Pal.
Hyun Ji, what's wrong?
What happened?
Bong Pal.
What should I do now?
What I saw at
the hospital wasn't a coincidence.
I can see ghosts.
She's human now.
She deserves to have a normal life.
You don't know how it will affect her
if she finds out the truth.
- Hyun Ji.
- What should I do now?
Don't worry.
No matter what happens
I will protect you.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let’s Fight Ghost]
Now Hyun Ji can see ghosts.
If a ghost attacks you this way...
Let's practice
as if it's a real situation.
How did you get to know Bong Pal?
- It was like fate.
- I miss you.
I don't want her to
live like me, so please help.
He's not after Bong Pal next, is he?
What's wrong?
I thought I got my memory
back from the accident.
- Is he Park Ji Hoon?
- You go alone.
Bong Pal!
- Where are we going?
- It's kind of far from here.
- Help Hyun Ji more than me.
- You punk.
Don't be afraid.
I will always be with you.