This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Bong Pal!
Hyun Ji, find the weapon!
It's the only thing that will stop him!
Monk Myung Chul!
Bong Pal!
Bong Pal, are you okay?
Monk Myung Chul.
Monk Myung Chul!
Monk Myung Chul! Wake up!
Bong Pal.
- Bong Pal.
- Monk Myung Chul.
Move your hand, punk.
I can't breathe.
Are you okay?
Help me up.
Let's see that punk.
Goodness, this rascal.
The gods have looked kindly upon him.
He's still breathing.
Goodness, you suffered a lot too.
You went through a lot.
Bong Pal! Hyun Ji!
[Final Episode]
Good job.
Let's go, Mr. Joo Hye Sung. Let's go.
Monk.
What is going to happen to
Professor Joo Hye Sung now?
In some ways, he's a victim too.
In our eyes, yes. But to normal
people, he is just a murderer.
An evil spirit took over his body because
he had hatred in his heart at the start.
You can't overlook that crime.
Oh dear Buddha.
I'm going to go home and get some rest.
You take Hyun Ji home.
Yes.
I'll see you later.
Hyun Ji!
Let me look at you! Are you okay?
You're not hurt anywhere?
I'm okay.
- Dad.
- Let's go inside.
Young man, I clearly told you that
I do not like you seeing Hyun Ji.
She's been in danger twice
already because of you.
- What if she got hurt?
- I'm sorry.
Mom, stop. Bong Pal did nothing wrong.
Go inside the house with your dad.
Take her inside.
- Mom.
- Honey.
Let's go, Hyun Ji.
We're going to leave here tomorrow.
If you have feelings for
Hyun Ji, then end it here.
It's best for both of you.
I believe you understand me.
Ma'am.
Please give this to Hyun Ji.
Please.
No Hyun Joo.
Im Hyun Soo.
Park Ji Hoon.
And Joo Jin Myung.
You remember these people, right?
Mr. Joo Hye Sung.
Yes.
I remember.
I killed them.
I...
killed all these people.
Hye Sung.
- You're home.
- Yes.
Is it okay to drink when you're injured?
There's no medicine for
getting beaten by a ghost.
Alcohol is the best
to overcome the pain.
There's no food either.
Just wait a little bit.
Thanks.
Gosh, this looks good.
Wow, you really know how to cook.
Is Hyun Ji leaving?
Yes, she's leaving tomorrow.
I see. It's time for everyone
to go back to their normal lives.
You must be sad.
- No, I'm fine.
- Good.
It's not like distance is going
to break you two apart, right?
On days like this,
let's drink up and go to bed.
Oh goodness.
This is nice.
Why did you do it? I know it wasn't you.
- Let's talk to the detective again--
- I did it.
The crimes I committed in my heart are
bigger than the ones I physically did.
If I didn't have those bad
intentions in my heart back then...
It wouldn't have come to be like this.
My hand...
I killed those people in my heart.
That fact will never change.
- Hye Sung.
- And...
don't ever come here
again. If you see my face...
It will only give you pain.
No, it's not true.
I'm going to come every day.
I'm going to come and see you.
I'm going to keep coming
until you forgive me.
I'm going to come even
if you refuse to see me.
I'm going to come every day to see you.
- What's Hyun Ji doing?
- She's talking in her room.
With who?
- I swear.
- Leave her alone. It's the last time.
I'm leaving today.
Our stuff is all packed and ready to go.
Bong Pal.
I hope you understand why Mom did that.
I completely understand.
Don't worry about it.
- Thanks.
- Study hard down there.
- That way we'll be able to meet quickly.
- I will.
Hyun Ji, let's go.
I have to go now.
Hyun Ji, get in.
Okay.
I don't want to go.
I want to be with you.
I don't want to send you off either.
Why aren't you here to see me?
I don't know when we'll
see each other again.
- Don't you miss me?
- I do miss you.
But I'm afraid I won't be able
to let you go if I see you.
- Bong Pal.
- Hyun Ji.
I want you to get back to your
normal life as soon as possible.
I don't want you to put
anything off because of me.
We'll be apart for now, but we can always
be together once you come to college.
Once that happens, let's formally ask
for your mother's permission to date.
I know it'll be hard...
but let's look forward to that day.
Let's be patient and wait.
Okay, I will.
Take care of yourself until then.
This is how you're supposed
to eat a lettuce wrap.
Where's my phone?
Hello?
Yes, this is the 24-hour exorcism
service, how may I help you?
Chapter eight on conjunction.
Please turn to the correct page.
[2018 SAT Exams]
[Hyun Ji's college admission results]
[Wait List Results]
[Hyun Ji]
You see me, don't you?
How dare you ignore me!
Go away!
I don't want any bad luck on
an important day like this.
I said get lost!
Why are there so many
ghosts like that these days?
Please enter the six digits of
your birthday for Myungsung University.
[Hyun Ji]
Hello?
- Bong Pal.
- What happened?
I'm sorry.
I didn't pass the exam.
You didn't get in?
That's okay, you can
just do better next time.
With that score,
you'll pass for sure next time.
Still, I wanted to
go to school with you.
You're graduating this year.
Well, I'll sit this semester out.
Forget it. Don't be ridiculous.
You need to get a job right away.
That way you can start
planning for the future.
That way...
- That way what?
- You know what I'm talking about.
So what is it?
- You really don't know?
- I don't know.
Is that right? Then you're
going to live alone forever.
Why should I live alone?
I'm going to live with you.
After four years.
Why after four years?
By then, I'll have a stable career.
You'll be graduating about
that time, so it's perfect.
What do you think? You like it, right?
Who said I'm going
to live with you, huh?
You're funny.
Ah, when do classes start?
- March fifth.
- That's coming up soon.
You're going to be busy.
How am I going to wait another year?
It'll pass soon enough.
- Come join our club!
- Hello!
A price that doesn't honor
the value of the property...
It's not simple like this.
Okay, that's all for class today.
I want you to submit a group report
next week on resource distribution.
Quiet.
Here are the designated groups.
Take a look before you leave.
Good job on your first day of class.
See you next week.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Senior Bong Pal.
We're in the same group
and we're counting on you.
[Park Bong Pal]
- Okay, let's do our best.
- Okay!
See you next week.
Hey, Bong Pal!
Bong Pal, Bong Pal, Bong Pal!
- Senior.
- We're in trouble.
- What's going on?
- We're in trouble. What do we do?
What's wrong?
You'll know once you get there.
Senior! Senior!
[Notice of Compliance]
In Rang is gone, Seo Yeon is gone,
and not a single freshman is willing...
What are we supposed to do now?
Our club is in danger
of being shut down again.
- That's too bad, I guess.
- That's... "That's too bad, I guess."
We're in a crisis right now.
As co-president,
how can you be so nonchalant?
Who is co-president?
- Me?
- Then who else would it be?
It's just the two of us.
Who else would it be?
You have to be the next
president once I graduate!
I'm not really interested.
So... the tradition and
history we're so proud of...
Are you saying you want to get
rid of our Blood Sausage Soup club?
I have to go to class. See you.
Don't go.
Be strong.
Don't go, Bong Pal. Don't go, Bong Pal.
Bong Pal, Bong Pal, Bong Pal!
Bong Pal!
You selfish bastard.
[In Rang]
Hello?
What time is it? Come quickly if
class is over! What are you doing? Huh?
I'll be right there. Don't get annoyed.
- Hurry up! Class is over!
- Stop nagging.
- Move it!
- I'm coming!
Exorcism is about getting rid of
ghosts, evil spirits, and monsters
that inhabit humans and places.
It is a scary and dirty job.
Shamans, monks, and the spiritually
blessed have been exorcising for years.
In 2018, Blood Sausage Soup has
joined hands with these people...
Excuse me.
Is there anything you're curious about?
I don't know where and what went wrong
- but I need to ask now.
- Yes, please go ahead.
Isn't this
a blood sausage soup restaurant?
I wanted a bowl of it to go.
- You want it to go?
- It's a service everyone offers lately.
No... it's not.
- Yes, we're...
- Gosh, I'm so sorry!
- I came to a ghost-catching business.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- No, I'm sorry.
- I'm truly sorry.
- Not at all. I'm sorry.
- I should've been more clear. Goodbye.
- Yes, goodbye.
- Goodbye.
- This is not a restaurant.
Did you get work for us? Huh?
Our name is Blood Sausage Soup,
so he came to eat.
What time is it right now?
Why are you MIA lately?
Did you pass out the flyers?
I did. I did pass the flyers out
but I think we need to
hire a part-time employee.
It's kind of hard doing
this all by myself.
A part-time employee?
How can that just easily
come out of your mouth?
We haven't had a single job
since we opened up our business!
And wait a minute.
Look at this.
I see that you ate a special
variety meat set yesterday.
I told you to cut off
meals at 5,500 won!
5,500 won meals are hard to find.
I just ate one for 5,000 won!
We will never be able to pay
my grandma back at this rate!
I got this investment because I believed
in you! You said it would be a hit!
You said we could pay
it all back in a month.
The thing is, if you look at the way
the economy is doing these days...
What about new freshman recruits?
We're still...
Still?
We received a grant from the school
and we still have no new members?
We're going to jail
if the school finds out.
Look, I'm doing my very best.
- Let's clean this place up.
- Huh?
Let's do some cleaning. Let's clean
the windows and dust the office.
My head hurts,
so I'm going to rest a bit.
- Clean?
- Go ahead and start.
You want me to clean?
I'm the CEO.
I have to do all the dirty work just
because you got the investment money.
Yeah, I don't blame you
for rubbing it in my face.
- Do we have coffee?
- Yes, we do.
- How do you want it?
- Just black.
- Goodness, it's been a long time.
- Yes, Monk Myung Chul.
I hope I'm not late.
The thing is, I've been
trying to get a hold of you
and you're not answering your phone.
Is there something going on?
The shamaness has told us that your
prayers and energy have no effect at all.
Which shamaness is going around
saying such nonsense about me?
What do you mean nonsense?
Why are you here?
Why can't you cross
over to the afterlife?
Believe. Redeem your sorry soul!
Who is this pitiful-looking man?
Get rid of him.
What is this?
She's from Daeryong Mountain.
She calls herself
the 1,000-year-old virgin shamaness.
A virgin shamaness?
Why are there so many?
She's not a virgin shamaness!
She's just a con artist!
You insolent fool! Leave immediately!
You have no credentials or pedigree!
How dare you con these good people!
How dare you call me a fraud!
I can't believe you dragged this
good-for-nothing monk into the house!
I'm a great and honorable
monk who catches evil spirits!
Leave if you're done! How dare you
impersonate a shamaness, you fake.
Fake? Fake?
- Oh my.
- What's wrong?
What is going on?
Have you lost your mind?
Goodness, attention!
Congratulations on your promotion.
Stop, you're embarrassing me.
Chief.
Why did you push her?
I didn't push her.
This woman couldn't control her
anger and she tripped and fell.
She says she's a virgin shamaness.
Please check and see.
I think this woman is a fraud.
Why do you keep hitting me, woman?
Stop her! She's attacking me!
Calm down!
Have we met before?
You look familiar.
- I go to church.
- Hallelujah?
Amen.
Stop her!
- Senior.
Where are you going?
- I'm going home.
- Don't go home.
There's the freshman
welcome party today.
Ah.
- I'm not interested in those events.
- No, you have to go.
You have to be there.
- Please go.
- Let's go together.
Senior, let's go.
Let's go.
Are all the drinks poured?
- Do you all have drinks or not?
- We do!
It's rare to drink with us seniors!
Economy major cheer on
the count of three, got it?
- Yes!
- One, two, three!
Economy major!
There is a really pretty freshman
girl who got admitted this year.
I saw her too. She's totally hot.
Hello, I'm economy major
Kim Ji Eun, class of 2018.
Please take good care of me.
Hello, I'm economy major...
- She's so cute.
- Please take good care of me.
Hello, I'm economy major
Lee Dong Min, class of 2018.
It's my goal to become
the Adam Smith of Korea. Thank you.
Hello, Seniors. I'm economy
major Kim Hyun Ji, class of 2018.
I'd appreciate your guidance.
Hey, she's the one!
- I have a question.
- Yes?
By any chance, do you have a boyfriend?
Yes, he's here.
He's here?
Why did you lie about not passing?
I did it on purpose
so I could surprise you.
I had no idea. I was wondering how
I was going to wait another year.
You said it'll pass soon enough.
I didn't mean it.
But where are you staying?
At my uncle's.
It's close to your place too.
Really? Good.
- Aren't you happy to see me?
- Of course.
From now on, I'm going
to stick to you like glue.
You better be good to me from now on.
- Older sister?
- Of course, I'm older than you.
You're one year younger than me.
Older sister, my butt.
Let's get the nicknames out of the way.
Bong Pal, repeat after me.
Older sister.
No.
You better listen to me.
One more time. "Older sister."
- Forget it.
- Why? Just say it once, okay?
Older sister. Older sister.
- No, I don't want to!
- Say "older sister"!
Just say it this once. Please?
- Now go in.
- Okay.
- Good night.
- What's the matter?
- I just like you so much.
I like you a lot too.
- Go in now.
- All right.
- Sweet dreams.
- You too.
Hi, Monk Myung Chul.
Hello.
Where is Monk Myung Chul?
Bong Pal.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, you're not a kid.
How could you get into a fight, huh?
In my field, there are
business ethics to follow.
That shamaness didn't do it.
That's why I... taught her a lesson.
- Thank you. I will go now.
- Monk Myung Chul.
- Yes?
- Well...
You're not well and all.
Why don't you stop working?
Stop working and stay with me.
- With you?
- Yes.
Your place in the mountain
isn't very comfortable.
I emptied the spare room.
Move in with me. I know it's such
a hassle to commute back and forth.
Bong Pal.
You're the only family member I have now.
Gosh.
You know how to make people cry, huh?
Do you have any sausage at home?
On a day like this, it'll be great
to have soju and sausage.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Hyun Ji!
Hey, Soo Jin.
Do you have time tonight?
What? What about tonight?
Management department guys
asked three girls out on a blind date.
- Can you please come with us?
- A blind date?
Well, you know I have a boyfriend.
We know that you're going out
with one of our seniors.
Can you keep this from him
and come out with us this once?
We were afraid
the guys would be a disaster.
So we told them we'd bring
the prettiest girl in our department.
They told me that they'd bring
the handsomest boys. Please.
Come on, me the prettiest girl?
If Bong Pal finds out,
he will get really mad.
Once people know you two are going out
you will never be asked
on a blind date.
You got into college and will graduate
without being on a blind date?
Wow, she is really pretty.
With the other two,
she looks even prettier.
Hello, I'm a freshman in
the Management department, Kim Tae Young.
You're as pretty as we've heard.
Really? Thank you.
What is this? Only three boys were
supposed to come meet us.
They all begged me to come along.
We managed to cut many others.
Here.
Thank you.
[My love Bong Bong]
Your call is being redirected...
I'm done with my class.
Where are you?
I'm discussing homework
with my classmates at a café.
I will call you later.
Let's break the ice, shall we?
Can we go around
and introduce ourselves first?
- Sure.
- Me first?
What homework all of a sudden?
I guess I will just go then.
Drink up! Drink up!
Alcohol is coming. Drink up!
It will make you want to dance.
- A knight to the rescue.
- I can drink this.
- No way.
- I will drink it.
- Come on.
I'm the knight for you!
[We're on a blind date with girls
from the Management Department.]
[They're the best.]
- Hello, In Rang.
- Hi, Pal. Where are you now?
- I'm at home.
- Are you?
Do you happen to know where Hyun Ji is?
Hyun Ji?
She said she's
at a café doing homework.
Ah, she's doing her homework at a café...
Pal, do you want to take a look
at the video I'm sending now?
Sure.
This is the game that Hyun Ji likes!
Here we go.
You two look like a couple.
- Don't we?
- Let's go for the second round.
Did you two already decide?
- Hyun Ji...
- Yes? What?
Senior Bong Pal.
- By the way, who is this?
- Me?
I'm Hyun Ji's boyfriend.
Bong Pal, are you really mad?
I always wanted to
go on a blind date at college.
Can you let it go this once, please?
When you have a boyfriend... what?
You went on a blind date
and you want me to let it go?
- I told them that I had a boyfriend.
- What?
When we were introducing ourselves,
I told them I had a boyfriend.
If you don't trust me,
go ask them.
I just went there to feel
the craziness of college life.
- You got into college for this, did you?
- Yes.
- Why else?
- Oh my.
I was kidding.
It took me seven years
to become a college student.
I'm just loving it.
I want to try everything
I haven't done before.
So please don't be mad, Bong Pal.
Bong Pal. Bong Bong.
Bong Pal, please...
I'm so sorry that I'm turning cute...
- Gosh.
- You laughed, didn't you?
- I did not laugh.
- Yes, you did.
- Come on, you so laughed.
- Hey, you laughed.
- No, I did not.
I hate to say goodbye.
Me too.
Sweetie, where are you?
I'm up in Seoul now.
- Come home early.
- My mom must be here.
- Bong Pal, just go.
- What?
If my mom sees you,
she might say something.
- Get home safe. I will go.
- Hyun Ji.
Hey, what are you doing?
Bong Pal, hold on.
Bong Pal.
- Hello.
- Hello...
I heard you came up to Seoul.
I wanted to come by to say hi.
Ah, did you?
Why don't you come in?
By the way, isn't it too late
for you to hang out at this hour?
Mom, please don't say anything to him.
Did you come by because you
wanted to tell me something?
I have a feeling that you didn't
just come by to say hi...
Well, ma'am...
Hyun Ji and I'd like to get
your permission to go out officially.
Well, haven't you two been going out
without my permission all this time?
No, we haven't seen
each other all this time.
Can you stay out of it for now?
Are you sincerely asking
for my permission?
Yes.
Then if I tell you not to see her
will you never see her again?
Mom.
Honestly, I didn't have a good feeling
about you from the beginning.
When my daughter came back
from near death
you showed up out of nowhere
and followed her saying you liked her.
What parents wouldn't
be suspicious to accept you?
I understand.
Mom, are you serious?
- You mean it, right?
- Yes.
You got into college
and are all grown up now.
How can I possibly stop you?
Well, he doesn't seem like a bad boy.
Of course not. He's a very nice person.
Plus, he does so well in school.
He has a full scholarship
for all four years.
And there aren't any sports he can't do.
- You like him that much?
- Yes, I do like him.
Thank you, Mom. I love you, too.
What are you doing?
You're too big for this.
Oh my.
Today, Mrs. Yang
went out of her way to make this.
Try.
Excuse me, officer.
Thank you.
I made it when we had time for crafts.
If you don't like it,
you don't have to wear it.
I'm sorry.
It's so pretty.
It seems that it took us
too long to get to this point.
I'm sorry, Hye Sung.
Don't blame yourself anymore.
Now I am not angry or resentful anymore.
We can't go back
but let's share what we couldn't before.
Let's do that, Hye Sung.
I will.
Mother.
- Then...
- See you later.
Sure, have a good day.
I'm not picking this up.
- I'm here to throw this away.
- I didn't say anything.
I guess something is bothering you.
What? Nothing is bothering me.
Now that I look at your face this way
I see you have a face for good fortune.
Um, do I?
You shouldn't hurt yourself at your age.
Pleae be careful.
Thank you.
Oh my goodness.
Come on.
I'm so out of your league.
Well, he has an eye for beauty, I guess.
Oh my, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Here.
Haven't we met before?
Do you know me?
Se Ri!
- Se Ri.
- Hon, what took you so long?
I've been waiting for so long.
I can't go out with someone
who isn't punctual.
You're mad, aren't you?
I'm very sorry.
- Hon, let me carry them for you.
- Honey!
What is this guy doing here again?
Honey, I was wrong.
Please forgive me this once.
Why won't you leave
me alone? So irritating.
I told you that we were done.
Why are you doing this?
Se Ri doesn't want you.
Because of you, she's changed.
Why did you come on to her, huh?
What do you mean I came on to her?
Be a man and get lost, will you?
- Honey.
- Se Ri.
- Bong Pal.
- Seo Yeon.
- Long time no see.
- It sure has been.
I heard you got a job.
- At a good company, I hear.
- Well, I'm just doing an internship.
What brings you here at school?
- I needed to get some academic papers.
- Academic papers?
Honey, what are you doing here?
- You're the one from last time...
- Hi, I'm his girlfriend.
Ah, you have a girlfriend now, huh?
- Congratulations. You two look good.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- I will see you later.
- See you later.
What was that about?
Don't smile like that.
You look like a fool.
I didn't smile.
By the way, can you call me that again?
I don't want to.
Hey, please.
Hey, call me by that name again.
Aren't you late for your class?
I'm late. Excuse me. Sorry.
Honey, pay attention in your class.
How come there is
so much fat in this pork? I hate it.
I like the stew with tuna in it.
- Kimchi stew is better with pork in it.
- I agree. Isn't it?
That was an insult to pork kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew is better with pork.
- I agree. Isn't it?
That was an insult to pork kimchi stew.
When we're talking about kimchi stew
it's obvious pork kimchi stew
is the best, isn't it?
When the juice from the pork
meets sour and spicy kimchi
it gives the stew deep flavor.
- She doesn't know that, huh?
- I agree.
Why would she throw away such good stuff?
You seem to know
about deep meat flavor, huh?
It's not easy to know that
at our age, don't you think?
I'm Goo Dae Hyung, a sophomore
in the physical education department.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
I haven't seen your pretty face
around here. You must be a freshman.
- I am.
- A freshman, huh?
- Did you join any clubs yet?
- Not yet.
Not yet? Why don't you
join our club then?
What kind of club is it?
It's a club where we work
together to learn new flavors.
It's called "Let's Eat."
Among the nessecities of life,
food, clothing, and shelter
food means more than
just feeding ourselves.
It not only satisfies
our desire to feed ourselves
but also helps with stress from social
lives and loneliness from isolation.
So our club is sort of promoting
the pleasure of dining together.
So what do you think?
Doesn't it sound fun?
No, not at all.
- Hello, senior.
- How dare you?
You just got up in the middle of
trying to sell medicine?
- I'm sorry.
- Plus, you punk...
You can't recruit people
at a sacred place like the cafeteria.
Where are your ethics?
- I'm sorry.
- Go over there and stay.
Hyun Ji here will have an upset stomach.
I will. Please enjoy your lunch.
Ones who are so smooth
with words are not to be trusted.
You're not going to fall for
what he says and join his club, are you?
- It'll be a disaster.
- Of course not.
In Rang graduated,
but why are you still here?
You can't talk about it so openly.
It's top secret.
Actually, do you have time after lunch?
I have something to tell you.
[Life and Sundae Soup]
You've been given such
a fantastic opportunity to be here.
Now your life will be divided into
before and after
you experience Sundae Soup.
Kim In Rang.
These are
the light refreshments we prepared.
I hope you enjoy them.
Here we go again.
By the way,
Chun Sang isn't a student, is he?
Isn't he a scam artist?
By promoting
academic-industrial collaboration
we, Sundae Soup, contribute to
local and national development
and lead innovative cultural tradition.
In doing so, we'd like to
contribute to your bright future.
Once you join our Sundae Soup...
No need to listen anymore. Let's go.
Top-notch multi-communication.
We provide speedy and accurate service.
We provide 24-hour exorcism services.
We can do it all. Where...
Hey...
Hey guys, Bong Pal.
How could you just leave?
We still have part two.
I'm not going to join any clubs.
- Why not?
- I need to study hard so I can graduate.
Gosh, isn't this too harsh?
You don't want to be the president
or even join the club?
Why don't we just
get rid of the club then?
But we can still work together, huh?
We couldn't do any work without you two.
Bong Pal, Hyun Ji.
We're begging you this once.
If our business goes bankrupt
I will owe my grandma so much
and she will break his arms and legs.
She will break them.
Please save my arms and legs.
If we work together
we could really hit a jackpot.
Chun Sang, it's just that...
- I don't need money anymore.
- Me neither.
Guys, it's not about money, you know.
You need to keep in mind that
we're not doing this
to make money, right?
Have you forgotten
the sacred idea of Sundae Soup?
Like a pot that is boiling 24 hours
at a rice soup restaurant
let's try to help
those who are suffering.
What do you think about the idea?
Did you already forget our promise?
Bong Pal. Hyun Ji.
Your power comes
with great responsibilities.
Will you really let
your power go to waste?
Do you know how many kids
are waiting to be rescued?
Hold on.
Hello, this is 24-hour
exorcism service, Sundae Soup.
I'm a representative, Kim In Rang.
How may I help you?
A ghost? A ghost?
Are you hurt? Calm down.
Take a big breath.
Where are you at?
I will come right over.
I understand. All right then.
Gosh, what do we do?
These people's cry.
We can shine some light on their misery.
Let's do it together.
- Let's go, please.
- Please.
Someone is hurt.
- Bong Pal.
- Yes?
What Chun Sang was saying
isn't entirely wrong.
What do you mean?
It's hard to see ghosts.
But we can help them at the same time.
Why would you want to help ghosts?
Aren't they the same as us?
They haven't crossed over to the other
side and are just lost right now.
Think about it.
Not all ghosts are bad.
They have their pain
and sadness just like us.
My son. My son.
- Monk Myung Chul.
- Yes?
Why do you exorcise?
It's a tough job, but doesn't pay much.
I help with the lingering attachment
of the ghosts who can't leave yet.
I help get rid of people's fear.
That way, everybody finds their way back.
They go back to the places
where they belong.
That's why I do it.
Do you think I can do the job?
Bong Pal.
When I found out that
you'd go around exorcising
do you know why I was so against that?
Not sure.
It was because I could see
hatred in your eyes then.
You can't see the world right
when you have so much anger in you.
You were hurt by ghosts.
But not all ghosts are bad.
In a way, we should feel sorry for them.
Are you asking if you can do the job?
It's up to you what you think.
Making others happy makes you happiest.
If your eyes can give the dead ones peace
you're not cursed,
but you have a special gift.
By the way, it's so unlike you
that you're saying all good things.
When do I ever say bad things, punk?
- I think this is your first time.
- What?
Please continue.
Ah, it's so good.
- This is really nice.
- Yes.
How long has it been?
Seriously, how long has it been?
I love going together like this!
Hyun Ji. Bong Pal.
Let's do this for the rest of our lives!
Do this forever!
Let's go!
Bong Pal.
Yes?
Why did you change your mind so suddenly?
- I want to know.
- Know what?
The reason why we can see ghosts.
Let's go.
- Let's fight ghosts!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let’s Fight Ghost]
[Thank you so much
for tuning into Let's Fight Ghost.]