This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Fight Ghost]
I see ghosts and I can beat them up.
Seven girls fainted not too long ago.
Seoyi Girls' High School.
Can you get rid of a ghost?
- I will pay you 10 million won.
- Deal! Deal!
Ghost!
Do you want to die, huh?
Do you want to die?
You've never kissed a guy before?
That was my first kiss, you bastard!
He used to be in such demand.
What happened to him?
What is he doing?
He's not a high school girl!
He's a pervert!
You perverted bastard!
- Give me my 10 million won!
- I don't have it!
Don't ever appear before
me again or you're dead!
You're an elite college student?
Park Bong Pal.
Mom, over here!
- Bong Pal!
- Mom!
Honey!
Mom.
Bong Pal.
Why don't you ever
play with your friends?
You're always playing by
yourself in the corner.
Let's go.
Look.
It's so much fun if you
play with your friends.
The moogoonghwa flowers have bloomed!
I was wrong! I'm sorry, lady!
Please forgive me! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, lady!
Please forgive me!
I was wrong! I'm sorry, lady!
[Let's Fight Ghost]
[Episode 2]
What has he been up to all night?
Why is he just coming in?
Hey.
What took you so long?
I've been waiting for a long time.
What's with you?
How did you know to come here?
Did you forget?
I'm a ghost.
So why did you come here?
I just need to confirm one thing,
so just hold on, okay?
- What are you doing?
- Just hold still for a second, okay?
- How dare you get fresh with me!
- Hey!
- What?
- I need to check something, okay?
Give me a break and what's
with the disrespectful language?
You're obviously way younger than me.
Thanks for thinking that I'm young,
but it's been five years since I died.
You're just a college sophmore.
I'm older than you.
You're older than me?
Forget it.
Why do I bother to even talk to you?
I'm tired. Go away.
You're so annoying.
Ah, I forgot.
What's this?
Ta-da.
Who said you could come in here?
Can't you just say "thank you"?
Thank you very much.
Now please leave.
You're actually quite
tidier than you look.
Please go. Go.
So do me this one favor.
It's not hard to do. All you have
to do is just close your eyes.
Forget it. You're not the first
ghost to nag and plead like that.
I don't what you're up to,
but look for someone else.
Should I introduce you?
All I need is you.
Help me out just this once!
Please? Please? Come on!
No! No! No!
And you're pretty
shameless for a ghost.
You didn't even pay
me my 10 million won.
Can't believe you're upset
over a measly 10 million won.
A measly... a measly 10 million won?
I know I left a charm that
exorcised ghosts in here.
Here it is.
Take this!
Don't touch that. We won't be
able to get the AS if you break it.
We lost everything else,
so let's be careful with that.
Should we just get the AS?
Chun Sang!
Chung Sang, I found it! I found it!
Wow! I was right, wasn't I?
He just hit a ghost, right?
- We didn't see wrong, right?
- I think so. I'm not sure.
I'm right! That's a ghost right there!
- You saw it too.
- Right, I did see it.
This guy can really see ghosts.
He threw a solid punch
right to that ghost's face.
Wow, our junior is no joke!
But Chun Sang, we saw the ghost too.
What's the matter with you?
That was a silver code!
Oh yeah... silver code?
When a person is in the grips of
terror, they can see the ghost.
The moment where that ghost and you
connect is called the silver code.
- Ah, silver code!
- Are you not going to study?
Are you the vice president
of this club or not?
I am.
The thing is, our junior isn't
seeing ghosts with the silver code.
Look. He's staring right at the ghost.
That's why he can fight
against the ghosts!
Wow! Wow, I really want to recruit him.
Hey, does he go to our school?
Hurry up and find him.
We can't lose him! Find him!
- Already?
- Yes.
Sophmore economics major, Park Bong Pal.
- Hello!
- Hey there!
He's so cool. Now that is what
a man is supposed to look like.
What are you? A squid?
Hey, you should get a dog too.
What is this? You look sad
and pathetic eating alone.
Dog my butt.
You're so rude.
It's just how I am.
I love rolled eggs!
Go and buy some for yourself.
Come to think of it, you keep
forgetting that I'm a ghost.
How am I supposed to buy it? I can't!
Ghosts can only eat food
that is given to them.
Haven't you done ancestral rites before?
Oh.
Now that you know, give me
a piece of that egg and rice ball.
Oh, sure. Here. Here you go.
Seriously, it's so good.
- Goodness, you're eating alone again.
- How sad.
Let's formally introduce ourselves.
I'm a junior physical education
major and my name is Choi Chun Sang.
I'm Choi Chun Sang...
And this is...
I'm a junior computer science
major and my name is Kim In Rang.
- And?
- And...
What do you mean "and"?
Didn't we overcome
that terror the other day, my brother?
We saw it. We saw your courageous
battle against that ghost!
So...
How about we do this together?
Let's destroy this darkness together!
I don't want to.
- He's stubborn.
- He's tough.
That was refreshing.
- You're sweating.
- Am I?
Yes.
Wow, there's a lot of students in here.
My attendance list has 22 students, but
I see the waitlisted ones are here too.
Yes.
My class won't be fun.
I think your expectations are too high.
I'll introduce myself first.
Due to personal reasons, Professor Lee
Ji Sung will no longer teach this class.
Therefore, I will be taking over
for the rest of the semester.
I'm Joo Hye Sung, a veterinary professor
at this school. It's nice to meet you.
Professor, you were
totally cool earlier.
Is your hand okay? It doesn't hurt?
Yes, I'm fine.
I feel like I've become a celebrity all
of a sudden. It's a bit embarrassing.
Okay, let's start class.
The enrolled students might be distracted
so I ask the rest of you to leave please.
I'll see you guys next semester.
Yes, 22 students is the perfect
size for a class, don't you think?
I'm going to call each of your names.
- No Hyun Joo.
- Here.
It's nice to meet you.
- Park Bong Pal.
- Here.
- Im Seo Hyun.
It's nice to meet you.
Jung Shi Ah.
- Here.
- Are you happy?
Oh, she's pretty.
You like girls like Im Seo Hyun, huh?
All slender and willowy.
Please go!
- Do you have nowhere to go?
- No, I don't.
You're seriously driving me crazy!
You, over there.
Student Park Bong Pal.
- Yes?
- Is there a problem?
No, I'm sorry.
Okay, let's continue.
Na Jin Soo.
Here.
It's nice to meet you.
It's been a week
and the ranking... oh my god!
We're dropping like crazy! Why is
Sadako posting so many negative comments?
I don't think we'll even be able
to pay for the maintenance fees.
You scared me.
What are we to do then? Don't
you know how expensive that thing is?
Is anyone inside?
I'm from the housing agency.
I know you're inside.
Please vacate the room by next week.
If you don't, we'll enter
without permission. Understood?
- So what are we going to do now?
- What can we do?
We have to use any means
necessary to recruit Park Bong Pal.
Don't you think that'll be tough?
It seems like he's not very
close to his colleagues either.
Is he being ostracized?
I think he's the one
who's ostracizing them.
A lone ranger in this lonely world. He's
definitely the person we're looking for.
Just stick to him like glue no matter
what and tell him he's our savior.
It won't happen right away, but
he'll come around if we don't give up.
Once that happens...
The money and fame will
be falling from the skies.
Our popularity will go up.
And we'll have so many new
members joining our club.
- Among those members...
- Tons of them will be girls.
- They cut off the electricity.
- It's so dark.
- First class was great.
- Thank you.
The first class is always hard.
Ah, I hear there is a student that
helps with this class. Who is it?
It's me.
- Im Seo Hyun?
- Yes.
I'm sure it's tough preparing
the lecture by yourself.
Is anyone willing to help out?
Here.
Park Bong Pal?
Then please go ahead
and help Im Seo Hyun out.
See you all next time. Good job.
Thank you.
You're a junior in our major, right?
Sophmore economics major?
- Yes.
- You don't know me very well, do you?
- We're in the same major.
- He knows you very well!
I don't really attend the major events.
Liar.
I'm Im Seo Hyun.
Senior economics major.
Yes, it's nice to meet you.
Great, I look forward
to working with you.
Yes.
It's all because of me.
Don't forget it.
You know you like it!
Eat carefully. You eat so well.
You must've been very hungry.
Professor, I was looking for you.
What for?
The previous professor asked
me to take care of this file.
I don't know what to do with it.
I'll take it and give it to him.
Thank you.
Hey, eat slowly.
Isn't he the dog that bit your hand?
You're quite famous, aren't you?
You're famous for being evil.
He's so cute.
Are you going to raise him now?
No, I'm keeping him temporarily
until the owner comes for him.
If not, then I'm going to take
him to the hospital tomorrow.
Yes, this is Joo Hye Sung.
Professor, it's two
hours before the seminar.
You're not in the waiting
room. Where are you?
Ah, I'm at the school right now.
I'm sorry, I'll leave right now.
Yes.
I'm sorry, but if you have time,
can you watch over him until he's done?
There's medicine mixed inside,
so he has to eat all of it.
- You just have to watch him.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
You have to eat all of it, okay?
- Goodbye.
No, I didn't make it.
I'm going to head to the hospital.
My shoulders feel so stiff.
I'm thinking of getting a physical exam.
Honey, your skin is so great!
- Kyung Ja!
- Hyun Ji, what are you doing here?
- I'm following someone.
- Who?
He's... I'll tell you later.
See you soon.
See you.
Honey!
Taxi! Taxi! Oh my, honey!
It's crazy hot. Why are
you working out so hard?
That ghost yesterday
must've really gotten to you.
Shut up and leave!
It's better to work out together.
Who's going to work out with you?
Stop playing and come down.
Gosh, you're pretty weak for a guy.
That's why you're
always getting beaten up.
- Besides, I'm so light.
- Yeah right. Come down!
Hey, aren't you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Let's go down and order some
fried chicken! What do you think?
I bet it's so good! Chicken! Chicken!
Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!
- Hey!
- Chicken!
Hey!
- Hey!
- Catch me if you can!
- I swear!
- Come and get me!
Goodness, poor soul.
- What a pity.
- Someone died over there again.
- Where? At Gampo?
- Yes.
I'm sure he died because of
the ghost that haunts there!
You know, that girl who came from
the coffee shop a long time ago.
- Eun Shil?
- Yes, Eun Shil!
They discovered her
dead body in the closet.
That wretched husband of
hers beat her to death.
Right, and ever since,
people have been dying there!
Her husband got stabbed
there and died too.
- It serves him right!
- Exactly.
Oh my gosh! Who are you?
Where is this Gampo place?
Go over there!
Goodness, you scared me.
- The head is the best part.
- Oh my gosh.
- Who is he?
- I have no idea.
Seriously, who is he?
I'm telling you it's fine!
What's wrong with all of you?
Goodness, what is going on here?
Goodness, I'm so sorry!
No, it's quite all right.
- By any chance, are you Monk Myung Chul?
- Yes.
- I'm Monk Myung Chul.
- What took you so long?
Please go inside.
Goodness, the energy of this place!
So this is where the person died.
- And it was yesterday?
- Yes, that's correct!
How did you know that?
They say you're old news...
No, you're very courageous.
Anyway, something bad happens
whenever you go inside there.
Rumors are spreading and I'm so upset!
Monk, I leave it up to you.
I understand. Let's see here.
- What is that?
- Do you see something?
I feel a menacing energy.
I feel a woman's energy.
There's a story, too.
Her name is... Eun Shil?
- Eun Shil?
- Is she in there?
- You can see that too?
- Hush!
I didn't put you in
a bad position, did I?
It's simple.
Just in case, please step back.
Yes.
Lady! Lady, call the shaman!
Call the shaman!
Lady!
[STAR VETERINARY HOSPITAL]
Doctor, you're here.
Oh my, who is this?
He's a new member of the family.
Please give him some vitamins.
You're a little late.
I had to go to school because of him.
- Is the surgery room ready?
- Yes.
- I'm going to change my clothes.
- Okay.
At this rate, we're going to be a safe
house instead of a veterinary clinic.
We're spending more money on
food than on hospital supplies.
What if we end up going bankrupt?
I know.
Come here. Goodness.
You're so adorable.
Where did you come from?
Bong Pal, wait for me!
Just that one...
Hey, please give me one bite.
Look at that over there.
It's going fast.
I also want to ride it.
Can you make kimchi stew
instead of bean paste stew?
I have a knife in my hand,
so be quiet.
Kimchi stew and rolled eggs, please?
Can you please go away?
Can't you go home
and whine there? Why me?
I said I had nowhere to go.
I don't remember my home or my mom.
I don't know why I died, either.
That's why I've been stealing food
from memorial services for others.
Do you know how sad it is to do so?
This one time, I got bitten
by a dog at this house.
Don't you feel bad for me?
Have you changed your strategy?
I don't feel bad for you at all.
Bong Pal.
Now you really need to go.
He may be a useless monk now,
but he used to be really good.
I don't know what he might do to you.
Gosh.
I thought you'd be away
for a few more days.
Here is a present for you.
What happened to your face?
Well, I have my reasons.
I may have to stay with you
for a few more days.
I'm sensing this strange energy here.
Well, who could this be?
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Sure.
Have a seat.
You're not even a kid.
Why did your face get all beaten up?
This sausage tastes good.
Bong Pal.
I hope you stop trying to exorcise.
It's not something
you should consider lightly.
If so, can you lend me some money?
About 90 million.
Let's just eat.
Can I have some of that too?
Where are you going
in the middle of dinner?
I want to grill more sausage.
- We have plenty left here.
- It's not for you.
There is a stray cat around here.
What kind of stray cat
comes up to the fourth floor?
There is this wicked cat.
Make a lot. A lot.
What shall we eat?
I'm all happy now.
Doctor Joo, we're done for the day.
We will see you tomorrow.
Sure, have a good evening.
I will wrap up here, so go ahead.
- Okay.
- Have a good night.
- Get home safely.
- We will.
Let's see...
[LOOKING FOR A NEW OWNER
FOR AN ABANDONED DOG]
Oh my. You're the one I saw
at school, aren't you?
How can you be this cute?
What brings you here?
I didn't know
this was your animal hospital.
- You live nearby, huh?
- Yes.
Ah, thank you for what you did yesterday.
No problem. It was nothing.
By the way, you haven't
found its owner yet, huh?
Ah...
Not yet. We have to find someone nice.
By the way, can you keep
this location from other students?
I understand.
Then I will go.
Get home safely.
Gosh, why does he sleep like that?
Oh, this must be him, huh?
Then they are his mom and dad?
Why does he live alone then?
[TEST PREP FOR CIVIL SERVANTS]
Wow, he's very frugal.
He's so precise.
This is why he doesn't give me a chance.
That way, I can confirm something.
A chance?
Okay. That's not lips.
That's blood sausage.
Blood sausage.
Oh my goodness!
You scared me.
What was that?
What did you just do to me?
What do you mean?
You!
- Did you just walk on top of me?
- It was the stray cat.
The stray cat?
The cat must have a lot of karma.
Meow.
Oh my, I must have gotten hit badly.
This is lasting a long time.
Did he check the message or not?
How come he's not responding?
Bong Pal.
Did you read
the last letter from your dad?
What did it say?
- I have no idea.
- Didn't you read it?
Hurry and read it.
- I threw it away.
- Why did you do that?
Aren't you curious
what your dad is up to and where?
Not really.
That punk... why did he
have to throw it away?
He's just like his dad, seriously.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I threw away something by accident.
- You're trying to steal this box, right?
- No.
The company we have a contract
with is picking this all up.
How can you steal them?
Boxes have been missing for days.
I'm trying to look for something,
not steal them.
Mister, even if it's hard to get by...
you should work to
make a living, not like this.
You shouldn't try to get things for free.
I do work. Actually, I live in Unit 402.
The boy threw away something
by accident, and I'm here to get it.
You keep on lying.
It's been so long since someone
moved out of Unit 402.
This tall good-looking boy
lives in Unit 402.
I've lived in this apartment
building for 10 years.
Stop lying. Just leave it and go.
Mister, you're going bald
because you want things for free.
Seriously, gosh.
Why would you bring
my appearance into this?
- What else should I bring up then?
- You could just say nothing.
Oh my! I told you to leave it, Mister.
I just need to find this letter.
I know you'll steal the box
while you pretend to do so.
- Why do you keep saying that I'd steal?
- That's how you look.
Leave it here! Oh my.
Why hold my hand? You pervert!
I pushed you slightly.
Why did you fall back like that?
Who are you?
I'm the president of
this apartment community.
You're the president.
We're trying to separate our trash.
Why get so worked up?
I didn't get all worked up.
I simply said I lived in Unit 402.
- You know the tall boy...
- Did she leave?
I was trying to find this letter here...
She's nowhere to be seen.
I didn't see it. That's why...
The boy has been living here for years.
I told him to say hi
to his neighbors and all...
He's been by himself.
Bong Pal.
- Hello.
- Off to a class?
Yes, microeconomics.
It's Professor Kang's class, huh?
It must be tough. Have fun.
- I will see you in class next week.
- Sure. Bye.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You're in a good mood, huh?
I was until I saw you.
What do you mean?
I'm happy to see you.
- It's good that you're happy.
- Of course, it's a good thing.
You even have no shame, huh?
- I'm even pretty too.
- Stop kidding me.
With your face? I don't agree.
Go away so I can study.
He's started to scare me now.
He's talking to someone, right?
Yes, it seems he's talking to a ghost.
Wow.
I said go away.
Hello.
This is Park Bong Pal.
Sure, I can do that.
Well, why don't I come by
in two hours then?
All right then.
What is it?
Why are you suddenly all happy?
I'm going to work now.
Don't follow me.
I'm coming.
Seriously! I told you not to follow me!
Gosh.
Please don't follow me.
I'm begging you, please.
Then why don't you do me a favor first?
Forget I said anything.
Chun Sang, he was just talking
to a ghost again, wasn't he?
I think so...
I got goosebumps all over,
but I like him.
- Let's go.
- Seriously. How does he do that?
Why didn't he fix this broken washer?
He should fix the broken doorbell, too.
Why doesn't he fix things? How lazy!
By the way, where did I leave my sword?
Did Bong Pal take it by any chance?
He wouldn't have taken it.
Oh my goodness.
It's there.
He's moving.
Why does he keep coming
to a place like this? It's spooky.
Should we take one and start?
Shall we?
Well... here it is.
Let's go.
Oh my, who do we have here? The exorcist?
What? Are you the exorcist I called?
- Correct. I'm Park Bong Pal.
- Well...
Aren't you too young
to do this kind of work?
You look like a student.
Are you sure you can do this?
Buy yourself some clothes, will you?
You don't look convincing
because you go around looking like this.
Well, just let me do the job.
What if you take off with the deposit
like the monk yesterday?
I will find that monk and kick his butt.
I'm totally different
from those con artists.
I will get paid after the job
is done, so don't worry.
You can wire the money
after you see the job is completely done.
All right then.
I like the way you do business.
Room One over there.
I'm counting on you.
Now Ghostnet has returned.
Sorry that we're airing
this without any notice.
This has never been done in Korea.
Now we're starting a live broadcast.
Follow follow me.
- What's happening?
- I don't know. Just keep rolling.
Go now.
Run away now! Hurry.
Go in there.
Want to die, huh?
Go in there, damn it!
Gosh, it's even scarier here at night.
What was I thinking?
I'm back here
because I left my sword behind.
Oh my.
Fine. I will come back
when the sun rises tomorrow morning.
He's fighting with a ghost, isn't he?
It looks that way.
What a show.
Did they hire an actor for this?
He might win the Oscar.
How do they think this is a show?
Please don't say this is a show.
We're actually filming a ghost now.
This is a live broadcast,
so don't interrupt us.
We're scared to death now.
What's happening?
Mister, you're dead!
- Are you okay?
- Yes, are you okay?
It's not there!
Bong Pal, attack his side!
Hey.
She was trapped here
because of that jerk earlier.
Bong Pal, you did well today.
You knocked down an evil ghost
and sent her away to a good place.
Come on, don't be shy.
Let's go.
Why is this here?
Hey.
Like this time and the last time...
how did you know
the weakness of the ghost so well?
- You can see it?
- What if I can?
Do you want me to tell you how?
- Yes, please.
- I don't want to.
Hey, why do you keep
following me around?
- You don't happen to like me, do you?
- No way.
- Then you're trying to drain my energy?
Then why do you keep
following me around like a dog?
- I don't have any memories from my past.
- Memories?
Ah, you mentioned you
didn't have memories last time.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
I don't remember anything such as...
why I died, where my home was,
and who my parents were.
But for the first time after five years,
I got this glimpse of memories.
When you and I did...
- What about last time?
- You know last time...
I got my memories back then.
That's why I'm trying to do it again...
When and what did we do?
You know what it is.
- I still don't know what it is.
- Last time...
Gosh, just forget it.
Subtitles by DramaFever
I will help you.
If you help me study,
I will pay you 10,000.
Yoo Joo, an unknown idol,
was found dead in her condo.
- That's my ID.
- You wrote so many negative comments.
I can't do it! No!
No!
When he's in danger,
we will show up.
That's being a real man.
He gets paid one million
for exorcising a ghost.
How do you have this, Seo Yeon?
It's not me,
but a student named No Hyun Joo.
Of course, I'm happy to receive
a present after five years.
What's the deal with that monk?
He's always around you?
I like you 100 percent.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Gosh, where did I leave that sword?
I can't remember.
Envelopes for medicine?
Did someone take it and commit suicide?
- Who are you?
- He's a monk.
Ah.