This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by Dramafever
[Lets Fight Ghost]
So... did something pop up? You said
your memories would return if we kissed.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Anyway, since I did you a favor,
I need you to do me a favor too.
It's nothing difficult.
Just help me out like you did today.
I noticed earlier that
you're quite useful.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Yeah. Yes.
If you help me with the exorcisms, I'll
overlook the 10 million won you owe me.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Hey, where are you going? Hey!
Did she just run away?
What if her memories
returning was all a lie?
[She's such an attention whore.
Get lost.]
[Are you bragging right now?]
[Did you get an abortion
again? Murderer.]
[Episode 3]
I'm so freaking tired.
Sorry.
Hey, where are you going? Hey!
You're an idiot for
listening to a ghost.
It's not the first time a virgin
ghost played you like that.
I'm so angry.
Let's see here.
I totally forgot to buy groceries.
It's all because of that crazy ghost.
Seriously though, where
did Monk Myung Chul go?
She's really nowhere in sight.
Fine, I better not catch you.
You're still here.
Just where is my honey?
I know for a fact it's this school.
Honey! Honey! Honey, Honey! Honey!
Where are you, honey? Honey!
- Hi, Hyun Ji.
- Where have you been?
- Finding my honey.
- "My honey"?
Yes.
It's been 30 years and I finally
found the man of my dreams.
I'm only going to follow him now.
You changed guys again?
You said that other guy was the
man of your dreams last time.
It's the real deal this time.
He's so tall and handsome.
He was looking straight at
me with those dewy eyes of his.
I got butterflies in my stomach.
Plus, he's pretty broad-shouldered.
He's perfect to cling on to.
I see.
What's the matter with you?
Did something happen?
The thing is...
Really?
So, it wasn't a soft and squishy
blood sausage, but that guy's lips?
Yes.
Oh my gosh! I'm so jealous!
No, wait. So you kissed
that guy again, right?
Did you remember anything?
- No. Nothing!
- Nothing?
- Absolutely nothing?
- Yes!
I don't know what happened! Some
memories came back for sure last time.
How strange.
What should I do, Kyung Ja?
Whom are you looking for?
Were you looking for me?
Hey, it's been a day since we've seen
each other. Aren't you happy to see me?
I'm very happy to see you.
- Come on, you're scaring me.
- "Come on"?
You really don't know?
You're shameless, selfish,
and arrogant to boot.
Forget it. What would I
talk about with a ghost?
Just stick to him
like glue no matter what.
Who knows? Your memories
might come back again.
You said he's an elite
college student, right?
Then ask him to help you with
your SATs. Do everything you can.
I'm pretty sure he's got something.
Bong Pal, wait for me!
Bong Pal! Bong, Bong!
- How are you?
- Hello, Professor.
- What brings you here?
- Well... Professor.
About the dog you saved last time.
- Yes?
- May I take care of it?
Of course. That's perfect.
He hasn't met an owner yet.
Honestly, I saw him on the way here
and I can't stop thinking about him.
Ah, I see.
Can you come after class, then?
- Around three o'clock should be good.
- Yes, thank you.
It's a very happy day for him today.
I'm already looking forward to it.
Say goodbye to love.
You're back with me again.
Hey, have you decided
not to speak to me?
I will help you.
Answer me!
- Hand it over.
- Will you forgive me if I do?
- I said hand it over.
- No.
Hey, wait for me.
Why do you keep following me?
I said I'll help you
get rid of the ghosts.
Do you honestly believe
I'll trust a ghost's word again?
Why not? I'm very trustworthy.
You're lying about your memories.
I know exactly what you're up to!
- I'm not lying!
- What is it, then?
What about your memories?
Did they come back?
- No... they haven't.
- See?
I was told not to believe
the words of a virgin ghost.
My memories popped up last
time, but not this time.
That's why I did what I did. I'm not
being sneaky, so please believe me.
- You're going to believe me, right?
- Then what?
Your memories haven't returned,
so why are you agreeing to help me?
Well... I was wondering if you
can help me study for my SAT exam.
- SATs?
- Yes.
You have to be pretty
smart to attend this school.
Why would a ghost study for the SATs?
I don't remember, but I think I can't
cross over because I didn't take them.
I can't help but think that maybe I'll be
able to leave if I do well on my exams.
Please help me.
It's not hard to do.
If you help me study, I'll pay
back the 10 million won I owe you.
Two million won per exorcism!
What do you think? A great idea, right?
It's one million won per ghost.
Then, 800,000 won?
500,000 won per ghost.
Take it or leave it.
I'll take it!
500,000 won per ghost it is!
Wait for me!
- Chun Sang, aren't you going to class?
- No, I'm not going.
Class is not important right now.
This punk is kicking my butt.
You've been at this since last night.
Give it a rest.
Nothing good will come out of it if
you keep messing with Sadako. He's evil.
You said he emptied out
your account several days ago.
Yes, he did. He bled me dry.
You call yourself my friend, yet you
have no loyalty and refuse to help me.
Just go and get your scholarship.
This Sadako needs
a taste of his own medicine.
He talked crap about me on the live
broadcast and now he's bullying me here!
How dare he touch my pride!
You're so dead.
And he's the one who
uploaded that video!
Die, Sadako!
It used to be buy one get one
free. The promotion must be over.
What are you doing?
It's a toothbrush.
I know that, but why
are you putting it in here?
Because I need one
if we're going to be together.
Who said I'm going to
spend time with you?
- Put it back immediately.
- Why? We're a team now.
Some teams live together.
It's no big deal.
I don't live with ghosts, okay?
So you want me to go back and forth
slaying ghosts and studying?
It's more comfortable sticking
together, don't you think?
The truth is, I have no place to go.
Please! Please? Please?
Then including room and board...
it's 250,000 won per ghost.
250,000...
I'll never be able to pay
back the 10 million won!
- Forget it then.
- Okay, okay! Deal.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I'd like a mackerel, please.
- Here you go.
- Thank you. Have a good day.
Bong Pal, let's eat meat.
Meat! Meat! Meat!
Meat, my butt.
It's been a while since I ate meat.
We can use this to make some stew.
No.
- I said no.
- I want it.
No!
We're not eating meat!
- Let go.
- No.
I said let go!
Meat. Delicious meat.
I'm going to eat a lot of meat.
Are you happy? Because of you,
I'm overspending on living expenses!
You're going to eat it too.
Hey! Bong Pal!
Can you buy me that dress?
To celebrate working together.
No.
I know that dress will look really
good on me. Don't you think so?
No, I do not think so.
It won't look good on you at all.
No, look carefully.
What do you think?
It's pretty, isn't it?
Buy me this dress!
He's always negative like that.
Wait for me!
His eyesight is not that great.
You'll have to bring him in at
least once a week for the time being.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
Okay.
Once in the morning and evening...
Here, give this to him in
the morning and evening.
Okay.
It's time to say goodbye now.
Bye.
Goodness.
[Ju Hye Sung]
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Go ahead and hold him.
- Come here.
What do you think? Is he adorable?
What's wrong?
Why do girls like that
always flock to the director?
- She is disgustingly pretty.
- Hey!
One-sided loves are always sad.
Should we go grab
some drinks after work?
Really?
- It's your treat, right?
- Me?
[You have attacked Sadako.]
[You have been killed by Sadako.]
What the heck?
Chun Sang?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
- Lara is dead.
- Lara...
She died without even using her magic.
- Sadako, that bastard.
- I see.
It was fun, dumbass.
Dumb what?
Is your little sidekick helping you?
Let's be civil here.
You're crossing the line.
Look at you. You're just asking for it.
It's the same as your live broadcast.
Where are you?
Why? Are you going to come?
Come and find me.
Don't mess with me from now on.
You're either missing a finger
or a part of your brain.
Or is it both?
Famous singer Miz has
committed suicide in her apartment.
What's even more shocking is that
she left a video of it.
What the heck?
Seriously!
What is this?
Don't come near me!
Would it have killed
you to buy me that dress?
I bought you toiletries and meat.
Now you want a dress?
Do you take me for a fool?
It's not that. Look at this.
My uniform is all worn out
from wearing it for five years.
Then what about the ghosts that
have been dead for over 100 years, huh?
Haven't you seen clothes
of virgin ghosts up close?
It's really dirty and it stinks.
Ghosts shouldn't be
complaining about their clothes.
Can you even wear it
if I buy it for you?
Of course! You just have to burn it.
People usually burn
dead people's clothes.
- Just buy new clothes and burn them?
- Yes.
I don't have an endless supply of money.
- What are you doing?
- I'm looking at my stuff.
What's with that look on your face?
- Why do you look so pleased?
- I'm happy.
- About what? About that?
- Yes.
It's been five years since I've
received a present. Of course I'm happy.
Oh please.
I have no memories, so I can't even
eat food on the anniversary of my death.
It's my first gift ever since I died.
Ghosts can even brush their teeth?
Why? Are we not allowed to?
I'm a very hygienic ghost.
What's the matter with you?
You said
it's your first gift in five years.
Then it's been five years
since you've brushed your teeth.
Oh yeah, you're very hygienic.
It tastes better with a lot of meat.
Don't be stingy and put some more in.
I put in more than enough.
I'm doing all the work here.
Stop distracting me and be quiet.
It looks so good.
Bong Pal!
Where have you been?
I had to go find something.
- Why is that there?
- What?
That thing right there! I've been
looking all over for it today!
- Did you take it?
- Why would I take that?
- It was here since yesterday.
- Since yesterday?
I must be getting weak.
That smells delicious. Let's eat.
Sure. Please sit.
Gosh, what's the occasion?
I can't believe you made this.
- You made this for me, didn't you?
- Dig in.
Ah, you're a good boy!
That was good.
Oh, my stomach hurts.
That was tasty.
What about the meat?
I'm really sorry.
Is that monk always here?
Not always.
He's here about twice a month.
Oh my gosh!
What's up with this toothbrush?
That's my toothbrush!
Did you buy it for me to use?
Of all the colors, why did you pick pink?
That's mine! What is up with that monk?
I'll use it well.
No!
I am so angry!
I hope you fall flat on your
face and break your nose.
Goodness, did I break my arm?
Gosh, I ate too much.
Oh, my back.
Serves you right.
By the way, where do I sleep?
Why does he always sleep like that?
It's nice and soft.
How comfortable. How long has it
been since I've slept on a bed?
Hey, Bong Pal.
Why did you sleep out here
instead of your room?
It was hot.
If you were hot, why did
you hold me last night?
I did not!
By any chance...
Did you... did you
miss being in my arms?
Come on! Seriously!
People should definitely live together.
Where are you going without breakfast?
I have business to
take care of in Leechun.
Make sure you eat well. I'll see
you on your mother's memorial day.
- His mother's memorial day?
- And Bong Pal.
Don't go around exorcising ghosts.
And don't get close to virgin ghosts.
They're nothing but trouble.
They're monsters, got it?
Yes, I understand.
Don't just tell me
that you understand, huh?
All right.
I feel an energy in this place.
Do you see anything?
No, I don't see anything.
Take care of yourself.
I'm leaving.
- Goodbye.
- All right.
Does he think that all ghosts are evil?
There are so many nice ghosts
like myself out there.
I don't like him at all.
He's quick to pass judgment.
Bong Pal. When are we going to eat?
Do you always ask about food
the moment you wake up?
Hey. Let's redo our contract.
What? Why?
I said I'd provide
accommodation and food.
But seeing you eat,
I won't be able to afford this.
- So...
- So?
Let's change to 20 or 25 per exorcism.
Gosh.
How much can I possibly eat?
As you can see, this is what's left.
I had food that would last for a week.
How could you eat half of it in one day?
This is too much.
I didn't eat that much.
You ate a lot.
It's so petty to neg about food.
I can exorcise better when I'm fed well.
You haven't even started working yet.
What? If you don't like it,
we can forget the whole thing.
Gosh, how petty.
Do whatever you like!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Give me more.
Fine.
I'm so full now.
Where are you going?
- Why do you ask?
- So I can come with you.
I don't think so.
Even if we live together
let's not get involved in
each other's private lives, okay?
I will slap this Sadako, such a psycho!
I will slap him once or twice...
- I will end him, seriously.
- This is the place.
His address is in this dorm
for people studying for civil exams.
But is it okay to just come by like this?
According to the rumors,
he knows martial arts.
That's all bullshit, okay?
I will seriously slap him.
It's room 307... 307.
3 and wait.
Excuse me, I'm here.
Sadako, Black Star Angel is here.
Okay?
He's scared, huh?
Come on, seriously...
Get out! Get out!
He was notorious for writing
nasty comments on social media sites.
He's been sued a lot.
Also he was sued by the singer Miz.
- The idol singer who killed herself?
- Yes.
- Who are they?
- They're the ones who called the police.
They found him
when they came to fight him.
They came to have
a real fight from a game?
You go to Myungsung University, huh?
I see many students
from there these days.
The punk from last time
went to Myungsung too.
So you got his ID
and hacked his account, huh?
You got mad while chatting
with him and came here, huh?
Correct.
You were mad, so you killed him, huh?
- Correct.
- What?
No way! He was already dead
when we got there.
- That's the truth. Correct?
- Correct. We didn't do anything.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
We checked the CCTVs near his place.
Like they say,
they got there after he died.
Their identification
has been checked too.
- But you might want to see this.
- What's all this?
All the nasty comments
made against the late Miz.
They are so many.
They're only for this month.
Gosh.
Gosh, it's all curse words here.
Words can hurt more, you know.
Who would want to live
after hearing such horrible things?
What did you want me to see?
The screen names of those
who wrote nasty comments...
The one who wrote most is Sadako.
It's the screen name
of Yang Hee Soo, who died today.
The leader of the anti-fan group,
Kim Kyung Ho, wrote second most.
I just heard from the Gangsuh police
that he also died.
His fingers were all broken,
like Yang Hee Soo's.
The third person
who wrote the most is Jikdding.
And look at this screen name.
How do you say this?
Black star BJ 1004?
It is Black Star BJ Angel.
It's my screen name.
- You wrote a lot of nasty comments.
- No, it's just like I said earlier...
My account was hacked,
and Sadako wrote all that.
I didn't write them. I'm serious.
The famous idol
who killed herself a few days ago
filmed herself committing suicide.
It's shocking everybody.
The video is spreading
on the Internet and going viral.
It's still unknown who leaked it and how.
The police are having a hard time.
About Sadako's death...
it has nothing to do with Miz, does it?
Why did the detectives ask me
to call if something happens?
I don't have a good feeling about this.
- What are you doing?
- Chun Sang.
Look at this one here. This...
This is the site for Miz's anti-fans.
Sadako, who wrote nasty comments, died.
The site leader here has died too.
The news says his fingers were broken.
Is this about Miz's curse?
Be careful, whoever wrote nasty comments.
Isn't Jikdding in danger too?
No way. No way.
It can't be.
I liked Miz so much.
What am I going to do?
Will her ghost come to me?
It's ridiculous.
- Hey.
- Chul Sung, I need to go to my hometown.
What are you talking about?
Your hometown is Seoul.
That's what I thought,
but it turns out it's not.
I asked my mom.
It's all the way down in
Gyungsang Namdo, Jaechun.
- It's Jaechun.
- Jaechun is in Chungbook.
Why are you acting this way
when I'm scared to death?
- What is that?
Crazy bitch.
Do you still want to get
criticized after you're dead?
Did you have to follow me to school?
Why not? It's fun.
I don't go to school
to make it fun for you.
You don't have to worry about me.
Besides, I may never get to
become a college student.
- Don't you feel sorry for me?
- Only if you can shut up.
Don't talk to her. Do not.
You're all about talk.
What do you mean?
Why is the lecture so long?
I'm starving.
Can we go eat first?
Did you die of hunger or something?
Why are you always hungry?
Did I die of hunger?
Wait. It's that girl.
Oh my, you're so happy, huh?
Don't just look at her.
Go over and ask her to lunch.
What lunch? Let's go.
- Ouch! Hey!
- Bong Pal.
Hello.
Come on. Ask her to lunch.
Hi. You're done with class?
- Yes, I am.
- "Yes, I am"?
Gosh, what kind of man are you?
- All right then. I will go first.
- Wait, Senior.
There you go. You're doing well.
- It's just that...
- Hurry up and say it.
- About lunch...
- What about lunch?
I wanted to say enjoy lunch.
Oh, you do the same.
- See you later then.
- Sure.
Gosh, what was that about?
"I wanted to say enjoy lunch."
Can you ever date anyone like that?
- Hush.
- Don't repeat what I say.
- Do you want to die?
- I'm already dead.
Hey! Hey!
Professor Joo.
- Hi, Seo Yeon.
- How are you?
- How is the dog doing?
- Good.
He's doing well,
but he doesn't eat much.
Is that right?
It may be because
he's not used to where he is.
If you're worried,
bring him over to the clinic.
Thank you. When will be
a good time for you?
Well, any time in the afternoon
either today or tomorrow.
Great.
I will bring him over tomorrow then.
All right then. I will see you tomorrow.
You're not supposed to feed a cat here.
I've been wondering
who was feeding the cat every day.
We meet finally.
Hello, Professor Joo.
The building for animal research is here.
We're strict about wild animals.
We shouldn't feed
the wild animals like this.
I'm sorry. The cat looked so hungry.
Then feed the cat
at that corner next time.
Pardon?
The security guard comes by here often,
so you will get caught.
If you do that at the corner there,
no one will know.
- Not many people go there.
- Okay.
Wait.
By the way,
it looks like it just gave birth.
I saw kittens nearby too.
By the way, what's good for
a cat who just gave birth?
Well, they will like
shredded chicken breast or beef.
But I will have
to examine it to be sure...
Come on.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
It was vicious.
[Rest in Peace]
Why is this so confusing, seriously?
Here we go again.
It's all the will of Buddha.
Here we go.
I will start.
I'm sorry.
Buddhist prayer
is very modern these days.
Let me take this call. Excuse me.
What lousy timing, seriously.
Hello. Hold on a minute.
Hold on a minute, okay?
Park Ji Hoon,
34 Gyungwha Ro, Yang Joo Eup.
Yang Joo Gun, Gwangwon Do.
Hey, I'm asking you
because I can't be there.
It's near your place.
Go there and see what he's up to.
I can't get in touch with him.
He's Bong Pal's father.
All right then.
It's not good to have a crush
on someone for too long.
Go tell her how you feel.
What is it? Are you being shy?
- You want this big sister to help you?
- What big sister?
You not doing anything is helping me.
Bong Pal! Bong Pal!
- What is it?
- Mr. Bong Pal.
- I said I wasn't interested in the club.
- That's not it.
I wonder if you can
help Chun Sang at all.
God, Buddha,
and gods of heaven and earth.
Why is Kim In Rang taking so long?
It's just that...
You know the singer
Miz, right? She died
and Chun Sang wrote nasty
comments on the website.
No, there is this guy named Sadako.
Sadako hacked Chun Sang's account.
So... Chun Sang...
It's from Chun Sang.
Hello? I'm with Bong Pal now.
- Are you?
- Chun Sang, hello?
- Hello?
In Rang...
Hello?
Hello? In Rang...
Chun Sang!
We have to go now! Now!
We have to go now.
We have to go save him.
God and Buddha. Please save me.
Don't!
Stop doing this.
You killing people won't change anything.
All I wanted was to get complimented.
Why did they have to hate me so much?
Why did they hate me so much?
You're the one
who hates yourself the most!
Killing people won't change anything.
How dare you tell me what to do?
What could you possibly know?
Are you okay?
Yes.
You're the one
who hates yourself the most!
When you don't even like yourself,
who else would like you?
Chun Sang!
What do we do with him? Chun Sang!
I'm so tired.
Gosh, I can't walk any more.
I will go home first
and wait for you there.
It's my first time
being jealous of a ghost.
What was that? You said
you'd go home first.
- Why are you there?
- I don't know.
I'm too tired
to move to other places now.
Let me try again.
Gosh, you scared me.
I'm too tired
to move to other places now.
Let me try again.
Gosh, you scared me.
What was that? You said
you'd go home first.
I have no idea.
Other ghosts seem to do it just fine.
Why do I keep messing up?
My uniform is all worn out
from wearing it for five years.
Even the skirt is ripped.
- Good work today.
- I did a good job, didn't I?
Of course I did.
You did a good job, Hyun Ji.
I can't say anything to you.
Can we have meat today?
I couldn't eat it last time.
Fine.
What do I expect from a cheapskate?
- Sure, let's have meat today.
- Seriously?
I will go get some, so go home first.
You meant it, right? Hurray!
I'm hungry, so hurry up, okay?
Hurry up.
After she asked me to hurry back
because she was hungry...
Bong Pal.
Are you okay, Chun Sang?
Chun Sang. Chun Sang.
- Am I still alive?
- Yes, you are.
You're still alive
and your fingers are still there too.
You're alive. You have everything.
You're alive and you're good.
[Byeolnim Animal Clinic]
Let's go.
Good work, Doctor.
- Good work, Doctor.
- Oh my.
I didn't know what time it was.
- What happened to your hand?
- I got scratched by a cat.
I bet it happened
when you tried to feed it.
Thank you for your hard work today.
- We will go now.
- Sure.
- See you tomorrow.
- Good night.
- You too.
Get home safely.
Na Bi, where are you?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Lets Fight Ghost]
How dare they take off without paying us?
It will take us
only two days to get there.
Are you being bothered by ghosts?
We will take care of it.
- Did someone die here?
- He was a bad guy in his fifties.
All of a sudden, he sold his clinic
and came here.
He finally accepted the offer
to become a professor.
You said you'd tutor me.
When are we going to study?
No chance you will enter Buddhahood.
I didn't see anything. I'm serious.
- What are you doing?
- I'm just going to taste it.
It's very rare to see a drunk ghost.
- Hong Young Hee?
- Who told you to touch my stuff?
You're a ghost,
so stop acting like a human.