This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
I'm doing all sorts of things.
Am I doing this right?
Bong Pal.
How do I look?
- Huh?
- How do I look? Is it okay?
Well... the dress is pretty.
It's pretty.
- Let's go.
- To where?
To work.
- What?
- It's time to pay your dues.
What? Why are we working
this late at night?
This is a new dress! You expect
me to fight in my new dress?
[Let's Fight Ghost]
[Episode 4]
Yes, sir! Yes, I'll go ahead
and text my account number to you.
Have a good day!
I should send it to those seniors.
What the heck? What's going on?
Yes.
Right now?
Yes, it's possible. Yes.
- Let's go. We got work to do.
- Again?
- I can't. I am way too tired.
- No, they want us to come immediately.
Don't you think this is too much?
I'm so tired that I hit my head on the
door because I couldn't go through it.
- Let's take it easy today, okay?
- No.
I have to feed you and help you study
tomorrow. Don't you remember our deal?
Still, this is wrong!
You're working me like a slave
because of this one dress you bought me.
And you said you're going to tutor me.
When are we going to start studying?
Okay, okay.
Let's study after we're done, okay?
- No, I refuse to go.
- Where are you going? Let's go.
- I'm tired.
- Hurry up.
It's completely trashed in here.
When are we going to clean all this up?
The housing agency is going
to have a fit if they find out.
You're lucky you're still alive
and breathing. You should be grateful.
I am. I will be forever grateful
and... it's time to pray.
Dear God, Buddha, Allah,
thank you so much...
No!
No, I should be thanking
Bong Pal instead!
He may be a jerk, but he
came when I needed him most.
He's a real man.
How do you think
he knew I was in danger?
Well, the thing is...
Hold on.
- Oh, it's Bong Pal.
- He texted you?
Is he asking if I'm okay or something?
He's cool. He's a pretty decent guy.
- No, it's not that.
- What did he say? Let me see.
Please deposit the money into my account.
What is he talking about? What account?
Bong Pal says he charges
one million won per exorcism.
One million...
- What? One million won?
- Yes.
Wait, let me get this straight.
So... Bong....
Mmm... so, Bong Pal really
didn't come to save me.
- Correct.
- He's horrible.
- He's calculating.
- Do you have one million won?
No, I do not.
What are we going to do then?
He's not going to let this slide.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't
know. Just ignore him! I don't know.
Ignore him? I...
Is President Cha Chun Sang inside?
I'm from the housing agency.
I know you're in there!
You can't keep ignoring our phone
calls! It's only more trouble for you!
President! President!
President! President! President!
Oh goodness.
How long did I sleep?
I was so freaking tired.
Bong Pal. Bong Pal.
Bong Pal.
Sorry!
Hey, I didn't see anything.
I swear it!
Will you please make some
noise when you roam around?
I'm a ghost.
How am I supposed to do that?
From now on you are not allowed
to burst in whenever you like.
Fine.
You know, you kind of
look different today.
Your clothes look a bit tidy too.
Did you do something
to your hair as well?
What are you talking about?
Ah, you have the same class with her
today, don't you? I'm right, aren't I?
What are you talking about?
I'm going to go. Don't follow me.
Why? So you can have nice
and cozy class time with that girl?
No. You said you're tired, so rest up.
And do not go in this room or touch
anything without my permission.
See you later.
Is there anything else
I'm forbidden to do?
See you later.
Bong Pal, let's go to school.
What the heck?
You just said goodbye to me.
When? I never said that.
Aren't you tired of following me?
It's boring alone at home.
And I can't stay home when
I'm wearing a pretty dress like this.
Fine, go ahead. Geez.
[Eviction Notice]
I'm going to send you a seperate
maintence bill. Just know that.
Understood?
Yes.
Chun Sang! Chun Sang! Chun Sang!
Hold it in! Hold it in! Hold it in!
Seriously, what are we going to do now?
How am I supposed to know?
- What?
- Ghost!
What is it? What is it? What is it?
Why are you in such a good mood?
Just because. Don't I look like
a college student in this dress?
Oh please.
- Oh, it's Kyung Ja.
- Who?
Bong Pal, there's
someone I need to talk to.
Hey, who are you meeting--
I swear.
Kyung Ja.
- Hyun Ji!
- What brings you here?
I told you last time that
my honey is at this school.
Ah.
Hey, your clothes...
- How do I look?
- What do you think?
You look totally pretty.
You were pretty with your uniform on,
but you look even prettier in this dress.
You're up there in the ranks of
Jeon Ji Hyun and Song Hye Gyo.
Kyung Ja!
You would look perfect with
a pair of high heels on.
But who burned this dress for you?
By any chance,
was it that blood sausage?
I'm right, aren't I?
What the heck? He kissed you last time
and now he burned this dress for you?
I think he likes you.
- That doesn't make sense.
- Oh my, why not?
I'm a ghost and I have
feelings for a human.
There's no rule that a human
can't have feelings for a ghost.
It's not true. I had to
beg him to burn this dress for me.
And Bong Pal likes someone else.
You don't know because you haven't been
in a relationship with a guy before.
My instincts tell me that
he likes you 100 percent.
No, there's no way.
- Who did you see?
- Just a ghost that I know.
My instincts tell me that
he likes you 100 percent.
What's up?
Why are you smiling like that?
It's nothing.
Bong Pal.
Hello.
- You're here early.
- Yes.
- Let's prepare for class.
- Okay.
I knew it.
How pretty.
I'll take that.
- It's fine. Thanks.
- No, I'll do it.
Oh my, it's Superman.
Wow, it's written all over
your face that you like her.
What's the point when you
can't even talk to her properly?
- Ah, I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
There's no need to be embarrassed.
You guys are here early.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming out
this early to help me.
- Are those materials for today's class?
- Yes.
Did you get hurt? Those scratches...
Ah, it's no big deal.
- That looks painful.
- Goodness.
I didn't bring the materials for class.
- Bong Pal.
- Yeah?
It seemed like
that professor avoided me earlier.
You're being ridiculous.
Did I see wrong?
Why aren't these seniors
responding to my text?
Who? Ah, you mean that comedic duo?
They looked penniless to me.
There's no way they're paying you.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Seriously, these guys!
What is this?
What do you think it is?
They ran away.
How can you say that right now?
If I don't get paid, then
you have no means to pay off your debt.
What?
How dare they run away with our money!
Hey, call them again. Hurry!
Seriously.
Facility maintenance fee is 892,000 won.
You have until
the 23rd to pay the office.
- What is it?
- Maintenence bill of 892,000 won.
[Park Bong Pal]
- What does he want?
- Exorcism fee of one million won.
- He's really horrible.
- Hey, don't!
892,000 won... how are we going
to secure all this money? Huh?
I'm having a tough time as it is just
with the camera monthly payments.
It's not like I can call my parents.
- You really have nothing?
- I really have nothing.
Ask someone who has money.
I've spent all of mine.
Then call someone and borrow it.
Are you just going to sit and do nothing?
All right! Okay!
I'm the big brother here!
- Hello?
- In Rang, I'm completely broke.
I'm in a dire situation
and need to borrow money.
- I'm all you got?
- You're all I got.
You're the only close
friend that I have.
Hyun Joo!
Hey, Seo Yeon.
I didn't see you in class today.
I just had some
business to take care of.
Why do you ask?
We recieved some materials to take
home from class today. Just a moment.
- Hello, Professor.
- Hello.
Nabi.
Nabi, where are you?
Hyun Joo!
[Joo Hye Sung]
This belongs to Professor Joo.
What are you doing?
Are you going to eat lunch?
Do you only ever think about eating?
- What is this?
- What do you think it is?
You want me to tutor you.
I need to know what your skill
level is so I can plan accordingly.
Okay, you have one hour.
Right now?
I have a bit of a headache today.
Have you no intention of crossing over?
You said you need to take
the SAT in order to cross over.
Yeah, but not now.
You have one hour.
- Ready... begin.
- Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Number four?
Number two!
Just skip it if you don't know.
I'm going to solve all of it!
Hey... what's the minimum SAT
score for you to cross over?
I would need a good
enough score to come here
in order for me to cross over to
the afterlife without any problems.
Looks like you don't have
a chance of crossing over this year.
Huh?
- 32 percent?
- Yes, 32 percent.
At this rate, you won't even get
near the gates to the afterlife.
How do you expect to take
the SAT with these scores?
It's my first exam in five years!
Five years or 10 years.
This exam is not that hard.
A junior high kid would
do better than you.
So what? Are you bragging about
how smart you are right now?
I'm done!
You're the one who failed. How
dare you take your anger out on me.
It's not like that! I didn't sleep well
yesterday, so I'm not feeling that good.
- Then take it again.
- What?
Take what again? I'm very busy, okay?
Professor.
Oh, Miss Seo Yeon.
What brings you here?
I have something to give you.
Here. I think this belongs to you.
Ah, you're right.
Thank you, but how do you have this?
It wasn't me.
A student in our class picked it up.
- Who?
- Her name is No Hyun Joo.
Ah, No Hyun Joo.
The student who missed class today?
- Yes.
- I see.
Anyway, this is great.
I was looking for it. Thank you.
Not at all. You must be
busy, so I'll be on my way.
Sure. By the way, is the dog okay?
Yes, thanks to you.
- Call me anytime if you need anything.
- Yes, thank you.
Okay, take care.
Take it easy, you quack.
How can you make a living when
you do it so painfully like this?
I'm better than you, punk.
Give me your hand.
Ouch, be gentle!
Goodness, your pulse is so weak.
I can barely feel it.
- You're hopeless.
- Your skills are hopeless, punk.
Come on.
I'm surprised you're still
alive after all those encounters.
Does Bong Pal know that
you're in this state because of him?
What for? It's not nice to talk about.
Don't you dare talk
about this to Bong Pal.
And stop saying I'm in bad
condition. I'm totally fine.
Outwardly you look fine,
but you're a complete mess inside.
Make sure you take it
easy for the time being.
Have you been to that place
where Bong Pal's father resides?
- I hear he left a long time ago.
- Goodness.
It would be nice if he told me
where he's going ahead of time.
That man is chasing that punk, isn't he?
The evil spirit that killed his wife.
It seems that way.
Gosh, it's been over 10 years.
There wasn't anything special in
his room except for that picture.
Gosh, why was he in such a hurry?
He even forgot to send
the letter he wrote to his son.
And I hear someone else came
looking for him besides me.
Who?
The owner couldn't get
a good look at his face.
She said he was just
a young and handsome fellow.
- A young and handsome fellow?
- Yes.
Ouch! Hey!
- I don't think I can accept this.
- What?
Why not? I bought this two months ago
and there's still
two years left of the AS period.
It looks like you forced it on here.
The AS is difficult if you
personally install it like this.
It's better to buy
a new one than fix it.
No, I don't think so.
We never touched it...
It was you, wasn't it?
You're the one who
messed around with it.
Didn't I tell you not to touch it and
that we won't get the AS if it breaks?
I didn't do it.
You know how I bought this, don't you?
I do. I know you bought it
with your room and board money.
Right. I still have 10 months of
payments left and I lied to my family.
- You did.
- And?
Well, I didn't... I didn't do it.
It was these guys. They did it.
Hey, what's wrong? No! No! No!
No! No, don't do it...
He scares the crap out of
me whenever he's like that.
Damn it. Hey, In Rang!
In Rang! Shoo! Shoo!
- Lunch is on me.
- Go away!
In Rang, don't be angry anymore.
Should we order a bottle of soju?
Don't even think about it!
Soju, my butt.
We're broke
and we have no money for soju.
Take out everything you have.
You wanted to buy soju with this?
There's barely enough there to pay for
our meals and you wanted to buy soju?
Where are we going to sleep?
- What about you?
- I'm going home.
- Then what about me?
- You can come with me.
Your grandmother hates me.
No, she despises me.
In Rang, why are you in such a hurry?
I'm in a hurry because we
have to find a place to sleep.
Are you abandoning me?
Wait for me!
I have to read all of this?
You have to read all of this
and more. This is just the beginning.
There's so much you have to study for.
Okay, what do you want to do first?
Math first.
Not this one.
How about we start with Korean first?
- Let's start with math first.
- Why ask then?
I can hear you. Sit up straight.
Okay.
Let's see here.
My stomach is killing me all of a sudden.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Ghosts don't need to go to the bathroom.
Ah, my head hurts so much. Hold on.
Stop stalling.
You're the one who wanted to study.
- Let's do it properly.
- Okay.
This is easy enough.
Go ahead and solve it.
So, if the limit is A to B for
this equation, then GX equals B.
Then GX...
Are you sleeping?
She didn't solve a single problem.
Hey, Kim Hyun Ji. Hey. Whoa.
Let's just pick a random place.
How far are we going to walk?
This place is willing to give us
50 percent off. We have no choice!
We're almost there.
It's over there! Over there, over there!
That's the place.
Here you go.
Goodness, why do you
have so much baggage?
I'll keep it in storage
without charging extra.
- Just rest comfortably.
- Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Sure, let me take that.
Oh my goodness.
- This too.
- This as well?
Sure.
- Please rest up.
- Thank you.
Wow.
The owner is friendly
and the place is very nice.
But why is there no one here?
That's good for us.
It's all ours.
- Let's go break a sweat!
- Sounds good.
Sounds good, sounds good, sounds good.
I'm melting. I'm melting.
Hot, hot, it's very hot.
Chun Sang, how long
are we going to stay here?
Well, it's about tomorrow, isn't it?
Think about it tomorrow.
Okay.
- Let's sleep.
- Let's do that.
Let's think about it tomorrow.
I wasn't expecting a text from anybody.
Seniors, if this is how you handle
things, we may have a problem.
- It's from Bong Pal.
- Of course it's from him.
What did he say?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- He is asking for money.
- Wow, he won't give up, will he?
He's consistent, seriously.
- What should we do?
- Give it to me.
- I don't know. Let's sleep.
- I mean...
Then I will sleep too.
I don't know either.
In Rang...
[Please close the door tightly]
In Rang!
What is it? What?
Is this locked?
It's now open.
What was that about?
What is it?
- Are you up?
- Yes.
By the way, why was I sleeping here?
What do you mean?
You fell asleep there.
Did I do that?
Gosh, why didn't you wake me up?
I tried, but you wouldn't wake up.
Then you should've moved
me to the sofa at least.
How could you let
a woman sleep like this?
You're very heavy.
I won't throw my back out
because of you.
Gosh.
Gosh! He's such a jerk!
Wait, it's open.
Bong Pal told me not to go in...
Wow, why is there so much stuff in here?
Hong Myung Hee?
Who could that be?
Wow, these shoes may fit me perfectly.
- Hey, what are you doing in here?
- Bong Pal.
Whose shoes are these?
Can you burn them for me?
I told you not to come in here.
Who said you could
touch the stuff in here?
- Well, I was just...
- You!
You're a ghost.
So stop acting like a human.
Why is he all mad like that?
What did I do that was so wrong?
Oh my goodness...
Here. Are you okay?
Gosh, I keep seeing ghosts.
Is that because I'm cursed this year?
Chun Sang, take a look at this.
There was a reason
why that place was cheap.
This man died in there a month ago.
That place was known
to be haunted.
- You took me to such a place, huh?
- I didn't know that.
Anyway, they performed a very
expensive exorcism there and all.
Gosh, even if you perform an exorcism,
ghosts will still come.
They wasted the money.
They should've just given it to us.
I agree.
Let's find
an empty classroom to sleep in.
- Are you that sleepy?
- Yes.
Your call is being redirected...
Gosh, the phone is still switched off?
Seriously, guys...
- What is it?
- It's Bong Pal.
Seniors!
Senior In Rang!
It's not that we're trying
not to pay you.
- It may take a little bit of time.
- For how long?
- Two months.
- Two days.
That's right, two days.
How are we supposed to come up
with money like that in two days?
We can pay you back in two days.
- How?
- It's a secret.
How?
I'm saying it's a secret.
Gosh, she might not have had lunch yet.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Bong Pal must be having lunch by now.
Should I go over to the school?
You are a ghost.
So stop acting like a human.
I already know that I'm a ghost.
[Bul Ga Ma Sauna]
Did we really have to dress up like this?
If we're going to do it,
we should do it right.
Let's go!
[Temporarily closed]
Are you having a hard time
because of a ghost?
Even if there was an exorcism,
it wasn't helpful?
We will... take care of your problem.
Ah, it's Bong Pal.
Why didn't you turn the light on?
Why are you sitting in the dark?
So what if it's dark?
I'm just a ghost, not a human.
- Aren't you hungry?
- So what?
Will I starve to death
when I'm only a ghost?
Why does this pork belly look so good?
Should I make bulgogi with this meat?
It will be so good...
Wow, I'm full.
I will do the dishes tomorrow.
I knew it.
Take a look at this. Gosh.
The sale volume is definitely low
compared to his previous clinic.
Wasn't his clinic in the Gangnam area?
That's correct.
We were very busy then.
It's like a paradise here.
Then why did he start
this clinic all of a sudden?
It isn't doing well in this area.
I agree. He sold the clinic
all of a sudden and came here.
He suddenly accepted the offer
to become a professor.
Either way, he's so cool,
so I like it here.
Come on. Hurry up.
- Good work, ladies.
- Are you going somewhere, sir?
Yes, I need to go.
Wrap things up and go home.
- We will. Thank you.
- See you tomorrow.
I will go first.
Hello? Now?
Yum, I enjoyed the meal.
Yeah, I'm full.
- I'm off.
- Are you?
- To where?
- To meet my seniors.
Your seniors?
- Ah, they will pay you?
- Yes.
- Shall I come with you?
- Whatever.
Shall we have something to drink
first before we begin?
Here.
Bong Pal, drink.
No thanks.
You're not going to pay me in cash.
If I destroy the ghost there...
You will take 1.5 million
from the reward money.
It's like a win-win situation.
Three million!
Stay seated first. Have a seat.
Come with me quickly. Come with me.
What are you doing?
I just wanted to taste it.
- I've been curious about the taste.
- Put it down, will you?
You can't drink alcohol
when you're not old enough.
Fine.
Hey!
We were promised
four million for the job.
If we give him three, we lose money.
Plus, the expenses
to fix the room and camera.
Then what are you going to tell
the owner of the sauna, huh?
Will you catch the ghost yourself?
Do you want me to die?
Do you want me to get ripped to pieces?
That's what I was saying...
So three?
Hey.
Wow, woo-hoo!
So let's make a deal of three million.
Come on.
Let's go with 3.5 million.
- We'll suffer a big loss.
- I agree.
Done.
What exactly is the job?
So the job is...
[Sauna]
You said you'd work tomorrow.
Today we're doing a spot inspection only.
We want to be prepared
for tomorrow and all...
Then is he the exorcist?
He's not old enough
and just look at the way he's dressed.
Are you a student?
He's not the exorcist.
He's our cute office assistant.
He wanted to see
how our jobs are done.
So we brought him with us today.
- Didn't we, Pal?
- Sure.
Then look around and give me a call.
- Please take care of it.
- We will, sir.
Trust us and let us handle it.
Should we have him
fitted for a tuxedo too?
It doesn't matter how he dresses.
It's good as long as he
can catch ghosts, right?
I agree.
- He's not in there?
- No, he isn't.
Where did she go?
- I'm here.
- Me too.
Never mind.
Did someone die in here?
He was a man in his fifties.
According to the owner,
he was a regular.
He might have been a lowlife scumbag.
You know, those who try to
grab women and such.
They try to touch... you know, a pervert.
What's going on?
Hey, where are you going?
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
There is a ghost.
That bastard...
- He's strong.
- Bong Pal!
Why is he circling around?
His chest!
Attack his chest!
What took you so long?
Is it over?
Good work.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Cheer up, baby. Cheer up, baby.
Cheer up a bit.
Bong Pal, watch this, okay?
Cheer up, baby. Cheer up a bit.
It's rare to see a drunken ghost.
Hey, Kim Hyun Ji.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
See? I'm perfectly fine.
My Bong Pal...
Why are you so ugly, huh?
You're so ugly.
What do you mean you're not drunk?
You can't even stand straight.
What? Who can't? Me?
No way. I can walk just fine like this.
Watch me, okay? Watch me.
I can walk from here to there.
I walk just fine, right?
I can go places even better now.
Watch me. See?
Ouch. It hurts.
I knew it.
What are you doing? Get up.
Bong Pal, I'm hurt.
- Get up so we can go home.
- I'm not going.
I'm not going home.
Fine then. Stay here all night.
Fine, you bastard.
I will live here from now on.
I will spend the night here.
Hey, you...
You can't do this to me.
Come here so I can hit you.
You ducked?
Don't you dare move.
Why are you doing this?
You sure are doing a lot of things.
What kind of ghost is an obnoxious drunk?
Why not?
A ghost shouldn't even
be an obnoxious drunk?
A ghost shouldn't want to
put on pretty clothes either?
A ghost shouldn't do things like a human?
When I'm only a ghost.
When I'm only a ghost...
Don't say that anymore.
Did I die because I wanted to?
I don't know why I died.
I don't even know how I died.
I don't like being a ghost.
I don't want to be a ghost.
I didn't become one because I wanted to.
Ghost can have their feelings hurt, okay?
You're a bastard.
I don't even know what I'm doing.
- Bong Pal!
- Hey.
Hey!
Oh my, you're so pretty.
Gosh, why is a ghost so heavy?
What? How can I be heavy?
I'm so light. I must be light.
I'm as light as a feather.
Let's go now.
No Hyun Joo.
Who's there?
Professor Joo.
You're getting home late.
What brings you here?
I have something to ask.
What is it?
Where did you find this?
Wow, this neighborhood is very quiet.
Not many people are here.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Lets Fight Ghost]
The best way to have Bong Pal join
our club is blood sausage and pig feet.
I have no idea what you're saying.
- Do you want to do it with me?
- I'd love to.
In front of her,
you even blush and smile.
You know the thumping noise...
I finally walked up there.
- I'm running away.
- From whom?
- Master Bong Pal?
- He's very well known in the field.
Bong Pal.
Where do your parents live?
Have you talked to your father recently?
Why do you ask that?
Where has he been
to get mud on his shoes?
- Hyun Ji.
- Yes?