Snapchat: BioskopKeren.org
[Let's Fight Ghost]
I have no idea what I'm doing.
- Pal Bong! Hey!- Hey, hey!
Oh my, you're so pretty.
Gosh, why is a ghost so heavy?
What? How am I heavy? I'm light!
I must be light!I'm as light as a feather!
Let's go!
Make sure you hide real good.
I can see your hair.
[Let's Fight Ghost]
[Episode 5]
I can't believe I'm making hangover soupfor a ghost. What the heck am I doing?
Kim Hyun Ji, wake up.
Hey, Kim Hyun Ji.
- Why?- It's time to eat. Come out.
Oh, my head. Bong Pal, my head hurts.
What's wrong with me?I feel nauseous too.
You feel nauseous too? Nice going.
You were no joke yesterday.Can ghosts get drunk?
I guess so.
How did we get in last night?
You don't even rememberlast night, do you?
I thought my back would giveout because I carried you home.
- You carried me home?- Of course. Who else would do that?
Sit down and eat.
It's bean sprout soup!
- Did you make this hangover soup for me?- You wish.
I just had some left over,so I decided to make some. Why?
Delicious.
Thank you for the meal.
- What is it?- Heart!
What's this?
Heart!
Junior Bong Pal, our loveis going to arrive soon.
What's up with these seniors?
[3,500,000 won has been deposited.]
Please take your savings book.
[3,500,000 won fromdepositer Kim In Rang]
[Total amount: 134,500,000 won]134,500,000 won?
Wait a minute.How much is 100 million won?
Wow.
Wow, you're very rich.
Why have you been acting poor whenyou've been loaded all this time?
Let's use that money to buysomething good to eat, huh?
- That's not what I'm using it for.- Then where are you going to spend it?
Aren't you makingmoney to make a living?
Ah, are you going tobuy a house or a car?
No.
What are you going to use it for?
Are you thinking of buyingsomething extravagant?
It's my money and I'm going to use ithowever I want. Mind your own business.
It must be nice to seeghosts and make tons of money.
It's not all that great.
Why not? Because of your gift,you make a lot of money
and you have a pretty ghostlike me as your sidekick.
Gosh, you're being ridiculousthis morning. That's enough, okay?
I'm late.
That's my bus.
Hey, wait for me!
- Where did she go?- Bong Pal, over here!
It's nice to have a ghost around.
Look at that.
Can you scoot over?
Where am I supposed to sit?
- I'm sorry, but it's taken.- Excuse me?
What are you talking about? It's empty.
I'm sorry.
- 48.- 48.
- 49.- 49.
50--
- 50!- 50!
We just have to do thisseveral more times, right?
I know.
But we needJunior Bong Pal to make it happen.
I know. That's why weneed to recruit him.
How? He won't evenregister for our club.
- Who am I?- Choi Chun Sang.
Am I just Choi Chun Sang?
I'm a charming magicianwho can make everyone fall for me.
- Perhaps Gate? Bill Gates?- Bill Gates!
Bill Gates!
These are the final scores of yourlast reports. Come and take them.
Park Bong Pal,you're pretty smart. Good job.
I gave you over a week to complete thisassignment. What have you all been doing?
Copy and paste, grammatical errors,typos. Such poor and meaningless reports!
How is it that Park Bong Pal isthe only one who got an A plus?
This is Park Bong Pal's report. Takea look at it and get some inspiration.
This was a group project
yet Bong Pal did it on his ownand still did better than all of you.
You have until next week.
Any group that gets below a Cwill have to submit it again, got it?
- Got it?- Yes.
Good, I'll see you next week.
He's such a jerk.
There's some strange rumorsgoing around about Bong Pal.
What is it?
Something strange alwayshappens when you're with him.
I even heard that the kidwho fought against him died.
- For real?- That's scary.
I didn't like the look inhis eyes from the beginning.
Anyway, it's bad luckif you hang out with him.
There won't be any reasonfor us to hang out with him.
He's an outsider anyway.
Bong Pal.
- Bong Pal.- Yeah?
- Do you like being alone?- Yes.
It's not boring?You always eat alone too.
No, I like it.
I mean, it's fun hanging outand eating together with friends.
We would only talk about girlsand play video games. You call that fun?
It is fun! Talking aboutmenial things like that is fun.
That's how you build friendships andget to enjoy the perks of campus life.
Isn't that college life?
It's all a waste of time.I'd rather read another book.
Still, it wouldn't hurt to havea friend help you out when you need it.
It's fine. I can take care of myself.
The director is late today.
- He's never been late before.- I know.
He didn't return afterhe went out yesterday.
- Do you think he stayed out all night?- With a woman?
- No!- There's no way!
I'm sure he didn't.
- Oh my, you're here!- Hello, Director.
I'm sorry for being late.
I'll check the appoinment chartafter I come back from class.
- Please prepare everything until then.- Okay, we will.
Where has he beento get mud on his shoes?
- He probably went to the shelter again.- You think so?
Junior Bong Pal.
- Hi.- Do you have time to spare?
Why?
[Myungsung University: New Club]
[President: Choi Chun SangVice President: Kim In Rang]
Sometimes... a day will comethat changes everything.
We are in the center of that right now.
We will be in the center of it all.
How? With the state of theart multi-communication system!
Speed, accuracy,and a thorough AS screen.
A 24-hour...
exorcism system.
All of this...
has been gathered in one place.
The name is... Blood Sausage Soup.
Blood Sausage Soup!
Blood sausage soup? Is he settingup a restaurant? What is that?
I have no clue.
Hold on, hold on. Where are you going?
To class.
You're just going to go after listeningto this impressive presentation?
- I have no idea what you're saying.- What do you mean?
What do you mean?I'm saying let's work together!
If we bring work to you likelast time at the sauna
you come and save the day.
- And you get your end of the cut, right?- And we get...
That's not how we would put it exactly.
I mean, you're right...
but we would also be doingthis for the sake of world peace.
Peace.
So, it's kind of like a service fee.
- In what way?- So...
So we could provideyou with transportation.
Or like some sort of physical exam.
The truth of it is, you'll run intodifficulties if you do this alone
and we would be willing totake care of all that for you.
We would also collect all the exorcismfees that you still need to receive.
Please think about it.
You're too busy studyingand getting rid of ghosts!
There's so much stuff youneed to be concerned with.
If we hunt down work for you...
Hold on, hold on! You would takethe car we provide for you...
Right, good job. You wouldgo to the ghost and just...
Okay! Okay!
You would go and catch theghost and take our car back home.
How comfortable is that?
Hey, that's not a bad idea.What do you think?
Ah! We got some work for youfrom the community gym.
And we collected severaloverdue fees as well.
The community gym.How much are they going to pay?
- Three bank notes.- Three million won?
Deal.
Okay, then please go aheadand sign this contract.
I'm not interested in joining the club.
Still, this would mean that you haveagreed to work together as a team...
I'm going to go.
He's leaving.
We did it!
- We did it!- Blood Sausage Soup!
Bong Pal.
Hello, Senior.
You're going to class, right?Let's go together.
Sure, let's go.
What is it?
It's nothing.
By the way, have you decided who you'regoing to work with on the final exam?
It's a group project.
No.
Do you want to do it with me?
My Bong Pal can do it all by himself!
- Yes, I'd love to.- Great.
Let's go.
What's so great about her?
What?
I just thought of a good idea.
Bait that will makeBong Pal join our club.
- Hello.- Hello.
The weather is verynice today, isn't it?
Let's go somewhere!
I bet you want to havefun on a day like this.
Shall I let you all go early today?
Yes!
I'll think about it ifyou pay attention in class.
Let's check attendance first.
- Kim Ho Chan.- Here.
- Na Jin Soo.- Here.
Okay.
No Yeon Joo.
Student No Yeon Joo.
No Yeon Joo is absent again today.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat together today?
Since you're helping me with class, I'llbuy something good to eat. Is that okay?
Yes, it's fine with me.What about you?
It's fine with me too.
- Shall we go?- Yes.
Welcome.
Please have a seat.
- Oh, wait!- What is it?
Well, the thing is...
There's some dust here.
Thanks.
What the heck?
This dish is very good.
It's nothing.
He's gained a good amount of weight.
It seems that way.He must be eating well now.
Yes. What do you think?Isn't he adorable?
Yes, he's adorable.
Bong Pal, where do you live?
I live near the school.
What a relief. I felt bad for making youcome out early to prepare for my class.
You must be living by yourselfif you live near the school.
Yes.
Then where do your parents live?
Ah, they live somewhere else.
They must live far away.Do you see them often?
Not really...
Meet and call them often.
Have you talked to your father recently?
Why do you ask that?
It's nothing.
By the way, are the preparationsfor your final exams going well?
Yes, we're going to start soon.
Midterms didn't end too long ago.
it's too bad that you have toprepare for finals so soon.
- Dig in for now.- Thank you.
Hyun Ji, why are yousitting here like this?
It's nothing.
I couldn't find my honey.
Just where in the world is hehiding on this small campus?
Just thinking about it makes me angry!
Right, right, right?It's worth being angry over, right?
Absolutely!How could he take the chair out?
I know!
He was so sweet to me on the bus.
What a jerk!
- Huh?- He's always scolding and nagging me.
But he's always smiling and laughinglike an idiot in front of that girl.
Are you talking aboutthat blood sausage?
Yes. He's probably laughingand eating with that girl right now.
I see.
Who am I talking to?
It must be nice not having me around.
Watch where you're going.
Where have you been?I've been looking all over for you.
Hey.
Are you still hungover?You've been out of it since this morning.
I'm fine.
Why?
What do you mean why?It's time to go home. Let's go.
Was it good?
Yeah, it was good.
I'm sure it was sinceyou ate with that girl.
You know, it seems likeSeo Yeon likes that professor.
I don't blame her. He's good-lookingand he has a nice personality.
He's also very popular,unlike someone I know.
Cut it out.
It's Seo Yeon.
Not!
Do you enjoy making fun of me?
Yes, it's the best thing in the world!
- There's something on your shoe.- Huh? Where?
What a nice bow!
You are so immature! That was not funny!
Yes it was!
Hello, Miss Im Seo Yeon.
Who are you?
We are close friends of Park Bong Pal.
You know him, don't you?Economic major Park Bong Pal.
Yes.
We would like to talkto you for a moment.
Just for a moment.
Our club had a difficult startand it's on the verge of disappearing.
We have nowhere to go.What should we do, Miss Seo Yeon?
What can I do to help?
It's a very tiny favor.
[Club Registration Form]
Goodbye.
Ah, that's cold!
You're such a good sleeper.
You have no passionfor studying whatsoever.
I am passionate,but I fall asleep whenever I study.
Get your act together.
Passion. Fighting. Okay?
Okay.
So, how many did you solve?
You didn't even solve 10 problems.
I couldn't because it's hard.
Look.
In the case when you're looking for "r"
say you have two infinite sets ofnumbers and all conditions are met
and there's a and b...
- Hey.- Yes?
Oh... one more time.
In the case when you're looking for "r"
say you have two infinite sets ofnumbers and all conditions are met
and there's a and b...
[Star Animal Clinic]
You scared me.
I told you not to pop inwhenever you want.
I totally forgot.
Knock, knock.
Why did you come in?
Just because. I can'tfall asleep and I'm bored.
You sleep when you should be studying.Of course you can't fall asleep.
You were so cute when you were little.What happened to you?
You know, your mom is very pretty.
Those heels...
Whom do these belong to?Can you burn them for me?
Ah... they were your mom's?
Yes.
It's time for you to leave now.I'm going to bed.
Okay.
Bong Pal.
I'm sorry. I didn't knowthey belonged to your mom.
Good night.
- Hyun Ji.- Yes?
Turn off the lights.
Okay.
Dad, it's so loud!We moved here for nothing!
I swear!
Come out! Do you knowwhat time it is right now?
I've had enough!What the heck are you doing?
You're not the only ones who livehere! Come out! I said come out!
Shut your kids up!
It looks like Bong Pal lives here.It's close to the school.
- Did you tell Bong Pal we're coming?- I did. He'll come down.
But is this even considered a car? Huh?
I'm impressed that this thing evenmade it here. Where did you get it?
What do you mean?I had to go through a lot to get it.
I begged my cousinwho left for the army to get it.
How long has he driven this car?
500,000 miles?
What is this?Some kind of an airplane?
I knew it.
This is whythe engine was having trouble.
Just be grateful that we have this.
If this was what you were going to borrow
why did you say thatwe could provide transportation?
We should provide anythingfor him to work with us.
You've seen how picky he is.
Plus, we could sleepin there for a while too.
Sleep? In there?
- In here?- Are you crazy?
It's hot in here.
This car doesn't have air conditioning?
By the way, where are we going?
Weren't we going tothe community gym?
We got an urgent offer,so we had to switch.
Now we're going toan apartment building in Eunsung.
Every night, they hear a kid cry and...
you know, thumping noisesas if someone is running around.
So the tenants downstairs went up there.
They went thereand found the unit was empty.
It's been empty for one year.
A guy was offeredcheaper rent and moved in.
He had no idea thata ghost was living up there.
The rent of the whole building isgoing down because of the ghost.
The chairman ofthe building community is worried.
So she promised to payus a whopping five million.
Hey, that's awesome!
Here we are. That's the place.
Bong Pal, you stay here.
We will go meet with the chairmanand discuss the contract in more detail.
Which unit is it?I will go take a look around first.
You're such a professional, aren't you?
- What was the unit number?- Unit 617 in building B.
We will be right back.
Wow, there is a playground.
Bong Pal, can we pleasego there to play a bit?
Come on. We're here to work.
Gosh, she's all about eating and playing.
Bong Pal, let's play here a bit.
Bong Pal, let's ride this one.Sit there, will you?
What are you, a little kid?
- Plus, I don't like this.- You don't like so many things.
Here you are again.
Excuse me, I told you notto come here again.
Do you understand me?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy...
- Ma'am, please take her away now.- I'm sorry.
Hee Jun, let's go, okay?
Why did you come here again?
What if you get in trouble again?
Let's go.
Ma'am, please take her away.
The residents here willmake a fuss about this.
They're already unhappy the market valueis going down because of the ghost story.
- Do not show up here ever again.- I understand.
Hurry up now.
- Let's go.- Hurry and leave.
Hee Jun, let's go.
[Virgin Bodhisattva]
What? What do you want me to write?
I want you to write an amuletto keep ghosts away.
Give me a strong one.
Why do you go aroundcarrying the sword then, huh?
if you need to come here for an amulet...
Gosh, I've heard about you, but youreally are useless, aren't you?
Hey.
Mee Sook, change that name.
What's up with "Virgin Bodhisattva," huh?
You've been married three times.
How about Bodhisattvawho makes her husbands die fast?
- Or Granny Bodhisattva?- You seriously!
By the way, about the motel caseyou asked In Heok about...
Ah, Gam Po Motel?Everything was handled well.
I heard what happened.
You almost fainted and ranwhen you saw the ghost.
I didn't exactly run, but I wasgoing to return at another time.
Word travels fast, gosh.
But the one who handled itinstead of In Heok
is very well known to bequite good in this field.
Who is he?
He's called Master Bong Pal or whatever.
I don't know where he's from.
- He's quite young, I hear.- Master Bong Pal?
Bong Pal? Park Bong Pal?
It sounds right. Why? Do you know him?
Park Bong Pal, that punk...
Write me one now.
[I hate you]
[Dad]
Did I scare you?
I scared you good, didn't I?
- Are you mad?- Let's not kid around at work.
Gosh, you're no fun.
I scared you good, didn't I?
Stop playing and cross over, okay?
People can't sleep because of you.
- It hurts.- Are you okay?
- No, stretch. You don't want to bend it.- Stretch.
- You've stretched too much.- I'm sorry.
You saw how quickly I reacted, right?
This is how I am.
- Someone else would hurt their chin.- It's already back to normal, so stop.
Look straight ahead and drive.
All right then, Bong Pal.
We have to exorcise tomorrow.
So get plenty of rest at home.
I almost forgot, Bong Pal.
What do you think this is?
- What is it?- It's our second present for you.
This is our third present for you.
[Member application for Ghostnet]
Im Seo Yeon? That girl?
Why did you join?You said you weren't interested.
You joined because of her, didn't you?
Gosh, Park Bong Pal.
We finally got it.
Now we can move backinto the club room.
Hey, where are you going?
Hello.
To the apartment building in Eunsung.
Why now?We're supposed to go tomorrow.
You want to get back at that kid?
Make sure you hide real good.
I can see your hair.
I can see your hair...
What is this about?
That kid isn't playing.
What do you mean?
[Abused and Killedby Stepfather in Eunsung]
- He's running away.- From whom?
Whom is he running away from?
- The one who killed him.- Who is that?
His stepfather.
I've found you.
- You punk.- I'm sorry.
- Come with me, you little punk.- I'm sorry, Dad.
Come on, you little punk.
Seriously? Don't wehave to call the police?
He's a little kid.
What are you doing again? Leave!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, my baby.
Dad, I was wrong.
Don't do that. Dad, I was wrong.
Are you okay?
You! You killed my son?
You! You want to die?
Kill me!
Mom!
Bong Pal!
There you are, my baby.
Here you are, my sick baby...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I couldn't protect you.
I'm sorry, my baby.
Mommy is very sorry.
My baby...
I'm so sorrythat I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry, my baby.
My baby...
My poor baby...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, my baby.
He must have been waiting for his mom.
Gosh, he must have been so scared.
I'm sorry, Bong Pal.
My son. Mommy is very sorry.
Bong Pal, I'm very sorry.
Mommy, don't go.Mommy, don't leave.
Mommy. Mommy!
I'm sorry, my baby.
Bong Pal.
I'm sorry.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Bong Pal.
Bong Pal!
What are you doing here?
Have a seat.
I told you to stop exorcising.
I don't exorcise.
I know everything.
Master Bong Pal.That's what you're called, huh?
If you do that, how am I supposed toface your late mother when I die?
Why bring up my mother all of a sudden?
Gosh.
Gosh, why did I do that back then, huh?
If I hadn't made that mistake...
Don't worry. What you worryabout won't happen.
And I am not blaming you.
I'm grateful that you saved me.
- Get up and drink at home.- No, I won't, punk.
I have other places to goother than your place.
You're as stubborn as your father.
I'll go.
Gosh, it has to hurt.
I told you not to come here.You're a ghost!
- I'm not a ghost.- I said go.
- Go. I said go.- I'm not a ghost.
Ghosts are over there.
I'm telling you I'm not a ghost.
Mommy.
I'm sorry.
Ghosts... go away.
Snapchat: dramalovetv
[Let’s Fight Ghost]
- What's going on with me?- Why are you staring at me?
Something is wrong with me.
Do ghosts' hearts pound?
Let's go have our membership training.
- We have blood sausage!- We have blood sausage!
I will play Cupid instead.
You know one of your studentsnamed No Hyun Joo?
It's been a long time.
He closed down his booming business.
Why did he come here?
It's so immature of you to do that!
I did that to get back at you.
It's been known for that for a while.
A ghost from the water appears there.