This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
[Let's Fight Ghost]
Goodness, where am I?
I went down the wrong path.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Just who in the world would drag
a corpse here and bury it?
I know. He's a sly bastard.
[MYUNGSUNG UNIVERSITY]
[NO HYUN JOO]
[Let's Fight Ghost]
[Episode 6]
- Who said you can come into my room?
- Huh?
I just... I didn't mean to. I'm sorry.
- Why are you looking at me like that?
- What?
Just because.
Why the suit all of a sudden?
Are you going somewhere?
- Yes.
- Is it somewhere nice? I want to go too!
It won't be any fun
if you follow me. Don't come.
Liar. I know you're
trying to leave me behind.
I'm going to follow you.
Today is the anniversary
of Hong Myung Hee's death.
May she rest in peace...
Today is the anniversary
of his mother's death.
Why don't you eat before you go?
That's okay.
You still haven't heard
from your father yet, right?
Why would he call me
when he hasn't called you?
Goodness, why do I feel so strange?
I'm going to go.
- Sure, I'll see you at home.
- Okay.
Wow, the weather is so hot today.
It must be summer now. Right?
Bong Pal, do you want
to hear something funny?
What do you think is the
loneliest monster in the world?
- What are you doing?
- Come on, guess! What is it?
I don't know.
Solo-mon.
Okay then, who's higher in rank
than a "chujang"? (CHIEF)
- Chujangnim?
- It's gochujang (RED CHILI PASTE)!
A person higher than that
is a "sun gochujang".
- Are you having fun?
- Aren't you?
What kind of sickness does
a sheep hate the most?
Sheep hemorrhoids! ("YANG" MEANS SHEEP,
"CHIJIL" MEANS HEMORRHOIDS)
Hemorrhoids!
You smiled! See? I told you it's funny.
- It wasn't funny at all.
- You know you liked it. You smiled.
- What is this then?
- Don't. Just don't.
- It's funny! Guess one more, okay?
- No!
What is this?
Ah, it's new club members
who just joined our club.
Two people, at that.
What is this?
I wonder what this is?
Here's the maintenance fee.
Take it and give us our key.
You're late.
Ghostnet has already been disbanded.
You should've come sooner.
The voting is over as well.
So when you say it's disbanded... you're
saying our club has been terminated...
Chun Sang, what is he talking about?
I knew this would happen,
so I prepared this.
A new club request form.
The manager has even signed off on it.
It's been signed. Chun Sang,
when did you prepare all this?
The club name is "Blood Sausage Soup."
Blood sausage soup?
[BLOOD SAUSAGE SOUP]
Even if it's taken away from us,
would that happen again?
God... thank you.
It's still here! It's our table!
It's ours, Chun Sang.
Chun Sang!
Chun Sang, this isn't a dream, right?
If it is, I don't want to wake up.
Does it hurt?
- Yes, it hurts. I think it's real.
- I thought so.
- You were scared, weren't you?
- No, I wasn't.
This is the perfect day to have a picnic.
Bong Pal, should we pack some
kimbap and go on a picnic?
Picnic, my butt.
I have finals to study for
and you need to study for your exams.
You only think about
having fun all the time.
You have to take a break on a day
like this in order to study better.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Someone might think you've
been studying for a very long time.
It's barely been a week
since you started.
You're so unromantic.
Hey.
Why are you blushing?
What do you mean?
Are you okay?
What's wrong with her now?
Seriously, what's the matter with me?
It's still pounding.
Hyun Ji!
Kyung Ja, you're still here?
You haven't found that man yet?
Yes. I think I'm going to
have to set up shop here
until I find my honey.
What's with the look on your face?
Just because.
Kyung Ja, I think there's
something wrong with me.
In what way?
Do ghosts' hearts pound?
Well, the feelings of a ghost are
the same as when they're alive.
Yes, that can happen.
But why do you ask?
I don't know.
I don't know when it started, but my
heart races whenever I see Bong Pal.
And I suddenly get nervous.
You get nervous? And?
It hurts here.
There's something wrong
with me, isn't there?
From what I see, I think you like him.
What?
- I have feelings for Bong Pal?
- Yes.
You said your heart races whenever
you see him. That means you like him.
There's no way! Absolutely not!
Oh yeah?
If that's not the case...
By any chance, do you have
some sort of heart disease?
It must be nice to go on a retreat.
How great would it be to dunk your
feet in a river on a day like this?
- That sounds awesome.
- With a slice of cold watermelon.
And in the evening,
we'd sit around a bonfire...
and drink beer! Just pop
a cold can of beer and...
No. No... let's go on an retreat too!
We have new members and our club back.
It'll be a celebration
and grand opening of our new club!
A grand opening?
That's a good idea! I love it!
But do you think Bong Pal will go?
What do you think?
Put both hands together
and raise them straight to the ceiling.
Raise your left arm
and look up at the ceiling.
Stretch your leg back as you
stretch the left arm in front of you.
Slowly lower your leg.
Why did we come here?
We have to take Bong Pal to the retreat.
Our secret weapon is over there.
Excuse me, Miss Im Seo Yeon.
Hello.
We were admitted to the university
in 2010 and took four years off
due to financial hardship
and serving our country. Not once...
Not once did we go on a retreat in our
time here at Myungsung University.
We really want to go.
We want to go and experience this awesome
moment while we're still in college.
But with retreats, two is better
than one, three is better than two
and four is better than three.
It's not easy for us to ask
this heavy favor from you.
You want me to go on
a retreat with you guys, right?
Yes, that's correct.
Why did Kyung Ja say that?
That doesn't make sense!
Why would I like him?
Sorry!
Why did Kyung Ja say that?
That doesn't make sense!
Why would I like him?
Sorry!
Thank you.
Maybe Kyung Ja was right.
I told you to be aware
of your surroundings.
Oh... I was preoccupied, so...
Why don't you be
preoccupied with studying?
Also, where do you keep roaming around?
Why?
Were you bored without me in class?
I don't think so.
It was actually really nice to be able
to focus in class without you there.
No, no. There's no way
I would like a guy like him.
Bong Pal.
What do you think, Bong Pal?
A retreat?
It's not just any retreat.
It's membership training.
It will be the grand opening
of the Blood Sausage Soup club
and welcome orientation
for the new members.
A variety, spectacular,
action, suspense retreat!
Oh, a retreat?
It sounds like fun! Let's go!
I'm not really feeling it.
You don't have to prepare anything.
The car, food, location...
and the various activities
are all in one full package.
Let's go! You don't have to pay!
It's for free!
Huh?
Well, if you're not feeling it...
Im Seo Yeon mentioned
she's pretty exhausted from her studies.
She agreed to come along.
Well, if you're not feeling it, then...
Maybe we shouldn't go.
It doesn't sound like fun.
Ah, I hear it might rain tomorrow.
So, are you not going to go?
I guess it's just us three then.
Yeah, it's just us three.
Hey, let's not go.
Well... I'll think about going.
- Let's make it four of us.
- Okay.
Detective, the identity of the
dead body has been confirmed.
No Hyun Joo.
She's a Myungsung University student.
- Yes.
- The cause of death?
She died of asphyxiation.
It's most likely she was strangled
by someone's hands.
Her neck was broken.
How is that possible with human hands?
Well... I'm not sure.
Did you check the time of death?
Yes, the time of death was 24 hours ago.
She was supposed to go to class
that day, but she skipped it.
There's no trace of
her whereabouts after that.
She missed class?
What class was it?
It's a humanities class.
A class called Animal Society
taught by Professor Joo Hye Sung.
It seems like she was
very interested in animals.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Seo Yeon.
- Hello, Professor.
What brings you here?
Hi, Byul! Have you been well?
Is Byul sick? He looks healthy.
No. I was hoping you would
watch him tomorrow.
- Are you going somewhere?
- Yes, there's a club retreat.
A retreat? How exciting.
What club is it?
I'm not sure what club it is...
Ah, Bong Pal is in the club too.
Bong Pal must be going as well.
Yes.
- So...
- Yes?
Here.
Thank you for everything
and for Byul as well.
Oh, it's fine.
You shouldn't have.
Wow, the present is small, though.
Pardon?
I'm kidding. Can I open it?
Yes.
It's a fountain pen.
I was just about to buy one.
This is perfect. Thank you.
You're welcome.
- It's just you and me, Byul.
- Say hi to the professor.
Oh, he's gotten big.
When I asked, you didn't want to go
on a picnic with me because of class.
- What's up with that?
- That class wasn't that urgent.
I need to study for
my college entrance exams, too!
Let's just study at home.
I'm really going to study hard!
You said we needed to take
a break once in a while.
Once you start having fun,
you can't stop.
Let's stay home, okay?
Then you stay home and study.
I never said I was taking you.
What?
Hey!
I told you not to follow me.
Why did you come?
Well, you'll be gone. What am
I going to do at home by myself?
I won't be able to take care of
you because there's too many people.
- I know that.
- Bong Pal.
Senior!
It's just an retreat.
Why is she all dressed up?
It's not like you're
going to a fashion show.
It's that car again?
How are we all going to fit in there?
The sky is open to us!
I have you!
It's kind of tight back there, isn't it?
Sorry, we have so much stuff.
We only have an hour
to go, so hang in there.
We have to stay like this for an hour?
- Darn it!
- Be patient. We're almost there.
You know, you two look like a couple.
Bong Pal has a sky blue shirt on
and so does Seo Yeon. Sky blue!
It's not sky blue!
Bong Pal's shirt is sea blue!
Watch how you're driving!
Gosh, I'm so tired.
- This place is very nice.
- How did they rent this?
Wow, whose vacation home is this?
This vacation home belongs to
my one and only junior, my best friend.
They call him "young master" at home.
This is In Rang's vacation home.
Young master? Really?
It's unexpected, right?
It is surprising.
Our In Rang is that kind of person.
He's very wealthy,
but he doesn't show it.
He's such a humble man.
Just your average Joe.
Is that a compliment?
Of course.
This vacation home is really nice.
What's wrong with him?
Don't worry about him.
He gets speechless around women.
He's very bashful and shy.
Okay then, let's take our
belongings and enter the premises!
What are you doing? Hurry up
and open the door! This is heavy!
I think my grandma changed the passcode.
What?
- You didn't know she changed it?
- I didn't ask.
My grandma will kill you if she
finds out that I came here with you.
Why does your grandma
always want to kill me?
Just do something.
My grandma's birthday!
This is In Rang's vacation home for sure.
Gosh, how strange.
- Please be careful next time.
- Thank you.
- Thanks. It's really my vacation home!
- It's definitely his vacation home!
Did your grandma throw a fit?
She asked if "he" was
there and I said no.
- Who is "he"?
- You.
Good job!
- Please come in.
- Okay.
- Gosh, this is heavy!
- Come in.
- This is nice.
- Oh my!
- This house is really nice.
- Stay still.
I don't want to.
I wonder what's in this house.
I'm going to bring
the rest of our stuff inside.
That's great. What's gotten into you?
Let's go together.
I'll help you.
Okay, let's go.
Wait a minute.
Let's take this bag upstairs.
- Okay?
- Huh? Why?
Hold on, let me rest on this for a bit.
Come on, let's take the bags upstairs.
This place is so nice.
Hurry up, will you?
Are you okay?
Are you an angel?
What happened? What's going on?
In Rang, wake up!
Are you okay? You scared me.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Chun Sang, I saw an angel.
Don't be ridiculous.
You almost became an angel.
No, I really saw an angel.
She was right in front of me.
You poor boy. You almost
crossed over to the other side.
Let me see if there's a hole in the
back of your head. There's no hole.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay!
Still, you never know, so let's rest
for a bit. Come here and get on my back.
Come here. Okay, let's go.
I'm glad to see he's all right.
But did he see me?
Miss... Miss Angel.
Angel.
Ang... Angel.
Are you okay?
Miss Angel, I'm fine! I'm fine!
Please don't worry, I'm fine.
I completely forgot to bring the ramen.
Ramen is the best to eat
after drinking, right?
Bong Pal.
There's a little grocery store down
the street. Can you go and buy some?
Okay.
And if it's boring to go by yourself,
then Seo Yeon can go with you.
Yeah, I'll go with you.
I have to buy some stuff anyway.
Okay, sure.
I'll just take care of this first.
Sure, sure, sure.
Let me get my wallet from the car.
I forgot to bring it with me.
Okay.
What's for dinner tonight?
Oh, meat! Nice!
Bong Pal.
Take your time buying the ramen.
No, you can make the ramen.
Take your sweet time, okay?
Take advantage of this romantic moment!
I am the messenger of love.
The bridge of love.
Okay.
Bong Pal, where are you going?
Are you going to buy ramen?
- What the heck?
- Love is in the air.
Oh, ramen.
I am the bridge of love!
What the hell?
Bong Pal.
You don't need to go get ramen.
We have some inside.
He did that to tease you,
so don't go.
Bong Pal.
Don't go.
We already have ramen.
Seo Yeon has something to get anyway.
She can go alone.
Tell her to go alone.
- Bong Pal, let's go.
- Sure.
Stay quiet.
I will be right back.
This one too, please.
- Did you get everything?
- Yes.
Oh my, you look strong
and this one is pretty.
Are you two dating?
No, we're not.
- We go to school together.
- That's how it always starts.
Let's see... there are four ice creams.
Oh, wait a second.
One more, please.
Who is it for?
There are only four of us.
- I just really like ice cream.
- I see.
They were begging,
so I just came along.
But I'm glad that I came.
I've only been going back and forth
between home and school.
Me too.
Isn't it surprising that
you and I came to
this retreat together?
We weren't close until we started
to take Professor Joo's class.
You're right.
What's with your answer?
You don't think we didn't
become close, do you?
That's not true.
I'm kidding.
Gosh, it's hot.
Wait.
Thanks.
Let's go.
How did you end up
falling and rolling down?
Did you fall on the stairs
or trip on your own?
Can you just go get me some water?
You just want me to get you water?
Sure.
- We're back.
- Hey.
Oh my, are you hurt?
My head...
What is he saying?
Why did you get back so early?
Why didn't you take your time?
Here it is.
- Are you okay?
- Of course I am.
By the way, what's up with him?
He just fell and rolled down the stairs.
In Rang, here's ice cream.
Sorry.
There are two left.
I will eat these two then.
This one is mine.
You ate yours on the way here.
I like ice cream.
I got it. You're such a pig.
I will let you have it.
Hey, Kim Hyun Ji.
- Here.
- I won't eat it.
Are you sure? I will eat it then.
Since when do you care about me?
See? This is boring here, isn't it?
It's not boring at all.
Wow, this sausage looks awesome.
We will all have some drinks.
Wow, alcohol.
- In Rang, come over now.
- Sure.
Now let's celebrate
our first retreat.
Let's toast to that.
I say "blood sausage" and you say "soup."
- To Blood Sausage Soup!
If you're not going to drink it,
why not give it to me?
You shouldn't drink.
Wow... meat!
In Rang, hurry up. Hurry!
Here we have meat.
Have some meat.
Now we will go get the meat.
Bong Pal, the meat looks good.
Can I have some meat?
Meat. Meat.
In Rang, there wasn't any beef
when you were buying pork?
Oh my, thanks.
I'm in the athletic department.
I should eat beef.
- Just eat what we have here.
- Okay.
I understand.
Bong Pal, the sausage
is good too. Try some.
I will.
Wow, it's beautiful to see
how Seo Yeon takes care of Bong Pal.
Give that to me.
Why don't you two start dating?
- Oh my.
- Funny.
- What are you talking about?
- Why not? You two are single.
Two lonely single people could go out.
- Go out! Go out!
True. You could do that.
- They can't do that.
- That's enough.
We've been hearing
such a thing all day today.
It may be because
we're dressed alike today.
I agree.
It's weird that the smoke
only goes in her direction.
- It's because she's pretty.
- You're right. She's pretty.
- Now the smoke is coming toward me.
- No, it isn't.
- Senior, let's switch seats.
- It's okay.
- Wow, it's beautiful.
- Wow.
Oh, you...
- To Blood Sausage Soup!
- To blood Sausage Soup!
- All right then.
- Thank you.
Excuse me,
are you Professor Joo Hye Sung?
We should've called first.
We were in a hurry,
so please excuse us.
No, it's okay.
How can I help you?
You know one of your students
named No Hyun Joo, right?
No Hyun Joo is the one majoring in dance.
Correct. When was
the last time you saw her?
She's been absent for the last two weeks.
That's probably when I saw her last...
- Did something happen?
- She was found dead.
What? Found dead?
Were there any students
close to her in your class?
Or anyone who fought
for her attention?
Well, I don't know anything about it.
I took over the class
in the middle of the semester.
I don't have any personal
information on the students.
We were told that.
Thank you for your time.
Wait.
If you think of anything
please call this number.
I will.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Oh my, it's hot.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Just go in there!
- Wait.
- Shoot.
There's a rock between my toes.
We've come all the way here
and you're not going to jump in?
- You're no fun.
- I'm okay here.
- It feels cool.
- I'm okay too.
There is a whale!
What are they doing?
Get under the water!
Where did you go? Save me!
One, two, three, cheese.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
Hello there.
Let's take a group photo
to remember this place.
I'd like that.
- I'm okay.
- What do you mean?
Come this way. Come over here.
One, two, three.
Now I will take one for you.
In Rang, what are you doing?
- You said you'd take a photo of us.
- You're slow, aren't you?
There.
Get closer to each other.
One, two, three.
What are you doing? Get closer.
Such a Seoulite.
One, two, three.
- No, no. Your hair was a bit messy...
- Your hair was...
Look here. Bong Pal,
what are you doing? One, two, three.
[RESTRICTED AREA]
You go there.
Senior, what's the matter?
You have no appetite?
About Professor Joo Hye Sung...
- You have his information, don't you?
- Yes.
Hold on.
By the way, what about
that professor all of a sudden?
Nothing. I'm just curious.
Joo Hye Sung is 30 years old.
He's the youngest professor
in the Department of Veterinary Medicine.
He was the owner of
a well-known animal clinic in Gangnam.
And he recently started
a small clinic near the university.
And he was offered a very good position
before he took the job at Myungsung.
- Like what?
- He was offered a teaching job at
a very prestigious university overseas.
So he was getting ready to leave.
But he changed his plans
at the last minute.
He came to teach at Myungsung instead.
Myungsung is one of the good schools.
Why did he turn down
such a good position?
He closed down his booming business.
Why did he come here?
It's close to the university.
Or he didn't want to live abroad.
[HONG MYUNG HEE]
- In Rang.
- Yes?
Can you turn up the volume?
It's too high.
It's good now. It's perfect.
I know how busy you are
with school and job hunting.
But you managed to come.
For that, I want to thank you,
new members.
This trip is celebrating the foundation
of Blood Sausage Soup
and we welcome you to join in
this variety show for our retreat.
By the way, why is the name of
the club Blood Sausage Soup?
Well, that's because...
When you're tired and things are tough
a bowl of blood sausage soup
can warm you up.
Like the bowls at the restaurants
sizzling 24-7 all year
we thought we could be something
warm for those who struggle.
And that restaurant was where
we all decided to work together.
He may become a scam artist one day.
Now, before we start,
let's sing our national anthem or not.
Let's play games first!
- Let's go!
- Hurray!
Drink up!
Until you drink up, I will dance.
Look at my shoulder.
I'm pouring you more.
- One.
- Two.
- Four.
- Five.
- Seven.
- Eight.
- 10.
- 11.
- 12.
- 14.
- 16.
- 17.
18.
19, 20, 21.
22, 23, 24.
- 25, 26, 27.
- 28, 29, 30.
- Drink up!
I say blood sausage and you say soup.
- Blood Sausage.
- Soup.
You're doing it well.
It's been a long time.
Oh my, it's me again.
It's me again.
If you have any questions,
ask me now.
I will answer all your questions.
In Rang, go ahead.
- Me?
- Yes.
I want to ask...
Never mind. Time's up.
- Bong Pal, how about you?
- I don't really have any.
Forget you then.
Im Seo Yeon, if you have
any questions, ask me now.
- I will answer all your questions.
- Well...
Well, what is your last name?
It's Choi. Choi from Ohkyung.
It's Choi of
the 35th generation from Ohkyung.
It's C-H-O-I in English.
Choi is my last name.
35th generation?
Now we will do it again, okay?
- Now, it's your turn, Im Seo Yeon.
- Im Seo Yeon.
Well, is there someone
you like these days, Im Seo Yeon?
Yes, there is.
There is someone she likes.
I'm dying to know who it is.
Any questions?
Let me see.
Oh my, that's an angel.
- She's an angel.
- An angel is here.
- There is an angel here.
- Go to sleep.
You're really hurt here, huh?
Fine then.
I will ask for In Rang now.
Is the one you like here with us?
No, he isn't.
He isn't?
Well, then let's turn this again.
Well, do you like him a lot?
Yes.
I think so.
Can I spin the bottle now?
It's you, Bong Pal.
It's your turn.
Bong Pal, is there someone you like?
He drank because he was sad.
If you don't want to answer,
you should drink.
Let me go to the bathroom.
Hey, you.
How can you leave
in the middle of the game?
I will also go out to get some air.
How can you leave us here?
What am I supposed
to do without you two?
You're being too loud.
You need to quiet down.
I will play this game by myself then.
From what I see, I think you like him.
Yes, I think so.
What's wrong with her?
What do I do?
Seo Yeon!
Get her! Get her.
Get her.
- Are you okay?
- What happened?
- I don't know.
It felt like someone was pulling
me down from the water.
- I might have tripped then.
- Oh my.
Oh my, you're bleeding here.
We don't have any medicine.
I will go get some.
I told you not to play around, didn't I?
- Seo Yeon is hurt because of you.
- Because of me?
I didn't do that.
You were the only one next to her.
Who else would have done that?
- I already said it wasn't me.
- I don't believe you.
You've been after her since yesterday.
Why are you messing with her?
What's wrong with messing with her?
I did that to get back at you.
Are you acting this way
because I didn't take care of you?
This is why I told you to stay home.
This is so immature!
I'm sorry for acting immature.
I shouldn't have followed you here.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- Yes?
- Is there a pharmacy around here?
- Why? Is someone hurt?
She was in the water and got scratched.
You guys have a lot of
energy in the morning.
Is it because you're young?
Did you guys play
behind the villa by any chance?
- Yes.
- Why did you play there?
There is a sign telling people
not to play in the water there.
- You didn't see it?
- No, we didn't.
It's notorious there.
Even my grandmother almost
died there when she was little.
A ghost from the water appears there.
- So many people have died there.
- That's right.
Don't ever play in the water there.
Kiddo!
Was it because of me?
- I didn't do it.
- You were the only one next to her.
- Who else would have done it?
- I already said it wasn't me.
Bong Pal!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Fight Ghost]
How come we don't have any work?
You said you'd launch our business.
Should we go meet with our investor?
This is our business plan.
Blood Sausage Soup?
Exorcist hotline, how can we help you?
You're in 12th place? Focus, will you?
What's wrong with your grades?
- What is it?
- I thought she looked at me.
By the way, do ghosts get sick too?
Of course. Of course.
What now?
He said he was the son of the dead guy.
It's a hassle that
they came to ask questions.
We now have a problem.
I have a little bit of my memory back.
- What did you remember?
- Bong Pal, where are you?
Sorry, but I won't be able to come today.