This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
[Let's Fight Ghost]
A ghost from the water appears there.
Because of me? I didn't do that.
You were the only one next to her.
Who else would have done that?
I already said it wasn't me.
Bong Pal!
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hyun Ji.
Kim Hyun Ji.
Are you okay?
Bong Pal.
I was so scared!
Do you know how scared I was?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay now.
12th place?
12th place? What kind
of ranking is that?
You went down from third to 12th place.
Don't you know how big
of a difference that is?
What's wrong with you lately?
Get your act together!
I work my butt off to get
you private lessons! What is this?
[Let's Fight Ghost]
[Episode 7]
Hyun Ji, I'm heading out.
Hyun Ji.
[LANGUAGE ACADEMY]
Hyun Ji, wake up! Hyun Ji! Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji.
- Bong Pal.
- What's wrong? Are you sick?
I just don't feel so good.
I wonder if it's because
you fell in the water.
Is it that bad?
I'm okay. I think I'll be
fine once I get some sleep.
- Go to my room and sleep.
- No, I'm good.
Hello?
Bong Pal, where are you?
Senior, I'm sorry.
I don't think I can go out today.
Can we talk about
the final project tomorrow?
Why? Is there something going on?
No, I just don't feel so great.
Oh? You're not too sick, are you?
No.
Okay, get some rest
and let's meet up tomorrow.
Yes, I'll see you tomorrow.
Hyun Ji, go sleep in my room.
What the heck am I supposed
to do when a ghost gets sick?
It's not like I can
take her to the hospital.
Hyun Ji, eat some of this porridge.
You didn't even eat breakfast.
She must be really sick.
- It's coming!
- Bong Pal.
Miss Seo Yeon and...
It's the angel!
It's the angel.
Let's put it right in here.
How long are you going to
play that? Stop it already.
This is amazing.
- Where did you get that?
- This? I borrowed it from a friend...
Where did you get a friend?
You don't have friends.
I do... not have friends.
You shouldn't poke at
someone's pain like that.
Give it to me.
This... I mean, this...
Where did you get this? You probably
wasted all your allowance on it.
It's actually not as
expensive as it looks.
It's not...
Whether this is expensive
or not is not important!
Are you out of your mind?
Just what is wrong with you? Huh?
Look! Look! Look, look, look!
The retreat fees, gas money... there's so
many bills we have to take care of!
You're supposed to spend quite a bit
of money when you start a business.
This may not seem very important,
but our club members might...
It's necessary to help
our members organize.
But we're spending
more than we're earning.
That's why I have
an investment plan lined up.
An investment plan?
This measly amount of money?
We can take care of this in one blow.
Don't... Don't worry!
What should we do?
You want to go meet that investor? Huh?
An investor?
[SHAMAN]
What is it?
What's taking you so long?
Where are you?
Oh, did we make plans?
Sorry, I've been out of it today.
I can't go today. I'm going
somewhere and I'm on my way there.
- Where?
- The place Bong Pal's father is staying.
I need to see him with my own eyes.
I have a bad feeling about this.
It's okay, I'm perfectly fine! Hang up!
Just where is my honey?
Oh, Honey! I finally found you!
Honey! Honey!
- Are you awake?
- Yes.
Why am I here?
I moved you in here.
You must be hungry.
Lie down while I heat up the porridge.
I told you to lie down.
Why did you come out?
I'm totally fine now.
I think I was just tired.
Really? That's a relief.
Go ahead and eat.
Thanks, Bong Pal.
It's nothing.
Why didn't you go to school?
Ah, I was kind of tired too.
But do ghosts get sick too?
- Yeah, our hearts race too.
- What?
What?
It's nothing.
By the way, some of my memories
returned while I was sleeping.
Oh, really? What popped up?
I was lying down and someone
was looking down at me.
Who was it?
Well, I couldn't see their face.
Oh right, and some lady was crying.
I wonder who it was?
She was crying with such sorrow.
Have a good day.
Goodness, what is this?
Why are there so many
people looking for that man?
I mean, the acupuncturist
came last time.
What's going on today?
It's nothing really.
I came to ask some questions.
What is it?
I heard a young person came looking
for the man who lives in that room.
Yes, he came.
My eyes are bad, so I didn't
get a good look at his face.
Oh, his son?
He's over there.
He was a good-looking young man.
His son?
I assumed he was his son.
Your son is here to see you.
His face just got serious
when I told him his son came.
He just ran into the back mountains.
I thought he was running
away from money he owed.
Anyway, he ran away and never came back.
Where are the back
mountains he ran away to?
So, my honey lives in this neighborhood!
I think Hyun Ji lives
around this area too...
- You're here.
- Hello, Director.
What's the schedule for today?
You have three appointments today.
- I'll change my clothes then.
- Okay.
Even the clinic is cool
and clean like my honey.
Something bad happened.
He wasn't chasing something.
He was being chased.
Hey, I told you to get some rest.
Why are you following me?
I'm all better now.
Look, I'm fine.
I swear, you don't listen.
I'll see you at
the study room at 11 o' clock.
- Who is it?
- It's Senior Seo Yeon.
We're supposed to talk about
the final project today.
- Just the two of you?
- Yes.
Wait for me!
Remember the puppy factory incident
that was a huge issue a long time ago?
Should we use that as our topic?
Yeah, that sounds good.
We can include this as well.
- I think that'll be fine.
- Okay, let's go with that.
Hurry up and get it over with.
Why here?
What do you mean why?
We came to meet the investor.
- But this is my grandma's house.
- Yes, it's your grandma's house.
The investor is my grandma?
That's correct.
Why do you keep bringing
this up? It's ridiculous!
You know very well that I moved out
because I don't want any help from her.
Let's go!
We're not asking for a free ride.
We're asking her to take a chance on us.
It's not necessary. Let's go.
Let go, let go, let go!
In Rang.
- Grandma!
- Goodness, my precious baby!
Goodness, when did you get here?
You should've come to
me first and said hello!
How long has it been?
Goodness, my precious baby!
Hello, Grandma.
Why do you have that
nuisance with you?
I told you not to hang out
with people like that.
It's good to have friends,
but you need to be more selective!
Grandma, Chun Sang is a good person.
- And he has something to say to you.
- What?
What nonsense is he going
to talk about this time?
I swear! Anyway, let's go inside!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
What are you doing?
Come on in!
Dig in, my precious baby.
Goodness, you've lost so
much weight. Eat a lot.
Goodness, look at you eat.
Why are you so nervous?
Hurry up and dig in!
- Dig in.
- Yes, thank you for the food.
So, you have something to say to me?
Yes, the thing is...
We're thinking about starting
an international and trendy business...
Talk slowly, you rascal!
How dare you try to pull a con on me!
Just get to the point.
In Rang and I are trying
to start a proper business
but we're struggling due to lack
of funds, so we came here to talk to you.
It hasn't even started,
so why would you be struggling?
What kind of business are you making?
Ah, yes...
- This is our business plan.
- What is it?
Blood sausage soup?
When did you prepare all this?
You want to start a restaurant?
No, it's not a restaurant.
A state of the art
multi-communication system
with a speedy, thorough,
and accurate 24-hour AS screen.
We're planning to set
up a exorcism system!
You punk!
What are you saying?
You con artist!
Wait until I get my hands on you!
You punk!
- Let's stop here for today.
- It's over!
Gosh, look at the time.
Do you want to eat lunch together?
Lunch?
What lunch? You're not
going to go, right, Bong Pal?
- Let's eat together then.
- Good, let's go.
What should we eat?
Whatever you want to eat is fine.
Bong Pal, let's eat some other time.
I need to talk to Professor Joo.
Sure, that's fine.
I'm really sorry. I promise to buy
you something really yummy next time.
- It's okay. You should get going.
- I'll see you in class.
What's up with that girl?
She's the one who asked you to lunch.
Right?
Let's go.
Was Byul good while I was gone?
He was very bad.
Maybe he takes after you.
What? Really?
I'm kidding. He was a good dog.
By the way, did you have
a good time at the retreat?
Yes.
You said you're in the same
club as Bong Pal, right?
- You two must be very close.
- Yes, I think so.
I see.
- Professor.
- Yes.
These are the list of
students for next semester.
- I need your signature.
- Sure.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Have a good day.
So, what did you guys do at the retreat?
Hello, Professor.
It's good to see you again.
Yes, hello.
What brings you here today?
We didn't come here to see you today.
- Are you Im Seo Yeon?
- Yes, that's correct.
There are several questions I'd like
to ask you in regards to No Hyun Joo.
Do you have the time?
Hyun Joo is dead?
Yes, it's unfortunate,
but that's what happened.
When was the last time you saw her?
Well... she missed class last week.
I think that was the last time.
Do you remember how she was?
Anything miniscule is fine.
She looked... nervous that day.
Hyun Joo!
Hey, Seo Yeon.
You missed class today.
I just had something to take care of.
But why do you ask?
There were some
printouts today. Hold on.
Hyun Joo!
[JOO HYE SUNG]
A fountain pen?
- Do you have that pen?
- No, I gave it to the professor.
Professor?
Yes, it belonged to
Professor Joo Hye Sung.
Professor Joo Hye Sung
of the veterinary medicine department?
Yes.
And there's nothing else you remember?
Please leave a message after the beep.
I hope nothing bad happened to him.
[MONK MYUNG CHUL]
Tell me!
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Did your grandma deposit
the money yet? Check again.
You're really amazing.
After all that abuse,
you still don't have it together.
Why can't she understand
this awesome idea?
Should we seek her out one more time?
Well, if you want to die, then go ahead.
Yo, Bong Pal! Long time no see.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
It's because we missed you.
How come we don't have any work?
After that one incident, that was it.
Don't worry about that, okay?
Just think of it as a temporary break.
Even frogs crouch and wait
like this before they jump.
Yeah, just like that.
I have something to give you.
Here, these are yours.
Those are the pictures
I took at the retreat.
Gosh, you two look good together!
You guys look like a couple.
I'm going to go.
Sure, see you.
You two really look good
together! The perfect couple!
- Are you stupid?
- What?
There's something there.
Gosh.
My precious baby, Grandma
sent you some pocket money.
Make sure you eat on time
and buy lots of yummy food to eat.
And don't hang around with that loser.
- But who's the loser?
- I don't know, loser.
Why the library all of a sudden?
Why do you think? We came to study.
We can study at home.
It's hot at home and it's cool in there.
Then you study in the cool
library and I'll be at home.
You're not going anywhere.
You have to study too. Follow me.
Bong Pal, I solved everything...
What are you doing?
Huh? Ah, nothing.
- I solved everything.
- Already?
I was there too.
[BONG PAL LOVES HYUN JI]
Why are you all happy?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Did you finish grading yet?
I did a good job this time, didn't I?
How can you possibly smile
at a time like this?
Did a good job? My butt.
My teaching was such a waste of time.
Gosh, it was number four.
I was so close.
Why don't you give up taking the SAT?
- How can your score not improve?
- Maybe I have a lousy teacher.
What? You will never find
a teacher who is as good.
This is because the student
just isn't smart enough.
If you keep putting me down,
how can I possibly improve my score?
Then what? What am
I supposed to do for you?
Don't just push me, but reward me
like you give a carrot to a horse.
Carrots, please.
Carrots, my butt.
If I do well on the exam,
you should reward me.
Fine. All right.
If you get higher than
80 points on the next exam
I will grant one of your wishes.
Really? Will you grant all my wishes?
I will decide within my budget.
- If it's something doable, I will.
- Hooray!
You promised just now.
I will study really hard.
It'll be a breeze to get
higher than 80 points.
What is it?
No, I thought she looked at me.
- I might have seen it wrong.
- Let's go.
Hey, you're studying at this hour?
Of course. I'm all motivated now.
All the answers are number four.
Wow, it looks good.
- Fighting.
- Sure.
Fighting.
Come on, I asked you to do it with us
because Yoo Jin is good.
Isn't Yoo Jin going
to prepare for the Olympiad?
I was able to find a very good tutor.
The tutor won't take
fewer than two students.
If we take too long,
we may not be able to get in.
Okay. I have to get
Eun Sung's snack ready now.
All right then. Call me later.
Eun Sung. Eun Sung.
Eun Sung.
Get out.
Oh my, these look very expensive.
Seriously.
By the way, why did we come here?
What? What do you mean why?
You know your clothes make
who you are, don't you?
Look at Bong Pal.
Who would think he's an exorcist?
We should order him a suit.
We should have money first
to order him a suit.
Yes, we do have money now from
the investment we received.
The investment?
How is that the investment?
It's my allowance!
How dare you.
Your money is my money.
My money is yours...
We can't do that between us.
Wow. How come you're
looking at a suit for yourself?
I'm the face of our company.
Wow.
Why did you ask me to come here?
I asked you here to order our uniforms.
Uniform? I want to order
one for myself too.
- What uniforms?
- Come here.
It's okay, so come here.
You should dress up like this, see?
How cool is this?
People won't look down on you
if you dress up like this.
When you're this stylish,
you will bring more work, too.
Go put it on. Come here.
- Come over here.
- Well...
Come on. Here...
Try it on and come out.
See? We already have a client.
Hello, we provide exorcism service 24-7.
This is Choi Chun Sang.
How may I help you?
Wow, you look cool.
You look the best among them.
Bong Pal, can you also get me a uniform?
I'm the only one without one.
You keep asking me for things.
Bong Pal, hurry up.
Get me one, please.
Open the door! I said open it!
Open the door! Open it!
What happened?
Your hand...
Since that day, my child has...
Eun Sung, you're wearing makeup...
Take off those clothes. Now!
- Leave me alone.
- What?
Don't you feel sorry for your daughter
who has you as her mother?
You don't know how much your daughter is
suffering because of your greed, do you?
Eun Sung.
Why are you doing this, huh?
Eun Sung?
Your daughter is dead.
How could she live with someone
like you? It's suffocating.
That's why your husband cheated on you.
He didn't want to live with you.
Didn't you know that?
Come back.
Come back!
Ever since that night
I've taken her to
the hospital and shamans.
It only made her symptoms worse.
You have no idea
what a good daughter she was.
I don't know what happened to her...
Eun Sung, please...
- Please stop.
- Open the door now!
Open the door! Open it!
Eun Sung!
I will go in.
Take this.
Bong Pal, I'm not getting
a good feeling about this place.
- So please be careful.
- I agree.
Don't get hurt.
I will be back.
Are you like the shaman
I saw last time?
No, you seem different.
You came with something else, too.
She's the one I saw at the library.
She also saw me then.
A ghost went into her body.
What should we do?
We should take the ghost out of her body.
Who said you could do that?
Bong Pal!
Why do you go around
with her tagging along?
That's some strange hobby.
How about bringing me along instead?
Ma'am.
You can't. It'll be okay.
Eun Sung.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
What do you think you're doing now?
Why do you care?
How about you?
You don't want Eun Sung to die.
This is what she wants.
She's not brave enough to
kill herself, so I'm just helping her.
Don't show off when you know nothing.
No!
Eun Sung, wake up.
Eun Sung! Eun Sung!
Eun Sung!
Eun Sung.
I'm sorry, so don't do that.
I did that
because I wanted you to do well.
But I was wrong.
So please don't do that.
Don't do that, Eun Sung. Don't.
Don't call my name like that!
Please help my Eun Sung...
Eun Sung, don't do that. Don't.
- Don't come closer. Don't.
- Eun Sung...
Don't do it. Don't.
Eun Sung! Eun Sung!
Eun Sung, wake up.
My child... Eun Sung.
Mom!
- Mom!
- Eun Sung.
- I'm scared, Mom.
Mom, did I do this to you?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
No, I'm okay as long as you're okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
What can we do to help now?
Go rest. We will take care of the rest.
You go over there.
Bong Pal.
The lady I saw
in my dream last time
- I think I know who she is.
- Who is she?
My mom. She was my mom.
She was just like Eun Sung's mom earlier.
My mom would have cried just like her.
It's good that you're getting
some memories back.
If it's not my mom,
at least one person misses me.
Let's go. I need to go study hard.
Now take the exam.
You have one hour.
Wait a minute.
I'm ready.
Now you begin.
Now take the exam.
You have one hour.
Wait a minute.
I'm ready.
Now you begin.
What is it? My score isn't
higher than 80 points?
- No.
- Seriously?
Actually, yes.
You did a good job. It was worth it.
Of course it was worth it.
I tried so hard.
So now you will grant my wish, won't you?
- A promise is a promise, so...
- Yes!
What is your wish?
There is a place I've been wanting to go.
Where is it?
- An amusement park.
- An amusement park?
What are you, a kid?
Why would you want to go there?
Only kids go there?
You said you'd grant my wish. Let's go.
Okay. Your wish isn't very grand.
I will go with you.
Since we're on the subject,
can we go tomorrow?
- You said your exams are over tomorrow.
- That's right. Fine then.
My exams will end at 3:00 p.m. tomorrow.
- Let's meet at 4:00 p.m. at the park.
- Sure.
Hooray!
Sir, this is Detective Yang.
Detective Yang, what's up?
You conducted an autopsy
on No Hyun Joo, didn't you?
I already sent the document.
Didn't you get it yet?
Yes, I did. I just have
a few other questions.
- What are they?
- No Hyun Joo's neck was broken.
Was there a chance it broke
when her body was tossed there?
There is no chance.
If it broke after she died
there would be a visible
physical trace on the outside.
But there was none.
Then...
I'm certain that her neck broke
when she was getting strangled.
Can a human be strong enough
to break a live person's neck?
It's not impossible,
but it's hard for average people.
I see. Thank you, sir.
- I will come by next time.
- Do that.
- I'm back.
- What is it?
This is the video file of
the camera near No's place.
- Did you find anything?
- Not really, but something was odd.
- What was odd?
- You might want to see it yourself.
Play it then.
This is No Hyun Joo here.
And then this corner here...
Someone was there.
- What's wrong?
- It didn't record from that point.
They say it wasn't
a camera malfunction. Take a look here.
For five minutes, the screen went blurry.
He knows how to break someone's neck.
And he also knows
how to manipulate the camera.
Who on earth is this man?
Who is he, huh?
Gosh, I managed to come in.
Oh my, this is where
my honey works, huh?
Joo Hye Sung?
Even his name sounds cool.
Wow, it's nice here.
What is this?
He's good, isn't he?
Oh my, he's so photogenic too!
He's so cool.
Wait, where is this sound coming from?
It might be around here...
[KIM HYUN JI]
Oh my goodness.
It's so annoying that
she managed to come in here.
We now have a problem.
Bong Pal, it's at 4:00 p.m. today.
You know that, don't you?
- Don't be late.
- I understand.
Bong Pal.
Seo Yeon.
- Did you just finish your exam?
- Yes.
- Are you also taking one?
- Yes, one liberal arts course.
- Where are you off to now?
- I'm meeting someone.
- Excuse me.
- All right. Bye.
Seo Yeon!
Are you okay?
He's late...
Did his exam take longer?
Mister, please hurry.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Fight Ghost]
Hyun Ji! Kim Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji! Did I ask you
to follow me around?
You wanted to follow me around.
Gosh, you scared me.
Good for you that you're alive.
Do you walk around
with a ghost by any chance?
No, she was an angel.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Am I wrong?
Now we have a new assignment, right?
She died because of you.
Do you know that?
- My angel.
- She's pretty just the way she is.
When she smiles,
she's much prettier.
Bong Pal.
I like you.
Hyun Ji!