This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
[Let's Fight Ghost]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Oh my, he's so photogenic too!
He's so cool.
Wait, where is this sound coming from?
It might be around here...
[KIM HYUN JI]
Oh my goodness.
It's so annoying that
she managed to come in here.
We now have a problem.
You... can see me?
What should I do?
What did you see in here?
Kim Hyun Ji.
I knew it.
- Kyung Ja.
- Hyun Ji, where are you going?
- I'm following someone.
- Who?
- I'll tell you later. Bye!
- Bye!
Don't resent me.
[KIM HYUN JI]
[Let's Fight Ghost]
[Episode 8]
Senior, are you all right?
Yes, they said my arm
will get better in a month.
- Thanks for bringing me here.
- Not at all.
- Senior, I'm sorry, but I have to go.
- Oh, sure.
I hope you're not late for
your appointment because of me.
No, it's okay. I'll see you at school.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Hyun Ji!
Is she waiting inside?
Sir, you can't enter
because we're closed.
- There's someone I have to find...
- Excuse me?
Never mind.
Hyun Ji.
Kim Hyun Ji.
Where did she go?
Hyun Ji!
You're here.
I'm sorry that I couldn't make it.
Why couldn't you come?
The thing is...
Something came up.
I'm sorry. Let's go to
the amusement park some other time.
- Fine.
- Did you wait for a long time?
No! I just left right away
when you didn't come.
That's a relief. I thought
you were waiting for me.
Why would I wait for
you this whole time?
Have you seen that person before?
He's about 174 centimeters tall
and 44 years old.
And his name is Park Ji Hoon.
Do you know the boarding house in
Yangjoo Village? He lives there.
It's my first time seeing him.
Monk, it's very rare for
accidents to occur here.
If there is, we get a report right away.
I've never seen this man before.
I'll make a report now, so please go to
the back mountains and search the area.
What search?
What do you mean?
I just showed you that picture.
This rock is all coated in red!
Look how red this rock
is next to the green one!
Something happened,
so please go and search the area!
That is not going to be of any help.
There's not many people in
this precinct to go on a search.
Then what are you going to do?
This is bad!
Please, that's enough.
If you're that upset, fill this out.
There's blood splattered
all over the mountains!
We're not going to get anything
done by writing a report!
Please don't throw a fit here.
Just fill that report out.
How do I fill this out?
[KIM HYUN JI]
Where is it?
Where's that package?
Tell me.
Do you think I'm going to tell you?
That child died because of you.
Do you know that?
That child died
because you didn't tell me.
Tell me.
If you don't...
Your son will die.
This is your last chance.
Tell me!
- Aren't you going?
- Where?
- To school.
- No, I'm not going.
I'm going to stay home.
That's a surprise. You always follow me.
Do I have to follow you every day?
Fine then, stay home.
I'm going to go.
That's right, I'm going to stay home!
I'm really not good at
this "hard-to-get" thing.
I never asked her to follow me.
She's the one who's
always tagging along.
Gosh, it's actually nice
not having her around.
You scared me!
- How long have you been there?
- I just got here.
What are you mumbling to yourself?
Nothing.
Why did you follow me?
I'm not following you.
I'm going because I want to.
Well... I'm sure you are.
What is up with that puppy dog smile?
Who are you looking at?
This picture is from our retreat.
Who is making you smile like that...
No. Not... not Seo Yeon.
Absolutely no way!
Never ever never!
What are you going to
do if Bong Pal finds out?
Are you a weirdo? Huh?
You're being treacherous!
- How dare you have feelings for...
- What are you talking about?
Why would I have feelings for Seo Yeon?
You're being ridiculous.
Then who is it?
Then...
Is it me?
Yeah, take me instead.
You can have my body.
No! Get away from me!
Ow, my nipples.
Who is it then?
Is it Bong Pal?
No.
Hello.
Bong Pal, he keeps smiling whenever
he looks at you. He's acting so weird.
No, I'm not! That's not true!
Who's making you smile then?
Look.
What is that?
Is it a ghost?
Is that a picture of a ghost?
Hey, it's me!
They got me on camera!
My angel.
Your angel. An angel?
The angel you saw at the retreat?
Yes, it's that angel.
He says I'm an angel.
Angel, my butt.
Right, when I rolled down
the stairs that time...
If it wasn't for my
angel... I would've... died.
At that time the angel asked me...
"Are you okay?"
She saved me with those
words and stole my heart.
Oh my gosh, I think
he's fallen for me. Right?
At that moment...
I think you did get a hole
in your head back then.
That ghost didn't steal your
heart, she took your wits from you!
- Wake up!
- Who cares if it's a ghost!
Look!
She's so pretty, kind, and cute.
- What do you think?
- She's kind?
- She looks nice.
- She's cute?
I guess I must be pretty.
It was love at first sight.
- Right?
- Oh please. Happy?
Someone just said they like me.
Wouldn't you be happy about it?
Anyway, he is not normal.
- Who?
- Who do you think? Senior In Rang.
I could understand Chun Sang
because he's naturally weird.
But Senior In Rang is weirder.
No way, he's not weird at all.
That's a natural response
from looking at me.
You're the one who is weird.
You're a bit overconfident today.
She's so pretty, but she's
prettier when she smiles.
Seriously, she's just
an angel when she smiles.
What are you doing? Hurry up.
What's so pretty about her?
Senior In Rang is crazy.
That girl's arm is injured.
Bong Pal.
Hello, Senior.
I didn't even say a proper
thank you to you yesterday.
I would've had a hard time
if you weren't with me at the hospital.
Thanks for staying with me.
You said you had a prior engagement.
Were you late because of me?
- Ah... yes, well...
- What the heck?
He was preoccupied because
he was with that girl.
If it's okay with you, I'll treat you
to a meal today. What do you think?
- That's okay.
- It's because I'm grateful.
Okay.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
I have something to say
before we start class.
I'm sure there are other students
who already know about this.
Your fellow classmate No Hyun Joo
has been in an unfortunate accident.
Hyun Joo's funeral information
is on the class website.
If you know her, it would be nice
if you can make it to her funeral.
Okay, I'll start calling off names now.
- Kim Oh Chang.
- Here.
Okay.
- Na Jin Soo.
- Here.
Thank you.
- Park Bong Pal.
- Here.
Thank you.
Good for you that you're alive.
And Bong Pal likes you too.
Okay, that's all for today.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you.
Bong Pal, what do you like to eat?
Let's eat what you like.
I'm sorry, Senior,
but let's just call it even.
- I have to go home.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
- Sure.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
- Are you heading somewhere?
- Yes, there's a seminar.
What's going on?
It's nothing really. We forgot to ask you
a question the other day.
What is it?
Where were you on the day
No Hyun Joo was murdered?
Ah, I have to ask because it's protocol,
so please don't be so concerned.
I was at the hospital clinic that day.
The hospital clinic?
I understand. I apologize for
bothering you when you're so busy.
- Not at all. Have a good day.
- Yes, thank you.
You're home early.
Weren't you supposed
to have lunch with her?
I didn't eat with her.
Why? She would've bought you
something delicious to eat.
I just wanted to eat at home.
You bought meat.
Yeah, I want to eat it.
- You don't like it?
- I don't feel like eating it
but I'll give it a taste
since you bought it.
You said you were only
going to give it a taste.
Yeah, but I still can't taste it.
Eat slowly, or you'll lose your jaw.
About the amusement park.
- Let's go tomorrow.
- Really?
Yes.
Hey, that's not fully cooked.
Eat this one.
Here.
What is this?
You're my partner.
Wear it when you work.
Really?
Wow!
Okay, sure.
The breeze is cool and nice.
I like it too.
Let's hurry it up!
- Mr. Kim, help this team out.
- Okay.
Come on, let's hurry it up!
There's not much time left!
- Okay, we got it.
- Come on!
- Come on, let's go!
- This is scary.
There's nothing to be afraid of!
I'll pay you twice the amount,
so let's get this over with!
- I'm not sure about this.
- It's perfectly fine!
Mr. Kim, over here! Hurry it up!
- Hurry it up!
- We're going!
Hello?
Excuse me? Hello?
Hello? I can't hear
you very well. Hold on!
What?
I see. What am I supposed to do then?
We have to take it down in
order to occupy the space.
Ghosts or whatever!
We have to make a living too!
Hello?
I swear!
What's wrong over there?
The backup generator has gone out!
Seriously, nothing is going as planned!
Who is crazy? Me?
- Who is crazy? I am?
- What the heck?
I'm not crazy!
Why would I be crazy? Why? Why?
Who is crazy?
I'm not crazy! I'm not crazy!
Wow! Wow, did we really get a job to do?
We've been hoping it wouldn't
be the Samil Mental Institute.
Wow!
- Did you call Bong Pal?
- Of course.
Make sure you check the camera and all
the necessary equipment thoroughly today.
We might be able to capture
a ghost on camera for real today.
Right.
Setting!
What do you think?
It fits you well.
What are we going to do
about the amusement park today?
- We're supposed to go today.
- We can go after work.
Work hard so we can get there quickly.
Let's go.
Senior, where are we going today?
You brought the camera with you.
Huh? Oh...
Make sure you're ready today.
Why?
The place we're going to is one of
the scariest locations in the world.
That's right.
It's the Samil Mental Institute!
- Is it your first time hearing about it?
- Yes.
Everything about Bong Pal is great,
but he's clueless about this field.
In Rang will give you
the 411 on that place.
That place was shut down
due to human rights issues.
The doctors and caretakers illegally
held the patients against their will
and abused them as well.
It was very severe.
One patient couldn't take
it anymore and escaped.
That's how the world found
out about the hospital.
The police came and discovered
seven patients who died in the hospital.
Seven people.
The building owner called exorcists
and shamans to get rid of the ghosts.
There are rumors that a shaman fainted
within 30 minutes of entering.
This is a place full of
ghosts with deep grudges.
Hey, look over here.
What the heck?
Wow, Chun Sang!
Chun Sang, Chun Sang, Chun Sang!
Whoa!
- Whoa!
- I'm going. Grab onto me.
- Grab onto me. Hold tight!
- Don't let go. Don't let go.
They're such scaredy-cats.
Why are they doing this kind of work?
You want to fight? Let's fight!
Both of them are not normal.
- I'm going to go.
- Okay.
- Grab onto me!
- Don't let go.
Don't let go!
Hyun Ji, are you okay?
What's wrong?
I'm okay.
Bong Pal! Bong Pal! Quickly, come here!
What is it?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Look over there.
I think it's over there.
- That's where the ghost is?
- Yes.
"Hospital Admission."
I think it's over there.
- Chun Sang!
- What?
Chun Sang!
It's the Casualty Department.
Hey, start recording.
- Hold me tight.
- I will hold you tight.
When I look this cool,
I have to hold your hands?
Let's just go.
Is this the right place?
Where did they go?
It looks like something is in there.
One, two, three.
- Oh my goodness.
- Oh my.
- Oh my god! What is this?
- It's just string.
- Where is Bong Pal?
- What?
Let's go find him.
- Pal!
- Bong Pal. Bong Pal!
Wait. This is the right place.
He may not have gotten here yet.
He might have gotten lost...
- What if we got lost?
- Call him.
Hurry up and call him.
It's okay here.
Gosh, what is this? Bong Pal.
Bong... Come on.
Darn it.
Hey, don't touch things in here.
- I told you not to touch things in here.
- I'm sorry.
Bong Pal, didn't you say
seven people died in this hospital?
Yes, why do you ask?
Take a look at this.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
And eight.
Kim Jung Soon died of a leg fracture.
[NAME OF PATIENT: KIM JUNG SOON]
- Pal.
- Bong Pal.
Uh, we're coming in, Bong Pal.
Excuse me, Bong Pal.
[PLEASE SAVE ME.
PLEASE HELP ME.]
- Bong Pal.
- Pal.
- Wait a second.
- What is it?
My back is killing me, gosh.
- Better now.
- He's not in here.
Hey, what is this?
I wonder what it is...
There is the angel. Angel.
An angel, my butt.
- Get over here now!
- Hold on.
Miss Angel.
[PLEASE HELP ME.
I WANT TO GET OUT OF HERE.]
Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji.
Bong Pal, stop.
These ghosts won't hurt us.
What?
Come over here.
Over there.
[HELP ME. SAVE ME.
I WANT TO GET OUT OF THIS PLACE.]
I think they want us to help them.
Detective Kim!
- Did you find something?
- Yes, I did.
They wanted us to find them.
The dead people here
all became missing persons.
It's good that they are found now.
I will go now.
Bong Pal, wait a minute.
Well...
It's just that...
Do you walk around with
a ghost by any chance?
It's just that...
Do you walk around with
a ghost by any chance?
How can you say that?
No, she was an angel.
Isn't she with us now?
- Well...
- I saw everything earlier.
I saw her rescue us.
Didn't you? I did see her.
It was my first time seeing
a ghost fight another ghost.
Are you working with that angel?
Yes, but she's no angel.
- Her name is Hyun Ji, Kim Hyun Ji.
- Hyun Ji?
Kim Hyun Ji. What a pretty name.
Is it? So is she right next to us now?
She's right here.
Right here?
Hyun Ji, thanks so much for
saving us last time and also this time.
And...
you're so pretty.
Oh my, it was no problem.
I'm pretty, all right.
Don't you agree?
I can't stand hearing this. I just can't.
Wait a second.
So Hyun Ji is right around here...
What do you think you're doing?
I was just wondering
if she was around here...
Still, you can't touch a girl like that.
Did my hand touch her?
Hyun Ji, I'm sorry.
I didn't think it'd touch you.
- What's the matter with you?
- I will go now.
- Hurry. Aren't we going today?
- I'm coming.
Bye bye.
No way. Such a thing is here, huh?
He was acting funny.
Why did he get mad?
See you tomorrow!
[TICKET OFFICE]
Can I go in now?
- Now?
- Yes.
You can, but you won't
get to ride many at this hour.
You may be able to ride
only the Ferris wheel.
I like the Ferris wheel.
- One ticket, please.
- Sure, it's 10,000.
By the way, didn't you
come at this hour yesterday?
Ah, I did...
The last ride of the Ferris wheel
will be in 10 minutes.
Let's run. We might be late.
- Here it is.
- You're riding this alone?
Yes, I am.
Did you come here yesterday?
Well, yes, I did come,
but I was late.
You weren't here, either.
I see.
Too bad that you will only
get to ride one tonight.
I still like it.
If you do well on exams,
I will bring you here again.
- Let's get here earlier then.
- Sure.
Are you that happy?
I didn't know you'd like
something like this.
Bong Pal.
I like you.
What?
- Well, Hyun Ji...
- Don't say anything.
I didn't say that to hear your answer.
It's just how I feel.
I'm crazy. So crazy.
Why did I have to tell him
that I like him right then?
Gosh, how am I supposed
to face Bong Pal again?
Puppy, what should I do now?
I don't think I can go home like this.
Look at me, please.
What should I do?
What should I do, huh?
Hey, Kim Hyun Ji.
Bong Pal.
How could you disappear like that?
Kim Hyun Ji!
Bong Pal.
Professor Joo, hello.
You live nearby, huh?
Yes. So this is your hospital, huh?
I've passed by this place so many times.
By the way, who were
you calling just now?
- Pardon?
- I thought you were calling someone.
- Kim Hyun Ji?
- Ah...
- Is she your girlfriend?
- No.
- She's just someone I know.
- Ah, is she?
I will go now then.
Sure, get home safe.
Bye.
What should I say
when I see Bong Pal again?
Gosh, what should I do?
Hyun Ji, are you asleep?
Get some sleep then.
Bong Pal.
I like you.
Is he still asleep?
- Good morning.
- It sure is...
I need to go to the bathroom...
What good morning, gosh.
Well, I'm done.
I'm full, too.
Gosh, this is crazy.
So what? She could
have feelings for me.
It's not a reason to avoid her.
Okay then. Go out and act natural.
Okay, okay.
Gosh, it's so uncomfortable and crazy.
Act natural.
Gosh, should I go stay
somewhere else?
There is no other place to go.
It's so uncomfortable
for two of us alone.
[CHUN SANG]
Hi, Chun Sang. I will be right there.
Hyun Ji, we have work. Let's go.
- Do we? Let's go.
- Sure.
Sure, I should do something or anything.
You sure know how to do
a good job. Are you already done?
We will get some money again today.
I don't know where she is,
but you also did a good job, Hyun Ji.
- Good work.
- Chun Sang, she's over here.
Good work.
By the way, where is In Rang?
He said he had to go
get something from the car.
- Wait. Are you already done?
- Yes, it's done.
- Is she hurt?
- I'm not hurt.
I'm talking about Hyun Ji, not you.
Is she hurt?
- She's not hurt at all.
- Oh my, thank God.
- So Hyun Ji is with us now, right?
- Correct.
Hyun Ji, I got something for you.
- What did you get?
- What could it be?
- These.
- Wow, they are heels.
- Wow.
- Hey.
You've never gotten me anything.
You got heels for a ghost
you can't even see?
Quiet.
Does Hyun Ji seem to like these?
Tell him that I love them.
She hates them.
I said I love them.
She hates them?
She says she's never
liked heels. Right?
I do like heels.
She's never liked them, huh?
- Well, too bad then.
- Isn't it?
- We will go now.
- Sure.
Gosh, why do you lie?
I so want to accept these...
Park Bong Pal!
No matter what you do,
certain things just can't work out.
It's okay.
Do you know what I
went through to get these?
We will exchange them.
- Pardon? Our doctor?
- Correct.
What was his schedule on the first?
He didn't have
anything specific that day.
He was seeing patients
until the afternoon.
What time in the afternoon?
He ended early that day.
Around seven.
He usually stays until nine.
- He may have had an appointment then.
- Was it that day?
- It's when he didn't get back.
- He didn't get back all night?
Correct. He usually sleeps here.
He left earlier and came back
the next morning that day.
- Oh my, you're here!
- Hello, Director.
I'm sorry for being late. Please prepare
everything until I get back from class.
Where has he been
to get mud on his shoes?
- He came back with mud on his shoes.
- Correct.
Thank you.
- You're late.
- I had a seminar.
What brings you here today?
We just came by for routine questions.
We're off now. See you next time.
- Thank you.
- Was everything okay?
- Yes.
What should we do?
What's the matter with you?
You wouldn't let me accept the present.
I agree. Why did I do that?
It's so childish.
What?
You've changed your clothes.
- It's convenient being a ghost.
- Well, you know how it is.
I can't take this anymore.
It's so uncomfortable.
Bong Pal.
What?
Shall we play a game
to grant our wishes?
We will play rock-paper-scissors.
Whoever loses will have to
grant the winner's wish.
Why grant wishes?
I don't want to play.
Can we please do it?
I didn't even get the heels or anything.
Fine. Let's play.
We're doing it.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
I won!
One, two, three.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot! Hooray!
One, two.
Yes! Hooray!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot! Hooray!
I won! Hooray!
You're such a kid.
So what's your wish?
Well, my wish would be...
to take back what I said yesterday.
I don't like being uncomfortable
with each other.
Just forget everything I said.
That's my wish.
One minute you're confessing
and now you want me to forget?
Why are you confusing me?
You understand, right?
It's my wish,
so you have to do what I ask.
If you do what I ask now
I can stay with you longer.
Bong Pal.
Hyun Ji.
I'm not feeling well...
Kim Hyun Ji.
- Bong Pal.
- Hyun Ji...
Hyun Ji!
Kim Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji.
Bong Pal.
Where did you go?
Don't ever disappear again...
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Fight Ghost]
I love you, Kim Hyun Ji!
It was so hot that you slept in my room.
You're so crazy about a girl
that you'd sell your country.
Love makes you do crazy things.
You crazy punk!
He's too perfect to be considered human.
Puppy, where are you?
Who said you could come in
without my permission?
You look familiar. Have we met?
Are we going to be okay this way?
People can see you.
I don't care if they look at me funny.
It's about you, Hyun Ji.