This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Fight Ghost]
So what's your wish?
Well, my wish would be...
What I said yesterday.
I take it back.
I don't like being uncomfortable
with each other.
Just forget everything I said.
That's my wish.
One minute you're confessing
and now you want me to forget?
Why are you confusing me?
You understand, right?
You have to grant my wish.
If you do what I ask now
I can stay with you longer.
Bong Pal.
Hyun Ji.
I'm not feeling well...
Kim Hyun Ji.
- Bong Pal.
- Hyun Ji.
Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji.
Kim Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji.
Bong Pal.
Don't ever disappear again.
Never again.
[Let's Fight Ghost]
[Episode 9]
- Good night.
- Okay.
Hyun Ji.
- What?
- Well. It's too hot.
From now on, you can sleep in my room.
- Me?
- Yes.
I don't like hot weather.
- Good night.
- Okay.
Don't disappear.
Never again.
His father had an accident
and passed away when he was young.
Thereafter, he has been living
with his mother.
He lived in a dorm during
his middle school years.
And he has been living alone since then.
It seems like he keeps in touch
with his mother
but they never visit each other.
- Is this all?
- Yes.
Honestly, there's nothing to look into.
He's always on time with his bills.
His hospital payment
record is also clean.
The only thing we have is
his medical records.
- What is it?
- It's nothing special.
It seems like he was very ill
when he was young.
He has several medical reports.
- What do other people say about him?
- They are all busy complimenting him.
They said he is nice and diligent.
It's obvious that they say that.
He participates in
five different volunteer groups.
And he does surgeries for
homeless dogs for free.
People said they have never
seen him upset or irritated.
He's a genius and has perfect
looks and a perfect personality.
That's right. He is perfect.
He's too perfect to be considered human.
Not even a bit.
Aren't we supposed to change
our investigation plan?
- Did you find No Hyun Joo's cell phone?
- No.
I contacted the phone company.
They said that her phone was turned off
in front of her house.
Check if we missed anyone
on her calls list.
- Okay.
- And track down her location.
Check the path she took and compare it
to where we found the body.
Okay.
Did you hear how Hyun Joo died?
- Her neck was broken.
- Really?
- Oh my.
- Did they find a suspect?
No, not yet.
It's Eun Soo.
- Who is he?
- Last semester
he told Hyun Joo that he liked her.
Professor Joo.
Did you come here to
condole with her family?
- Yes.
- Well. Professor Joo.
You should go and comfort
them too. Bye.
- Are you awake?
- Yes.
Aren't you hungry? Wait just a bit.
- Are you not eating?
- Huh? I'm eating.
- What? Is it not good?
- Huh? No, it's delicious.
Then why are you eating like that?
What's wrong with it?
I always eat like this.
It turned green. Let's run.
What's the title of the book?
Economic Theory.
Economic Theory...
It should be somewhere here.
- Oh, it's right here.
- Huh?
Excuse me.
Oh...
I have something to do.
See you later.
Hey, where are you going...
- Enjoy.
- Thanks. Have a safe trip back.
Hey, In Rang. Let's eat. Eat.
Wow. One, two, three.
Wow. Why do we have so many?
I ordered one for Bong Pal too.
So then with Bong Pal... We have three
people. But we have four of these.
Hey, you.
After you started earning money...
You spend too much. You have changed.
Okay then.
This one. Grilled beef bento.
I like this a lot.
I will try some.
- This one is for Hyun Ji.
- What?
- That's for Hyun Ji.
- Hyun...
- Angel?
- Angel.
You are so crazy about her
you might even forsake our country.
You even bought shoes for a ghost.
Love is crazy.
Crazy. Crazy. You have gone crazy.
Why don't you just date her?
That's embarrassing.
Gosh.
You are insane.
Hey, you are a human and she is a ghost.
Don't you know what that means?
She is a dead person. Okay?
Why don't you marry her and have kids?
Are you that happy?
Ghosts can't live with people.
Can't you understand that?
But a wedding... You are far too ahead.
You should go to
Sam Il Psychiatric Hospital.
You should stay in a hospital.
Gosh. Gosh.
How could you eat now?
We are going to eat together once
Hyun Ji and Bong Pal get here.
Our angel is not even here yet.
How rude. How could you eat this?
Wait.
Don't move.
I thought my heart was going to burst.
If Kyung Ja was here,
we could talk about Bong Pal.
Where is she anyway?
Why is it so hard to see her these days?
She's not here either.
Did she go home?
Oh, Pal, Pal, Pal. Welcome.
- Hello, In Rang.
- Hi, Hyun Ji.
Hyun Ji didn't come with me.
Really? Where is she?
I think she went home.
Our Bong Pal. Have a seat.
Our Bong Pal, do you have any worries?
- Well. A woman...
- A woman?
I want to do something for her.
I'm not sure what I should do.
- This is not about me.
- Yes, this is not about you.
- This is about your friend, right?
- That's right.
Woman. Woman.
Woman. Female. Woman.
Should I give you some
good dating advice?
It's not easy to figure out what a woman
wants or what you should do for her.
Dating? Do you know what love is?
A baby bird like you should
stay out of this. Got that? Huh?
Before you find out what she wants
you should find out what type of person
she's attracted to.
Assistant? Look here.
It's okay even if
you are not that good-looking.
Do this.
Put your hand here like this.
Move your fingers.
It's okay even if you look like a squid.
Those are not men's charming points.
Then what are men's charming points?
In English, we call it "charming."
Ah... Ah... Charming.
Shall we start now?
Step one.
The side profile. The neck muscles
that symbolize masculine beauty
and the sharp nose that is full of
intellectual beauty.
When women see those things
they will fall for you.
They will totally fall for you.
Step two.
Eye contact.
There are times when unpolished beauty
and eyes that are like the ocean
can do the trick.
When you look at her with those eyes
she might melt like a glacier
because of global warming.
She will melt like that.
Step three.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
Don't cry, you fool.
You must be able to make her laugh
when she is in despair.
When an apple smiles, what is it?
A smiley apple.
A sense of humor.
We can say that the sense of humor is
one of men's strongest charming points.
Is this helpful to you?
That's okay. I have eight more.
There are 11 steps.
Step four.
I think I'm okay. That's enough.
Hyun Ji.
Kim Hyun Ji?
Bong Pal.
Where were you?
I told you to stay by my side.
Don't disappear.
I looked everywhere for you.
I'm sorry.
- What were you doing?
- Nothing, really.
Charming.
What are men's charming points?
Step one.
- Hyun Ji.
- Huh?
- Bong Pal.
- Bong Pal?
- What?
Are you not feeling well?
What's wrong with you?
I have a stiff neck.
- Is this not it?
- Step two.
- Eye contact.
- Eye contact. Okay.
- Hyun Ji?
- Yes?
What?
Do you want to have a staring contest?
No. My eyes hurt.
- Is this not it either?
- Step three.
We can say that the sense of humor is
one of men's strongest charming points.
Hyun Ji, do you want me to
tell you something funny?
- What is it?
- Who is the poorest king in the world?
Hm...
The king who earns the least.
Isn't this funny?
- What is the hottest phone in the world?
- Well.
Video call.
Okay then.
When an apple smiles, what is it?
Smiley apple.
Are you sure you are okay?
Are you okay?
Yes.
- This is not working.
- What is?
Oh... It's nothing.
Let's eat lunch.
Meat! Meat! Meat! Wow!
Wow, it's all done. Can I eat it now?
- Here, eat it.
- Which one would be good?
Meat is always the best.
That star is the brightest.
That one? That's Altair.
The Altair and the Vega?
Yes. And that one right there is Vega.
The one spread out is the Milky Way.
Oh, that's cool.
I didn't know that before.
Those two stars are really far apart.
They must be sad.
They only get to see each other once
a year and they are that far apart.
Shouldn't they be happy because
they can at least see each other?
Even if they only get
a day to see each other.
How do you know so much
about constellations?
Oh, my father taught me when I was young.
- Shall I tell you more about it?
- Yes.
The one shining on top is Aquila.
So there's Aquila...
Bong Pal, are you asleep?
Go to bed.
If you want to go out tomorrow...
Really? Are you going on a date tomorrow?
Well.
Okay. It's a date.
Okay. I will get up early tomorrow.
Good night. Dream of me.
What do you want to do today?
The things all the other couples do.
Eat out, have a cup of tea
watch a movie, and walk together.
Okay. Let's do what other couples do.
Okay.
Oh. Hey!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey!
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Excuse me.
What's taking her so long?
What am I supposed to
wear on a first date?
Bong Pal.
Why did you tell me to leave first?
Just...
Let's go.
This is not it.
It's just like the one you already have.
It's not bad.
Knock, knock.
- Mister, what do you sell here?
- We sell maggolli.
Oh, really? Can I have some?
No drinking for you.
What about this?
You are so pretty.
Two tickets for 10 o'clock.
We have couple's seats and regular seats.
Which would you like?
Couple's seat please.
Just a moment please.
Bong Pal, let's eat that.
Can you really eat this all by yourself?
This is nothing for me.
It feels like we're a real couple, right?
Yes.
What would you like to eat?
What you want to eat.
Excuse me.
May I take your order?
I will have Set Number Two.
Set Number Two is for two people.
Yes, I'm okay with that.
Oh, and can I have
another glass of water here?
Okay.
Here.
Aren't you doing too much today?
You took me out to the movies
and a full-course meal.
- I can handle it.
- But still...
Fine. I will exorcise more
and make you a lot of money.
They're all dead now.
Sounds good.
Wait. It's raining.
Let's run.
Hold on.
Shall we go?
Bong Pal, aren't you getting all wet?
It's okay. Let's go.
[CRIME SCENES]
Sir, are you going to question
the testifiers again?
I should do something.
The analysis team asked
me to give this to you.
Thank you.
What is it?
These are the photos from the toll gate.
Sir, you might want to see this.
The license plate matches, right?
Yes, it's Professor Joo's plate number.
Before we question the other testifiers
bring Professor Joo to the station.
- If he resists, arrest him.
- Yes, I will.
- A fountain pen?
- I gave it to Professor Joo...
On the day No Hyun Joo
was murdered, where were you?
I was at my clinic.
See you later.
Hyun Ji!
Hyun Ji. Did the power go out?
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
- Are you feeling better?
- Yes, I am.
Bong Pal.
There is something
I've been meaning to ask you.
What is it?
When did you start seeing ghosts?
Maybe when I was five...
I think it started from around then.
You were so little.
- How did it happen?
- I'm not sure.
According to Monk Myung Chul
there are still evil spirits inside me.
Evil spirits?
What are they?
I don't really know.
I don't remember much before I was five.
It must have been scary all the time.
I was at that time.
I'm okay now.
Thank you, Bong Pal.
- For what?
- For everything.
Everything seems good
when I'm with you.
When I woke up as a ghost
without any memory
I was so scared and lonely.
But not anymore.
Even if I don't get my memory back
I like how things are now.
I'm so glad that you can see me.
I'm also glad that I can see you.
Sir.
It's a photo of your car taken
at dawn on the second.
Is it your license plate number?
Yes, it's my car.
I see.
You passed the toll gate at 11:28 p.m.
You arrived at Insung at 1:38 a.m.
You took Road 34.
You got to Mount Woojung.
You came back to Seoul
early that morning.
- Do you remember?
- Yes.
I don't know if you're aware.
But No Hyun Joo's body
was found near Mount Woojung.
She was murdered
on the night of the first.
It appears her body was abandoned
in the early morning on the second.
Is it a coincidence that you
happened to be near there?
Why did you go to the mountain
in the middle of the night?
I feel like I'm a suspect.
Please answer my question.
I went to see my mother.
My mother lives in the area.
- Your mother?
- If needed, you can confirm it.
- You're good at this, huh?
- Because it's the truth.
Hello, this is Detective Kim.
Sir, can I see you quickly?
Excuse me.
What do you mean?
One of the witnesses
for the case just died.
Who is it?
His name is Lee Min Soo,
a student at Myungsung.
Phone records show that he talked
to No Hyun Joo on the 30th.
I included him on
the list for the testifiers.
It appears he jumped
from his place and killed himself.
- He committed suicide?
- Correct.
And he claimed that
he killed No Hyun Joo.
The approximate time of his death is...
right after he came back
from No's funeral.
Who are you?
I'm sorry. I killed Hyun Joo.
I didn't mean to do it.
He texted his mom
before he killed himself.
He said he killed her in the text.
No Hyun Joo's cell phone
was found in his room, too.
It seems that he was following her
around since last semester.
The boss told me to wrap up this case.
He wants us to investigate
a murder case in Woohyun.
What should we do?
Get the documents
and put them on my desk.
I will. Gosh.
You're still here. Hello there.
- Do you know the dog?
- Yes.
When you gave me a hard time,
she was there for me.
When did I give you a hard time?
Bong Pal.
Wow, it's that handsome professor.
Hello, Professor Joo.
What are you doing here?
Well, I was looking at the dog...
Were you?
Why don't you go in and look?
- We can have some tea, too.
- I want to go in.
Come on. Come inside.
You look like you're
watching your girlfriend.
- Pardon?
- Why so surprised?
You had love in your eyes.
- I guess you like dogs, huh?
- Well...
That dog is very pretty.
Ah, it's almost summer break now.
Have you completed
your volunteer hours yet?
Not yet.
Then can you help me
with the volunteer work I'm doing?
I can use some help these days.
It will fill up your volunteer hours.
What do you think?
It sounds good.
I was looking for something actually.
- Good then.
- Where are you going?
Where are you going?
Hey, puppy. Where are you?
Where did she go?
There you are.
Come here. You're so pretty.
Professor Joo.
- I will go now.
- Ah, wait a second.
When did I tell you to come in here?
It was not nice of you.
- Go upstairs first.
- I will.
[KIM HYUN JI]
- I will go now.
- Sure, take care.
Wait, that punk is...
Bong Pal. Bong Pal.
Monk Myung Chul.
Who was the man at the clinic earlier?
- Professor Joo?
- Professor?
Yes, he's a professor at my school.
Ah, then he also lives
in your apartment building?
No, it seems that he lives in his clinic.
At his clinic?
- What's wrong?
- What?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Aren't you on your way home?
- Yes.
- Let's go. It's hot.
Bong Pal.
Are you studying for the SAT?
Why do you have photos in the back?
I thought I needed to
work on foundation courses.
By the way, why didn't you call?
When have I ever called you?
What is it?
Is there something on the balcony?
Nothing. It's nothing at all.
By any chance, have you noticed
anything weird around you?
No, nothing much.
- Why?
- It's fine then.
Let me see.
I can't come out?
He can sometimes feel
the presence of ghosts.
Did he save
his dad's contact information?
He's his dad after all.
He still hasn't saved
his contact information.
One two three six?
May 13th?
If this was sent on May 13th
it's when he was still
staying at that place.
Middle school graduation?
- Bong Pal! Bong Pal!
- Yes?
When was your middle school graduation?
I think it was February...
Probably about then.
Why do you ask?
Nothing. Never mind
and get back to your things.
Hello, senior.
I will be right there.
Monk Myung Chul, I will be back.
Sure.
If it was his graduation...
Whatever happened at the graduation
that he sent such a text?
Wait, he taped the graduation.
Let me go find it.
He definitely taped
the ceremony at that time.
September, June, May... wait.
According to the Gregorian calendar,
it was February.
It was February 24th. February 24th...
Yeah, it's February 24th.
Well, they said the ghost
went to this man's body.
So stay behind Bong Pal today, Hyun Ji.
- It's dangerous.
- Okay.
Good for you that
he's looking out for you.
- Are you jealous now?
- What is Hyun Ji saying?
Are you okay?
What are you thinking about?
Sit properly!
Gosh...
Hyun Ji, are you okay?
[24TH DOO WON MIDDLE SCHOOL GRADUATION]
What do I do? No!
No! No!
No!
My brother was very ill a while ago.
Then he got well and one day,
he suddenly had a seizure.
Brother! Brother!
What's wrong? Brother!
Brother, open the door!
Are you okay?
- Brother, open the door!
- Open the door!
Since that day, he's been
lying in bed like that.
He screams like that
whenever he wakes up.
My mom thinks a ghost is inside his body.
We will go in first.
Oh my, what's wrong with this?
Gosh, no.
Please, no. No!
- Brother! Brother!
- No! No!
Brother, it's okay.
Bong Pal, look over there.
This woman is the ghost
from a few minutes ago.
So you're saying that girl
was strangling my son?
If she's dead, she should've
just gone to the other side quietly.
Why my son? Oh my.
Let's go inside.
- Oh my goodness.
- Gosh.
By the way, who is that woman?
She and my brother went out a while ago.
So what is it that you want us to do?
Once he falls back asleep like that
he doesn't wake up for two days.
He might be stable until then.
Then we will come back in two days.
- If anything happens, call us.
- I will.
My goodness...
Did he really tape anything there?
Bong Pal! Bong Pal, look here!
Smile a bit, will you?
Why was that man there?
Please take care.
- You saw that, didn't you?
- Saw what?
Didn't he make you think about something?
- No.
- No?
Your logic clearly stopped working, huh?
If you follow around a ghost,
the same thing will happen to you.
If a ghost drains your energy like that,
how can you possibly survive?
Will you be drained like
that man and live your life, huh?
A ghost and a person
are not meant to be together.
Quiet down. Hyun Ji will hear you.
You think she heard me?
Of course she did.
How could she not hear you?
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Bong Pal.
Are we going to be okay like this?
To other people...
our relationship doesn't make sense.
I like you.
I don't care what others think about us.
I like you just the way you are, Hyun Ji.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Fight Ghost]
- You're so ugly.
- Stop it.
We will also have to separate
like them some day.
Bong Pal, who are you talking to now?
This ghost was seen
here and there on campus.
But the way it looks is very peculiar.
Wait, it's the tape from my graduation.
Why was he watching this out of the blue?
You have the address
of the professor's mother, right?
Mom!
He killed the person he liked
and himself out of guilt.
How can you be in love with a ghost?
Bong Pal, I want you to be happy.
Hyun Ji!
Kim Hyun Ji!