The engine is completely burned. It's not working at all.
I'm in here! Please help me!
- Let's follow the emergency action. - Roger. Mayday. Mayday.
What is going on, seriously?
- Ki Joon! - Ji Ah!
Stay right here for a few minutes. I'll find out what's going on.
HL0079. We're in a dive!
You jerks, our plane is crashing.
Mom.
Can I stop diving?
I don't have to be a diver just because you are.
- You can quit. - Seriously?
Won't you try to convince me otherwise?
I've never wanted you to live...
the way that I do.
You should do what you want in life.
Why did you make me go in the sea when it's so cold?
You always make me catch seafood.
This is the only thing I can give you.
I don't have enough to support the rest of your life.
The least I can do is teach you how to make a living...
as a parent.
Do what you want.
If it's too difficult, you can always come back here.
I'll still be here.
Joon Oh.
Joon Oh, wake up.
Wake up, Joon Oh!
Come on, Joon Oh.
No, please wake up, Joon Oh.
Joon Oh, are you awake?
Where is everyone?
Joon Oh!
No, Joon Oh.
Please wake up, Joon Oh.
Joon Oh!
Wake up, please.
Here's some water.
No, don't drink it.
You can't drink it yet.
What is it?
Where did you come from?
Where are we?
Why can't I drink it?
Why not?
Where on earth are we?
Hey, where are we?
You seem fine enough to yell.
Wait here for a minute.
Don't touch those.
Where are you going? Hey, hey!
The plane crashed!
I seem completely fine.
Gosh, what's this?
Is... Is this the engine?
Gosh, that was hot.
Ki Joon!
Yeol, Ji Ah.
Where's my phone?
The plane just crashed.
Come on.
Darn it!
Oh, no.
My goodness.
Where are we?
(Episode 2)
According to the doctor, due to meningitis,
she has a temporary memory loss.
To retrieve her memory as soon as possible,
- I'll do anything... - Investigator Oh.
Doesn't she seem too calm?
She expresses her opinions and feelings without a problem.
It doesn't seem like she went through a traumatic experience.
She speaks very clearly.
She's way too calm.
Whether it's medication or hypnosis,
we have to take every measure possible.
Yes, Ma'am. I got it.
Let's go.
- Be careful! - Yes. I'm coming.
Hurry up and go.
Ms. Ra Bong Hee.
Gosh. Could you come with us for a minute?
Someone wants to see you.
Who is it?
- It won't take long. - Please come this way.
- What are you doing? - Come on.
- You'll find out soon. - Who are you?
- Gosh. Don't use force on her. - Let go of me.
- She's feisty. - Let me go.
What are you doing?
- Who are you? - Well... We are...
Whom should we say we are?
- I asked you who you were. - We are...
here to see the mudflat.
That's right. We heard that octopus is great for health.
We thought we'd catch some...
Bong Hee!
- Get her! - Hey!
- Stop! - Bong Hee!
Gosh.
She's there.
- Stop! - Get her!
- Go and stop her! - Sir.
Wait!
- Wait. - Hey!
My gosh. Give me my jacket!
- I told you to come right away! - That's why I'm here!
My goodness.
You punk! Come here!
- You jerk! Come here. - Who are these punks?
- What did you just do? - Gosh.
- Gosh. - Bong Hee!
No... Joon Oh!
- What happened here? - You jerk!
- Hey. Let's go. Hurry! - Run.
And?
What?
Fine.
Yes, Sir.
Here you go.
- What's going on? - What happened?
Bong Hee. Are you all right?
- Are you okay? - Is anyone hurt?
Yes.
Why did it have to be the plane I was on?
Why!
Why did you crash so easily?
You're an expensive jet!
You idiot!
Gosh. Why can't I eat them?
Goodness.
Is anyone out there?
What? Were these yours?
Give it back.
I'll buy you one later.
Give it back! I said give it back to me!
Gosh. I just drank a little water. What's wrong with you?
I told you not to drink it. This is a deserted island!
When we get out of here...
What did you just say?
This is a deserted island.
Everyone except us is dead. That's the only food we have.
What did you say? Did you say this was a deserted island?
The plane crashed, and we're the only survivors?
Did you check that side?
What about the others? Have you looked for them?
What about Ki Joon, Ji Ah, Yeol, and Tae Ho? Did you check over there?
This is a prank, right? The octopus thing must've been a part of it.
You're not a stylist, are you? You must be a new actress.
Where are the cameras?
What about the others?
What happened to the others?
They were not just celebrities.
They were my family whom I have shared joys and sorrows...
for many years.
There is...
a rumor that this accident...
is a self-fabricated scenario that our company plotted out.
I cannot believe this.
It has been revealed that Ms. Ra, the only survivor of...
- the accident came back to Korea. - As their fans, we must know...
The families of Legend Entertainment's artists...
started to demand for an investigation to find out...
the truth about the artists' survival.
At 10am today, the fans of the missing artists demanded for...
a question and answer session with Ms. Ra,
the stylist of Mr. Seo Joon Oh...
to find out the truth of the accident.
There is a possibility that they might...
distort Ms. Ra Bong Hee's memories and testimonies...
for their own profit.
According to the fan clubs' statement,
a number of...
malicious rumors have spread because there hasn't been any clear...
announcements from the authorities regarding this accident.
A deserted island.
A part of her memory came back.
They were in a deserted island somewhere.
- Here is the next news. - Are you sure?
Yes. She says she's sure.
Bring Bong Hee to the headquarter immediately.
Yes, Ma'am.
Why are you refusing to do it?
Tae Young. We got an order...
to investigate on this case directly from the executives.
If we handle it well, you and I will...
I have something else to do. I'm sorry.
Is it because of your sister?
If a wrong rumor spreads...
I won't cause any trouble. I'm working with Prosecutor Cho.
Do you think she is still alive?
- I hope so. - What if she's dead?
You're throwing away a chance for you to get ahead...
to investigate it. What are you going to do if she's dead?
I'll just have to do...
what I'm supposed to do whether she is alive or dead.
What is the thing you're supposed to do?
The truth.
I will find out the truth.
It is my job to make sure that law is never used wrongfully.
It's also your duty.
As in this case,
manipulating the truth isn't our job.
So you're saying the plane crashed like that,
and only two people survived.
I mean, Seo Joon Oh...
and you.
Yes.
Don't believe everything she says. We need accurate information.
Grill her more.
Ask her for details.
I'm not sure how this question will sound,
but how did you feel...
when you realized that you were on a deserted island?
You don't believe me, do you?
I couldn't remember anything...
about the last four months.
It must look strange that my memory came back partially all of a sudden.
It's already strange enough that I survived the plane crash.
You probably want to know whether I'm lying or not.
I know you're trying to sound me out.
Well, I'm just...
I don't really remember...
what happened to everyone.
But...
if I tell you everything I saw and felt...
to the best of my recollection,
will you believe me?
Will you believe what I tell you?
I don't know whether they're still alive or not.
I don't remember how many are alive or dead,
but will you go there to rescue them?
Then... Then I will...
do anything you want me to do...
to recover my lost memories.
So...
So please...
Don't leave them abandoned there.
We won't be going home today.
Say yes.
One day,
I was wondering why something like that happened to me.
Out of so many people,
why did it have to be me?
I resented my reality.
It's medicine for meningitis.
I thought it may help you recover your memory.
One day,
the fact...
that people died...
tortured me.
One day,
I felt grateful to be alive.
Then on another day,
the desire for survival made me...
feel all desperate.
Hey, there's a ship. I see a ship over there!
There's a ship! Here!
We're here! Gosh.
Hey. Hey!
Hey!
Here!
You're doing so great! Keep going!
- Here! - Can you swim all the way there?
- Help! - That's it. Go! Keep going!
Even in just one day,
hundreds of different feelings...
and emotions went through me.
I was hurt physically...
Gosh, what should I do?
And my heart was wounded as well.
Are you okay? Did you hurt yourself?
- Let me see. - I can't get this to work.
Like a person who received a death sentence,
I was taking a day at a time in a state of inertia.
Then I saw it.
What did you see?
Hope.
10, 15.
10, 25.
- Did you see anyone around here? - No.
He must've gotten rescued.
After 25 days.
- We can live, too! - Yes, we can live!
- We can live! - We can live!
We can live!
We can live. We can live.
- We can go home! - We can go home!
Home! Home! No matter what happens,
I will go home!
- Home! Home! - We can live!
After seeing a ray of hope right in front of my eyes,
this thought crossed my mind.
"I must survive."
"If I survive,"
"someone will come to my rescue."
Have you thought about looking for other possible survivors?
We did try to look for them, but...
Why did you come out already?
I think we've done enough for today.
Are you going to say the grass is hurting your skin again?
I'm hungry. I can't look for anyone on an empty stomach.
We ate bread in the morning.
Hey, we should live first.
No. Let's search for a bit more.
Ask her how she sustained herself for four months.
I'll be specific.
How did you survive?
There are no people,
which means there are no houses, either.
It also means that there's not a single light.
If you have to stay in a place like that for over four months,
how do you think you'll live?
You can tie it?
Be careful.
Gosh, get your jacket out of the way.
No, not that one. Tie it on the bigger tree.
- This one? - Use your fingers.
It hurts my skin.
I'll do it. Leave it.
You should've just done it yourself from the get-go.
On three! Good. That's it.
Good job.
- In 1, 2, 3. - 3.
- Push it harder. - I'm pushing it. Three!
- On 3! - 4!
Should I...
Let's do it again.
- Pull it again for me. - A little more. To that side.
To the right or left? I can't see.
Lift it more. When will you work on this side?
Plants contain water in them.
If we hit the right spot, we can get water to drip from them.
It's coming out. See?
It's working. I told you.
You were right.
We'll be able to drink it next year.
Hey, we've already been here for a few days.
We probably won't have to stay here for 25 days.
I can't do this.
I'm only going to drink this for the rest of our time here.
You can have the other two. We're good then, right?
The same goes for food. I don't eat that much.
I'll take this and...
There's too many of this, so I'll take this one, too.
Okay? Done.
Put them down.
How shall I divide it up?
The statements she gave in the last few days have been consistent.
What should we do?
Call China.
There are 143 small islands around Huizhou, China...
where Ms. Ra Bong Hee was found.
It is estimated that 97 of those 143 islands...
are uninhabited.
If they find any trace of human habitation or dead bodies,
we requested them to contact us immediately.
How long will it take?
Based on the investigation... I'm not sure, but if I...
How long will it take to search 97 islands?
We asked the experts...
to investigate as soon as possible...
Don't simply say you'll do your best...
as soon as possible.
Just give me the facts.
Actually, I...
Locating 97 islands and completing the search...
after receiving enough funds...
are expected to take at least three months.
I'll get fired in the meantime.
Where is Ra Bong Hee?
She's at her mother's house.
- Does she have bodyguards? - Yes.
Tell them to make sure that no reporters approach her.
If the public finds out about her memory loss, we'll be in trouble.
I'll tell them.
Stay in charge of the task that has to be done in the headquarter.
Keep recording the video and send it to me.
Yes?
Mr. Yoon, they found her.
Your sister was found in Huizhou, China.
However...
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry, Sir.
Where in China?
I'll come back with a lot of seafood.
What are you doing?
- Can't you tell? - It's not necessary.
If anyone passes by, they'll see it.
Here's your lunch.
Hey.
- Give me some more. - I can't.
I'm working.
- Give me some more. - What you're doing is unnecessary.
I shouldn't eat it.
Excuse me, Sir.
- Your barbecue is ready. - What?
Would you like some wine, Sir?
It's rice and pineapple.
It's pizza.
Would you like some barbecue, Sir?
- I don't really like pork. - Okay.
Here's jjamppong, Sir.
It's spicy jjamppong.
Hello.
- Byeong Joo? - Do you like shrimp?
Here you go.
Is this what you do for a living?
Thank you. It's sausage.
Is it delicious?
Is it good?
Why are you eating these now?
Have you lost your mind?
I didn't mean to.
Gosh, have you lost your mind?
- Why did you eat them now? - I didn't.
I was only eating in my dreams.
My goodness.
I burped out air.
I burped out air because I'm hungry.
I'm doing everything to survive.
I was saving these. How could you finish everything?
I said I was eating in my dreams. Why would I eat all of it?
You've lost your mind.
You're crazy for eating everything only to save yourself.
Hey!
Darn it. Listen.
Is that how you'll talk to me? Did you just call me crazy?
You're my stylist, and I'm your boss.
How dare you call your boss crazy?
Do you want to get fired?
If we get rescued like that man,
I'll send you a box of these to your house.
Be careful with your words.
Otherwise, I'll fire you. Understand?
Okay.
- Now that this happened... - Goodness.
It's because I'm sorry.
I wasn't burping. I was just apologizing.
What should we do? I ate everything.
I ate all of these.
I finished everything that we had. What will you do?
What else can we do?
We'll catch food.
Where did you come from?
Start a fire while I get some food.
I can't start a fire without a lighter.
That's why I'm asking you. I wouldn't if we had a lighter.
Start a fire, okay?
How can I start a fire?
What will you catch?
This is impossible.
Gosh, how can I start it?
I knew it was impossible.
- Where did you get it? - I found it.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to start a fire with the lens.
That's just a piece of glass. It wouldn't start a fire.
You need a convex lens. That won't work.
Why are you telling me only now? I've been trying for hours.
I just saw you do it. Start a fire somehow.
I'll come back with fish. Here are your presents.
- I can't start a fire. - Here you go.
I caught three.
Oh, my goodness! That startled me.
Goodness.
I almost caught fire.
I already set up everything.
What did you do in the past? You can do anything.
It's not that I can do anything,
it's you who can't do anything.
Can you call me by my name?
I have a name. It's Ra Bong Hee.
Okay, Ra Bong Hee.
It looks delicious.
You seem to adapt well on deserted islands.
It's a perfect place for you to live.
I can't starve myself without trying.
I survived until now, so I'll stay alive until we're rescued.
It looks delicious. Here you go.
- What? - Try it. It's ready to eat.
- Just like that? - Yes.
- I can't debone fish. - What?
I've had fish bone stuck in my throat when I was young,
so I can't debone fish.
Debone it for me.
Is there anything you can do?
Have you forgotten already?
Hey, do you want to get fired...
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
I'm starving.
You keep making me feel terrible and cheap.
It hurts me to say this, but you make me repeat...
that I have to fire you.
I'm tired of it.
Okay, I understand.
While you debone the fish,
you should eat some, too.
It's delicious to eat food while you cook.
Here you go.
You take a bite, and I take a bite.
- Isn't it delicious? - It's amazing.
Oh, my. We should've eaten things like this from the first day.
Those chips are useless.
- There's some here. - Eat this.
Drop the bone here.
Here.
I should grill all of it.
Hey, hey. Joon Oh.
- What is it? - Come outside. Hurry up.
- Come on. - Why? What's going on?
What is it? Did you find something?
- That sound. - Where?
Listen carefully.
- What is it? - Be quiet.
- You saw that, right? - I saw nothing. Let's go back in.
No, you can't.
Look at that.
My gosh.
Joon Oh, do you see that?
Joon Oh, look at that. Joon Oh...
- Joon Oh, get back here. - I'm far-sighted,
so I have to see from afar. Hold on.
- Gosh... - Don't do that.
We'll go in there on the count of three, okay?
Yeol.
Hey. Hey, Yeol.
Yeol!
There. Tie it now.
Good.
In 1, 2.
Hey, you should drink some water.
Have one more sip.
Take a big sip.
Are you up?
How's your arm?
Thanks to you, it feels much better.
I'm glad. Have a seat.
I was making some porridge.
The only things we can get here are fish and clams.
It's almost ready.
It's done. Use this as a spoon...
You can just drink it with this hand.
Thank you.
By the way,
there's something I want to ask you.
How did you not die?
Are you all right?
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
Sorry. That probably sounded weird.
That's not really what I meant.
I just want to know how you managed to survive...
and how you knew that we were here.
That's what I wanted to ask you.
After the plane crashed,
I woke up and...
I thought I was the only survivor.
I waited for a few days...
thinking that a rescue team would arrive soon.
Then I saw a light.
That was last night.
Oh, that light.
We grilled fish...
and ate it here.
Do you think people will come...
to rescue me?
We found a trace of someone with the name "Alden" over there.
I'm not sure what his nationality is,
but it looks like he was here long before we ended up here.
It seems like he got rescued after living on this island for 25 days.
That's what I think.
Bong Hee.
Have you ever thought about the possibility that we might...
die here?
There's a big chance...
that no rescue team will come...
as it stands now.
Gosh, why are you so pessimistic?
I saw him.
That Alden guy.
Are you...
serious?
If people were able to find this island...
and came here even just once,
they would've taken...
those bodies I saw as well.
Those corpses.
It's cold.
Hey, you woke up.
- Joon Oh. - Yes.
You two are so chatty. I couldn't even sleep.
Have you eaten anything yet?
Hey, that's not going to be enough.
You have to eat some fish.
We caught many fish.
Hey, let's grill a few of the leftover fish from yesterday.
Is there none left?
Right, we ate everything yesterday.
Go catch a few more fish, then.
Goodness, look at you.
You're tattering my heart to pieces again.
Hey, if you're going to keep this up,
I'll fire you when we go back to Seoul.
Fine, fire me.
Go ahead and fire me, you jerk.
Fire me.
Fire me all you want if you're lucky enough to get out of here.
But you know what?
You won't be able to leave here.
Neither of us will be able to get off this island. Do you understand?
- Hey, why... What's... - You jerk.
- Are you out of your mind? - Seriously!
- Stop, guys. - Let go.
You psycho. Make your own food...
and catch your own fish, you jerk.
- I won't eat anything. - You're unbelievable!
Joon Oh, Joon Oh!
Joon Oh, Joon Oh. Get up.
What now?
Light.
People.
It must be people.
Hey, wait! Do you even know where you're going? Gosh.
It's probably not people who came to rescue us.
Joon Oh, they could be like us. Survivors.
It means they can be people we know.
- I'll be back, okay? - Yeol, Yeol.
Hey, you don't even know where it is. You're injured. Yeol!
Yeol!
It's gone.
- Let's go closer to it. - Okay.
I think it was around here.
Let's split up.
Scream if you find anyone or if anything happens.
Okay.
Hello?
Can anyone hear me?
Help!
Bong Hee!
Help me!
I'm stuck in here!
You should've been careful.
Come on.
I have one question.
When you first saw the light,
why did you keep running without looking back?
Did you want to help the other survivors if there were any?
Is that why?
I didn't go to help.
I actually went there to get help.
If anyone was on that island,
I thought their situation would be better than ours.
I understand how you must've felt.
You're right. I would do the same thing, too.
Do you think you're on a date?
Stop talking about unnecessary things...
and ask her who the survivor was.
Yes. All right.
Now, Bong Hee.
That light from a cellphone.
You found a survivor in the face of danger.
Who was that person?
Do you remember? Do you?
It's cold.
- I just... - You startled me.
Come on.
Thank you for saving me.
You'd do the same thing for me.
Thank you anyway.
I won't forget that.
That's right. You shouldn't. Remember it forever.
- You were so... - Joon Oh!
- Yeol. - Bong Hee.
Are you okay? What happened?
- I stumbled. - You didn't get hurt, right?
I didn't. I'm okay.
You two shouldn't have...
Let's just go. It's cold.
You have to remember, Bong Hee.
Who was it?
Who was that person?
Did that person die or not afterwards?
- That's... - Do you remember that?
That person was...
- No! - Where are you going?
No!
That person was...
I'm sure it was...
I did see that person's face.
Did you see it? Who was it?
I saw the face, but...
I'm sorry.
Ji Ah!
Ji Ah.
How... How did you...
Where have you been? Why did you leave me alone?
Ji Ah. Are you hurt?
Stop crying, Ji Ah.
How did you manage to survive until now?
Have you been here by yourself? Have you?
No. I was with someone.
They found her near the seashore,
but it wasn't the plane crash that killed her.
What?
He says it seems like she was murdered.
I've been staying here since the crash.
Then I met her. She was alone.
- Why are you saying she's strange? - Just come. We're almost there.
She's been anxious. She barely eats.
Who would be okay in this situation?
She even tried to kill herself a few days ago.
Why?
She says she wants to die, and it's miserable being here.
He's asking how he's related to her.
Tell them she's his sister.
Are you okay, So Hee?
Medically speaking,
she's supposed to remember.
You're saying...
it's possible that Bong Hee is pretending not to remember...
when she actually remembers.
Is that it?
That is what I can tell you.
Medically, it doesn't make sense that she doesn't remember.
(Missing 9)
I think they were quite close on the island.
Do you understand the situation?
Do you remember who killed my sister?
People can kill others to save themselves.
You can kill again since we're on a deserted island.
It'll be shocking news if people find out that you're still alive.
- Are you sick? - It won't kill me.
You might die.
We don't know who's alive or dead, but there must be survivors.
I doubt everyone else died.
- Tae Ho? - You're still alive!
Whether we starve or get killed,
we'll die here anyway.
- So Hee is acting strange. - So Hee!
One of the missing people was Seo Joon Oh.
He has an interesting background.