Subtitles by DramaFever
[Resemblance to any historical
figures or incidents is fictitious.]
Hey, Persimmon. Is your name
Yeon Hui, by any chance?
Let's go, Yeon Hui.
I will protect you.
The person who her curse
is passed onto will fall ill
and ultimately die within half a month.
Why... is this happening to me?
- Be gone, foul creature!
- So, why did you have to be born?
Not a single person
wanted you to be born.
- No!
- You're the only one who has to die.
This is all my fault! So I'll be
the one to die, instead!
That child must live.
Such is the will of the heavens.
- We will begin anew.
- We only have 49 days left now!
I couldn't light a single candle
for six months!
Why? Why are you going
around killing those who are
associated with the Hundred-Year Tree?
They say that it's
a mistake that I'm alive
but I'm going to fight to
the bitter end to survive.
It's you... right?
Persimmon.
I must help her fulfill
her destiny, but...
I must see the princess
as soon as possible.
If you leave, you'll be able to figure
out whether or not I was right.
So the people who made wishes
all died because of me, in the end.
They died because of my curse.
Come back with me.
There is someone willing to sacrifice
their life for the Princess.
Can I not break free from this curse,
no matter how hard I try?
If his feelings do not waver despite
seeing Yeon Hui in her cursed state...
Yeon Hui!
Poong Yeon will be the final person
who'll be able to break Yeon Hui's curse.
[Episode 11]
Why did you do that?
Why, damn you!
Young Master...
Yeon Hui... where did Yeon Hui go?
What happened?
Poong Yeon!
How did you...
What about Yeon Hui?
Where is she?
Long time no see, child.
I can see you haven't forgotten me.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why did you kill those who
made wishes on the tree?
Did I not tell you that you're cursed?
If you'd just died that day, all those
people would've been perfectly fine.
Do you still not realize
that you must die?
Stop struggling. You won't be able
to use your powers in here.
Why are you doing this? What does
my curse have to do with you?
The fact that you were born
was a mistake on my part.
Therefore, I must be the one
to take your life.
What... do you mean by that?
How pitiful.
Don't be so scared.
It'll be over before you know it.
You were just a reject
who never could've dreamed of
having the throne, if not for me.
Don't be too upset, since you've
had your chance on the throne.
Leave my presence, at once!
Sir Choi? Did you cast
a soul-retaining spell on him?
Leave the palace at once.
You dare to possess the valuable
body of His Highness?
- I know all about your plans.
- And?
Are you planning to stay in there,
up until after 9 p.m.?
You're as good as dead. Your body is
only still moving thanks to black magic.
If you were to do anything rash with
that body, your entire being would rot.
- It matters not.
- Just try and endure it, then.
I've waited a long time
for this day, as well.
I won't be defeated so easily.
Is it too much for you?
If so, stop it already.
You'll really die at this rate.
Don't feign concern for me!
Sir! Sir!
Are you all right?
I'll distract them,
so you sneak in and find Yeon Hui.
I'm only asking you this because you're
her talisman. Not because I trust you.
Go!
Your Highness!
What happened?
Has Hong Joo made her move?
What about His Highness?
His Highness has followed her
into Sungsuchung!
There isn't much time.
How is Sir Choi faring?
You must have been waiting
for quite a while, Crown Prince.
All you must do now is follow
my directions. Will you do that?
Crown Prince, use that knife to
pierce through that girl's heart.
If you do, you'll be granted a new body.
What are you doing?
Hurry and stab her!
She's someone who should
have died in your stead anyway.
It's all because of her
that you ended up the way you did!
Hurry! Hurry and stab her heart!
Hurry up and do it!
What are you doing?
Stab her!
Yeon Hui!
So it was you who was
acting as her talisman.
It was you, wasn't it? The one
who's truly behind all the murders.
You must realize that facing off
against me means waging your life.
My life?
Sure, why not?
If that's how you feel, I'm sure you
won't feel miserable about being killed.
Kill him.
No!
Take Yeon Hui, and go!
Yeon Hui.
Are you all right?
What are you talking about?
How did you manage to get here in one
piece, when Yeon Hui's curse is active?
Who's the one who
has changed their mind?
I'm sure you know by now
that Yeon Hui is the princess.
And you know that the people she loves,
as well as the people who love her
are all doomed to die.
Such is her curse.
I'm sure that the choice
will be simple for you now
since you've broken free
from the curse now.
We must kill the cursed princess
for this country, and His Highness.
Will you aid me in this endeavor?
I'm sure that the real Yeon Hui
will return if I kill you.
If you kill me, the princess
will be cursed forever.
And then she'll have that
horrifying appearance forever.
Wasn't it hard for you
to see her like that?
It's not your fault. That fearsome thing
is not the girl you loved, after all.
That's why I'm saying
that we must kill her.
Shut your mouth.
I'm the only one who can
save His Highness!
If you can't believe me,
go ahead and kill me.
Just see what happens to
His Highness and the princess.
Are you awake?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt? That really
shook you up, didn't it?
You said that you'd be by my side!
You said that you were
going to stick right by me!
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I won't ever leave your side again.
I'll stick by your side, no matter what.
Are you all right, sir?
Thankfully, you didn't sustain
any serious injuries.
I'll soon recover, so there is
no need for you to worry.
What happened to Poong Yeon?
Yeon Hui's curse
is no longer affecting him?
I find that a bit odd too, sir.
But nevertheless, it's a relief
that he's safe now.
What did Hong Joo do to you, sir?
Are... are you suffering from
the effects of her black magic?
I'm only alive due to the black magic
coursing through my veins.
Seeing as my body will
not obey my commands
I don't think I have
much longer left to live.
Sir.
I will no longer be able
to use my body as I wish
once it is completely
overtaken by black magic.
And there is much that I must tell
Yeon Hui before that happens.
Yoh Gwang.
Sir. I will help you.
- Remain seated.
- I apologize.
You worked hard. Thanks to you, the
royal family has evaded a great tragedy.
However, there is no way
that Hong Joo will just give up now.
She won't give up easily, Your Highness.
That child...
is called Yeon Hui, correct?
I saw her earlier.
You said that she must break the
curse for all of this to end, correct?
Yes, Your Highness.
Are you awake, Your Highness?
What happened?
Didn't you tell me that I'd be
cured if I did as you said?
Did you deceive me?
I apologize, Your Highness.
Choi Hyun Seo's son got in the way, and
I was not able to complete the ritual.
What did you say?
How did Poong Yeon...
Shut your mouth.
How much do you trust
Royal Guard Choi Poong Yeon?
Are you trying to cause strife
between Poong Yeon and myself?
What do you mean? I merely asked
a question out of curiosity.
I merely wanted to know how
deep your trust in him is
and whether or not that trust
could be easily broken. That is all.
I hear that Sir Choi raised the princess
as if she were his own daughter.
Her name is Yeon Hui.
It seems that Sir Choi was not aware
of the fact that she was the princess.
That's probably why he never
reported this to you.
What is this place?
Go inside. There's someone inside
who wishes to meet you.
Are you... Yeon Hui?
Yes. But, um...
who may you be, ma'am?
I am... I...
I'm sure all of this is quite sudden,
but will you hear me out?
What exactly is going on?
I don't know either. She would've
had to know sooner or later, but...
but I do wonder if this is
the way it needed to be done.
But I do also wonder about what other
methods we could've use instead.
- I just... don't know.
- What?
It's nothing you need to--
What's the matter?
- Sir.
- Is she meeting with Her Highness?
Yes.
We meet again, sir.
I couldn't introduce myself properly
due to the circumstances yesterday.
I'd like to ask you something,
if you don't mind.
What is it?
That Hong Joo tried to kill Yeon Hui
last night by controlling the king.
And Hong Joo called the king
"the Crown Prince."
Is Yeon Hui's curse related
to the king, somehow?
A long time ago
I received help from Hong Joo to have
children because I was barren.
And thus, I gave birth to a pair
of beautiful twins.
However, my children had a
curse placed upon them.
They said that I could only
save one of my two children.
And so, for the sake of the royal
family, I chose the Crown Prince.
I... cast you, my own child, aside.
And yet, you're still alive and well.
What on earth are you talking about?
I believe that you've
mistaken me for someone else.
I'm a mother who does not even
have the right to plead for forgiveness.
I shoulder the blame.
All of it.
W-why are you acting this way?
It's okay if you hate me and curse me.
It's okay if you do not acknowledge
me as your mother, either.
But please... break this curse.
Last night, Hong Joo attempted
to kill you with the Crown Prince's soul
in order to spread your curse
to the rest of the royal family.
It's all my fault. It's my fault
for using black magic!
It's because of my crime that my
children have been made to suffer!
I... have no idea what
you're talking about.
That shamaness told me that it was due
to a mistake on her part I was born.
Was that... really true?
Hong Joo will try to kill you again.
We cannot allow Hong Joo
to sully the royal family any longer.
Princess. You're the only one
who can save us.
I'll help you in any way I can,
so please...
help your older brother
escape Hong Joo's clutches.
Please, save the royal family!
My child!
Do not call me that.
Father!
Father! I missed you.
I missed you so much!
The person in there has been
saying strange things to me.
She said that she was my mother,
and called me "Princess."
She said that everything
was her fault...
and that I'm the result
of someone's mistake.
What did she do wrong?
Just who am I, exactly?
Father.
- Father!
- Princess.
I, Choi Hyun Seo, would like
to formally greet you.
I locked you away in the Black Forest
in order to protect you from the curse.
Father! Please, don't be like this!
It's all my fault.
Please, don't be like this.
I'm sure that it will be difficult, but
you must accept these facts as truth.
The only one who can face Hong Joo
and break the curse on this land
is you alone, Princess.
Please, stop.
I'm sorry that you had
to find out this way.
Hong Joo is the one behind the
Red Gentleman's Robe killings.
She's been killing innocent people,
while trying to deceive you.
We must arrest her immediately
and confine her.
Hong Joo told me to keep you
at arm's length
and now you're telling me
to do the same with her.
Your Highness!
I trust you. Do you think
I'd trust her over you?
Poong Yeon.
I cherish you. And I believe
in your loyalty to me.
I believe in your deep
affections for me.
I no longer wish to fall for
Hong Joo's deceptions.
The princess's name...
is Yeon Hui, eh?
If you've found the princess,
bring her before me by tomorrow.
Please do not break my trust in you.
Why here, of all places?
I want to ask my older brother.
I can't bring myself to believe
what that woman and Father told me.
And what if he confirms what they said?
Will you believe it?
I'd like it if my older brother
would tell me that this was all a lie.
Just what is a mother?
I'm not so sure.
Just what is a mother, anyway?
When I was young...
I'd come home crying after I was
teased by the neighborhood kids.
And when that happened, my mother
would take my hand and hold it tight.
Her hands were so warm.
It made me feel so much better.
I think that all the mothers
in this world are similar.
So... don't be too sad.
She said that she cast me aside.
Because I was cursed.
Why should I see her?
Who even am I?
I don't even know who I really am.
The you that I met in the
Black Forest that day
and the you that I met once more...
and... the you that's in
front of me right now
are all just Yeon Hui to me.
Whether you're cursed,
or have black or white hair
or are a princess,
or not...
you'll always be just Yeon Hui to me.
Where have you been?
You've been gone for quite some time.
I was... going around
looking for you, sir.
You went missing all of a sudden, so...
- Many things have happened.
- Where are you going?
I must meet Yeon Hui.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I apologize, ma'am.
Is your heart being swayed
by Young Master Poong Yeon?
No, ma'am. It's just that he's quite
a formidable opponent, so I hesitated.
I hear that hesitation is akin
to death for a warrior.
But if you hesitated because your
opponent was Young Master Poong Yeon
I can make him disappear for you.
He will definitely
meet with the princess again.
Didn't you tell me to get close to him
so that I could find the princess?
This time, I will definitely find out
where the princess is hiding.
Please give me the opportunity to do so.
Heed this: there is nothing more
destructive than your own feelings.
Please, don't go.
Can't you just not go?
Oh, I apologize.
It's just that you don't look well.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Are you all right, sir?
That man named Heo Joon...
is he close to Yeon Hui?
A curse seal has appeared on Mr. Heo.
He's been afflicted?
I guess it's not affecting him though,
since he's a human talisman.
So he's able to protect himself,
as well?
You were pursuing the Red Gentleman's
Cloak before, were you not?
Did you find them, by any chance?
I'm saying this because I really
must capture that person, too.
But if you've found any clues,
please tell me! I'll help you!
- Oh, are you hurt?
- I have nothing to tell you
so please shut that mouth of yours.
You're quite a nuisance.
Is your body free of any scars?
And what about your heart?
Older Brother. Did you know
who I really was this whole time?
I only just found out.
What do I do now?
I want to live as Father's daughter,
and as your younger sister.
Nothing will change between us.
Yeon Hui. I'll stay by your side,
as I did before.
Many people have died
because of my curse.
And you could end up getting hurt, too.
I don't care about the curse.
Come away with me. I'll find a place
like the Black Forest for you to live in.
All you have to do is live hidden
away in there, like you did before!
I'll stay by your side
and protect you.
I have something that I must show you.
Come with me.
This is Chungbing Temple,
where I currently live.
I've been living here this entire time,
trying to light all of these candles.
All this in order to break the curse
and be with you and Father again.
I'll help you to break this curse.
I'll be by your side and help you
so that you don't ever have to take
on such a horrifying form ever again.
Older Brother!
The me who takes
on such a horrifying form...
and the me in front of you
right now... are both me.
I'm sorry, Yeon Hui.
I'm quite tired today.
I must be heading back now.
Older Brother, please!
Older Brother.
That ghastly form is not really you.
I'll be in touch.
Why are you drinking so much,
when you have such low tolerance?
Seol Gae. It seems that
I've hurt Yeon Hui again.
I told her that I'd protect her,
but I'm not doing anything.
Sir.
The king told me
to bring Yeon Hui to him.
How could fate be so cruel?
How could I possibly kill Yeon Hui
with my own two hands?
But... do you know what makes me
even more miserable than that?
I worry that I may lose Yeon Hui, and
yet I'm seriously considering doing it.
I'm worrying what I must do away with
Yeon Hui, for the sake of the king.
I loathe myself for being this way.
I hate the fact that I'm trying to run
away with Yeon Hui because of all this.
Get up.
I told you to get up already!
How long will you stay like that?
You can only feign illness
for so long, you know.
If you don't want to get fired,
hurry and head out!
I don't want to.
Just leave me alone!
- You terrible lout!
- "Terrible lout?"
Stop it with that, already!
This is all your fault, you know!
Obviously I seem like a terrible lout,
when you compare me to Joon.
If you couldn't give me
an attractive face
you should've at least
given me a decent brain!
Father did nothing wrong!
This is all your fault!
Stop saying things befitting
terrible louts, and eat already!
Do you even know what this is?
This is Hanwoo beef, which is
served to the king himself!
I sent some to him so that
he would not forget about you.
You are indeed the one who
caught the fake Red Gentleman's Cloak
but it's the king who closed the case
without properly investigating it.
The king may be a useful asset
to you, so you needn't worry!
Do you really think
that he'll take my side?
If Joon finds out the truth, I'm
sure he'll blame me for all of this.
That's why you must move up higher,
so that he can't treat you lightly!
That's what "Man In Ji Sang" means,
after all.
It means a person who
stands above many others.
The higher you climb, the more
authority you'll have over people!
And then, you'll be able to take
care of Joon without lifting a pinky.
All right.
There's nothing better for reinvigorating
someone than this Hanwoo beef
so eat a lot of it,
and regain your strength.
And then, go to the palace.
Here you are.
Your mother will do all that she can
so you must do whatever it takes to get
into the king's good graces, all right?
Make sure you chew it properly.
Poong Yeon!
What's going on?
Why didn't you tell me?
If you'd just told me, I never would've
taken Yeon Hui out of the Black Forest.
If I just hadn't done that, I never
would've hurt Yeon Hui like this.
Why did you do that?
Why, pray tell?
I'm sure that you're facing
much inner turmoil right now.
I know. Who could I
possibly blame for this?
This is all my fault. It's all my fault.
Father. What do I do now?
It will be fine, as long as your
feelings do not change.
My feelings have not changed.
My heart still belongs to Yeon Hui.
She's the only woman
that I've ever loved.
But that woman suddenly
changed into someone else.
So how could I accept that so readily?
Yeon Hui hasn't changed.
She's just fallen into danger.
You must protect her,
as her older brother!
Older brother? No! I refuse! I will no
longer take on such a role in her life!
Poong Yeon! What would have changed
if you did know about her curse?
If you can't accept it now, I'm sure
you couldn't have accepted it before!
Poong Yeon. As your father,
I don't want to see you get hurt.
But I hope that you will do your
utmost to protect this country.
This is what you must do,
even at the cost of your own life.
That's what I wish from you.
You must protect the princess.
And if you can't do it as a man,
do it as her older brother.
No!
I don't care whether she's
a princess, or a monster!
I'll get the Yeon Hui that I love back.
- Sir Monk!
- Seo Ri. Run!
Seo Ri!
How did you...
So this is where you were,
lighting these candles?
You want to try and
break the curse, eh?
You're not even aware of all the people
who are dying because of these candles.
Do you remember the curse?
Everyone will die because of you.
And now, he'll die
now because of you, too.
Mr. Heo!
Die. Die!
Die, you bitch!
Die!
[Mirror of the Witch]
In the end, it was
because of my curse.
This is the last thing I can do.
If Yeon Hui can't break the curse,
he'll fall ill for 15 days before dying.
- Please, don't go.
- Keep Heo Joon here
and watch over them.
The child who clung to your every
word no longer exists in this world.
If you drink this, Heo Joon,
you can save yourself.
Who is the one who has
forsaken your love?
- Say it again.
- I will mix our blood
and now, the two of us will be
together until we die.
The princess must not be captured,
for the sake of this country.
Chase after them, and
find your younger sister.
Have you hidden Heo Joon?
I'll come to the palace.