Subtitles by DramaFever
[Resemblance to any historical
figures or incidents is fictitious.]
Mr. Heo!
Die. Die!
Die, you bitch!
Die!
Your black magic
will be the death of you.
Your body will be torn to shreds
and fed to dogs!
And you'll die thusly,
without leaving behind a trace!
If you kill me, you'll never
be able to break your curse.
I don't care.
Your existence is curse enough!
A disgusting, evil curse that
just won't get away from me!
So, please, die!
I'll make you disappear so that you'll
never be able to pester me again.
I'll kill you.
No, Seo Ri!
You can't commit murder!
If you kill this woman,
all of the candles will go out.
Let's just take care
of Mr. Heo first, okay? Seo Ri!
Let's take care of Mr. Heo first.
Seo Ri.
What are you all doing?
Pursue the princess!
[Episode 12]
I'll grant you a leave,
so go to the princess right away.
What is the matter,
Your Highness?
Last night, Hong Joo left the
palace with her warriors.
Surely, the princess must be in danger!
What do you mean, the princess?
Who just said that?
What brings you here,
Your Highness?
I was taking a stroll, when I saw
you hurrying somewhere.
I grew worried, so I followed you.
Is something going on?
And what do you mean
by "the princess?"
Is there another princess besides
the one that I'm aware of?
Of course we should
have a princess, if anything.
You don't have an heir, after all.
I was talking with Sir Choi
regarding an heir to the throne.
And you're telling me that
that's what had you in such a frenzy?
What could be more important
or urgent than that?
There are some who say that we may
need to bring in a branch family member.
You're always talking
about a damned heir.
That's all you can talk about,
even when I'm as ill as I am?
Your greed knows no bounds.
Your Highness, please do not worry.
You are fated to have many heirs,
so once you make a complete recovery
you will soon be able to see an heir.
I will prepare an offering for the
strengthening of his constitution.
Oh, really?
What a great thing to hear.
Sungsuchung and the Imperial Taoists
are going to such great lengths for me
so how is it that my affliction
only grows worse, day after day?
It's a disease that even the
royal doctor could not cure.
So how could you expect it to get
miraculously better overnight?
Tell me, Chief of the
Imperial Taoist Branch.
Is the reason that Sungsuchung's Chief
Shamaness's prayers have been futile
because her intellect is lacking?
Or is there another reason for this?
You know. Ill intentions,
sabotage, or something like that.
According to what the
heavens have told me
the one who has brought all this
calamity to our land is Hong Joo.
It's because you've turned away
from everyone else's council but hers
that your once-faithful
subjects are now leaving you.
Therefore, I will rid her
from this palace.
Such are the sentiments that my
heartfelt prayers will be based upon.
Poong Yeon sure does take
after you in many ways.
However, if what you said just now
was not merely advice to me
it would be no different than a
direct attack toward me, the king.
Furthermore, if you are
trying to stab me in the back...
Queen Shim, who is standing behind me,
will have to pay the price as well.
This death is your fault
this time around, as well.
I think we've managed
to lose her warriors.
How is Mr. Heo doing?
He won't open his eyes.
She only broke the holy seal
on him with black magic
so I'm sure that he'll be fine.
He'll definitely awaken.
This is all because of my curse.
It's all because of my curse
that Joon is dead.
I never should have
given him my heart.
It's all because of this
forsaken heart of mine!
Sir Monk. Please go to my father
and ask him to find us another talisman.
You're in grave danger right now because
you don't have a talisman with you.
Will you be all right on your own?
- That doesn't matter.
- All right, then.
I'll be back.
Are you all right?
Let me examine you.
Why didn't you chase after the princess?
You were gravely injured, so--
If you really had my best interest
in mind, you should've pursued her.
My body acted before I could
think things over properly.
I offer you my deepest apologies.
Where are you planning to go,
with your body in that state?
She didn't seem to have gotten very far.
I must go and search for her myself.
Chief Shamaness!
It seems that the king
knows about the princess.
If you send soldiers hastily, the entire
country may find out about the princess.
Please head back for now, Your Highness.
I'll do my best to deal
with this situation.
I'm sure that the king will use
the princess to pressure me.
The princess must not be captured.
For her sake, and the country's sake.
Sir!
I don't know how Hong Joo found
out about Chungbing Temple.
She stabbed Mr. Heo, and the
holy seal on him was broken!
Hong Joo sustained some injuries as well
but I'm sure she'll be pursuing
us again soon enough.
What do we do now?
The curse has spread to Mr. Heo,
and Yeon Hui is alone right now.
Sir. We must make haste. Quickly!
Take Yeon Hui and stay hidden
for as long as you can.
What? You're not coming with me?
The talisman is our first priority. I'll
have to find a way to create a new one.
What are you doing?
You can't. It's dangerous!
This is the only method we have left.
Are you not aware of your
body's current condition?
You're dying right now!
This is the only thing left
that I can do.
I'll proceed with this as soon as
I regain some of my strength
so stay on the move
with Yeon Hui until then.
Sir!
Go to Poong Yeon and ask for his aid.
There's someone that Mr. Heo
knows in Banchon.
I'll take Yeon Hui there first.
Yoh Gwang.
Bring me the Oblivion Potion.
What?
Heo Joon.
Don't go. Please.
Please, don't go.
Mr. Heo!
What happened with the talisman?
Sir Choi is searching for
a method right now.
But until then, we must remain
on the move. So let's hurry.
Come to your senses, Mr. Heo!
Hurry and get up!
We must hurry, as well.
Is that man named Heo Joon
close to Yeon Hui?
A cursed seal has appeared on Mr. Heo.
- Where's the person looking for me?
- Over in that room.
They seem like weird people, though.
We can't take them in, okay?
- Okay.
- Sheesh! Hurry up!
So what's this urgent matter
you mentioned?
Huh? What's with him?
What happens when one
falls prey to the curse?
If Yeon Hui cannot break the curse
he will be ill for half a month,
before succumbing to death.
Is that the true nature
of Yeon Hui's curse?
Her curse is to be forced to watch
helplessly as her loved one dies.
You were only safe before
because Yeon Hui was within the
holy confines of Chungbing Temple.
Is there no other safe place
than Chungbing Temple?
Not that I know of.
It was difficult enough for us
to even find Chungbing Temple.
It'll be too difficult to continue
fleeing if Heo Joon is with you.
Leave Heo Joon here.
I'll accompany you.
But even so, leaving behind
a sick person is a bit...
He can barely walk properly.
Taking him with us will put
Yeon Hui in greater danger.
I guess it cannot be helped, then.
We can't let Yeon Hui
get injured, after all.
Seo Ri!
Abracadabra... ahh!
Abracadabra!
Hey, you! If you're a ghost,
leave immediately
and if you're Heo Joon,
get up right now!
What's this?
Can you look into that symbol for me?
I think it's a symbol letting one know
one's affiliations, or something.
I don't need your help,
Older Brother.
So please leave.
Are you acting this way because
I proposed that he be left behind?
Older Brother. If you're doing
this out of concern for me...
please don't.
Is that man that important to you?
Is he so important to you that
you'd cast me aside like this?
Just what was I to you, then?
The older brother that I dearly miss...
is one who'd understand me
when I was upset.
He was kind, and told me that everyone
had a reason for being born.
The Yeon Hui that I so desperately
searched for, for five years
was a kind girl who always trusted me,
and always held my hand.
No. What you missed was a
foolish girl who was ignorant
of everything outside of the Black
Forest, and clung to your every word.
But that girl no longer exists.
The reason you became this way
is all because of that damned curse.
I will restore you to who you once were
even if I must kill everyone
who made you this way.
Have you awakened, ma'am?
What brings you all the way here?
If you refuse me,
I will have your head.
Tell me, how can I restore Yeon Hui
to the way she once was?
- Please, have a seat.
- You brought the curse upon her.
I don't care about the curse, though.
All you have to do is revert her
to the way she once was.
I really love the look in your eyes.
The one who inflicted pain on one's
heart does not know how that pain feels.
Nor do they realize how
cruel they'd been.
You insolent wench!
Don't you go mouthing off as you wish!
Do you think that her heart will revert
to the way it was if you kill me?
Who knows? Her heart may never
have been yours to begin with.
Your disgusting magic
has ruined everything.
The fact that Yeon Hui has changed,
and the king is in his current state
is all due to your evil
black magic, is it not?
I only learned how to use this evil
black magic due to your father.
You didn't know that I was his disciple?
Stop spouting nonsense.
I was a mere court lady.
I faced many hardships, and Sir Choi
was the only one I could depend on.
Hong Joo!
What happened?
They tried to kill me.
They dragged me away, and tried to
make me have the king's heir by force
and tried to kill me when things
didn't go the way they'd planned.
There's no way that
I'll just let this slide.
I will definitely make
them pay for this!
I understand how upset you must feel.
But you must cast aside your
hatred to live your life in peace.
How could you possibly say that to me?
I'm neither a virgin, nor a
proper human being anymore.
Hong Joo. You're quite a talented child.
But if you harbor grudges,
your powers may become twisted.
I'll help you, so let's begin anew.
You need a lot of mental and physical
energy to create a holy talisman.
Furthermore, you must pour
your life energy into making it
so it may be difficult for
you to recover afterwards.
Isn't it quite dangerous to do, then?
Must I really learn such things?
Hong Joo. You must use magic
for the greater good.
You must be willing to throw everything
away if it's for the greater good.
What did I just say?
"You must be willing to throw everything
away if it's for the greater good."
But I don't know why
I must learn such things.
I'm learning these things
in order to protect myself
and so that I won't have
anything else taken from me.
You must cast aside that greed
and self-serving attitude!
Aren't I learning all of this
so that I can become greater?
Hate. Rage. Jealously. These are
dangerous for a shaman to feel.
If you're harboring such feelings,
quit learning from me immediately.
If one can quell such terrible
feelings, and learn magic
can one gain the power to win
someone's heart, as well?
If you must win them over with magic,
they are not true affections.
They took everything from you.
And they've made it so that you
can never have anything ever again.
I didn't learn black magic
from Sir Choi
but he stopped me out of guilt,
since I was once his pupil.
And that's how I ended up this way.
The sadness that you're
feeling right now
and your despair, that is
even deeper than your sadness...
it's not your fault at all
that you're feeling such emotions.
You're merely paying for
your father's mistake.
And who is the one who
forsook your love?
It is the fault of those
who have wronged you.
So hate those people, instead.
Channel your rage toward them.
All you must do is forget.
I'm only telling you these things
with your best interest in mind.
This is the only way
you can survive.
If it's all Father's fault,
I'll make things right on his behalf.
So don't you ever go spouting your
nonsense at me, ever again.
You'll be asking me for help,
sooner or later.
Let me ask you this, as the
captain of the royal guard.
Why did you save the princess?
Answer me.
This is an order.
What is it that you heard?
Let me ask you this,
as your son.
Why couldn't you stop Hong Joo?
Why did you let her live
when she uses black magic?
I believed that I could
make her good again.
I wished for Hong Joo to forsake
her sinful life, since she was my pupil.
Did you trust her?
If you truly are the one who caused this
curse, I must charge you with that crime.
Answer me!
If you pose any sort of
danger to Yeon Hui
what must I do, then?
Isn't it only natural that
I cannot trust you
if you're still compassionate
toward her?
Do not trust me.
You're right. The reason why Yeon Hui
was cursed is because I let Hong Joo go.
And the reason why you cannot accept
Yeon Hui is because I deceived you.
No... do not trust me.
I'm going to break Yeon Hui's
curse for her.
- What did you just say?
- I cannot do as you command.
You're saying that you cannot
bring the princess before me?
Poong Yeon!
Didn't you say that you'd
lay down your life for me?
I will receive the punishment for
not heeding your command
and my father's crime
of letting the princess live.
Please, do not forgive me
of these crimes.
Say that again.
Say it again, damn you!
You are no longer the
captain of the royal guard.
And you are no longer
my cherished friend, either.
Leave. And do not ever show
your face in the palace again.
Please strengthen your resolve,
and please take care of your health.
Evil spirits, begone!
What are you doing in
front of someone else's room?
- Hey, what are you doing? Sheesh!
- Be still!
- Evil spirits, begone!
- What are you talking about?
That guy is possessed by spirits,
so why is this one fine?
He's not possessed.
He's just--
They're just a bit ill
right now, is all.
Ill? What kind of illness
could they have?
Listen. There are so many
criminals in Banchon
that you'll be kicked out of here
immediately if you seem even a bit off.
But you people are
just way too strange!
Heo Joon is on the run for a
crime that he didn't commit...
But... what's up
with you two? Huh?
We're being pursued, and by
really scary people, at that.
So please, help us out a bit
so that we can leave here safely!
I'm begging you.
Hey, what are you doing?
Geez, just from the looks of you--
Stop it, already!
Let go!
- Why, you little--
- You creep!
- When did I ever--
- Let go!
Why, you -- ow!
Hey! Hey!
- Oh, you're here, sir?
- Where is Heo Joon?
- He's in this room.
- Did you bring what I asked for?
This is the Oblivion Potion.
I'm sure you're better aware
of what this is than I am.
If you drink this, you'll lose all your
memories regarding Yeon Hui
and it'll save your life.
This is the only way you can survive.
Are you telling me to run away
like a coward?
If you die, Yeon Hui will be left to
shoulder all the misery alone.
This isn't completely for your sake.
It's for Yeon Hui's sake, too.
I'm sorry, but these memories are a
precious gift to me from Yeon Hui.
I cannot forget her.
I'll survive somehow,
and protect her no matter what.
Those feelings must
be strong enough
for you to be able to sacrifice
yourself for her in the end.
You must be the one to
light the 108th candle.
Father.
- Please, don't do that.
- Hong Joo will make her move soon.
Please move to another place
as soon as you can.
What about the talisman?
I'll make you one while
you flee from Hong Joo.
Is there a safe place for us to go?
Won't Hong Joo chase me
no matter where I go?
I will write a letter to Queen Shim,
so please deliver it to her.
Is this what the princess wants?
- Yes, Your Highness.
- Will this be all right?
Won't it be too dangerous?
I also believe that this is the
best measure for her to take.
Well, this is a request that she
has made, so I must help her.
I'll leave the rest to you.
This is improper behavior
for a lady, you know.
Looks like you're only able to hold
back because you're such a manly man.
Hurry and break the curse, and save me.
Don't ever let go of this
hand, all right?
Because I have no intention
of letting go, either.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
There really is no place left
for me to return to anymore.
Is it because of me?
No, it's so that I can live.
And so that I can figure out
who I am, and where I can go.
We're already on the same side.
I have to catch
the Red Gentleman's Robe
and you have to catch the woman
controlling that murderer.
We're on the same side, so
we have common enemies, huh?
Since we're on the same side,
I'll let you be our side's leader.
You intimidate me a little, you see.
So I'm willing to be
really obedient to you.
Don't worry about me, and go.
Just don't get hurt.
I'll come and find you.
We'll definitely meet again. For sure.
Eunuch Kim.
Eunuch Kim!
You called for me, Your Highness?
Bring me the one who was promoted due
to the Red Gentleman's Robe incident.
If you're one of my men, I'm sure you're
ready to cast your life aside for me.
Of course, Your Highness!
Then I'm sure that you won't have
any qualms even if I beheaded you.
Um, why, exactly...
You dared to lie to me
about the Red Gentleman's Robe?
I... I really knew nothing about that!
They looked similar to me, so -- ahh!
I really did not know
that the body was a fake!
Please kill me, Your Highness!
Since you asked me to kill you,
I'll go ahead and do it.
But if you were to give your
life to me, and do as I say
I may revisit my decision.
So, what will you do?
I'll do anything you command
me to, Your Highness!
Chase Choi Poong Yeon,
and bring me his sister.
His... sister?
She's his treasured little sister.
He refused to bring her to me,
so I must force her here.
I think I know a way.
How about making a royal decree?
Just do as I've commanded,
and bring her here.
Yes, sir! I will bring that
girl to you without fail!
What will you do now?
I've lost the king's favor
for Yeon Hui's sake.
I have no intention
of evading her anymore.
How did you get a palanquin?
Um, that is...
I'll have a look around
the surrounding area.
All right.
Yeon Hui!
No! No!
Mr. Heo!
Are you hurt?
It's not my blood.
I've lost them. I think they know
she's here, so hurry and go.
I heard everything from Sir Monk. I'll
watch over this man, so hurry and go.
Let's hurry.
We don't have time.
Stop it!
Don't do it.
What's this?
Huh?
Chase after that palanquin!
The princess is in there!
Yes, ma'am!
Move out of the way!
It's the Queen!
Move aside.
What brings you outside of the temple?
Have you hidden the princess?
The princess? Are you talking about the
princess you told me was dead?
Are you planning to oppose me once more?
Have I not acquiesced to you?
Couldn't you tell that from
the fact that I spared you
even though you lied about
the princess being dead?
It seems that I've been keeping you.
Please, be on your way.
I'm in no rush.
Seeing my son reminded me of my
husband, so I'm going to visit his grave.
Would you like to join me?
I have an urgent matter to look into.
Is it important enough that you'd
dare to reject my invitation?
They're matters that have
to do with Sungsuchung.
They're important to me, but not
important enough for you to know about.
Is that right? Eunuch Park.
Let's get going.
Move out of the way!
It's the Queen!
I'll go to the palace.
What do you mean by that?
There are some instances where
the most dangerous place
can also end up being
the safest place.
I cannot live on the run any longer.
I must make it so that they
can never pursue me again.
Please listen to me carefully.
When I became the Head
of the Imperial Taoist Branch
I did it with a resolve to protect
the country at all costs.
And the reason I'm creating
a talisman for you
is due to that resolve.
So even if I die, you must not
be shaken by feelings of guilt.
What are you saying?
If you must risk your life to craft a
talisman, Father, I have no need for it.
I'm letting you know in advance because
the work I'm doing is dangerous.
Be not afraid, Your Highness
and go to the Queen right away
as soon as you get a talisman.
She will most certainly
lend you her aid.
Father.
I feel relieved now that I see
how brave you've become.
Where is the princess?
It's "Her Highness, the Princess."
Do not speak so insolently.
You risked your life
for such a futile cause?
I have no regrets.
You wouldn't understand
because you've never risked
your life to protect someone.
Did I not tell you that this
would cost you your life?
Give me your hand.
I will save you.
I'd prefer it if you killed me instead.
I guess I'm fated to watch you die.
I regret... ever letting you live.
You've heard of "hyulmyung," right?
It means, "blood-bound fate."
From now on...
we'll be one until we die.
They say that this symbol is that
of the Amsagol Homeless Girls.
I checked them out, and this symbol
was on a lot of girls' shoulders.
You're sure that they
were women, right?
They only capture girls,
and mistreat them
and sell them to brothels
when they get older. Bastards.
So, what are you going to do now?
My suspicions have been confirmed,
so I have to check for myself now...
whether or not the one
who figured out our location
at Chungbing Temple and Banchon...
may actually be a woman.
Oh!
What are you doing?
I came here to thank you personally.
You know, it really took a lot
of effort to find this place!
Here's a gift for you.
You hurt your arm, didn't you? I used
to be beat up a lot when I was younger
so I know how to make the most
effective salves for injuries.
I was going to make you some before, but
we were attacked at Chungbing Temple.
Anyway, sorry for the delay.
Here.
I don't need this.
Look here. I know you're injured,
so I can't just let you get it infected.
Are you all right, sir?
Sir.
Where is the princess?
Take me to her.
Sir!
I'm sure that the princess
will have left the palace by now.
If we can't find her,
we'll have to drag her out.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Mirror of the Witch]
It was due to a mistake on my
part that you were born.
That terrifying version of you
is not really you.
Please, save the royal family!
My child!
Father! Who am I, exactly?
This is all because of the curse.
I'll break it, for sure.
- It's a curse wherein...
- Please... please, don't go!
you must watch the person
you love die before you.
This is the only way
that you can survive.
I can't forget about Yeon Hui.
I'll protect her, for sure.
I can no longer live
my life on the run.
I'll go to the palace.