Subtitles by DramaFever
[Resemblance to any historical
figures or incidents is fictitious.]
[Episode 13]
Are you happy to see me?
Of course. You know how long
I've searched for you.
Have you come to meet your brother?
That's my brother?
You shouldn't be so callous. He ended
up like that because of you, after all.
What you do is so detestable that
I can no longer bear to sit and watch.
Oh my. So you're
killing your brother after all.
The Queen will be saddened
to know what you've done.
If one of us must die...
shouldn't I be the one to live, since
I'm the one who's actually alive?
Stop this nonsense
and give that back right now.
I created you two. Thus, I'll be the
one to decide who lives and who dies.
I'm sure you'll try to use
the king to try and kill me again.
Do you know how many people
have died due to your horrific acts?
Just go ahead and do it, then.
Do you think I won't be able to kill you
just because the Crown Prince is gone?
Then...
I'll just see for myself
whether or not using this
is the only way you could kill me.
Where is the princess?
Take me to her.
Sir!
Sir! Sir!
Sir! Please snap out of it!
You're already back
from the memorial site?
I changed my mind, so I came back.
Did you call the princess to the palace?
And if I did?
You'll have to hide her well.
I searched all of Joseon to find her.
So finding her in the palace
will be a simple feat.
The princess is in the palace.
- Are you sure about this?
- I'm sure that the Queen has her.
The Queen, eh?
She may have found out that we intend
to use her as a sacrifice to heal you.
And so, she decided to
hide her within the palace.
She will try to meddle with my affairs,
so we must capture her before then.
How nice of her to walk right in
here, on her own two feet.
I really wish to see the princess.
Hurry and bring her to me.
I don't think that the Queen will easily
relinquish her hold on the Princess
so I'll have to hunt for her.
Hunt, eh?
If you'd just grant me permission
and means to do so within the palace
I'll capture her for you.
No. The hunt is more thrilling
to partake in than to watch.
I'll be the one doing the hunting.
- Then, I'll do the spectating.
- All right.
It'd be best to perform funeral rites on
the Crown Prince as soon as possible.
I will ask Father... no, Mr. Choi,
about how we can perform the rites.
We can take our time.
Just... let me be with him
for a bit longer.
Then, I'll wait until you're ready.
No. I'm sure that Hong Joo is already
devising a plot to capture you.
I'm not sure if we can complete the
rites safely with her on the loose.
There's something you must do, Queen.
Great job. Where is the princess--
Your body and soul are both mine now!
You shouldn't be able to move
or think of your own free will!
Look at me.
Please don't despair.
You're fine now, aren't you? You need
to just stay the way you are now.
I'll help you.
I wish to live as a person.
There is much you must do for me.
- Um, about before, at Banchon--
- No need for thanks.
I did it for Yeon Hui.
Even so, I'm thankful.
Thank you.
- If that's all, leave now.
- No, I'm not done.
On the day you came to Banchon,
did you come with your guard?
You know, the woman named Sol Gae?
I did. So what?
I was just wondering if you two
always travel together.
That's none of your business.
She seems like a faithful warrior.
Since when has she been with you?
What is it that you really wish to know?
Just how deep her loyalty to you is.
How much do you trust that Sol Gae?
She's my right-hand woman, and my sword.
In other words,
I trust her with my life.
Since I've answered your question,
tell me why you've asked me this.
I asked you this because the king is
searching for the Red Gentleman's Robe.
If I catch the Red Gentleman's Robe,
what would you do?
I am no longer the
captain of the royal guard.
However, if it's for His Highness
and Yeon Hui
I will help you discover who
the Red Gentleman's Robe is.
There is someone I suspect
may be the Red Gentleman's Robe.
When I am certain that it is them,
I'll tell you who it is.
- Sir.
- What brings you here?
There's nothing for you to do, so go get
some rest at home until I call for you.
Your face...
You have a fever.
Are you ill?
No, sir. It's because it's hot outside.
I'll follow you even if there's
nothing for me to do, sir.
No, there's no need for that.
Red Gentleman's Robe.
If I manage to catch them as I said,
I'll hand them over to you.
So, um, the ex-captain Choi Poon Yeon
met with his younger sister
and I pursued them.
But she got into a palanquin
and disappeared, so...
there was someone I knew next to
her, too, so I watched him closely
but he disappeared, too...
Your Highness!
Out of my utmost loyalty for you,
I searched every nook and cranny I could
but they're nowhere to be found,
Your Highness!
Never mind.
Excuse me?
Thank you for your unending grace,
Your Highness!
So you're telling me that you know what
Poong Yeon's sister looks like, correct?
Yes. I saw her myself!
She has a coldness about her face,
but she has a great body
and she has shining, doe-like eyes!
Yes.
You really got a good
look at her, didn't you?
Well, I've had a knack for noticing
details since I was young--
There is something
that you must do for me.
Yes, Your Highness?
It's something that you
have a real talent for.
- Your Highness.
- What is it?
The ex-captain, Choi Poong Yeon,
has requested an audience with you.
What is the reason
that you've come to see me?
I have something to ask
of you, Your Highness.
What is it?
I know that Yeon Hui is in the palace.
I've bought clothes for her to wear,
and I'd like to give them to her myself.
Ah, I did hear that you two
parted without a proper farewell.
However, Yeon Hui cannot meet you now,
so leave this here and go.
I'll pass this along to her.
Your Highness, there is someone who
is after Yeon Hui's life in the palace.
How long will you be keeping her here?
I will take her.
You do know that she's
the Princess, do you not?
There is something
she must do for the royal family
so worry not, and take your leave.
Are you not concerned in the
slightest for Yeon Hui's well-being?
What did you just say?
Your Highness!
How could you betray me
and side with the Queen?
What is the meaning of this?
How dare you barge in here
with your soldiers in tow?
I'm not here to attack you.
I heard that you may be in danger,
so I came to protect you.
- Tell her what you saw.
- Yes, sir!
Well, um, that is, um...
there's a witch who's been the cause
of many bad rumors within the country.
As, um, the captain of the royal guard
I was pursuing that witch in case she
poses a threat to our nation's security.
But I saw her enter your room!
I was so surprised that I reported it to
the king, and ran over here. Yes.
You said that you saw that witch
with your own eyes, correct?
Yes.
Indeed, I did.
And I think that she's hidden herself
somewhere near the Queen's quarters.
Are you seriously trying to
use that pathetic excuse of a tale
to try and be rid of me?
King! Why not just accuse me
of treason, instead?
Give me a legitimate
reason for your doing this!
What would I gain by kicking you out?
It's not like be you'll be
the ruler forever.
You'll have to step down from your
position anyway, when I'm cured.
I was just worried about you, so I
dragged my sickly body all the way here!
So are you telling me to be touched
to tears by that, or something?
I cannot allow you to defile my quarters
for such ridiculous reasons.
Take your soldiers
and leave, immediately!
Surely this is not something to get
so worked up over, Your Highness.
I merely wish to check and see
if there may be anything here
that may be a danger to you.
- Search the room!
- Yes, sir!
I think there may be something
behind that folding screen.
Your Highness!
Your court is gathered at the reception
hall, and are waiting for you.
What is it?
Is something the matter?
Who are you?
She's Princess Yeon Hui,
the late Crown Prince's sister.
I'd like to officially introduce
myself to you. My name is Yeon Hui.
What is the meaning of this,
all of a sudden? Explain.
I heard that the princess, who was
thought to have died during childbirth
was actually alive.
Therefore, I searched
far and wide for her.
Starting today, I'd like to officially
announce Yeon Hui as the Princess.
I guess it's true, then.
I'm talking about the rumor that
the queen actually gave birth to twins.
Having twins is bad enough,
but keeping it hidden, at that?
Queen! Is what the king said
really the truth?
You mustn't dishonor the royal family
by putting things like that, King.
I have nothing to say
in regards to the fact
that I had twins
makes you feel uncomfortable.
This was something that was
decided upon by the heavens, after all.
The princess who was born
as the Crown Prince's twin...
because of her, the country and
the royal family have been cursed.
I also heard a rumor that
she's the cause of my illness.
What do you make of that?
If that rumor is true,
I will take responsibility.
If the punishment is the loss of your
title, will you be able to handle it?
If you want to dismiss me
from my position
you must prove that she really is
the source of the curse upon this land.
If it's true, I won't have to prove it
since the downfall of our
country will serve as such.
Then, I'll dismiss you
from your position then.
Before you start accusing me of crimes
shouldn't we celebrate,
since the princess has returned to us?
Are you not happy?
Yes. I couldn't possibly be happier.
I really did wish to see the princess
that I'd heard so much about.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Right now, your safety takes priority,
so just worry about that.
Congratulations on returning
to the palace, Your Highness.
Make sure you always bow your
head before the princess, just like that
and mind your manners.
If anything happens to her,
I'll blame it on you, no matter what.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
That does not sound quite fair,
Your Highness.
We will soon perform funeral rites
at the Imperial Taoist Branch
for Crown Prince Soonhwe.
I'd like for you to help us,
since you're the Chief Shamaness.
How about it?
Of course.
Have you delivered the message
to the Red Gentleman's Robe?
Yes. I told her to keep herself
and the ceramic urn hidden
and then to bring it here at 9:00 p.m.
Hey, Red Gentleman's Robe!
I missed you so much!
Sheesh, what's up with
the violent greeting?
Why don't you put that down, first?
I feel bad fighting you
when you're handicapped.
You didn't use the medicine
that I gave you?
Sol Gae. Who gave you that name?
Was it the people who sold you,
or was it Hong Joo?
If you tell...
Poong Yeon who I am...
I'll... kill...
Just keep acting
stupidly confident, Princess.
Soon, you'll feel humiliated for
not realizing that you have a fake.
You've come?
We were just about to get started.
You also had a special relationship with
him, so shouldn't you say farewell?
You cherished him so much.
How could I possibly
compare my grief to yours?
Well, it also pained me greatly
to see him go, as well.
- Did it really?
- Yes, Princess.
Then why did you swap
his cremains with a fake one?
Crown Prince.
What are you doing?
Say your farewells to him.
I will wish for him to have
a pleasant afterlife.
This isn't the end.
I've resolved to pay for my crimes,
and will ensure that you do the same.
Are you all right?
I'll go and get some air for a bit.
So if you send the Prince's spirit off,
she won't be able to kill you, right?
- Seo Ri!
- Sir Monk!
Are you all right?
Thank goodness.
What about Father?
I haven't seen him.
- Where is he?
- That is...
Father!
- Are you all right, sir?
- Yes. I'm fine.
That's a relief.
You brought him back safely, didn't you?
I think it'd be best to hurry
and finish the funeral rites.
Please escort the Queen here.
Yes, Father.
Please go with Yeon Hui.
Oh... yes.
Let's go.
Sir, are you really all right?
You needn't worry about me.
Do I have to call you "Princess" now?
No. This is just a protective
measure of sorts.
The title will help protect me.
So don't worry too much.
I'm not worried.
I'm just scared.
I'm scared that I'll be
separated from you again.
- Older Brother.
- What's going on?
Do not follow us. I want to
speak to her privately.
Change into this, and meet me outside.
Let's leave this place.
I know that you're doing this
because you're afraid I'll be in danger.
But--
Not only Hong Joo, but the
king is also after your life!
So how could you just
march in here?
It's because everyone
who is after my life is here.
I'm going to stay close and see
what they're planning for myself.
That's the only way I can really defend
myself against them, and stop them.
That is all I have time to think about.
I don't have the luxury to be worrying
about the relationship between us.
I tried my best not to
avoid you when you transformed.
I tried my best to overcome my fears!
And I... wanted to protect you,
as a man.
So why is it that you
won't give me a chance?
The only reply I can give you...
is this.
Don't ever turn your back on me again.
Let go. I'm sure that
you're hurting Yeon Hui.
This isn't something for you
to be getting involved in.
I told you to let go.
Let go of him.
Let go of him, okay? Now.
Let go of me, too, Older Brother.
I'm going to go with him.
If I let go of your hand now...
you will never see
your older brother again.
Queen.
Abra...cadabra.
- Sir Monk!
- What happened?
They snuck up on me, I was blindsided.
What about Father?
Thankfully, he'd stepped out
for a bit when this happened.
Great job.
The urn is gone.
You insolent wench!
You're at it again!
You can't fight fate
no matter how hard you try, Queen.
Your fate is to choose for
one of your two children to live.
Since you've chosen the princess,
I'll do as I wish with the Prince.
What are you planning
to do with the prince?
That's none of your business.
I'll do with him as I wish
whether that may be letting him
rot in hell forever, or making him king.
The Crown Prince is no
longer your child, after all.
What the hell are you saying?
The Crown Prince is my child!
He's my son, damn you!
Didn't you cast him aside, though?
- I've never once done that!
- Then...
you should've let me kill the princess
so I could bring him back to life.
You shouldn't have called her here
to have her challenge me!
None of this would've happened
if Crown Prince were still alive!
If you'd killed her properly the first
time, my son would still be alive!
Do you get it now?
Do you understand why the Crown Prince's
life takes priority over yours?
My son!
You've cast Yeon Hui aside,
but all she ever did was protect you.
Don't ever mess with
my children, ever again.
You okay?
This is a Dream Elixir.
If you drink this
you'll be able to see the person
you want to see in your dreams.
I'm sure that you'll have
trouble falling asleep tonight
so drink this before you go to sleep.
- That one looks like you.
- That one?
- That one looks like me?
- Yes!
I really don't see the resemblance.
Mother, you've turned your head.
Tilt it a bit more this way.
Yes, like that!
If I were to take the memory of just one
day with me as I go on to the afterlife
I'd choose a day like today
when we laughed together
about nothing in particular.
I'll use this day to give me hope
until the day that we will be reunited.
I pray that day will come soon.
All I have left now is you.
Only your skill can kill the princess
so you must end her life
with the holy fire this time.
That's the last page
of the Grimoire of Curses.
Only the sacrifice of someone who truly
loves Yeon Hui can light the last candle.
If Hong Joo finds out about that,
Mr. Heo will be in danger.
Sir.
Yoh Gwang. If I become
evil once more, kill me.
I can't do that.
I won't!
I'm begging you. If I'm a danger
to Yeon Hui, you must not hesitate
and save Yeon Hui.
Please kill me before Poong Yeon
and Yeon Hui see me in my evil state.
What do you want?
Am I crazy to want an apology from you?
I mean, it really did hurt
when you stabbed me.
People who seek me out only
ever threaten me, or plead with me.
So which one will it be for you?
I'm curious about something.
About the girl that you
stuck onto Poong Yeon...
what were you going to do
if she hadn't found Yeon Hui?
Are you the one who returned
the proper urn to her?
You know, I'm debating how I should
use this trump card in my hand.
- What should I do?
- What is it that you want?
Stop bothering Yeon Hui,
and stop killing people.
That's all I want from you.
I'll think about whether or not
I'll honor your simple request.
I'll give you some time.
He has Sol Gae.
Follow him.
Wow, this is great. The soup
here is especially great today.
When you're feeling weak, there's
nothing better than beef soup and rice!
Just look at this beef.
So tender!
Huh? Hey, you!
Wow, you're right!
The soup really is amazing!
Wow. Here, let me get some.
Hey!
- Wow, look at that.
- What's with you?
Wow.
Just shush up, and eat.
Sheesh.
As for the hunt... I gave the Queen
a lot less credit than she deserved.
The princess has been
formally introduced to the court
so it'll be difficult to
capture her now.
If we don't sacrifice her, you'll keep
having thorns sprout from your body.
How about we take care of
another thorn in your side?
I mean the Queen, who is
protecting the Princess.
Are you telling me to get rid
of the Queen, somehow?
There's no way that I'd allow that.
I'll pretend that I didn't hear that.
So, if anything happens to the Queen,
it won't be my fault.
I'm sure that it's difficult for you
to forget about the Prince.
Worry not.
I'll send you to his side soon.
Can you use your black magic
to win over someone's heart?
[Mirror of the Witch]
Do I just have to return
Yeon Hui to you?
I'll show you what the
truth really is.
She was a bright child. What
a shame that it's come to this.
If you cannot find a
charm to break the seal
the Queen will not live
past tomorrow night.
Kill them, right now.
Stop it!
If you can't kill
him, I will.
She's merely a cursed monster.
This was all a part
of Hong Joo's plan!
- I must save Yeon Hui.
- You can't do anything.
Father!
Now, light those charms on fire.