[Resemblance to any historical
figures or incidents is fictitious.]
[Episode 15]
So you're saying that you'll
try to cure my illness?
How could someone like you do it
when the best doctors in Joseon cannot?
Your disease is not one
that doctors can cure.
I'm sure you've seen many doctors
and taken hundreds of remedies
but you still haven't been cured, and
that's because science cannot cure you.
So, is Hong Joo's black magic
the cause, then?
Yes. I've also fallen prey
to that woman's black magic.
Such is the true nature of that woman,
who you keep so close to you.
Your disease, whom nobody could cure
and nobody knows the cause of...
is caused by her black magic.
I'm sure of it.
I didn't want to believe what
that shamaness told me before
and I don't want to
believe you now, either.
Leave immediately
if you do not wish to die.
What will you do if you
sacrifice the princess
but your disease
doesn't get any better?
If that's the case, you must endure
that pain until your death.
This is the only real chance you'll
ever get at curing your disease.
Doesn't the fact that you've even
agreed to see me in the first place
just go to prove that you're
already at your wit's end?
One day.
I'll give you just one day.
Go ahead and try to
prove me wrong, then.
If you cannot, I'll kill both
you and Hong Joo.
The fate of the princess rests on this
one day, so please aid my endeavor.
What are you asking me
to help you with, exactly?
Please lock Hong Joo up for one day so
she won't be able to use black magic.
Are you all right, Young Master?
Just what did you do to me?
I was merely testing out your skill.
It seemed that Sir Choi's powers
have been passed onto you
so I just awakened your latent powers.
I'm sure that your body
will need time to adjust
since it's your first time
using your Taoist powers.
- What do you mean, Taoist powers?
- Have you heard of the "sammaejinhjwa?"
It's a type of power that calls
forth a holy flame.
What do you mean by that?
How could I possibly...
I'm sure that you're a bit
worked up right now.
However, the holy flames have
the power to defeat the curse.
In other words, you have the power
to do away with the princess's curse.
Now, you are the only one
who can save Yeon Hui.
If you feel a bit overwhelmed,
go and ask your father for advice.
He'll probably give you
a wise answer.
I have something to ask you.
It seems that I've inherited your power.
I've gained the power to use holy flames
but I'm not sure as to how
I should utilize my newfound power.
It seems that you're now walking
on the same path that I once did.
You can break the princess's
curse with the holy fire.
Is it true that only the evil curse
within her will be harmed by this?
I should have killed the cursed princess
a long time ago with my holy flames
but I could not. But we can break
her curse even without killing her.
I regret not finishing the job
myself, many years ago.
Are you telling me that you
once tried to kill Yeon Hui?
You know that a terrible curse
has its hold on Yeon Hui, correct?
However, when you took
Yeon Hui to the Black Forest...
So, what must I do now?
Help Hong Joo and kill
the cursed princess
and protect Yeon Hui. It is for that
reason that you've inherited my power.
Help Hong Joo?
Is that truly what you wish me to do?
That is what's best for
the sake of the royal family.
What is it?
I do not think that I will be able
to receive your treatment today.
You'll have to stay in a cell,
just for today.
And what is the reason behind that,
Your Highness?
You told me to obey you
if I wished to live, correct?
In order for me to do that, I must
keep you at a distance for today.
I'm sure that your pain will be
a lot worse today, though.
What are you planning that you'd even
be willing to withstand such agony?
Don't doubt me. You'll come
to know everything after today.
I understand.
I'll do as you say.
Heo Joon has entered the king's
chambers. What should we do?
Don't do anything. This isn't something
to blow out of proportion.
Then, I will do an
examination of your body.
Please take off your robe.
You must do so, for me to
be able to get a good look.
I apologize, Your Highness.
Did you find evidence that black magic
is what is behind all this?
There's no clear mark to indicate
that this was caused by black magic.
What did you say?
Then, did you lie to me?
Your Highness, a student who can't trust
his teacher will never learn anything
and a patient who does not trust
their doctor cannot be healed!
I'm your doctor today,
so please entrust this to me.
Are you trying to educate me right now?
Don't misunderstand.
I'm only allowing this
because you said that this was caused
by black magic, and that you'd cure me!
So don't go blabbering
whatever you want to.
If you keep doing so, I'll chop off your
head and throw it at the princess.
What is Heo Joon up to?
- Sir!
- Tell me.
What is he doing by the king's side?
You can overcome this, sir!
I'm sure he's trying
to save the princess.
Not... not yet.
Right now, Yeon Hui
could potentially die, sir!
You're all right now.
Now, you...
Is something wrong with him?
He lost all of his holy powers while
making a talisman for Yeon Hui
and now he's succumbed to black magic.
What?
Then, what's happened to Sir Choi?
I'm not sure.
He hasn't completely succumbed and
he's trying his best to fight back, but--
Is there any way I can help?
How did things go with His Highness?
I searched the king's
entire body carefully
but I didn't see anything indicating that
his disease was caused by black magic.
I was going to ask
Sir Choi for advice, but...
We don't have much time.
I must go to Yeon Hui's room
and look through the spell books.
Incantation.
If she used that, she wouldn't
have left any visible marks.
What's that?
It's a method of spellcasting,
by chanting words.
Everyone will want to kill you.
Everyone will look down on you.
And everyone will curse you
behind your back.
No matter how hard you may try,
you'll never escape this pain.
How can we break the spell
if she used that kind of method?
The only method I know of
is to destroy the root
but it'll be hard, since this
spell has no tangible root.
I'm sure that Sir Choi
would know of a way.
Where are you going?
There's something that
I must investigate.
It seems that Hong Joo has cast a
spell on His Highness with no root.
Sir Monk called it "Unryungsool."
Is there a way to break such a spell?
You do know of a way, don't you?
Please, tell us!
- There is no way.
- Is there really no way?
Why wouldn't I have told
you already, if there was?
Yeon Hui's life is at stake.
Please, think about it once more!
I, too, wish to save Yeon Hui.
It pains me to say this, but what
can we do, when there is no way?
All we can do is accept fate.
That's not something
that you would say, Sir Choi.
So you were playing doctor,
weren't you?
Even if you knew the method,
you wouldn't be able to do anything.
Who are you saying is truly
speaking, if it isn't me?
- This is all I know.
You definitely wanted
to protect Yeon Hui.
Didn't you make a request of me, since
you became unable to do so yourself?
Do you think I'd honestly tell you
that I don't know, when I do?
If you really can't believe me, why not
go and find a method for yourself?
Your body and soul are both mine now!
You shouldn't be able to do as you wish!
Sir! Sir!
Are you all right?
Do not despair. All you have to do
is act normally, as you are now.
Look over the Grimoire of Curses.
There are still many things
that you must do for me.
I completely understand.
- Hey, it's time to switch.
- Already?
Here. Good luck.
Yeon Hui!
- We don't have much time.
- Are you all right?
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine.
I think I can prove that the king's
disease is the work of black magic.
Sir Choi said that there should be
a solution in the Grimoire of Curses.
- Father did?
- Yeah.
Black magic seeps into people's hearts
through their weaknesses.
And I think that's the case with the
king, after seeing him in action.
So there's a solution in the
Grimoire of Curses, eh?
We'll have to make him
be honest with his feelings.
How about an elixir that
makes people tell only the truth?
The truth elixir?
We may be able to break the
black magic spell on him, with that.
I'll need white poria cocos,
lucid asparagus
gwigook, and picrorhizae rhizoma.
One more thing, though.
It won't have any effect if the drinker
has no desire to speak the truth.
Even so, we have to give it a shot.
I'll try and make it.
I think we'll have to leave now.
This won't do. Let's leave
together now, Seo Ri.
Let's leave now, and
finish lighting the candles.
No.
I've done nothing wrong.
I came here because I was sick of hiding.
So I'll prove my innocence and
leave here, with confidence.
All right, then.
Just trust in me, and wait.
Um... was Father really
the one who helped you?
He came here with Hong Joo before,
and he was acting strangely.
Yeon Hui. Don't worry,
and wait just a bit longer.
I'll come back to get you soon.
I need gwigook.
Gwigook.
The gwigook is...
here's a tool for chopping.
Gwigook.
Gwi... gook!
Gwigook!
- Gwi... gook! Gwi!
- Gwi?
Gwigook... gwigook.
Gwigook.
- Gwigook.
- Put one in, and grind it.
Grind it?
This is my first time making this,
but it doesn't look quite right.
Maybe you're starting
to lose your memory?
Let's see here.
First...
Hey! Hey!
Did you say that you'd
cure the king's ailment?
Yes, Your Highness.
There is no remedy that
the king has yet to try.
Don't get cocky and put
Yeon Hui in danger.
Just do nothing.
This is the only solution
available to us right now!
Are you telling me to entrust
Yeon Hui's life to you, then?
My knowledge just may end up
saving the princess's life!
I'll give it a try.
If any harm befalls the
princess because of this
I won't forgive you.
The day I've promised you
is now at its end.
If any harm befalls my body
or you cannot cure my ailment
I'll execute both you and the princess.
Let them in.
What is this?
This is medicine that can
cure your ailment.
- And who is the one who made this?
- Me, Your Highness.
You're telling me to drink
the medicine you've made
even though you're not even a doctor?
Is that what you're
telling me right now?
You've entrusted your
body to me, have you not?
I told you to get me evidence
that this was caused by black magic.
I never said that I'd drink some mystery
elixir that just may be poisonous.
I know very well that
you have your reservations.
However, please trust that I'm genuinely
concerned for the princess.
Such are the feelings that I put into
making this for you, Your Highness.
Your Highness!
He cannot be trusted!
Please, reconsider!
Your Highness!
Kill... kill that man.
- Capture this man!
- Yes, sir!
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Mr. Heo!
What's going on?
The king fainted!
My expectations of you were high. Who
knew things would end so pathetically?
It's not over yet.
You're still alive, after all.
Don't you get it?
You're the one who will be dying now.
No. That won't happen.
What did you do to Father?
He made a talisman for you, and
ended up losing his life in the process.
And when that happened,
I saved him.
Father... died?
What did you do to him?
Sir Choi and I are of
one mind and body now.
If you kill me, he'll die too.
Please remember that he will die slowly
beside me whenever you light a candle.
I will turn my father back to normal
so that you can never touch him again.
Sure. Go ahead and try.
Our deal is off. Now you'll have to deal
with the consequences of your words.
Your Highness.
Joon.
It wasn't enough that the
princess attacked me
you tried to kill me with poison, too?
I'll sentence you two
to death by drowning.
King! You must not kill the princess!
The curse upon the royal family
will only worsen if you kill her!
Please return to your quarters!
You'll be the next one executed.
- King!
- Leave right now!
Are... you scared of the princess,
Your Highness?
What did you say?
- Or do you fear Hong Joo?
- Don't blubber on carelessly!
Are you scared of losing the throne?
What are you so scared of
that you've been rendered to this?
You have the most power and
authority among all of us here!
Shut your mouth!
I know that you accuse me of being
a cruel tyrant behind my back.
Isn't that why the princess
tried to kill me?
I wasn't trying to kill you.
How could I kill you,
the king of this country?
All I wanted to do was protect you
from Hong Joo's evil plans.
See? There are even people
who wish to protect you!
No. No. There are only people
who wish to kill me in this country!
There are only those who wish
to pry my power away from me!
And you lot are the same.
Why did you trust me, then?
- What did you say?
- You let me stay at the palace
and you listened to what I
had to say, did you not?
You could have easily killed me,
or ignored me!
However, you trusted me
and took the medicine.
What made you so desperate
that you believed me?
Wasn't it for the sake of
protecting the throne?
Or did you want to give up the throne?
If you say one more word,
I'll kill you right now.
You just wanted to make an example of us
to those who say that you don't
have the right to be king, didn't you?
You wanted to be acknowledged
as the rightful ruler of this land.
Yes.
I wanted to be acknowledged by others.
Do you think I became king
because I wanted to?
You don't know how much pressure
and fear comes with this position.
People looked down upon me for being
a mere half-relative to the royal family.
They spread malicious rumors about me,
and made fun of me...
and tried to kill me, too.
I want to do my best, too.
And I want to be acknowledged, too!
I wanted to become a
good king to my subjects.
But... no matter how hard
I tried, it wouldn't work.
So what am I supposed to do, exactly?
Now, due to my illness, there's
nothing that I can do anymore.
There's nothing I can do
for this damned country!
Your Highness!
That was the black magic
plaguing your body this whole time.
- Capture her!
- Yes, sir!
Did you truly think that you'd
survive after you did this to me?
What do you mean?
Are you pretending that
you know nothing about the fact
that you cast black magic
on the royal family?
How could a mere shamaness
dare to do that?
All I've ever done was use my powers
for the royal family, as you've wished.
What did you just say?
If you truly believe yourselves to be
innocent, then feel free to punish me!
You're the one who wanted to have
an heir no matter what it took, Queen.
And you're the one who
asked me to cure your ailment
even if I had to kill the
princess to do it.
So what have I done wrong, exactly?
Impudent wench.
Are you trying to bring us all down with
you so you can get out of this?
That's right. I can't disgrace
the royal family just to punish you.
Send them in!
Tell me what crimes you've committed.
I killed people under the orders of the
Chief Shamaness of Sungsuchung.
I brought people's hearts to her,
and she used them for black magic.
- Is this the truth?
- Yes.
You still claim that you are innocent?
So, what will you do now?
Will you slice me into pieces?
- You wench!
- You asked me for help
saying you'd do anything,
and now you're "unearthing the truth?"
You royal family members
have always done this to me.
You're weak, feeble, and cowardly.
You people never change,
no matter how much time passes.
Make sure that you're careful, too.
They're keeping you by them
because they need you now
but you, too, will be
cast aside like a stray dog.
Shut your mouth!
Come forth!
I'll have you torn limb from limb,
for everyone to see.
- Come over here!
- Wow!
Hurry it up!
Come on!
Here, here, sit!
- Hey, did you know?
- What?
That bastard, Heo Joon,
is all locked up now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Forever. And ever.
- So, you caught him?
Um, of course.
I guess you can say that I did.
- Really!
- So what's happening to him?
Him? Well, he was captured
after trying to poison the king
so he'll definitely be
torn limb from limb.
Sheesh, I've never seen
an unluckier guy than him!
I know, right?
Hey, if he'd just laid low when I let
him, he wouldn't be on death row now!
That man!
Over there!
That man is wanted for
lying to the king! Arrest him!
- Arrest that man, now!
- Yes, sir!
- Drag him out!
- Wait a second!
Hey, where are you taking me?
Huh? I'm higher ranked than you!
Hey! What's your name, punk?
Father.
That shamaness told me that Father
had already died a while ago.
That's a lie, right?
Sir Choi is no longer able
to move or act as he wishes.
If we get rid of the black magic
spell on him, he may return to normal.
But his dead body is only moving
right now because of the spell
so if we break the spell on him,
he will surely die on the spot.
Then, when she said that they were
one in body and mind...
When she dies,
Sir Choi will die as well.
Sir.
You were truly the
Red Gentleman's Robe this whole time?
Answer me. Are you truly the
Red Gentleman's Robe?
I apologize.
Did I seem like
that much of a joke to you?
Was it funny, helping me search
for the Red Gentleman's Robe
despite the fact that it was
you this whole time?
Did I seem like a fool to you?
- That wasn't my intention. I just--
- I trusted you.
I truly regarded you as a close friend,
and I was so thankful for your efforts.
And yet...
you... you...
Did you only spend time with me
due to your ulterior motive?
Who am I supposed to trust now?
Please do not forgive me.
Despite all this,
you were still my friend.
This is my last act
of friendship to you.
All the thorns that had appeared
on your skin are now gone
and you have no scarring left.
Yes. Thank you.
- Um, Your Highness.
- What?
Since you're completely cured,
could you do me a favor?
Yes. As for what you wanted...
Didn't I already release the princess
as I said I would, though?
I mean, shouldn't you have done that
anyway, since we proved our innocence?
Hmm, well, yes.
When I think of how much you humiliated
me, I want to chop your head off!
Leave now.
Um, go ahead and tell me what you want.
I can't think of anything now,
but can I cash in this favor later?
You wily rascal.
Stop smiling.
Yeon Hui!
Were you waiting for me?
I'm not sure where I should start
looking for my father.
- Hong Joo... Hong Joo has...
- What about her?
What did she do this time?
Hong Joo has escaped.
I am in your debt, Young Master.
Don't misunderstand.
I'll make you pay for your sins after
I've turned Yeon Hui back to normal.
What must I do now?
All you must do is bring forth your holy
flames when my preparations are complete.
Will Yeon Hui really go back
to normal after I set her aflame?
You still can't trust me, sir?
Well, I'm sure you'll find out
when you go ahead and try it.
Was my first encounter with Sol Gae
all a part of your plan?
Yes.
You truly are a fearsome individual.
One needs to see the big picture
to bring forth a big revolution.
Furthermore, revolutions must be
carried out without feelings attached.
You must ensure that Sol Gae is the
last one you show your weakness towards.
If Hong Joo has disappeared,
I'm sure she's up to something.
And I'm sure that it will
put you in danger.
We'll have to post some
guards near your chambers.
- I'm all right.
- Yeon Hui.
You are now a part of the royal family.
You must remember that your well-being
is linked to the well-being of this land.
Yes.
Furthermore, distance yourself
from that man, Heo Joon.
I know that he has been
of much help to you.
I'm quite thankful toward him for that.
However, you're the princess.
You can't just let a commoner like him
accompany you like he had before.
I'll do my best to find a
suitable position for him.
He's someone I've given my heart to.
It seems that your feelings
for him run quite deep.
Will giving you some time suffice?
I feel a bit relieved that the Queen
ordered royal soldiers to guard us.
Yeon Hui. I think I'll have to find
a way to earn a living now.
So I don't think I'll be able
to come see you too often.
But, I'll continue to watch over you
until you light all the candles,
and until you're completely safe.
Okay.
Go and get some rest now.
You don't look too good.
Yeon Hui!
[Mirror of the Witch]
You know, Yeon Hui, I'd like
it if you lived a rosy life.
Will you be able to handle Sir Choi?
- Mr. Heo!
- You can't kill or save them.
Just what is that shamaness that she
can cause such an uproar?
Sir Choi Hyun Seo will help us.
Where is my father now?
I saved him with my black magic,
when he'd died due to the princess.
I don't see that man who's
usually always by your side.
Why would he come with me,
when I came to die?