Subtitles by DramaFever
[Resemblance to any historical
figures or incidents is fictitious.]
Hey, Persimmon.
Why are you here?
Older Brother...
[Episode 4]
What brings you here?
And is she sick?
Her body is cold, and she's quite pale.
I think it'd be best
to bring her to a physician...
Oh, um... don't misunderstand.
Um, this is like a work uniform for me.
And it's not that kind of job... I'm
selling something nowadays, and--
Do you know my little sister,
by any chance?
Uh, no.
At any rate, thank you for helping her.
I'll take care of her from here
on in, so you can go.
Then, goodbye.
So that stiff was her older brother?
They're not alike at all.
I wonder if that girl will be okay?
She looked really unwell.
Oh, whatever! I should be more
worried about myself right now.
Mother!
- Poong Yeon!
Yeon Hui!
Yeon Hui! Yeon Hui!
Yeon Hui! Wake up!
Yeon Hui!
- Why did you do that?
- Father.
Why didn't you listen
to what I told you?
Father.
- Why?
- Why... is this happening to me?
I'm so scared, Father.
Please, save me.
How could this have happened?
I asked you a question!
Didn't you say that he'd be fine?
Didn't you say that
nothing would happen to him?
So what's this, then? Save him,
right now! Save him! Save him!
Eunuch Park, escort the Queen out.
Your Highness, please calm down!
Crown Prince... please, open your eyes.
This can't happen. You can't die!
You can't!
Please, open your eyes!
Please, no!
- Queen Shim!
- Your Highness!
Help her up.
Choi Hyun Seo.
Mother.
Let go. Let go of me, bastards!
Mother...
- Lady Sohn.
- I thought you were a clever child
but it seems to me that you're
not aware of your place.
Therefore, I'll thoroughly
educate you tonight.
Just what exactly are
you planning to do?
Please, stop.
Please!
Begin.
No! No! No!
Stop that, right now!
No! No! Stop!
Mother! Mother! Mother!
- Stay still!
- Mother!
Mother! Mo--
Mother! Mother!
Mother!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
So please, tell them to stop!
Please, tell them to stop!
Please! Please! Let her live!
- Please! Let her live!
- Stop.
I heard that you've been working hard
to buy your mother's ownership papers.
Joon. There's one thing that people
misunderstand as they go through life.
They mistakenly believe that they can
escape their wretched situations in life
if only they work hard.
However, there's something you can't
escape, no matter how hard you work.
Do you know what that is?
It's your parentage.
A parent who is affluent
can offer their child a lavish life.
However, the only thing that poor
parents can offer their children
is the sheer pathetic
nature of their life.
Since parents pass on the quality
of their lives to their children
you should never have been born.
You should never have
been born into this world!
Not being born would've been best
for both you and your mother.
But, who can you blame now?
You can only blame your own cursed life,
for being born to such a mother.
Don't do anything.
Don't try to escape your wretched fate.
Don't try to fight against it, either.
Just live as if you were dead.
That's the only way you
and your mother can survive.
Do you understand?
Y-y-y-yes!
Heed my words. If you didn't
understand what I told you today
your mother will really
be in there next time.
Mother.
Let's run away from this place.
Poong Yeon! How is it that you
can't swallow even a drop of medicine?
Poong Yeon!
Please, come to your senses!
- M-m-mother.
- Poong Yeon.
Have you regained consciousness?
Are you all right now?
- Poong Yeon!
- A ghost!
- Go away!
- What's the matter?
Why are you acting this way?
Please, Poong Yeon--
A ghost! A ghost!
Look at me, Poong Yeon.
Look at your mother!
- A ghost!
- Poong Yeon!
Yeon Hui!
Yeon Hui! Yeon Hui!
Her powers are unstable at the moment.
When she releases energy,
she loses consciousness
so we cannot move her yet.
The spell on the Black Forest
is beginning to break.
We must move her as soon as possible!
But what if she ends up being noticed
by Hong Joo while we're doing that?
That'll really mean the
end for all of this!
But if we leave her like that, she,
the Crown Prince, and Poong Yeon
will all end up perishing!
If we do that, Yoh Gwang
could fall into danger, too!
What are we supposed to do, then?
There's no other way!
Are you all right?
Don't worry too much. Your father
will take care of everything.
We can restore everything back to the
way it was if we go to Chungbing Temple.
Chungbing Temple?
What kind of place is that?
Well, that's... I'll tell you when
we get there, so wait just a bit.
I'm sure Father hates me now.
What do you mean?
I disobeyed him,
which is why this happened.
So I'll bet that he hates me now.
There's no way that's true.
He treasures you so much.
So how could you say such things?
I'll bet that he's having quite
a hard time right now, too.
Since this has effected not only you,
but Young Master Poong Yeon, too.
What do you mean by that?
Huh?
Did something happen
to my older brother?
This won't do.
Let's just go back.
Please, Monk! Let me
just see his face for a bit.
We'll both be in trouble
if your father finds out!
- We can't.
- But, if I don't see him today
I don't know when else
I'd be able to see him again.
Then we'll just see him for a short bit,
and then come back out, okay?
These talismans won't last much longer!
Do you understand?
Be careful.
Older Brother.
How did you end up like this?
Please wake up, Older Brother!
Older Brother! Are you regaining
consciousness? It's me, Yeon Hui!
B-b-begone... begone, you foul creature!
Older Brother! Are you regaining
consciousness? It's me, Yeon Hui!
B-b-begone... begone, you foul creature!
Older... brother.
Please... please, please!
Please, go away!
Please, leave me!
I... I want to live!
I want to live!
I'm telling you, I want to live!
Let's take our leave, Yeon Hui.
Come on, let's go.
You insolent wench.
How dare you come here!
Mother.
Poong Yeon.
This is because of you!
This is all because
of your damned curse!
And the fact that Poong Yeon
became this way
is due to you and your
damned curse!
This is why I could never love you
as my own daughter, Yeon Hui!
You never should have been born.
You should never have
come into this world!
I'll beg you on my knees, like this.
So please, disappear.
Please go far, far away
from my Poong Yeon!
Please!
Take Yeon Hui away.
Yes, sir.
Let's go, Yeon Hui.
Come on.
Monk. How can I get to Chungbing Temple?
I'll go there.
I'll do whatever I'm told to do.
So please, save my older brother.
Sir, we cannot delay this any longer.
Sir. A person from the palace
has come to see you.
You all go ahead and leave
for Chungbing Temple with Yeon Hui.
I'll soon follow you all
with the Grimoire of Curses.
- Yes, sir.
What brings you all the way here?
I came to apologize.
I underestimated you.
Who could I possibly blame?
It's all my fault.
When you readily agreed
to kill the princess 17 years ago
I shouldn't have let myself
be fooled by you so easily.
You're Choi Hyun Seo, after all.
What is it that you want to say?
Where is the princess?
You didn't kill her.
It may have been because you felt
sympathy or pity toward the child.
I completely understand.
However, you must tell me now:
where did you hide the princess?
The princess... is dead.
You saw it with your own eyes,
did you not?
You saw that she was burned to death.
Ah. So is this your answer?
I fully understand.
Then, I'll be going.
What is it?
The exit is that way.
Sir. If the princess
is actually still alive
you will be guilty of blatantly
disobeying the Queen Dowager
and taking the Crown Prince's life,
and will be tried for those crimes.
And the person who her
curse has transferred over to
will be ill for 14 days,
before dying.
However, I'm sure that those
things won't happen... will they?
Surely you didn't do such a thing,
as someone who treasures this country.
Isn't that right?
Excuse me!
Can't you see that I'm closed?
Um... I heard that you
sell tickets to get to China.
And that's... why I came to see you.
You've come to the wrong place.
We don't have such luxuries in stock.
I came here from Cheondong.
I need two boat tickets
headed for China.
Please.
Come to the booth in two hours.
It's 200 nyang.
Are you all packed?
Joon... the more I think about it,
the more dangerous this seems.
Let's forget about this idea.
If we're caught, you'll be in danger.
Mother. I've given up on a
lot of things by living in this house.
I had to degrade myself
just to survive here.
But... I'm not going to
live like that any longer.
Joon.
At the very least, let's live our lives
doing what we want to do, from now on.
Hey, I said that I'd pay you! Come on!
Come on! Just once!
Why not, huh?
- Come on.
- Come here.
Stop it!
Oh. Wow. This country of
Joseon is so old-fashioned!
Due to some stupid regulations, we
can't even wear flashy things like this!
Isn't that right?
How tacky.
Honestly, a good-looking guy like me
should be allowed a ring like this.
Right? Huh?
Of course!
It really suits you, sir!
Why not take this chance and buy one?
It's hard to even find quality items
like these for sale these days!
- Really?
- Of course!
This is an import from China, but
trade restrictions have gotten so rigid
that finding such things
for purchase is quite difficult!
Figures. These are just as
beautiful as the ladies here!
There's no way that these
could be from cruddy old Joseon!
All right, I'm in a good mood.
You all can pick one out, each.
I'll buy one for each of you,
so pick one out!
- Really, sir?
- Yeah!
- Wow!
- How magnanimous!
- Young Master.
- What?
What is it?
Excuse me for a moment.
Mommy!
Hey, go all the way in.
Wait here. I'll hurry and
get us the boat tickets.
I've given up on a lot of
things by living in this house.
I've degraded myself
just to survive here.
I won't live like that any longer.
I'm here to see Mr. Kapachi.
Here's the amount you asked for.
Please hurry and give me tickets.
I only sell tickets to a person once.
Do you know why that is?
Because the people on the boat
either make it safely to China
or they become fish food due
to their trip going not so well.
Or it's because
they were captured.
Do you know how most
people end up, though?
They get captured.
The type of people to pursue you
people are quite wicked and persistent.
If you're caught, you die in
the worst way imaginable.
But if you're not, you're on
the run for the rest of your life.
This is the last chance you'll have
to change your mind.
You still want to go, though?
I'll get on that boat,
no matter what happens.
The boat will leave at 1:00 a.m.
You must not even be a minute late.
Yes, sir.
Are you going to Yeon Hui?
Wife. I have no time
to explain right now.
I'll tell you everything
once I've returned.
Please, don't go!
It's all over now, anyway.
I'm saying that everything is over now.
What... do you mean by that?
What did you just say?
I told the shamaness from
Sungsuchung everything!
And why in the world did you do that?
You really don't know?
The strange mark that appeared
behind Poong Yeon's ear...
that's because of Yeon Hui, isn't it?
It's because Poong Yeon
developed feelings for Yeon Hui!
We must break Yeon Hui's curse to save
the country from Hong Joo's black magic!
I don't need any of that!
Who cares about this damn country
when my son is laying there dying?
That shamaness definitely said that if
only Yeon Hui dies... if only she dies...
our Poong Yeon can live!
She promised that she'd cover everything
up if you no longer interfered in this.
So please, don't go.
I've packed everything you'll need.
Let's hurry up and get going.
Just stay here for a second.
So the Imperial Taoist Branch
works together to hide the cursed child?
You still call yourself
loyal subjects to the throne?
Get them.
Chun Kwon!
Chun Kwon! Chun Kwon!
Sir!
No!
Foolish bastards.
Do you know what her curse is?
The fact that you're dying like this
is all because of her.
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean,
everything is because of me?
Pitiful thing. Nobody told you
about your curse?
All the people you love will die.
And all the people who
love you will die, too.
That's the curse upon you.
Are you sad, my child?
Are you miserable?
So, why did you have to be born?
Nobody wanted you to be.
Do you wish to save everyone?
If you do, all you have
to do is die. Just you.
Stop!
Stop this.
You must not take this child away!
Do not get in my way longer, sir.
I cannot forgive you for meddling
further, even if it's you!
Sir, please run away.
Chase after him and the princess!
You mustn't lose them!
You'll have to get through me, first!
Who wants to be the first one to
join me on the path to the afterlife?
I'm sure they couldn't have gotten far.
Search the area thoroughly!
We must find them and
bring them to the palace!
- Yes, ma'am!
Yeon Hui.
Father.
Yeon Hui. Listen carefully to
what I'm about to tell you.
If they catch sight of me,
you must run straight ahead!
You must not look back, and
run straight ahead, all right?
No. I don't want to!
This is all my fault.
I'd rather die than let
more innocent people die!
No. You mustn't, Yeon Hui!
You must live!
You must go to Chungbing Temple
and break this curse!
That's the only way that
we can all survive!
You must go to Chungbing Temple.
I'm sorry, Yeon Hui. And I know
this is late, but happy birthday.
Father.
He's over there!
Chase after him!
Yeon Hui. You must not die.
You must live!
You must go to Chungbing Temple
and break this curse!
That's the only way that
we can all survive!
Over there!
Where is the princess?
I don't know.
She's fated to die, anyway.
So how could you throw away everything
for such a child?
No... that child must live.
That's the will of the heavens.
The will of the heavens?
What is that, exactly?
Yielding to a fate that
was so unjust previously?
Is that the "will of the heavens"
that you speak of?
Being born with nothing to my name, and
being a target for those who were rich?
Having to bow before people even
if they trampled on me or laughed at me?
Is that the damned "will of the heavens"
that you speak of?
Those who worship the heavens
have a duty!
Paving the path for the will of the
heavens to be carried out is our duty.
No. I won't live like that any longer.
I'm going to be the one to trample
on them, and rise to the top.
Hong Joo. I know very well
how you must feel.
However, you're going
about this the wrong way.
That fact that things came
to this today is all my fault.
Let's go back to the palace together.
Let's stop here, and atone for our sins.
Don't fall any further into ruin,
Hong Joo!
I'm sorry that this is how I'm paying
you back for what you've taught me.
However... I don't believe in
the heavens, starting today.
From now on, my will is going
to be the will of the heavens.
We must capture the princess,
at all costs!
We must capture her, and kill her!
Hey, Persimmon. Is your
name Yeon Hui, by any chance?
Are you sad?
Are you miserable?
So, why did you have to be born?
Nobody wanted you to be.
They said that there isn't a person
who never should have been born.
No matter what kind of person they are,
all the people who were born
were born with the purpose of
helping to shape this world somehow.
Do you want to save them?
If you do, only you
need to die. Just you.
Everything is my fault.
I'd rather die instead.
No, you can't.
Subtitles by DramaFever
The cursed princess
will not die so easily.
Bring Hong Joo here, right now!
- They brought this upon themselves.
- Mother!
I'm... so sorry!
Young Master.
You dropped this.
Bring that person before me, right now!
We must catch them,
no matter what.
You're under arrest for
allegations of murder!
- I'll break the curse, for sure.
- It wasn't me!