Subtitles by DramaFever
[Resemblance to any historical
figures or incidents is fictitious.]
I can feel the energy of the princess.
Sir!
Seo Ri. Seo Ri!
Seo Ri!
We meet again.
So everything in
the Grimoire of Curses
was about her?
That's why Seo Ri needs you.
I don't know how you have
the Ok Choo Kyung symbol
but as you saw, that will
protect Seo Ri from the curse.
[Episode 9]
Let's see.
So he works as a boundary,
but he's a human boundary...
Ok Choo Kyung.
How messy.
It's all been ruined.
So over here... In here...
At this rate,
you might even untie my robe.
It's just...
This is something very precious.
So we must take good care of it.
Sure.
By the way, why were you
locked up in jail?
Lady Yeon Hui's brother...
By the way, does her family
not know that she's here?
They would be better off not knowing...
Wait a minute.
Why are you changing the topic?
Have you committed
a grave crime by chance?
What if the police are
chasing after us right now?
I've been framed.
That freaking Red Gentleman's Robe
or Blue Gentleman's Robe.
I feel bad enough about
being accused of murder.
What did you just say?
The Red Gentleman's Robe?
- What? Why?
- Do you know him by chance?
Or have you seen him?
If I knew him, I would have captured him.
What's going on?
The people he has killed
all made wishes to Seo Ri.
Because of the Red Gentleman's Robe
Seo Ri hasn't been able
to break the curse.
What?
Seo Ri doesn't know about this,
so you can't ever tell her.
You're awake.
Why is he here?
I'm asking you a question.
You see...
Seo Ri, hold on. Seo Ri.
Wait. Seo Ri.
- Do you think that makes any sense?
- I don't like this situation either.
But what can we do?
Look how unharmed we are even
after the boundary broke down.
So Lord Heo is our human boundary
who can protect us...
There is no such a thing.
The boundary is fine.
When you went outside,
the boundary was breaking down.
But it was restored
because Lord Heo came back.
He's serving as our boundary
right now as well.
Last night.
Were you the one who saved me?
I mean, according to Monk Yoh Gwang
Apparently I did.
Did you see everything?
I don't need him.
Send him out.
Seo Ri. Seo Ri!
You can't go anywhere.
Just stay right here.
Seo Ri!
Is it because you're embarrassed
that he saw you like that?
It's actually better this way.
He knows everything inside
the Grimoire of Curses.
Bring me the wish plaques.
Seo Ri. That's not what's important--
We need to light the candles
as soon as we can.
Father told me everyone will live
once I break the curse.
We don't even know
how my brother is doing.
So I'm saying let's stay with that man
until we finish lighting all the candles.
He is our only option right now.
Seo Ri.
Why are you awake already?
Why don't you lie down a little longer?
I'm fine.
I think I was just tired.
Fortunately, I feel much better
after getting some sleep.
You should take it easy.
Here.
I thought your body may be weakened,
so I've gotten you some medicine.
Sure.
- What's wrong?
- It's nothing.
By chance...
Have you found Yeon Hui?
Not yet.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
She's just been in my thoughts lately.
Are you all right?
Sir.
I had the same symptoms
the day Yeon Hui disappeared.
I wonder if something has
happened to Yeon Hui.
What do you mean?
How could the criminal have escaped?
While I was using the bathroom,
he disappeared completely.
Someone unlocked the door for him.
That means someone from
the inside helped him.
It wasn't me.
If he has an insider's help,
he may have also escaped the inspection.
Couldn't he already have
escaped from the capital?
Who are you?
How are you related to
the Red Gentleman's Robe?
Me?
I'm a man who wants to capture
the Red Gentleman's Robe very badly.
No. He is still in the capital.
I need to go see the 100-year-old tree.
I don't get what this whole
boundary thing is
but bad things won't happen to you
if I stay by your side, right?
I don't believe that.
So don't worry about it and just leave.
You only stayed in that house
in the Black Forest before.
And it seems like now
you can't leave this place either.
Doesn't it feel suffocating?
Mind your own business.
I'm saying if there is some place
you would like to go to
I will go there with you,
wherever that may be.
All you need is for me
to stay by your side.
If there are some persimmons,
you could pick them yourself too.
Are you going to keep pretending
like you don't know me?
Didn't you see that
I'm not the same person I was?
You would be better off
not getting involved with me.
Then you should have actually
given me the oblivion elixir.
So it seems like you make people
an elixir based on
the Grimoire of Curses
whenever someone makes a wish.
And that seems to help you too.
I told you to mind your own business.
I've already found out about all this,
and I remember everything.
I...
would like to help you.
Your Highness.
There is an unfortunate rumor
amongst the public that
the Red Gentleman's Robe is still alive.
What do you mean?
Didn't we even confirm
the Red Gentleman's Robe's corpse?
Multiple people have reported
seeing the Red Gentleman's Robe.
So are you saying I captured
a falsely accused man?
Is that it?
- That's not it...
- Then what is it?
Find the source of this preposterous
rumor and bring them to me.
In front of everyone
I'm going to rip that man's tongue out
and set an example.
Your Highness,
Queen Dowager has arrived.
Tell her to return to her place.
You can't let emotions interfere
with the way you govern.
Your Majesty.
You need to be considerate of
your people's anxiety.
Sure.
However...
this is a place to discuss
the matters of state affairs.
Not a get-together for
the Royal Noble Consort.
I think you've lost your judgment.
How could you govern with clarity?
So?
If you lose your way
this entire nation will crumble.
If your mind is
too troubled to govern...
even I may have to take charge.
I see.
So are you telling me right now to
give up my throne?
I'm saying if need be
I'll take over and govern in your place.
Your Highness.
His Majesty is so healthy and well.
We can't have a Queen Regent.
- What if he isn't very healthy?
- Grand Eunuch!
I think Queen Dowager's
eyes are failing her.
Escort her back to her place.
Eunuch Park. Bring him in.
You're not even the royal physician.
But I heard you've been treating
His Majesty every night.
- Is this true?
- Yes. It is.
What is His Majesty's
health like right now?
From an unknown skin disorder
he keeps getting scratches.
Thus, he is in grave condition.
How dare you!
What do you mean?
What do you mean by
His Majesty's illness?
I understand your considerate
decision to conceal your illness from
the public and your officials
in order to keep them from worrying.
However, your well-being is
directly related to
the prosperity of this country.
This isn't something
you can just brush under the rug.
It's a lie.
Queen Dowager is setting me up!
Oh my. Your illness is so serious.
You need to take care of
your health, Your Highness.
Set your worries aside and
allow me to take over in your place.
Didn't you say you could heal me?
Don't be inpatient. This will take time.
I'll make sure
you feel comfortable soon.
I...
am a king barely
holding onto his throne.
Can't you see that
they've unwillingly placed me,
a collateral descendant
on the throne and
are making a mockery of me?
Everyone is trying to get me killed.
So.
You need to hurry and heal me.
Hurry.
Calm down, Your Highness.
You can take care of everything
once you've recovered.
I'll eliminate those who
stand in your way for you.
You would do that for me?
I've given you Sungsuchung
because you've wanted it.
Is that all you want?
Of course not.
I've returned to the palace to eliminate
this country's source of trouble.
So I must accomplish this.
I'm asking you for your true motives.
In addition
I'd like to help dwindle the power of
Queen Dowager, who had expelled me.
And as a mere shamaness
I would like to be
your loyal subject, Your Highness.
Raw yam, acorus gramineus,
and berberidaceae.
These are used to make
a ghost-seeing elixir.
What are you making this for?
Move aside.
Are there people who wish to see ghosts?
There is nothing for
you to help me with.
The sooner I reach our goal,
the sooner Yoh Gwang will let you go.
If you would really like to help,
just don't get in my way.
It seems like no one has made any wishes.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Why are you...
Why are you drinking that?
What are you doing right now?
Where are you going
after drinking that elixir?
Since I've drank the ghost-seeing elixir,
I need to go see some dead people.
- Huh?
- I need to capture someone.
If I ask the dead people
I may be able to find out
who he is and where he is.
So I need you to come with me.
You look pretty.
Yoh Gwang said we need to stay together.
Let go of me.
You want me to go by myself?
And abandon you here?
I'm fine. So just leave.
Really?
Yoh Gwang made it sound like something
horrible will happen if I leave.
Is it because you're nervous?
Nervous that I might not
be your boundary?
That gives us more of
a reason to step outside.
We'll know once we step outside.
Whether I'm your boundary or not.
I saw a ghost! You freaking bastards.
Where's the guy you've
passed the palanquin on to?
- We don't know who he is.
- You don't?
So you just gave it to
a man you didn't know?
The palanquin I was in?
If you endanger the royal police,
who's going to protect the royal family?
This is treason!
I'm going to ask you for the last time.
Where is that bastard?
We really don't know who he is.
We just did it for the money.
So you don't know?
I just can't use nice words with you.
You'll talk once I cut some
parts off your body, right?
Which part would you like me to cut off?
Hm? Take your pick.
Grab them.
We really don't know who he is!
Soon Deuk!
It was a job offered by Soon Deuk.
- Soon Deuk?
- Yes.
She's that girl who shows up
at the gambling den sometimes.
She offered us the job.
What's this?
Hey. Ma Soon Deuk.
Let go of me!
Let go! Let me go!
Hey!
What are you doing
to a woman right now? Huh?
Politely.
Soon Deuk.
Where's Heo Joon? Hm?
- I don't know.
- I think you do.
I need to capture Heo Joon
no matter what.
I'm going to kill him
once I capture him.
If you won't tell me where he is,
I'll kill you too.
Tell me where he is.
Where is he? Tell me.
I can't tell you what I don't know.
He went his way.
I haven't seen him since that day.
You guys are trying to screw me over.
Hey.
So Heo Joon
went into hiding after threatening me.
So if he's in hiding
then I'll just have to
make him reveal himself.
Hey. This is pretty. Take a look.
Keep your head up and
keep your eyes on the road.
People are staring at you more because
you're excessively covering yourself.
They're wondering how
hideous you must be.
It's just because
there are too many people.
What are you doing?
See? You're fine.
No one is looking at you weirdly.
To those people
you're just one of the many others
passing by this street.
Not so different from those people.
Just a very ordinary person.
They might stare at you
because you're quite pretty
but that's you're fault for being pretty.
So you deal with it.
Don't worry about me
and you worry about yourself.
She's being shy.
Has he lost it?
What's wrong with him?
Stop it! Stop it!
I don't know who's supposed
to be whose boundary.
Wait for me.
Who's the dead person you wanted to see?
A friend of mine.
The person who was killed because of me.
It'll be hard for us to
find any evidence.
Search this area thoroughly and see
if there are any odd objects or signs.
Sir.
Are we trying to capture
the Red Gentleman's Robe?
Or Heo Joon?
Both.
If we capture Heo Joon
we may get a lead on
the Red Gentleman's Robe.
If we capture the Red Gentleman's Robe,
Heo Joon will appear at the scene.
What's this place for?
A gisaeng house.
A gisaeng house?
- Was your friend a gisaeng?
- Yeah.
- What's wrong?
- It's nothing.
Why is it so quiet?
Gisaeng houses are always
quiet during the day.
This is when everyone sleeps.
How are you so knowledgeable
in this area?
This is like my home.
What's wrong?
Stay here for a while.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Why would you fall down from there?
Get it together.
She's not here. Let's go.
How will we find any clues this way?
Do you know Man Weol by chance...
Have you seen Man Weol?
All right. I understand.
Anyways. Stay well.
What did she say?
Let's go.
Yeon Hui. Should we...
I'm so sick and tired of it.
Yeon Hui, come.
- Let's go.
- To where?
The place where Man Weol died.
She may be by the place she died,
not where she was living in.
Is she here?
No.
Thankfully, she must have
went to a better place.
Man Weol.
Who has made you like this?
Let's go.
Sol Gae. Let's go back.
Already?
Shouldn't we stake out
or something?
We don't know when he'll show up.
We can't even mobilize any forces
since it's a closed case.
I think it'll be really difficult to
capture the Red Gentleman's Robe.
You said the people who were killed
hung their wish plaques here, right?
Yes.
What happened to your friend?
I heard she got killed while she was
waiting for me at that watermill.
By that crazy murderer.
Why aren't you asking me
about what kind of person I am
and what my plans are?
You must be curious.
You didn't ask me any questions either.
Weren't you scared of how I looked?
I was a little surprised...
and my heart ached for you.
Where will this road take us?
I don't think this will
take us to Chungbing Temple.
There is this place I wanted to see
before we go back.
So this is the 100-year-old tree, huh?
[I wish to see my missed one again.]
[A Killing Tree]
Let's get back.
Monk Yoh Gwang must be very worried.
What is all of this stuff?
What do they mean by "A Killing Tree"?
Where have you been?
How could you leave this place?
I've asked you to stay by her side!
Not go outside with her!
I've told you our lives are on the line
and begged you for help!
Did it all sound like a joke to you?
The 100-year-old tree.
What has happened to it?
People are calling it "A Killing Tree."
Did the people who
hung their wish plaques...
die?
My candles was blown out 12 times.
Those people...
Are they all dead?
Was it that shamaness's doing?
I think she found out
about your candles.
She's been sending assassins to
whomever hangs their wish plaque
on the 100-year-old tree.
So all those people have died
because of me too.
Because of my curse.
That's not it, Seo Ri.
Why is that woman doing this to me?
Hm? With what purpose?
I stayed in the Black Forest
because I was told to.
I've been lighting candles because
I was told I have to break the curse.
Because I was cursed...
I thought that was why
the shamaness
has been trying to kill me.
So I thought all I had to do was
break the curse.
People have died because
I've been trying to break the curse!
No matter how hard I try...
can I never break free of this curse?
Calm down.
I vaguely understand what you're saying,
but it's not your fault.
Your friend.
Was she killed because of me?
Why would it be your fault?
I've told you.
It's the Red Gentleman's Robe's doing.
Let go of me, sir.
Let go of me.
Please.
Queen Dowager wants to speak to you.
How's His Majesty doing?
What are you worried about?
About his quick and sudden recovery?
Or about His Majesty passing away?
I should be worried.
He has the body
my crown prince will receive.
I'll pass the body on to Prince Soonhwe
once His Majesty is healthy and strong.
So set your worries aside.
I heard you're in charge of
the state of affairs.
I must protect the throne
my prince will inherit.
Hold a ceremony to wish for
the well-being of His Majesty.
Even the general public must have heard
about His Majesty's illness.
Shouldn't we pray for
a full recovery of his health?
I will follow your orders,
Your Highness.
Attend tomorrow morning's meeting,
and bring this subject up.
[I wish to see my missed one again.]
Because of me...
my mother passed away too.
my friend died.
Because I kept on blaming myself...
I couldn't do anything with my life.
But.
Is it really my fault?
I just wanted to live like a human being
and be a good son to my mother.
I just wanted to do what others do.
They told me that's doing wrong,
and I shouldn't do anything.
But I didn't want to live like that.
They said me being alive is a sin.
So I'm going to fight till death
for my life and live on.
And if I keep going at it
I could be a help to someone else
and I might find a reason to live.
[I wish to see my missed one again.]
The Chief Shamaness has attended
our meeting today to discuss the ceremony
we'll be holding to wish for
the recovery of His Majesty's health.
Also
since His Majesty's illness is serious
I would like to hold the ceremony
not only in Sungsuchung
but also in the Imperial Taoist Branch.
Are you planning on turning
the palace into a shaman's house?
You've went against your people's wishes
to reopen Sungsuchung.
Why would you not reopen
the Imperial Taoist Branch?
Reconstruction of
the Imperial Taoist Branch
is something you've wanted, too.
That's right.
I would have taken care of it myself.
Whether it's the Imperial Taoist Branch
or Sungsuchung
I would have taken care of everything
without wreaking havoc like this!
I also have already selected
the right man for the position.
So please...
just stay put, ma'am.
Please hold off on your decision.
The appointed chief of
the Imperial Taoist Branch is
someone who has been serving
his duties very well for a long time
and who is an independent thinker.
I would like to appoint
Lord Choi Hyun Seo to it.
I, Choi Hyun Seo
will adhere to Queen Dowager's wishes
and perform my responsibilities as
the chief of the Imperial Taoist Branch.
- Where is Lord Choi?
- He headed to Queen Dowager's place.
Since I've reinstated you as you wished
please tell me the truth now.
What did you mean when you said
Hong Joo impregnated me
through black magic
with a personal agenda?
She was trying to appoint a king
based on her wishes
and inhibit His Majesty from passing
the throne on to his direct successor.
By preventing the production
of the direct royal descents
she's trying to destroy Joseon.
That's Hong Joo's plan.
What do you mean she's trying to
destroy this country?
Hong Joo told me she'll break the curse.
Hong Joo can't break the curse.
The black magic has caused the curse
and she's been bound by that magic too.
Then what are we supposed to do?
Is there no way out of this?
There is someone
who can break the curse.
Who is it?
Crown Prince Soonhwe's twin sister.
The princess.
What do you mean by the princess?
Queen Dowager didn't just give birth
to Crown Prince Soonhwe.
She also gave birth to a twin girl,
a princess.
What did you say?
The princess was born through
a memorial service to a dead soul
and she was abandoned without a name.
Did you say a curse?
That curse is the reason
this country is full of misfortunes
and you're sick with that illness.
So Queen Dowager Yoon ordered
the princess to be killed
but Lord Choi Hyun Seo
saved the princess.
Why would he?
Drawn by sympathy,
he went against her orders.
Did you say that man is back in
the Imperial Taoist Branch now?
He has sided with Queen Dowager.
Queen Dowager has ruined this
country with her mistake...
and she has started something to
cover up her mistake.
That princess.
Where is she?
That girl was still alive?
The late king asked me to protect her.
The late king knew about all of this?
How much of it did he know?
Did he know about the curse?
How the prince and princess were born?
Yes.
It's all my fault.
I'm the one who has brought this upon
the late king and the crown prince.
The princess will stop Hong Joo.
She will?
I've been hiding the princess away
because I was afraid.
I told her to hide from Hong Joo
and try to break the curse.
Even when her life was in danger
and there was no way out
I made her stay in that place
without telling her anything.
The princess will know by now too.
The fact that she can't hide anymore.
She's a strong person.
She'll figure out what it is
that she has to do
and face the person
she has to stand against.
Sir, I have a favor to ask.
- Seo Ri.
- I'll go.
Since she's after me
the person who has made a wish
will only be safe if I go.
Even I can't win against
the Red Gentleman's Robe.
- What if you get captured by her?
- I'm aware of this.
How dangerous and reckless this is.
I'm worried you two might get hurt.
But...
I can't just do nothing for the person
who has become a target
from trusting me and making a wish.
So, what could you do?
The only thing I could do is
tell the Red Gentleman's Robe to
come see me if she wants something.
[I wish to see my missed one again.]
And make sure that she can't hurt
those who've hung their wish plaques.
What?
All right.
Facing her head on is
the right thing to do.
Why are you encouraging her?
Those cowardly people will take advantage
of you if you hide and run away.
We need to show them
we're not scared of them.
Because that's the truth. Am I right?
Are you in pain?
So why didn't you just stay put?
Why would you recklessly
try to go against me?
You've probably saved me to
kill Yeon Hui.
But.
I won't be controlled by you.
Is that what you think?
Then give me the princess
and rest in peace.
You're barely staying alive
through my black magic.
Don't you know?
If you would like to live,
hold on to my hand.
You'll regret the day
you've saved my life.
No matter what,
I'll make you die with this curse
that you've started.
You will?
Me?
You've always shown me your back.
I won't ever again show you my back
based on an empty hope.
I would like to see you try then.
But don't you forget how
you're staying alive right now.
If you're in unbearable pain,
don't hold it in and come see me.
What kind of elixir have you made?
It's an elixir that helps people
to have happy dreams.
Since the person wants to
see the one they miss
I'm going to let them.
At least in their dreams.
I think this is it.
Let's go.
Is anyone home?
- I'll take a look over there.
- Sure.
Let's go.
On the 100-year-old tree...
Have you hung your wish plaque?
Yeon Hui.
Older brother.
[Mirror of the Witch]
I thought you were done
hiding and running away?
You must secretly bring
the princess to me.
Thank you for staying alive.
Without you,
I wouldn't be like this either!
This is the only way I could keep you
from getting in my way.
Fine. Let Crown Prince's soul
wander around this world.
Don't be swayed by this!
I'm sorry for being a lame son.
I'm sorry I couldn't be your son.
So this was what you were
trying to do, Hong Joo.
I need to meet with
the princess as soon as possible.
There's a guy who would
sacrifice his life for the princess.
Come with me.
No one has told me about it.
I don't know why
I was born with this curse.
Yeon Hui!
He'll break the curse for the princess.
Subtitles by DramaFever