Seo Yeon.
Wake up.
Mom...
It's okay.
It's okay, Seo Yeon.
Dad...
Seo Yeon, listen up.
You...
You have to get out of here.
- Okay?
- Dad.
What about you?
I'll be out soon too.
So...
you have to go first...
and get some help.
- Dad...
- Okay.
Seo Yeon.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at us and go.
Mom and Dad will be fine.
So don't...
Don't look back.
Can you promise me?
Good girl.
Okay. Go now.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
Seo Yeon.
Don't look back.
Don't look at us and go.
Mom and Dad...
will be fine.
So don't look back.
Can you promise me?
Help us.
Please help us.
What?
What do you...
What do you mean?
An accident?
Which hospital?
Okay.
What is it?
A car accident.
They got into a car accident.
What?
I'm not sure. Let's go.
My gosh, man.
That's so crazy.
My goodness.
What is it?
What are you doing?
Goodness, stop it.
I don't remember what happened.
- What's with you?
- Who are you?
- Who do you think you are?
- My goodness!
Let him go!
What are you doing?
- Let him go!
- You! Hey! Let him go!
- What are you doing?
Goodness, are you okay?
- I'm going to kill you!
- Stop it!
- What's with you?
- Stop it! Won Seok!
I'll beat him to death.
Won Seok!
Are you a thug or what?
Handle it by the law!
- Just deal with it by the law!
- Shut your mouth.
If you say another word,
I'll kill you.
How's Seo Yeon?
She doesn't remember yet.
You should see our father...
one last time too.
I can't.
I can't do that.
How can I see him?
How...
I was supposed to feel guilty,
sad, and angry.
But I dumped it on my older brothers...
Mom...
and my baby brother,
and lived in oblivion.
Going out for a run?
It's not that we didn't tell you on purpose...
I understand why you did that.
I'm going for a run.
It's not your fault.
Don't get any weird ideas.
She definitely thinks everything is her fault, right?
Man, it's all over.
What's going on?
What's over?
Why are you up already?
Go to sleep. Go back to sleep.
What's going on?
I'm in here, so don't turn off the lights.
Joo Hee.
Did I wake you up?
Are all parents...
like that?
What?
Are they willing...
to sacrifice themselves for their kids?
Can they die in their kids' place?
Well...
I think so.
Are your parents like that too?
I don't remember much about my dad.
But my mom was like that.
In order to leave as much money as possible for my sister and me,
she worked at a restaurant until the day before she passed away.
She passed away?
Yes.
She was very ill.
Why did you ask that all of a sudden?
I didn't know parents were like that.
I had no idea.
I'm sure we'll get along just fine.
Everything will turn out fine.
I'll come with you.
I need to see this guy who's giving you so much trouble.
Wake up.
Seo Yeon.
Dad...
I'm sorry.
Mom and Dad will be fine.
Don't look back.
Can you promise me?
(Lee Kang Woo)
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail.
Is she still sleeping?
My heart was too fluttering for me to sleep well.
My gosh.
I'm going to take you to school!
What? Mr. Chief Director.
"Mister"?
Hey, I'm the same age as your sister.
Where is she?
- She went to school.
- Already?
- Sir.
- Don't address me like that!
Are you dating her?
"Dating"?
Well... I guess so.
Why?
You're rich and handsome, so why?
I guess you're too young to be aware of her charms.
But then again, it'd be really weird...
if you knew them.
Anyway...
I hope we get along well, my dear brother-in-law.
"Brother-in-law"?
Do you want a ride?
Yes.
Yes!
You're so simple-minded.
- Get out.
- What?
Here? Aren't you coming?
Are you not going to work?
- No.
- Why not?
Just because.
Have you been sacked?
Are you jobless?
No! Go tell your sister to come out!
I don't want her to date someone jobless.
Why would she date someone jobless?
Hey, that's not true. I'm not jobless!
What a rude brat!
Seo Yeon.
The ex-chief director is waiting in front of the school.
By the way,
I thought you hated good-looking men.
Go, now. He's waiting for you.
Okay.
Go to class.
Seo Jun.
I'm sorry.
[VIU Ver] MBC E21 'Love with Flaws'
"Seo Yeon Blames Herself"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
My gosh, I got goosebumps.
What's wrong with her?
Gosh.
Do I look okay?
Hey!
What are you doing here?
I heard there was a suspicious car.
I came to check whether it was a pervert or not.
"Pervert"?
Who said that?
Are you protesting since you've been sacked?
No, I'm here to see Seo Yeon.
It's her.
Let's meet next time. I'm busy right now.
Move your car right now.
I wish I worked here as well.
Did the ex-chief director leave?
Yes, he just did.
Was he that obedient?
With that temper of his, he must've put up a fight.
I mean, it's nothing much.
It wasn't anything intentional.
But we told the chairwoman...
- a bit about him.
- A tiny bit.
- Yes, just a little bit.
- Just this much.
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
Why didn't she appoint such a wonderful man like you...
from the start?
Why did she appoint Kang Woo?
I know, right?
- I just can't understand.
- Me neither.
Anyway, we'll go now.
Thank you, sir.
Goodness.
All right.
- Thank you, sir.
- You never know what will happen.
Wait up.
I'm sure Aunt didn't do anything just yet.
What are you doing?
I need to take care of my own son.
Min Hyuk is whom you cherish the most.
Are you sulking because I removed Kang Woo from his position?
Yes, you're right.
Can you really not trust him?
He's never proven himself.
Exactly. That's exactly why...
I'll be taking care of him from now on.
And is your definition of that scheduling his blind date?
There are so many wonderful women out there, so why?
What?
Why is your wife so upset? Why?
Is it because I'm bringing Kang Woo into the headquarters?
No, it's not that.
Kang Woo must be dating someone.
- What?
- That's why she's been so mad.
What kind of girl is she?
- I don't know either.
- Who is she?
- Hear me out, Mom.
- Okay.
You and I should be on the same team.
And if we help Kang Woo,
- Kang Woo will get...
- Mi Ja!
- What is it?
- What are you doing, Mom?
- What's this all about?
- Stop it, Mom.
- Mi Ja.
Oh, no. This is awful.
I made this worse.
Kang Woo. I should tell him.
Mom. Mom! Goodness.
The water. The water is boiling. Hold on.
It's boiling. Wait. Where is that thing?
Goodness.
You are indeed talented.
Gosh. I can picture...
Park Seok Min and Hi-Seven in these outfits.
Gosh, the smell of money.
What's on your mind?
We shared our feelings...
and had a good time.
We even went on a date.
How could she not call me back the next day?
Is it about Seo Yeon?
Hey, she's not like you.
She must be in class.
What's she doing during her breaks? What about her lunchtime?
Texting me or giving me a call isn't that hard.
- How many times did you reach out?
- 10 times.
You sent 10 text messages?
No, I called 10 times. I sent 20 text messages.
How sickening.
Gosh, how sickening.
- Sickening?
- Come on. Know when to stop.
She'll get sick of you and run to the hills before this goes anywhere.
Is that what happened?
(Idiot)
Gosh, he's so sickening.
Hyun Soo keeps calling me.
I guess Hyun Soo really likes you.
It's hard to resist my charms once men fall for me.
I'm like a swamp.
What's wrong? You don't like him at all?
Well,
he's not a bad guy by nature,
but I'm not sure. Something doesn't feel right.
I could tell he has a lot of women around him.
And I don't feel comfortable...
because his label is bigger than I thought.
I thought you were interested in men's assets.
Now that I see a man with assets beyond my expectations,
I do feel a bit intimidated as I'm only human.
I don't want men who are richer than me by 10 places.
3 to 4 places higher would be perfect for me.
I'm talking about me. That's just me.
This has nothing to do with you and Kang Woo, right?
Hey, I'm getting hungry.
Let's go steal some food from the Health Office.
- No, I don't want to.
- What? Why not?
Just because.
He's not the school doctor anymore. He's the chief director now.
We can't be casual like before.
I don't believe it.
Did Mr. Lee finally...
Seo Yeon won't come here now.
Even if you prepare snacks for her,
she won't be coming here anymore, Mr. Chief Director.
Why not?
Do you have to ask?
Why were you confident enough to confess your feelings to her?
Don't get the wrong idea.
You know that she's not the type to discuss this with other people.
I catch on really quickly. That's all.
Was it your confidence or arrogance?
My stubbornness.
I thought so.
It's not just anyone. It's Kang Woo.
You guys are cousins.
Stop pursuing her, so Seo Yeon doesn't feel uncomfortable.
I'm not sure.
I'm a bit selfish.
I don't like it when things go well for other people.
Gosh. That line with that face. That was super cool.
Goodness, does he have his phone glued to him all day?
What?
What is it? Talk. You called me.
I didn't know you'd actually pick up.
I called you out of habit.
Are you kidding me?
- Bye.
- Let's have a meal.
Have a meal with me.
Come to think of it, we never had a meal together.
No.
- Why not?
- Then, we'll be friends.
What?
Seriously? She asked me to buy her a meal a while ago.
Gosh. She doesn't like money or food. What am I supposed to do?
That little munchkin. She's so cute.
Good morning. Hello, Seo Yeon. Aren't you on your break now?
Did you eat? Did you eat a lot?
I guess you're very busy.
I want to see you.
Call me after you finish work!
(Lee Kang Woo)
I caught you at the right time.
It looks like you really need these guys.
- Well...
- As you know,
I don't have a lot of friends because I'm wary of people.
You probably figured that out at the meeting.
Can't you eat with me?
I'll just eat.
As you can see, this happened.
Well, good for you.
This is all thanks to your hard work.
You told me to face my trauma...
to overcome my trauma.
Thanks to that advice, I met Seo Yeon again.
Then, I don't think you need to come in again after today.
But you see,
how am I supposed to date a woman?
Dating is not my area of expertise. However,
all of our psychological problems have one source.
What's the problem?
Which one should I ask you first?
Take your time.
(Management)
It's Seo Yeon.
At the bus stop...
Why didn't you take the bus?
I just walked home.
Did you wait for me at the bus stop?
No. Why would we?
We were exercising.
We met you here by chance.
Let's pretend that we did and have a drink.
Yes. Let's have a drink.
What? A drink?
(Episode 22 will air shortly.)
(Episode 22)
We're sorry we didn't tell you before.
I was 15 back then.
If I had known at that time,
I probably couldn't bear it.
I know that you two did it...
because you were worried about me and wanted to protect me.
Thank you.
Seo Yeon, you're all grown up.
I was worried...
that you would hate and blame us for not telling you.
Won Jae, are you crying?
I'm not. Who's crying?
Don't cry.
I'm not.
I'm not crying.
Let him be. He's in full menopause.
(Craft Beer)
You know,
I know you're all grown up,
but do you have to drink when I'm around?
I drank often around Won Seok.
I'm a regular at his place.
You should be stopping her instead of giving her drinks.
She's a better drinker than you.
No way.
You should learn to drink from me.
Our farewell is here already
Do not cry even if you are sad
- Yesterday, I cried - Will you be quiet?
Won Jae can't drink at all.
He doesn't live up to his build.
I'm sorry! My dear Seo Yeon.
I'm sorry.
- Quiet. - Hey!
Without a heart that hate, hate
- Hate you - What's going on?
I was wondering who's being so noisy,
- and it's you, Won Jae. - Hey.
My dear baby brother.
My little puppy.
- I'm sorry! - Smells.
- Why? - Hey, you take him.
You're heavy.
My dear, Seo Jun. I'm sorry.
- Why did he drink so much? - I'm sorry!
- My gosh. - Will you be quiet?
Without a heart that hate, hate, hate you
Stop being so loud! Darn it.
What?
Hey.
That's Seo Yeon's boyfriend.
What?
You should go in.
Let me introduce myself once again.
I am Lee Kang Woo.
Go inside.
- Hey, that guy... - Come on.
- honked at me. - Be quiet.
- He honked at me! - I told you to be quiet.
I'm going to kill him if he does that again.
You're getting kind of annoying.
Won Seok.
What's going on, Seo Yeon?
Is your phone out of battery?
Is it broken?
Never mind, I'm sure something happened.
Wait, did you...
already get sick of me?
I'm sorry, Kang Woo.
No, it's okay.
I'm not that angry.
So why were you out of touch the whole day?
Because I would want to see you if I heard your voice.
Don't you think you like me a bit too much?
Hold your horses.
No, never mind. I take that back.
Like me so much that I drive you crazy.
Completely.
Okay?
You're heavy.
Stay there even if I'm heavy.
You're a woman who can bear this much weight.
My dear Kang Woo.
What did you...
just say? Did you just say...
"my dear Kang Woo"?
If I...
become really mean to you,
you should hate me a lot.
- What? - You should cuss at me...
and blame me, okay?
Don't hold yourself back.
Okay?
No matter how mean you are to me,
the moment you say,
"my dear Kang Woo",
everything will be fine.
So when you're heartbroken...
or angry,
you can take out everything on me.
Everything.
I won't bother you like this again.
Call me when you have time.
I'll hold myself back even if I want to hear your voice...
or even if I miss you.
I'll wait patiently.
Go inside.
I'll see you off first.
Okay, then.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Are you dating him again?
No.
You aren't dating him again?
Is it him?
The boy...
that you went to see with Mom and Dad on that night.
Your middle school friend...
that you wronged in the past.
It's him, isn't it?
Are you okay?
When things get tough,
please help me out, Won Seok.
Anytime.
That easily?
She's pretending to be okay, isn't she?
You're sober already?
I get drunk quickly, and I sober up quickly too.
Keep your eyes on her!
Things look very dangerous for her right now!
You weren't asleep yet?
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
They have the same facial features.
It's the same guy.
I asked them to go.
It's because of me.
They passed away because of me.
Because of me.
Seo Yeon.
It's because of me.
They passed away because of me.
No, it's because of him.
He's the grandson of Shinhwa Food?
What do you do when you have free time?
Answer me.
What?
What do you do when you have free time?
What was that for?
I heard you got sacked...
and will be working at the headquarters.
That's the report for the last quarter.
- Read that. - Why would I?
You know what I'm doing.
And are you doing that right now?
How could you have free time when you're working on that?
You must be taking it easy.
Since you said you didn't want any of my money,
I thought you were taking it seriously.
I mean...
I wasn't talking about my working time.
Who was that woman last time at the police station?
- It's someone I like. - Which family? Name?
Joo family's only daughter among many sons.
I may be able to do that, but not you.
I can pick whoever I want, but not you.
What do you mean?
Can you introduce her to Mom and Grandma this instant?
- Of course. - You're so selfish.
What do you have?
Have you proven yourself regarding your work?
Are you financially independent?
Being so reckless could hurt her.
Don't underestimate Mom.
When it comes to her children, she's stronger than anyone else.
Especially if it's concerning you.
Kang Woo.
No, you're right. You made me realize it.
You're right.
You don't need to comfort me.
What do you mean?
- Pick that up. - What?
What? Okay.
I'm all for it.
No matter who you pick, I support you completely.
So please do the same for me.
Deal?
Deal.
Sir, are you waiting for someone's call?
No. Don't be ridiculous.
I should've dropped her in front of her house.
Did she trip on her way home?
What if she busted her knees?
Lee Kang Hee speaking.
Are you okay?
What?
Mr. Joo Won Jae?
Did you go home safely that night?
Of course.
I thought something happened since you didn't call.
Have you been waiting?
What? Not really.
Do you want to have dinner?
If you already have plans, then we could take a rain check.
I have no plans.
I didn't make any because I was waiting for your call.
Whenever and wherever. From 6pm to 12am.
We've made a deal.
You're a hardworking employee.
I'm glad we've made a deal.
Of course. I'm like no other.
I'm quite competent, you see.
So...
I'll see you later tonight.
I'm so embarrassed.
Did you have to go on and on like that?
I'll see you later, Mr. Joo.
You're so selfish.
What do you have?
Have you proven yourself regarding your work?
Okay!
Let's meet in the evening. I have something to...
(Let's meet in the evening. I have something to...)
My gosh.
Who are you?
[VIU Ver] MBC E22 'Love with Flaws'
"Seo Yeon's Decision"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Aunt?
I knew you were Mr. Lee's aunt.
But I couldn't connect the dots and think you were Kang Woo's mom.
Welcome.
Come to think of it, I saw you last time as well.
I'm such a fool. What a fool.
By the way, what brings you here?
I heard you're dating my son.
- What? - Don't be so startled.
Did you think I'd never find out?
I'll make it short.
Break up with him.
You shouldn't underestimate our family.
I understand that it'll be difficult to end things with him.
That's why I'm going to make it easier for you.
Okay, I'll do that.
I'm sorry for making you concerned.
I mean...
What? That was too easy.
I'd prepared 10 envelopes.
She didn't even take a look.
This place is cozier than I had thought.
Are you okay?
I saw my aunt.
Don't worry.
Kang Woo will never let go of you.
That is, unless you let go of him first.
He won't...
unless I give up first, right?
Right. He won't give up on you first.
Right. Please don't tell Mi Kyung about this.
It will upset her.
Okay. Don't worry.
Thank you.
I'm always grateful.
Mother, what if Kang Woo finds out?
You should have stopped her.
Goodness. I had no choice given the family she comes from.
You also heard what Mr. Kim said.
She lost her parents early in life...
and have half brothers.
Goodness.
Once he finds out, he'll be furious.
You know that Kang Woo can be even more stubborn than Kang Hee...
if he doesn't like something.
That's why I just need to keep your mouth shut.
Mom, I have a meeting to attend to.
- Sit down. - Okay.
Hand me your cellphone.
- Pardon? - Until his problem is sorted out,
I'll keep your phone.
Mom, I'm a working businessman.
I get a lot of work calls.
Now.
But still.
I must get some calls related to work.
Goodness.
Honey.
What happened?
I'm not sure if she's bold...
or stupid.
What do you mean?
She won't break up with him?
No.
She obediently said that she would.
What?
How many envelopes did you give her?
None.
What?
Look who's here.
Is it because you're the chief director?
You got off work early.
You're not a better chief director than me.
You look good.
I came by just in case.
So you really have no idea.
What are you talking about?
You don't know even if someone next to you is in pain...
or is about to die.
What?
Do you know...
what doctors must be the most careful about in the OR?
Pride.
Even a doctor who performed the surgery hundreds of times...
will make a mistake the moment he feels proud...
of his competency.
It won't be that bad...
if the doctor admits his mistake and walks out.
But once he begins to be stubborn about it, it becomes a problem.
What is your point?
Don't let your guard down.
If you make a mistake,
I will never waste that chance.
Seriously? You already got off work?
She's been MIA the whole day too.
Darn it.
Jung Ho, why didn't you come to practice today?
I told the dance teacher that you were sick.
Call me as soon as you get this.
Who are you? Why are you...
Joo Hee?
Look at you.
What? No tutoring lesson today again?
What? No.
Ho Dol texted me.
Won Seok, did you see Joo Hee just now?
Why does she look like that?
- What do you mean? - I mean...
Joo Hee didn't look like herself.
How is she supposed to look then?
Do you have to ask?
Sneakers, pants, and short hair.
But she was wearing makeup and a skirt.
Forget it.
What did your tutor say?
- What? - Why couldn't he make it?
He just said he couldn't.
Is he sick or something?
These babies must be so suffocated here.
When they look at other cars, racing on the street,
they must be jealous, right?
Do you feel suffocated...
in your office too?
I'm hungry.
Come here.
Take a seat.
These are new. So don't worry and put them on.
Thank you.
What did you have for lunch?
I just had a glass of milk.
I had a feeling.
This looks really good.
I've been to a lot of restaurants because I do sales.
This restaurant serves the most authentic home-cooked meal.
You bought the meal for me?
Well, I'm sure...
other guys probably already took you to fancy restaurants.
I just wanted you to have a meal comfortably...
even if it's just a meal.
Here.
Not really.
- You don't feel comfortable? - I've been...
to expensive and fancy restaurants before.
But I haven't been there with men.
Why not?
You must have dated a lot of men.
38?
You dated 38 men.
For 38 years,
I have never officially dated a man.
I've gone on a few blind dates.
But I had to study, learn about the company,
and work.
This really does taste like a home-cooked meal.
Won Seok.
Won Seok. Did you see this?
Why are you here again?
I thought your label stopped you from coming here.
As if!
Do you know how much money I bring in for the company?
Listen, Won Seok. Did you watch this?
This is totally crazy.
Shall we date?
(A Gay Getting Outed in Real-Time)
- I can't believe this. - No way.
- What's this? - I didn't know this about you.
I don't know. This dummy got outed...
which is really unfortunate for him.
Will you keep this up? What is it?
This is priceless. Smile for me.
- Ho Dol. - Just say it.
Did you really think I'd be like you?
Something is definitely up with Seo Yeon.
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail.
See? She's not answering her phone.
Yes. I came all the way to the last transmission location.
Let me look into this and call you back.
Excuse me.
Have you seen a woman like this around here?
No. I have not.
Okay.
But who are you?
I'm a police officer.
Bye.
No way. Why is the police officer looking for Baek Jang Mi?
What on earth is happening at this house?
I'm a crazy woman.
I'll be the only crazy one.
Just me.
Didn't I do a good job?
I didn't bother you, right?
I thought about you only a bit...
and worked a lot.
Wasn't I good?
Yes, you were.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
How much is this house?
- What? - Are you the owner?
Oh, it's registered under my name.
And all these things are yours?
I guess so.
Won Jae has a suit from this brand too.
He has great taste.
He's probably still paying it back because he bought it over 36 months.
You paid for it at once, didn't you?
Yes.
You really are awfully rich, Kang Woo.
What's wrong?
I suddenly realized it.
Realize what?
Your place and my place.
- What? - I had forgotten...
that you're the grandson of Shinhwa Food.
Why did I forget that?
Don't I seem really stupid?
It doesn't make any sense for you and me to be together.
Do you know why my brothers and I don't look alike?
They aren't my biological brothers.
As you know, both of my parents...
have passed away too.
I'm an orphan. An orphan.
What are you doing right now?
Need I explain more?
You're making me feel kind of miserable.
Let's call this off while it's not too deep.
Not too deep?
It's obvious.
I'll suffer from more damage if I date you any longer.
Were you...
counting numbers while you were dating me?
You have no idea.
You've never been the one who has less power.
So Kang Woo,
- let's break up. - Seo Yeon!
What's wrong, Seo Yeon?
What is it?
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Don't say that, Seo Yeon.
You have a guest with you.
Who are you?
Pardon?
Are you Kang Woo's girlfriend?
Yes, she's my girlfriend.
Why? You are. You're my woman.
(Love with Flaws)
She doesn't like you because you're handsome, then you're too ugly,
and now it's because you're a grandson of a rich woman?
Enough is enough!
I got you!
Who are you?
I'll protect Seo Yeon.
What if I don't need anything else but her?
Do you think that's crazy?
Whatever. I'm getting kind of sulky.
I'm going to kill myself.
Don't cry. Please don't cry.
Just toy me around, then abandon me.
Get a hold of yourself. You seem crazy.
Kang Woo is bleeding to death.
Why do you get scared and give up on me?
I don't love you.