That question earlier.
I don't...
hate you.
You're such a good person. How could I hate you?
No matter what anyone says,
you're...
a friendly...
and warm-hearted...
person to me.
I wish I could be...
someone like that for you, as well.
But I can't...
and I also shouldn't.
So...
don't be sick.
(Frog, Snake)
Don't go.
Stay with me.
Where did she go?
Move over.
This is a dream. It's a nightmare.
Let go of my finger.
- What are you doing to do?
- I'm the one who should ask.
You're in the men's room.
My life is over if we get caught. Leave right now.
Who is it?
Good morning, Seung Hyeon.
- Have you seen Dal Nim?
- Dal Nim?
Why would you ask me?
You know this is the men's room.
I thought she might be here because she was drunk last night.
Where could she be?
My legs look too long.
Really? Maybe she's taking a walk with Bo Nui.
She left last night with Mr Je.
My back is killing me.
- They did?
- They threw Mr Je in the water.
They threw Soo Ho in the water?
He seemed very upset. No wonder why he left at that hour.
I'll go look for Dal Nim.
Mr Je went back to Seoul?
What's wrong?
This.
Let's take this out as well.
You promised not to include any love life, gossip or rumours.
If you throw random questions on live broadcast,
- I'm going to pull him out myself.
- Not even his first love?
We'll make it sound nice.
Make it sound nice.
It must sound beautiful no matter what.
Okay.
First love...
What about me?
I was too young back then.
But after seeing you again, I know for certain.
The memories we have...
are very special.
You're right.
They were special.
Right? You agree, don't you?
Whether it was in spring or fall and in 2004 or 2005...
You remember every detail.
That's what first love is about.
I'm not sure if it was love to be honest.
I don't know what love is.
It's true that you were once my everything.
You were my everything.
You were for me at the time.
How about now?
They might be looking for us. Let's go inside.
I was his everything.
So it's the past tense.
It's 10 minutes before the start. Please get him on standby.
Okay.
Please don't move.
Yes, Mr Gary Choi.
Did Bo Nui leave?
She left to Seoul last night with Mr Je.
- They went together?
- Together.
(Frog, Snake)
Geon Uk!
He's sleeping well.
Thank goodness.
(Frog, Snake)
The number you have dialled...
The winner of Australian Open Tennis Championships 2016.
I introduce Mr Gary Choi.
Hello.
Hello, I am Gary Choi, also known as Choi Geon Uk.
Your Korean name is Choi Geon Uk.
This is your first time to reveal it, isn't it?
Yes.
Since I was little, I've been called Gary.
Your family background or history has never been revealed.
So many people are curious...
to know about it.
That's perhaps why...
Gary is nervous right now.
As an icebreaker, we will show you...
Gary's childhood video to which we exclusively gained access.
Let's watch it.
They were taken a long time ago,
but please pay attention to it.
If you either know him or have seen him,
please contact me.
What's the use of earning millions of dollars a year?
He doesn't know where his father is.
Have you ever resented him?
I resented him enormously.
Geon Uk!
I am sorry. I'm too late.
How did it go? Did it already end?
Where are you coming from?
I've been watching the show in the bus.
So where have you been?
Let's go out. Let's talk outside.
Gosh...
I am sorry.
Something came up.
- What came up?
- Mr Je was a little unwell.
I had to stay beside him.
Did he get into an accident? Or did he get a surgery?
He really almost died, right?
That's why you didn't answer my calls and got here just now.
Right?
Why would you say that?
- If he gets some rest...
- If it's not that, why would you...
If it's not that, why would you stay with him all night?
I'm sorry about coming late.
But a person was sick. You should understand.
No.
I can't do that.
I don't want to.
What is he to you?
What is he to you that you're pushing me away?
I know Bo Ra far better than he does.
Why do you keep taking him to see her?
Why are you upset? You are scaring me.
Because I like you.
Right.
I like you.
I feel certain now that I said it.
- Bo Nui.
- Stop it.
I think it's your anger speaking.
If you go on,
you will regret it later.
- No.
- I know it.
You and I...
We're not like that, Geon Uk.
Gary.
- You're here.
- Yes.
The director of the channel wants to see you.
We need to wrap it up.
Go back in there.
I'll see you at night.
I mean I will see you later.
Soo Ho! Soo Ho!
Soo Ho, I am here! Soo Ho!
What happened to him? Soo Ho!
Soo Ho! Soo Ho!
I told you to call before coming.
You are alive! Gosh, my darling Soo Ho.
I heard you fell in the water.
My heart was throbbing that I almost died on the way here.
By the way, why are you so okay?
What?
You even ate?
Did you...
Did you stay up all night with Bo Nui?
- Because I like you.
- No.
What is he to you?
What is he to you that you're pushing me away?
You're in love.
You miss her when she's not around and rely on her when you're sick.
You want to stay with her a little longer...
that you keep searching for her.
Look at you. You're not denying it.
This is just unbelievable.
I raised a tiger.
By the way, did you text her?
About the next date?
You didn't text, call or chat with her at all?
Hey! You have to move your boat when the tide is rising!
Bo Ra, what am I supposed to do?
(Mr Je)
What are you doing later today?
(To Mr Je)
How are you feeling?
(How are you feeling?)
You idiot!
You shouldn't send these!
You told me to send her emoticons!
Not these.
Be more charming. Send her a heart emoticon.
Don't you know about those dancing characters?
- What are the fingers mean?
- Hi.
- How about this one with a turban?
- It's smiling.
Tell me honestly.
You lied about your IQ, right?
Gosh... See? There's no reply.
After three minutes, it's time to send a new message.
But it's already been five minutes, and she's not replying.
She ignored it. What should you do?
I will text her for you.
For some reason,
you look strangely excited.
You should go on date with that wit.
Stop riding the bike every single day.
Doesn't your bottom hurt?
- Go.
- I'm sorry.
- Just get out.
- Let's wait a little more.
- You shouldn't have said that.
- Gosh.
- I can help you. Wait.
- Go.
You received a text message.
What are you doing? Give it back.
You poor thing.
Are you feeling better?
See you at work on Monday.
Bo Nui seems to be keeping you at a safe distance.
She's too good of an employee.
You'll probably want a drink soon. Call me.
Actually, see you on Monday.
The broadcasting station will give us a list of all the calls they get.
- Don't worry.
- Thank you.
Did Bo Nui give that to you?
I had my suspicions.
Since when?
I don't know.
It's either the day I saw her again...
or the day I waited for her all night.
It's embarrassing that you found out.
Are you thinking of dating her?
Date?
That sounds good. Shall I try that?
- Go for it.
- I didn't expect that.
I thought you'd be against it.
If you can break up with her after dating for a month,
I'm all for it.
Don't forget.
You're Gary Choi and you have to go back.
You have a month left to bask in your memories.
Hi.
Is Geon Uk home?
- Is that for Gary?
- Yes.
I feel bad I was late.
Do you also feel bad for running away after hearing how he feels?
Do you know about it?
At times, I'm closer to him than his friends or family.
I think he is confused.
We rely on and support each other.
That's why he is confused.
Sometimes, people don't know what they feel.
What about you?
Are you sure about your feelings?
For Geon Uk?
I don't have feelings for him.
You should've come earlier.
Why did you come so late and upset him?
Something came up.
Mr Je wasn't feeling well.
Soo Ho?
What happened?
Was he in some kind of accident?
The employees played a joke on him and threw him in the pool.
It wasn't too bad.
Did he go to a hospital?
- He wanted to go home.
- You should've known better!
You should've taken him to the hospital.
You could've at least called me.
This situation wasn't your call. You know that?
Why are you yelling at me?
Mr Je is okay now. I took care of him all night.
I was late because I had to make sure he fell asleep.
There's something you don't know about.
I know about it, too.
The accident he was in as a child.
How...
do you know about it?
Did...
Soo Ho tell you?
Yes.
I should get going.
Why was I fighting with her?
I have no right.
Don't go.
I won't go anywhere.
"I'll stay here with you."
"Should we get dinner?"
"Are you free tomorrow?"
That sounds better.
Are you free tomorrow?
(To Shim Bo Nui)
(From Shim Bo Nui)
Why do you ask?
"If you don't have any plans,"
"should we get dinner?"
"If you're free, should we get dinner?"
Let's get dinner if you're free.
I have plans.
She's always busy. Why is she so busy?
Should I go see her?
What should I tell her then? I can't say I missed her.
Ryang Ha?
It's Seol Hui.
I can't talk right now.
Is someone crying?
It's a goat. Let's talk later unless it's urgent.
It's about Soo Ho.
Why is everyone so worried about him?
What?
He's fine. Don't worry. I'll talk to you later.
Wait a second.
I've been saving myself...
for the past 26 years.
How could such an annoying guy like him...
be the man I spent my first night with?
Stop crying. I didn't do anything to you.
Listen, Dal Nim. Let's make this clear.
You were the one who came to my room.
Delete everything about last night from your memory.
I'm here to tell you we can't be together.
It was the opportunity of my life.
Are you shooting a drama? Do you have a camera hidden?
The drive back to Seoul with him...
Just the two of them...
I should've been the one leaving with him.
You're finally admitting that you like Soo Ho.
Try not to speak to me from now on.
Should I tell you something about Soo Ho?
- Tell me about it.
- You're a turn off.
Come on.
Before I say anything,
tell everyone here that nothing happened between us.
- Look.
- I spent my first night...
with this man sitting here.
Are you running away again?
Did you see me?
Should I leave if I'm making you uncomfortable?
No, stay here.
Is she not at home?
(Mr Je)
The number you have dialled is not available at this moment.
Please call again.
What are you doing?
I'm taking this for later.
You always miss the people you like.
- Geon Uk.
- I'm sorry for yelling at you.
It wasn't cool, was it?
Geon Uk.
- I...
- Don't say anything.
I haven't tried anything yet.
I'm going to do my very best to impress you and open your heart.
I want you to answer after I try everything.
With that said,
if you're free tomorrow,
let's go on a date.
Geon Uk!
Yes. Smile like that.
That's all I need.
See you.
Why is she not coming?
I was going to go after giving her the photos.
(I'm at the park. I have something to give you. Answer the phone.)
I am at the park.
I have something to give you.
Answer the phone.
(Mr Je)
It's for the better.
Who is it?
It's me.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I didn't get to sleep all night.
My head was about to explode.
What?
And I can't erase this.
If I erase this,
the memory from the night with you...
will probably be erased, too.
So I can't erase it.
I know it's impossible.
I know that these letters exist physically...
and have no contact with flowing time. I know that.
But it's just how I feel.
What is this?
You don't make sense...
no matter how many times I redo the calculations.
No function can solve you. So you are really a bug.
You are messing up my head, my life and my everything.
But I...
don't want to kill that bug.
I want it...
to stay in my head.
What should I do about this?
Should I kill it?
Or not?
You barged in early in the morning. What are you talking about?
Go. Okay?
Did you get dumped?
When the first serve fails, there's the second.
When I lose on the first set, I get to try again on the second set.
Give it to me.
That's true.
Okay.
What? Both of them confessed at the same time?
How can this happen when my love is a thorn path?
Hey.
I am so happy for you!
That's so good to hear!
It's Gary, right?
You will be punished if you lie.
When we were at the workshop,
he kept calling and looked for you.
I can't believe it!
He will soon stop.
He has to go back to Canada anyway.
Who's the other one?
Who would compete against the top of the human race?
It's someone you don't know.
Do you think I don't know about your small social circle?
It's him, isn't it?
It's the guy who keeps touching you gently like summer breeze.
It will only last for a while.
When it passes,
I will remember and thank how warm that breeze was.
I will remember it with a smile.
That's more than enough for me.
Don't be stupid.
Do you know how hard it is for a man and a woman to feel the same?
Just go with the flow.
Ride the wind and go to him.
No.
Just give me tips on how to reject a man.
You're so foolish.
How can you ask me that when I've only been on one-sided love?
I've never rejected a man!
How would I know?
Stop teasing me.
You are a bad girl.
Hi, Soo Ho.
It works. Bye.
What is it?
I was checking if it's broken.
Call me right back.
- I think I can't receive calls.
- Don't torture me.
- Just call Bo Nui.
- No.
Hi.
I don't need it. I'm good.
I am a sports agent, you know?
I know all about diet and dietary supplements.
Use your knowledge to take care of Gary. I'm okay.
I think Gary needs Bo Nui more than me.
Do you know?
- They...
- Don't tell me.
I don't want to hear it.
Right.
You don't like talking about other people.
My bad.
I like her.
That's why.
No way.
You're mistaken.
You said that you don't know what love is.
I'll have to find out if it's love or not.
Are you two...
already going out?
- Not yet.
- Okay.
That's all I need to know.
I should get going.
Okay, bye.
Am I being punished for hurting you?
You may be shaken for a while.
It took me too long to come back.
Don't say that.
It's me, Seol Hui.
I was everything to you.
Don't get sick. It hurts to see you like that.
Good night.
We have to check the employee pass, visitor's pass, barcode and iris?
Don't you think that's much?
Security is everything when it comes to IT companies.
Did you go over all the duties for the night shift?
Of course I did.
People used to call me Mr Meticulous.
I wrote it down right here.
There is a short man that comes here drunk...
between 11pm and 1am.
That's Mr Je's father. Don't let him in.
I feel bad for Mr Je.
No wonder why he's so sensitive.
Our personalities are formed during our early childhood.
He stops his own father from visiting his office...
- He's here.
- Hello.
Good morning.
Hi.
- How do you find the work?
- Yes?
Zeze Factory is like a paradise.
- It's nice.
- I see.
Oh, right.
If you run into people you know,
you should tell them how nice this place is.
To Bo Nui?
I was talking about all the employees here.
- Okay, I'll also tell Bo Nui.
- I mean...
I guess that includes her.
You do what you have to do. Have a nice day.
You, too!
Something's definitely going on between them.
Good morning.
Why hasn't he pushed the button?
Aren't you getting in, Mr Je?
Are you still upset?
- Why?
- About the joke we played on you...
Let's talk in the office.
- Close the door and go up.
- Okay.
Good morning.
Hi.
It's 28 hours and 15 minutes.
I mean us.
It's been 28 hours and 15 minutes since I last saw you.
Don't you...
have anything to tell me?
No, I don't.
He can't still be upset.
"Let's talk in the office."
That's what he said.
You idiots should all have resignations prepared.
It was for the unity of our team.
Can't the president...
sacrifice himself for that purpose? No, he can't.
Should we write our resignations by hand?
We should type it out.
- I'm going to handwrite it.
- Gosh.
- Good morning.
- Bo Nui.
Was Mr Je very upset that day?
- Is he mad at us?
- Why would you think I'm mad?
The people who ganged up and threw you in the pool...
are handing in their resignations.
Well...
I'm sorry.
What?
Are you making it a habit to hand in your resignation?
Are you serious?
We have four weeks left until the beta test.
Do you have the schedule ready?
I'll bring it to you before lunch.
Did you monitor Gary's broadcast?
Oh, I forgot.
I want you to remember where you work.
You don't need to work too hard. Just do...
Don't you think you should do a proper job?
I have high expectations.
What?
I'm counting on you.
What is going on?
- Falling into water must have...
- He must have gone crazy.
- His brain isn't...
- It isn't functioning right.
Bo Nui, what happened?
Did you turn both of them down?
I'm planning to.
I don't have the luxury to date.
How could you give up so easily?
I can never do that.
I spent my first night with this man sitting here.
Why are you doing this to me?
This is how you get Soo Ho interested in you.
Be quiet and write it down.
Soo Ho is...
Be objective.
Be cold.
Be confident.
What's going on?
I'm speechless.
- Mr Je!
- Gosh!
Do you know how many times I knocked on your door?
- You knocked?
- Here's the schedule.
I need your approval.
It's hot in here.
Dal Nim.
It's hot in here, isn't it?
I don't understand why it's so hot.
This is all because of global warming.
It's due to environmental pollution.
I'm part of an environmental movement. Drink this.
Wait a second.
It had trash on it.
He's so sweet.
Where is my other half?
You scared me!
- I think it really worked!
- Let go of me.
What are you talking about?
You told me to be objective, cold and confident.
It worked.
That can't be true.
This is a historic day.
Thank you!
I was coaching her to get dumped.
She came back crazy
She's insane
Make sure you don't leave anything out.
Right.
Okay, I'll call again later. Bye.
Hi, Bo Nui.
I heard you wanted to see me.
Have you had lunch?
I'm sorry about the other day.
I was so worried when I heard Soo Ho was sick.
I shouldn't have been so sensitive.
I'm sorry.
The same goes for me. I'm sorry.
I hope you and Gary work out.
Excuse me?
I know how he feels as I'm in a similar situation.
Similar situation?
Yes.
I want to start over with Soo Ho.
Soo Ho told me that I was his everything.
It was the same for me.
All we had was each other back then.
Oh, right.
This is a secret between you and me.
I'll tell everyone else later if it works out.
- Shall we eat?
- Yes.
Are you out of your mind?
You went to see her at 4am...
- and confessed your feelings?
- Yes.
That's when I organised my thoughts.
I don't know what to do with you.
Not even burglars break into houses at that hour.
Who in the world would appreciate that?
She probably likes you even less now.
Is that why she got mad at me?
You're so slow-witted, too. My goodness.
Listen. I'm glad that you now have a desire to date,
but you have a lot to learn.
Let's go and have you practise. Come on.
That's why she got mad at me.
Mr Koo! It's me!
She's so silly.
She still believes in these nonsensical things.
- Oh! Hello, Mr Je.
- Yes, hello.
Please speak casually to me.
No, I should be polite to my customer.
- I guess you're stepping out.
- Well...
Soo Ho! I'm sorry to make you wait.
Oh, hello!
Yes, hello.
By the way, you two look so much alike today.
From your height and shoulders to your eyes,
you could easily pass as a father and a son.
Stop talking nonsense!
I hope you both have a great day.
- You, too!
- Thank you.
What?
Mr Ahn from 01 Fried Chicken looks much kinder than you, of course.
I think your eyes are more slanted.
Gosh, stop it.
Where are we going now?
Do you think you look like a human now?
Stop wearing those ugly shorts, seriously!
I'll make you into a decent human.
A pretty woman
Walking down the street, a pretty woman
(01 Fried Chicken)
From your height and shoulders to your eyes,
you could easily pass as a father and a son.
Are you okay?
Let me take you to a hospital.
Sir, wait.
This is my store. Please call me if there is any problem.
You shouldn't be so stubborn when you're that clueless.
Wear those stupid shorts for your life!
Wear them to weddings as well as to funerals.
Gosh, I gave up.
Why? I think they look cool.
Hey, call now.
(Wood-fired pizza, pasta, risotto and steak)
This restaurant?
No! Call Bo Nui!
I made a reservation here for a full-course meal,
so call Bo Nui and tell her.
What if she says no?
It'll seem petty, but you'll need to exercise your authority.
Tonight at 7pm.
You must come.
(Mr Je)
Hello?
- Bo Nui, did you get my message?
- Yes.
You can't say no.
I'll be there.
You have to come!
- Okay.
- You promised!
Yes, you did it! She said yes!
- That worked!
- Gosh, it's hot.
Let's go.
Which way? It's this way. Let's go.
Gosh, Bo Nui!
Don't do that, please.
You stopped doing it for a while. Why are you starting again?
I'm doing it out of my devotion and dedication.
As you know, Bo Ra is all I need in my life.
Gosh, you are really devoted to her.
What is all this?
Sir, why are you doing this?
Let go! Get out of my way!
Sir, please stop.
- Please! Gosh!
- Oh, no.
Mr Ahn!
- What is going on now?
- I almost hit him with my scooter.
He showed up drunk.
Sir, what is the matter?
Who are you now?
Are you two ganging up against me now?
- You little...
- Mr Je.
What? Do you know him?
He's Mr Je Soo Ho's father.
He's Mr Je Soo Ho's father?
That's right!
I'm Soo Ho's dad.
You're not his dad.
I, Je Mul Po, is Je Soo Ho's dad!
- Mr Je, please calm down...
- Come on.
Go out.
I'll take care of this.
Don't say you're not going to come. I'll wait until you get here.
Sorry?
Oh, I remember you now.
You used to live in Hui Ae's neighbourhood.
Do you remember me?
Why should I?
How would I know a nerd like you from Seoul did...
to a young lady in a small town while hitting on her?
Well, it sounds like there was a misunderstanding,
- but I didn't...
- A misunderstanding?
What are all these?
Do you want to look like some sort an engineer, too?
Don't even dream.
I'm not sure why you keep...
hovering around my son and my wife,
but Soo Ho is my child!
He's my son!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Take him home.
- Get up.
- Let go! What now?
My son is here!
Look at this with your eyes wide open.
Even if this world comes to an end,
this genius will always be my son!
Is that clear?
Let go of me!
- Mr Je.
- Let go!
Yeong Il.
- Soo Ho.
- Take him home.
He's my son! Don't even dream!
You'll be punished for what you're doing!
(01 Fried Chicken)
You two should go now, too.
We'll help you clean.
It's okay. This is my store and my things.
I don't want others to clean up.
- But still...
- Bo Nui.
Please take him.
I'm sure it really surprised you.
Go and get some fresh air.
If I leave now, I won't be any different from my father.
I'll clean up before I go.
Just go.
I like Mr Ahn and this is his store.
Please don't mind me.
I heard that...
they almost got into an accident earlier.
I think your father has a misunderstanding about Mr Ahn.
No reason or misunderstanding...
can justify this.
Don't worry! I told you to just leave it to me.
No, I should finish it.
- Please go in.
- Goodness.
I'll get going, too. I'm sorry you had to deal with that.
- All right. Get home safely.
- Bye.
Bo Nui, you should go home.
I'll also head home after throwing this away.
Let's do it together.
Gosh, there's no need.
I can do it alone.
Goodness, give it to me.
Are you okay?
I told you I can carry it.
Forget it all.
Forget what you just saw...
and what my father did.
Please forget all those embarrassing things you saw.
I don't want to.
I'll remember everything...
from how you were considerate of me just now...
and how you did your best to make up for what your father did.
So please don't be embarrassed.
It's nothing to be embarrassed of.
Then can you keep doing this for me?
Whether it's my parents...
or my weaknesses,
I think I will not be embarrassed if it's you.
Mr Je.
To me,
Bo Ra comes first.
You protect Bo Ra.
I'll protect you.
I actually...
got a lucky charm for you.
It's a tiger lucky charm made exclusively for you.
I'll put it on you.
I didn't know that I'd end up...
giving this to you in front of this big bag of garbage. Here.
I cannot accept this. Please don't give it to me.
To me,
you're just my boss and nothing more or less.
I wanted to meet you today to tell you this.
I'm sorry.
- Please let me go.
- You said you don't hate me.
- I never said I like you.
- That night.
You were sick and you also helped me before,
so I forced myself to stay with you.
I missed Geon Uk's broadcast because of it, so I regretted it so much.
Did you say...
you regretted it?
Yes.
I'm not sure...
how you felt that night,
- but I was upset and uncomfortable.
- Stop lying.
For you, it's always either 0 or 1...
and go or stop.
I've chosen to stop.
So please let me go.
If you go now,
I won't ask you ever again.
You really...
don't like me?
You said I'm like a bug.
A bug in your head.
Catch it.
Catch it and kill it.
Is this...
what I'm supposed to do?
(The unsent message)
(Are you feeling okay? I'll see you at work on Monday.)
Are you free tomorrow?
(Are you free tomorrow?)
My goodness!
What should I do?
(Why do you ask?)
Why do you ask?
Let's get dinner if you're free.
Sure.
(Mum, Bo Nui, Bo Ra and Dad)
(Sure.)