If you go now,
I won't ask you ever again.
You really...
don't like me?
You said I'm like a bug.
A bug in your head.
Catch it.
Catch it and kill it.
Is this...
what I'm supposed to do?
- We shouldn't. - It's okay.
- I don't want this. - You're lying.
You told me you don't like me.
You would've left if you meant that.
However,
you were crying.
That means you're lying.
Like a fool...
Right?
I came this far...
without realising it.
I tried to stop my feelings.
I tried...
But my heart won't listen to me.
That's enough.
Let's stop here.
Why? You can't even hide your feelings from me.
You end up in tears before you can walk away.
I'll like you from afar.
I'll yearn for you by myself...
and get over it by myself. I can do that.
You'll end it even before starting anything?
Thank you...
for liking me.
Wait.
What do you want me to do?
If you want me to prove my feelings for you, I'll try.
If it's because of the superstitions,
I'll go to a fortune-teller with you.
Can you...
- do anything for me? - Just say it.
Forget what happened today.
Everything you said...
and the kiss.
I'll see you...
at work tomorrow.
Why is it so complicated?
I guess it's possible.
I see happiness in front of me.
Have I ever pushed forward for my own happiness?
It's warm.
I feel secure.
I feel safe.
I feel happy.
That isn't yours.
That happiness isn't meant for you.
Water!
What's this?
It's salted water.
You don't deserve to drink water.
Don't cross the line.
What's this?
You don't deserve to live with me.
Don't ever cross that line.
Where are all my shoes?
You don't deserve to wear any shoes.
Don't you think you've done enough?
Listen.
Isn't fighting with the night guard enough to blow off your steam?
Have you decided to make Soo Ho look bad...
by raiding the restaurant which his employees go often?
I'm Soo Ho's dad. You're not his dad.
You don't even deserve to breathe today.
What about you?
What kind of rumour are you trying to start...
by visiting that man so often?
You disgust me.
Don't you have a heart?
He used to spend his summers in our neighbourhood.
I was happy to see him again.
It reminded me of old times and made me wonder when I grew old.
You're good at making it sound innocent.
No matter how old you get,
you're still a man and a woman.
Nothing between you two can be that innocent.
Why? Did you want to run away with him...
by riding on the train you missed that day?
- Are you serious? - You talked about what I deserve.
You and I both don't deserve to be treated as parents by Soo Ho.
You didn't know what harm you were doing...
to our son and went around excitedly.
Don't pretend you don't know.
Stop right there, Je Mul Po!
(Korean University Hospital)
Oh, my... Look how nice the weather is.
Did you sleep well, Bo Ra?
Congratulations!
Congratulations, my friend.
That restaurant is nice, isn't it? Their steak tastes amazing.
You can count on that place to win a girl's heart.
Even if you're horrible at dating, that legendary restaurant...
You ruined it.
You ruined it, didn't you?
We didn't go there.
- Did she stand you up? - No, we didn't go there.
I didn't ask her out.
So I haven't gotten dumped yet. Got it?
Got it.
Clean this place up. I want it spick and span.
He got dumped.
He got dumped for certain.
Good morning.
Mr Je.
I have to talk to you.
Did you think about it all night and realise you made a mistake?
It's okay. I'll give you a pass.
I'm really sorry.
I know I shouldn't ask you this.
What is it?
Please be my lucky charm one more time.
Did you get a call from the hospital?
Bo Ra opened her eyes.
It's scary how greedy a person can get.
I thought it was enough to see her once,
but I want to see her after hearing she opened her eyes.
I know I'm being selfish,
but you came to my mind as soon as I got the call.
I told you...
I'd come with you whenever you want to see Bo Ra.
Aren't you going in?
Let's use this today.
Red colour drives out ghosts and bad luck.
I think this would be good for both you and Bo Ra.
Give it to me.
Do you want me to wrap it around my pinkie?
Bo Ra.
I'm right here.
Good job, Bo Ra.
Thank you.
That person is the president of the company I work at.
I wouldn't be able to see you if it weren't for him. I'm thankful.
I hope you can get better and thank him with me.
Wait a second.
There's something wrong with that introduction.
Hi.
I'm the guy your sister is interested in.
I have many questions for you.
Was your sister always this frustrating?
Or has she become like this lately? I'm curious to find out.
- Please stop. - I'm talking to her.
Bo Nui tried hard to save you.
She did things most people wouldn't imagine.
It's unbelievable.
So please get up from this bed...
and tell your sister...
instead of me.
Tell her to be happy.
Okay?
Tell her to love all she wants if she likes someone.
Tell her to hold onto the guy she likes.
Please tell her.
I'll see you again soon.
Give up.
Give up trying to force yourself...
and come to me.
- I... - Think carefully.
Bo Ra woke up the day after we kissed.
Isn't that a good sign?
- You're all crazy about fate. - You don't believe it, though.
I don't.
But I can understand you.
I understand you need something to rely on even if it's ridiculous.
I'm starting to be like that, too.
When I was little,
I was always bored in math class.
I always got the answers straight away,
but I had to wait until the other kids were done.
I guess you need time as well, Bo Nui.
You know what?
No matter how long it takes, the answers are given.
When you find the answer in your heart,
come to me by yourself...
willingly.
Let's go.
Don't you feel bad? Should I really cut it?
I like her.
I'll look good with short hair, right?
You have a small and pretty face. You'll look good with anything.
I'll cut it then.
I'm sorry.
- Gary. - Diamond or emerald, what's better?
What's happening? A ring?
I think diamond is too much.
Emerald is too humble though it is her birthstone.
Don't tell me you're going to propose to Bo Nui.
I'm so used to having girls hitting on me, so I wasn't alert.
I realised I accidentally confessed my feelings.
I have to do it properly.
Can we talk outside for a while? Let's go out.
Wait. I haven't chosen it yet.
You're leaving in three weeks. What are you trying to do?
Isn't it the same for you?
What are you going to do with Mr Je?
Is it going well?
He's looking elsewhere just for a while.
He'll come back to me soon.
You're very confident, Amy.
Confidence...
is everything I got.
You're serious about Bo Nui, aren't you?
Of course I am.
It's my first time to buy a ring.
Good luck.
You know that I don't like losing, right?
I will support you with every way possible.
So just win. Okay?
I knew you'd be on my side no matter what.
Which is better? Diamond is too much, isn't it?
Well, there's no girl who doesn't like diamond.
I'll choose it for you.
- The fried chickens are here. - Hello.
- Hello. - All right.
You're the first customer of the smart watch, aren't you?
- Yes. - The president of...
Coconut Company bowed to you on the spot.
- Coconut! - What?
No way.
01 Fried Chicken.
I thought you came up with that name using the binary system.
But that wasn't it.
"The genius first generation game programmer Ahn Yeong Il."
That's you, right?
("The genius first generation game programmer Ahn Yeong Il")
- It's you, right? - It's really him!
- Let me see it. - Sir!
- Oh my gosh! - You didn't know, right?
That's a long time ago. That's more than 20 years ago.
It's not a big deal.
You're here.
- Hello. - Hello, Sir.
- I was going to visit you. - It's all right.
Take this. I'm leaving.
Wait.
Just one minute.
This is it. I can't seem to figure it out.
The interface parameter has a problem.
Check the XML parameters.
Okay.
Mr Je must know it better.
Gosh.
I don't know if it'll be enough to pay for the damage.
This is unnecessary! I can't accept it.
- I didn't buy anything new. - Just take it.
Just come more often from now on.
That will do.
By the way, how do you know my mother?
During college, I went to do volunteer activities every year.
I gave computer lessons and fixed things for free.
We got to know each other then,
and here we are.
Hui Ae was very fond of me.
I mean your mother.
Then why did my father treat you like that?
Well, I'm not sure about that, either.
My apologies.
If you keep apologising to me,
I will be too uncomfortable to see you.
Gosh.
I guess you don't know,
but I've been your fan.
When I saw your first game seven years ago,
I was really touched.
Since then, I've been following you around...
whenever you showcase your new game.
I was like a girl fan.
You're still very skilled. Why are you running a restaurant?
I was at my peak when I was just about your age.
Everything I got my hands on was successful...
and people lined up to sponsor me.
The games I developed for myself received so much attention,
and I worked like a mad man.
When I finally got back to my senses,
I was alone.
Well, what kind of wife would be willing to live...
her whole life looking back of her husband?
I shouldn't have let her go.
You shouldn't do that.
Make sure to hold onto...
the person precious to you.
Gosh, I'm being ridiculous. Clearly, you're better off than me.
- Gosh... - It's my first time.
You're the first adult to tell me these things.
I went over the line because you are my friend's son.
Just forget what I said. I will get going then.
I will visit you sometimes.
I will go to your restaurant with Bo Nui.
Sure.
- Thank you for this. - You're welcome.
Are you going to go eat fried chicken with Bo Nui?
You're a beast.
(Mother)
What?
When you get dumped, you never fully realise it immediately.
- Gosh... - I love you, Bo Nui.
I love you, Bo Nui.
Oh, Bo Nui!
Bo Nui!
Soo Ho. Is that right?
Did you get exhausted?
You just solved the questions you knew. Why did you?
Let's smile. Only then you will get lucky.
You know what?
No matter how long it takes, the answers are given.
When you find the answer in your heart,
come to me by yourself...
willingly.
Hi, Bo Nui. How are you?
Hello.
You look nice.
You think so?
I wonder if Soo Ho will like it.
What?
I'm sorry.
My head seems to be filled with thoughts of Soo Ho lately.
I didn't know I said it out loud.
This must be why people say you can't hide your feelings.
Is Soo Ho in his office?
That's impressive.
Zeze Factory is skilled.
I'll prepare the beta test in this version.
Let's take some of the women out from the party scene.
It makes Gary look like a playboy.
I also noticed that he often falls down on the court.
Gary is quick on his feet...
and rarely has his knees touch the floor.
- I see. - I expected something better...
when I heard Bo Nui was in charge of the scenario.
You know Gary less than I thought.
Put more effort into it.
Gary was okay with this.
He'd agree to anything Bo Nui does.
Please tell us anything else we should modify.
Let's check from the beginning.
Of course.
Did you do anything to irritate the regional director?
What are you talking about?
Clients always give us feedback.
She was too picky about the smallest details.
I got the impression she was picking on you.
Is she trying to get back at you for dumping Gary?
No, that's ridiculous.
Why are you being so hard on her?
She's just meticulous.
I'm worried all that will come back to you.
Do you have a lot to modify?
No, I can get it done today.
We'll do a proper job.
Don't worry.
- Let's go, Bo Nui. - Okay.
What are you doing? Turn around and face forward.
Good job.
I'm proud of you.
Okay.
Let's have dinner at my place.
I'll cook something nice.
I can't. I have work to do.
(I can't. I have work to do.)
Hello?
When can we have dinner? Stop avoiding me.
I'm not avoiding you.
I'm going to wait until you get here.
I really can't go. Make sure you eat!
Are you going home now?
Do you still not have an answer?
I don't get it because I'm pretty sure you know the answer.
It's a yes or no question and the answer is yes.
The answer is that you like me.
It's yes between 0 and 1.
Coffee or tea? Yes.
It should always be yes.
- I already told you it's no. - Wrong!
You got it wrong.
Fine, I'll wait.
- Why are you sighing? - Gosh!
That's my bike.
I know. Can't you tell?
I was waiting here because I wanted to see you.
Why weren't you in the meeting today?
I took some time getting ready, thinking I'd see you.
Someone else is in charge of that project.
Is there anything I should know of?
Yes, there is.
It's something very important.
- What is it? - I'm...
hungry.
Buy me dinner.
Here is your sushi.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Sadly, I have something to eat.
Yes, you do.
Were you happy to save money?
That's not true.
Thanks for the food.
You remembered, didn't you?
On your 18th birthday,
you forced yourself to eat the sushi I bought...
and ended up throwing up.
Did I?
That was the first time you told me about your father.
Was it that day?
Can I have an order of sushi to-go?
- Yes. - Thank you.
Soo Ho, have you forgotten?
Why? You always remembered more than I did.
That day,
you opened up to me for the first time.
It's the day I became special to you.
I'm talking about that day, but you're...
Amy.
Why are you ordering food to-go? Is it for Ryang Ha?
Bo Nui is working late.
She has to eat.
You've changed a lot.
You worry about your employee's dinner.
I told you before. She's more than just an employee to me.
You're just being curious...
because she's different.
You're attracted to her because she's unique.
I know you.
You used to struggle over a problem for three nights...
if you couldn't solve it. This is the same.
Why did you become my friend?
You came back even when I told you not to.
I told you I was curious about you.
I wanted to know who the young genius was.
You looked terrified...
like a duckling in a strange place.
How was I supposed to leave you alone?
Do you think...
that was love?
Are you questioning me?
Or do you want confirmation?
No.
I just thought you'd know.
That's how I feel about Bo Nui.
I can't leave her alone.
I don't want her to cry.
I don't want her to be in pain,
and I don't want her to be unhappy any more.
I want to make it possible for her.
- See you. - Bye.
(Food recipes)
(Appetiser or dessert)
(Fruit sandwich)
Cut the crusts off the bread.
There you go. Good job.
I didn't know you had a dog.
You're cute. What's its name?
Wait.
Bark at him.
Oh my.
How does he understand? He seems like a person.
I have to go clubbing, so hurry up and talk.
Look.
This isn't going anywhere since that day.
So I made some plans.
Go on.
I'm thinking that if you help me out...
a little bit,
it would look like we were meant to be.
My love
She doesn't know that the bus already left.
Gosh...
At that time, he will realise.
Gosh.
"The blue bird was right next to me."
It's such a beautiful night, and I have to go through this.
Hey.
Do you think I like doing this?
Why would I meet you if it weren't for Mr Je?
If you treat me like this,
you'll miss all the important information.
We'll see if they are important or useless.
Who am I?
I am Soo Ho's only friend and guardian.
With my tongue's help,
you could be sitting next to Soo Ho...
in 30 minutes. You see?
I can make him sit right there.
Right next to you.
That's it.
I will do anything you ask.
Just tell me.
Let's take it off.
- What? - Take off your glasses.
And lose some weight.
Take off your braces, too.
Let's take off everything.
Let's think after that. Okay?
What are you doing?
It's delicious, isn't it?
You're thankful, right?
You must want to come to me by now, but you're showing no signs.
Okay.
I'll wait.
Don't whistle at night. It's bad luck.
Stop saying superstitious things.
I did it intentionally.
I chose "Sad Fate" on purpose so you can hear it.
- Why? - You follow the whistle version...
of the song you like,
and you find your crush holding something delicious.
It's nice, right?
You know the last memory is very important.
When a person evaluates an incident or an experience,
they tend to depend on the most intense or...
the last moment.
I will turn all your sad...
and hurtful memory into good memory.
I'll make it to be the most intense and last moment.
You'll remember it with a smile.
Still, you can't whistle at night.
Don't you remember?
Last time, you wrote your father's name in red...
and he got hurt.
Even if there is the slightest chance, you can't risk it.
But that was just a coincidence.
Why would you try to associate it with cause and effect?
Have you...
talked to your father?
He must be regretting it.
He loves you.
He loves you,
but he doesn't know how to express his love.
Have you ever thought that...
it would be easier if your father was not...
your biological father?
You can talk to him about that, too.
You can tell him how much and why you got hurt.
He can't know if you don't tell him.
We're very much alike.
We're both stubborn and we only think about ourselves.
We don't know how to apologise, either.
When we fight with someone, we'd rather not see them again.
You know how the magnets...
of the same poles repel each other.
It's right for us to keep this much distance.
Still, you're a family.
- It's too bad we are. - Mr Je.
When we start dating,
I should stop you from calling me Mr Je.
Let's go down.
Hello.
Oh, it's you. Welcome.
I heard Bo Nui is upstairs.
Yes. She's working overtime today. She's still upstairs.
You brought her food.
It's a secret.
Here.
Are you looking at this?
You should look here.
I should.
Let's see.
What are you doing right now?
You told me to look at the screen. I am looking at the screen.
That's all.
Well...
- That should be fine. - Okay.
So...
Oh, no!
- Gosh... - I'll file for a restraining order.
What restraining order?
We already kissed twice.
- Twice? Have you been dreaming? - What?
Dreaming? Are you serious?
Don't you remember?
You got drunk and went out of control.
You puked and kissed me!
My tiger!
People said I should hear the sound of bells when I have my first kiss.
But I didn't hear anything.
Your first kiss?
Isn't Amy your first love?
No! She's not! Everything was first for me.
I confessed my feelings, held hands and kissed for the first time!
So you're responsible for me.
Hey.
Well...
I'll go home now.
Do you think...
that was love?
I wonder, too. What was it then?
What was it?
Why does it keep hurting me?
Did you go home well?
Yes.
I miss you.
Hello?
It's not working well.
Good night, Mr Je. I will see you tomorrow.
How long will she struggle with this easy question?
Hurry up and come, Bo Nui.
All spirits in the world.
Please help me.
I want to trust him,
and I want to hold his hands.
Please help me...
so that I can control my feelings.
Geon Uk.
Come out.
I really worked late last night.
I wasn't avoiding you.
I think those reporters are here again.
Goodness.
I'm okay because I've been on TV, but your case is different.
Wear them.
Thanks, Geon Uk.
What did you make yesterday? You said you'd make something tasty.
I just picked up some tteokbokki.
I ate it all by myself.
You should've saved some for me! Let's eat together next time.
Okay.
Have a good day at work. See you later.
See you!
Sir!
What are you doing? Why are you hovering around?
Let me see your ID. Show me your ID! Sir!
Hey!
Who's that now?
Why are there so many hawkers?
Sir. Sir!
Goodness. Stop pestering me, Sir.
I'm telling you the truth!
I'm Je Soo Ho's father, Je Mul Po!
Shall I show you my ID?
There's no need.
It's written right here.
"There is a man that comes here drunk between 11pm and 1am."
"That's Mr Je's father. Don't let him in."
It's broad daylight and you're sober, so you mustn't be his father.
I guess you're here to pitch your idea to get an investment,
but meeting famous people isn't easy. Please leave now.
Mr Je Mul Po.
Hello.
Are you here to see the president?
Forget it.
- Don't let him know. - Well...
Is he really the father?
- How does he know you? - Because I'm an employee.
- What's going on with the scenario? - I shared it with team members.
- What about the design? - It'll be ready by the afternoon.
- What about dating then? - By tonight...
She said by tonight.
By tonight.
Soo Ho! I'm at your place!
Did you give my passcode to my mum?
Did I give your passcode to your mother? Yes.
You said you'd change it!
He was preoccupied with Bo Nui and forgot about it. Why blame me?
Gosh, this is so heavy.
Why are you here? I just came to clean your place.
I don't need your help with cleaning. I can do it myself.
I can make my place squeaky clean.
I filled up your refrigerator with food.
I was going to start cleaning after having this cup of tea.
There's no need.
All right. I'm sure you can take care of it yourself.
Are you leaving?
I should raid your place often.
I'm happy to see you.
Don't come here.
Then you should visit us.
Are you never going to see your father again or what?
He hasn't been able to sleep for the last few days.
Give him a chance, Soo Ho.
I'm going to change my passcode. Ryang Ha won't know, so don't ask.
Get going now.
I thought about it and realised that I don't know anything about you...
when you know many things about me.
Do you really have to know?
- Just like now, we can... - What do your parents do?
Do they live in Seoul?
Both of them passed away 10 years ago.
Do you have any siblings?
I have a younger sister.
She's sick and at a hospital now.
So do you take care of your sister alone?
Yes.
Which university did you go to?
You got into Zeze, so you must've graduated from one of the top...
I dropped out of university.
Are you and Soo Ho seeing each other now?
No, we're not. Never.
I think Soo Ho...
likes you, though.
I don't feel the same way.
I told him about it, and I won't reciprocate his feelings.
How dare you reject my son!
Sorry?
Come with me.
Hello.
This is pretty. Try it on.
Come on.
That looks so pretty on you.
What did I tell you?
That you'd buy me a mink fur coat if I don't accept these.
Just take them.
Put on those pretty make-ups and go on dates with Soo Ho.
That's really not what's happening.
Then why did Soo Ho put up your photos...
all over the walls in his room?
You said that he's cool.
You just don't see him as a man?
All right, fine. I won't force you.
You should still accept these.
We go to the same fortune-teller.
Just think of them as a gift from a friend, okay?
Thank you.
On that note, Bo Nui...
Could I ask you for a favour?
I see.
You put up her photos on your wall.
You actually did that?
I mean the Je Soo Ho I know?
Am I not allowed to do that?
I wish your mother saw them.
- It's too bad. - You little...
Did I just see you smile?
You're a pervert.
Bo Nui keeps rejecting you, so you must be heartbroken.
Do you enjoy pain?
Waiting for a train that will never arrive is a curse,
but waiting for a train that will arrive eventually...
is a blessing.
I need to use the washroom.
I think I'm going to vomit.
Are you writing a novel now? You didn't study literature.
No.
I'm getting this feeling.
It feels almost as if the volcanic magma is...
bubbling up from the bottom of my heart.
Who are you? I don't think you're Je Soo Ho.
Hey! Calm down. Calm down first.
Calm down and talk in a deeper voice.
Je Soo Ho speaking.
Yes.
Okay.
You got rejected once again.
You're getting a feeling? Whatever.
She wants to have lunch tomorrow.
- Yes! - Yes!
(Je Soo Ho)
Please...
unblock all blockages...
and untangle all knots.
- What's that now? - You need to come with me.
Don't say anything.
If you want to open your mouth, just say, "Yes. That's right."
That's all you can say.
What's this nonsense about?
If you say no, I'll divorce you!
"Hi. Well, what do you feel like eating?"
"Sure! Fish sounds good."
"Can you tell this shirt is new?"
What's wrong with the shoulders?
Was this always small like this?
Which side is the front?
I just put on what I always wear.
Why does my face look so dark today?
Love
I should take a shower again.
Goodness! What should I wear?
Bo Nui!
You're here.
- I... - I...
finally understood the theory of relativity.
From last night to this morning,
each minute felt like an hour.
But the hour it took me to get here felt like a minute.
Now that I'm looking at you, it feels as if time has stopped.
- Actually... - Let's talk inside.
- Wait... - Soo Ho!
Have a good time with your parents.
- I'll get going now. - Stay and eat with us.
It's not like we don't know each other.
It's been so long since our family last gathered like this.
The last time was when we went out for pork barbecue...
before you went to the States when you were 11.
Oh, my.
That means it's been 20 years.
That's right.
Now that we've gathered like this,
we should let go of all misunderstandings...
as well as each other's mistakes.
That's right.
Your father...
hasn't had any alcohol recently. He has completely quit drinking.
Stop it.
What's your problem? You have that disapproving look in your eyes,
and you're sitting with your arms crossed.
Are you my father or what?
Forget it.
Soo Ho, please.
It's been 20 years.
Go! Just go.
Until when do your parents have to beg you so desperately?
Why are you being like this? Bo Nui is here, too.
- Why did you do that? - Do what?
Be clear.
Why...
did you throw a seven-year-old into the sea?
That's how you learn swimming. You weren't good enough.
Why are you blaming it on me?
Do you know that I can't...
even go near water ever since that day?
Are you aware that even just the smell of sea nauseates me?
You run a fishery with water everywhere...
and ask me why I don't visit you.
So what?
Are you expecting me to beg you on my knees?
Gosh, he wants to win against his parents thinking he's smarter.
You've always been like that even as a kid.
Even when you were little,
you talked like a know-it-all.
How arrogant!
I was just a kid.
The ocean and dark nights frightened me.
I was just a child who was scared of strangers touching me,
laughing at me and watching me.
You two are the ones...
who didn't think of me as a kid.
That little...
Do not arrange things like this ever again.
Gosh, this is ridiculous.
Mr Je.
I'm sorry. I should've told you beforehand.
- But she said you wouldn't... - Right.
You should've done so.
This is only the beginning.
You told them about how hurt and wounded...
you were as a kid.
- From now on... - Who do you think angered me most?
It's you, Bo Nui.
I know I've been chasing you.
Did you think you could treat me however you want?
Did you think you have such right?
I was sad for you.
The fact that your heart has hardened...
- ached my heart. - How can you lie to me, though?
I told you that I was going to tell you.
It is true that your father was harsh on you.
But you were the one with the vilest attitude there.
What's wrong with opening up and offering a hand first?
That's how you love.
- If you don't even know that... - So I'm at fault again.
I didn't know that's how you thought of me...
and was so excited from early in the morning.
I thought we were solving the same problem,
but I guess I was wrong.
I'm sorry...
for bugging you.
(The first kiss)
That was his first kiss.
(Lucky Romance)
What do you want? Are you sad that I've stopped bugging you?
What should I do? I think he really hates me now.
My heart aches so badly for him. I like him so much.
I feel so bad.
How can I miss you this much when I hate you to death?
I'm the one who didn't know how to love.
Tell me properly. Say yes.
- Are you talking casually now? - You should as well, Bo Nui.
Shall I, Soo Ho?
Let's hang out a bit more.
We spent the whole day together.
Right. So we can hang out together for a little longer.
Bo Nui, thanks for being born into this world.