Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
I have to tell him it isn't!
Ever since you were young! Ever since you were puny, looking around like you know all about the world!
So pretentious!
But the sharpest one in there was you!
What's wrong with holding your hand out first?
What's wrong with taking the first step, that's how you love!
It worked out for the better. This is good.
Yes. Welcome!
Welcome!
Good morning!
Oh, Ms. Bo Nui! Welcome!
Did CEO Je come yet?
Yeah, he was here since dawn!
How...did he look?
What, he's always the same.
Why? Did you two fight? Because of Gary?
Excuse me?
Ms. Bo Nui, I say this because you're like a niece to me.
From the eyes of a family, Gary is way better.
He's young, he's got money, he's affectionate-look at fiesty CEO Je!
Do you think he'd ever make a lunchbox with his own hands?!
I'm telling you, guys like Gary are hard to find!
Made a lunchbox? Geon Wook did?!
Yeah! While we're at it, I've thought of this global sports business-!
Ms. Bo Nui!
Hello.
Did someone follow you? Or did you get a phone call from a number you don't know?!
Don't ever pick up, it'll be reporters.
A picture went up...
What picture?
Look at her smile! It's 100%!
Oh! Congratulations!
You kept pulling out saying it wasn't! You maxed out your levels, for sure!
What's going on! Keeping it a secret, even from us? I'm kinda sad.
Did it already get around?!
I'm going crazy...
What happened?
CEO Je, did you see the picture?
How are you going to handle this? Articles picking things apart have come up already.
There's a comment assuming it's an employee from Zeze too.
IM Sports has to release an official statement.
Gary, please make an explicit statement that it isn't true, then...
It's true. She's a precious person.
Gary!
It's true. Whether she accepts me or not, it's true that she's someone precious to me.
Wow...this is the jackpot! I mean, the almighty Gary has a crush?
It's hard. This is the first time it's ever been one-sided.
But...Gary and Ms. Bo Nui, if this is true it'd be the best for advertisement!
- Then?! Accept him!- Accept him!
Accept him! Accept him! Accept him!
- Ms. Bo Nui!- She always leaves when she's in a tight spot.
Why'd you do it this time?
It's fun!
Give it a rest already!
Noona!
This is a company. The workplace I have to go to-I begged you not to do anything!
Why are you so furious about me saying one thing?
Why did you pack the lunchbox?
How'd you know...
I can't accept. Not just you but anyone else too.
If you keep doing this, I'll only be more sorry. Is that what you want?
I'm not asking you to accept me! I won't ask you to do anything either...
But! Don't tell me to lie.
I have no intention on keeping my liking you a secret. I'm not embarrassed about it either!
And I don't want to hide it.
You...How can you only think of yourself?!
I thought things over 100, 1000 times because I thought it might hinder that person!
But is your heart the only thing that's important to you? Is that it!?
"That person"?
Are you going to tell the entire world you've got a crush? Let's think about where we are.
And don't corner the kid. I think whoever made him restless is just as responsible.
You're the one that moved his heart, how can you be the one getting mad about that?!
Amy!
It's true! It's not like you've fallen at first sight for a person you don't know!
You can't say Ms. Bo Nui has nothing to do with how you're feeling!
Don't play around going between two people.
I think I might be disappointed in you.
What are you talking about?
Amy!
Don't worry, we'll handle it.
It's not true.
I'm really not with Geon Wook!
What are you playing?
I thought you might misunderstand!
So I'm asking why you're explaining yourself.
Are you sorry now, since I told you I won't bother you anymore?
Whether you get caught in a damn picture, whether you're something with Gary or not, what does that have to do with me-?!
♬ Seeing your silhouette ♬
♬ Getting further away ♬
♬ I still ♬
Spirits, please.
I'll beg you like this...
Please...my feelings, my heart...
9, 9, 81. 9, 8, 72.
9 and 7, 63.
9 and 6...
♬ How could we forget ♬
♬ Oh, you will come back ♬
Bo Nui! Bo Nui, what's wrong?!
Is it because of Gary?! Did the branch manager say something again!?
Dal Nim...what do I do?
That person...I think that person really hates me now!
It's for the best, I can just end it now, but...
♬ When I meet you again ♬
But it hurts so much!
Things like the multiplication table didn't work at all!
It was probably the same way for that person too...
He was frustrated and he couldn't breathe,
he was in pain, all by himself, right?!
He's already in pain and I hurt him even more!
That person is in so much pain...
I like him so much...And because of that, I'm so sorry...
My Bo Nui, what do we do...
Why are you like that to Noona?
I know that I was mean to her. But it's infuriating!
What's Ms. Bo Nui doing with you and Soo Ho?!
It's not like that.
If it's not then what is it?! She's making you and Soo Ho all frazzled, then there she stands like she doesn't know anything.
How could I not be frustrated!?
It's because of superstitions!
What do you mean "superstitions"?
The two of them got tangled because of that.
Noona's little sister is a little ill.
I wish she wouldn't cry. I wish she wouldn't be in pain,
I wish she wouldn't be unhappy anymore.
I...want to make things that way for her.
So that was it...and I thought it was something else...
Why? Did CEO Je say something about Noona?
Soo Ho is misunderstanding.
Compassion as love.
He said he loves her?
No! A man and a woman don't just get together with words.
Until I see it with my own two eyes, I won't believe it.
Ms. Bo Nui...
Oh right! I said I'd give you the character animations-I'll give it to you right away.
The graphics came out really nice!
Ms. Seung Hyeon, as expected, you're the best!
Now...let's work...! Let's work!
What's wrong with the air today?
That's what I'm asking!
Excuse me...Gary...
♬ There's no combination of words I could write on the back of a postcard ♬
♬ No song that I could sing but I could try for your heart ♬
I know this is crossing the line but I have to do this.
Please...don't make Bo Nui suffer any more...
Is Noona even suffering because of me?
I can't breathe watching this, listen up!
Stop! Don't you know when to come in and leave?! Leave!
Don't you know how to leave without sticking your nose in business that's not yours? Leave!
Okay, so you're saying Ms. Bo Nui has no interest in you, Gary, whatsoever?!
That's good, I almost misunderstood!
That little punk would've been so hurt.
I understand well what you're saying.
Get back safe!
His voice...why's his voice so low?
At any rate, you're hateful, detestful, and frustrating!
What bastard is making Bo Nui suffer so much? Instead of just snatching her away!
Even if he wanted to snatch her away, she'd have to be snatched first.
If he tries to snatch her again, then another love will be off..this is so frustrating.
- You know?- Me?
- Who it is?- Who is it? What?
Me?
T-That's because she's so pretty...
I just assumed she had someone!
- I put $10 on her hitting it off with Gary.- $10!
I put $10 on that it doesn't.
Ms. Seung Hyeon, are you okay?
What.
Didn't you...like Gary?
No. I have someone else I like.
This is jackpot. Who is it? Is he here?
Just mind your own business.
You can't like me. You know I'm a married man, right?
It's me, it is. I totally reject.
Oh, CEO! You're leaving?
I think Ms. Bo Nui...is in the bathroom.
Did anyone ask?
Finish testing the mpc crash by tomorow.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
I have something I want to wish for too.
Please let our Sim Bo Nui not be swayed by a divinatory sign that's over.
And please let her have a clean ending with the tiger or whatever.
You worked too hard on image training.
It's not easy seducing someone you have no relations with.
It's better for you to fool yourself by thinking you like him.
I wish...it was just something like that.
Are you being genuine with Je Soo Ho?
What's important about my feelings?
It's all over anyway.
You won't say it isn't, even to the end.
CEO
CEO.
Hello?
Sim Bo Nui! It's Sim Bo Nui but I'm wrong again!
I've never been wrong about this in my life!
Ms. Bo Nui! It's me! Young Il Chicken!
Ajusshi!
He kept calling you and wouldn't pick up!
But why do I keep getting the question wrong-oh! Pyth-Pythagorean...
He hasn't had a lot to drink...
This isn't the wrong function, with the "m" and "a" in "f".
He's solving math!
This...If cosine goes in here then Sim Bo Nui...
He's completely drunk!
I'll be right there!
Don't go. Don't go to him.
You said it was over. You said it was all in the past now! So why are you going?
He's drunk. A man who doesn't have a drop of alcohol even at company dinners is drunk.
That's exactly why you shouldn't go even more.
If you really want to end this.
Where are you going!? Go a little later!
I...I have to go right now! When the full moon is up, I'm a tiger!
Roar!
You're so intoxicated, where do you think you're going! If you wait just a little bit, Ms. Bo Nui will be here!
Then I have to go even more!
You've written Ms. Bo Nui's name over 100 times up until now!
Why are you trying to leave now that's she's coming?!
Who? Me?
Sim B-Ms. Sim Bo Nui?
I don't know anyone by that name...I have to go!
I must leave! Goodbye.
- Huh?- Excuse me!
I can't go! I can't go!
I don't need you.
This...When did my stomach get so big?
♬ Could I love you ♬
Sim Bo Nui...
Why come here, like a fool...
Because I missed you.
I hate you like crazy...
But why do I miss you so much?
Stand up.
You have to go home.
Seeing you...it's nice...
♬ I wonder when it started ♬
♬ I can't even understand my own heart ♬
♬ I wonder if you knew ♬
♬ That we were looking at the same place ♬
♬Tell me♬
♬Tell me with your lips clamped shut♬
♬Tell me with loving eyes♬
♬Say you also feel the same as I do♬
♬I love you♬
♬The words I said from the first, I love you♬
♬Hurry and tell me the words for♬
♬which there is no better♬
♬Tell me♬
♬ Shall we try starting now? ♬
♬ It doesn't matter to me who's first ♬
I'm sorry. It was my fault from the beginning.
I went to you first
even though I shouldn't have.
♬Tell me♬
♬Tell me with your pursed lips♬
♬Tell me with loving eyes♬
♬Say you also feel the same as I do♬
♬I love you♬
♬The words I said from the first, I love you♬
♬Hurry and tell me the words for♬
♬which there is no better♬
♬Tell me♬
Agh!
I said you should go back home!
Don't wanna! I'm gonna go here!
Ah! Okay, I understand! So let's go home!
No!
Ugh...
Die! Die! Die!
You still can't go in?
I was always like this! How's Bo Ra today?
Bo Ra is fine now.
You're the one that has to be okay!
He's late today...
Excuse me?
I don't care anymore-come here!
Why?
What's this?
The last time, there's a guy who came with you.
Oh my, don't even get me started!
He came by every morning, bothering all of us!Tuesday- Blood pressure: 110/70/Pulse: 68/White Cell Count: 6100/CRP: 6
Oh yes!
Hello. About patient Sim Bo Ra, how much longer do you think she'll be in a comatose state?
♬ I didn't know you then ♬Wednesday
♬ I know you now ♬
He said that if he takes pictures like this,
Ms. Bo Nui could see her whenever she wanted.
♬ I'm loving you ♬
Have you eaten?
I haven't yet...Have you eaten?
The sheets came out nice from the side...
♬ I want to look at you ♬
I took it from the pretty face angle...
♬ Lean on me, have you been waiting ♬
♬ To me it's you, but it's taken so long ♬
♬ I say with my heart ♬
I found it, found it! I found it!Tiger Talisman
Roar! Tiger, roar! Tah-ee-gr!
♬ Lean on me ♬
♬ What should I do ♬
♬ I'm loving you ♬
♬ I'm loving you, this restless heart tells me it's love ♬
Happiness...is there!
I'm running for my happiness now!
♬ Lean on me, have you been waiting ♬
♬ Lean on me, to me it's you but it's taken so long ♬
♬ I say with my heart that I'll protect you ♬
The one who didn't know love...was me.
♬ Even when I close my eyes, I see you and I'm restless once more ♬
♬ A love I can't believe has come to me ♬
♬ Lean on me, can you feel it ♬
♬ Lean on me, forever like this ♬
♬ The times that have passed, we can't turn them back  ♬
♬ The times we didn't know it was love ♬
♬ Lean on me ♬
Bo Ra! I did the right thing, right?
Please tell me I did!
- Mr. Je, you're here!- Yes!
- You're here!- Yes.
Mr. Je, what brings you here?
How are the policies these days?
Are there limitations with trading?
What are you asking that for all of a sudden? You want to sell your fishing spot?
No, I just wanted to know...
Where are you going.
Can't you tell? I'm running away from home.
Don't play around!
Just like you said, you and I both have no right.
You're not "parents" just because you gave birth to the kid.
Let's end it. Being parents.
Damn!
CEO! When did you get here?!
As soon as I opened my eyes. The night is too long!
But if we go to work together, people will find out.
What, they can't?!
- It'll probably be...you know...- Why?!
Explain it to me logically!
Well, we can just tell 'em we met at the front!
This is a backside I've never seen...
Mommy!
Oh, are you okay?!
You must be new here!
Zeze?
Society is the hard life, isn't it?
The suffering starts with the CEO here.
When you're tired, come to the first floor.
I'll give you coffee for free. Also, this is a secret...
But, I'm a major shareholder here.
The first major shareholder.
You're probably the hateful, distasteful shareholder!
Y-You sound just like someone I know...
D-Dal...
Y-You're bundle of Dal?!
There's no way! Smile!
This isn't possible! How did you change so much?!
You told me to.
What do I do!? I'm embarrassed! I hit on...that bundle of Dal!
I've dishonored my family! This is embarrassing!
Where's our Dal Nim!
Wow, Dal Nim, you're like a doll!
You're so pretty!
I was clinging to Ms. Seung Hyeon for no reason!
Dal Nim, take a picture with me in a bit! I'll get 1000 likes no matter what!
Still, the best in our team is Ms. Seung Hyeon!
Making lines of people, is wrong!
You jealous girl!
- Oh! CEO...- Why are the two of them here together?
Yes! We met in the front! Right!?
- At the front...- Right at this front!
Dal Nim!
Are you wearing contact lenses?!
- You're so pretty!- Ms. Dal Nim.
Your eyes were actually quite big!
What's wrong with you!?
Just a bit anemic...
The...When will the beta be out?
Oh yes! We're planning on starting distributions next week.
I see...that's right...
The...Well, it's our first release since the Genius incident,
- so let's succeed no matter what!- Yes!- Yes!
Oh yeah...
Have strength, youth! Fighting.
- What is that?! What's wrong with him?!- I got chills!- I feel like I'm going to barf...
I thought the world was going to end!
Really?!
That's so good! You did great Sim Bo Nui!
That's right, by what means would you block the breeze in your heart!
- It's probably okay, right?- Of course it is!
We could double-date!
Double-date?
I think it's working out well for me these days.
- Should I say I finally see the light from my 2 years of crushing on him?- That's why you came all pretty!
Now say it. Who is it?
- Don't be shocked.- What's there to be shocked about!
- It's the CEO.- Huh? Why, what about the CEO? Did he say somethi...
The CEO!?
You...You said it was because of the divinatory sign...that nothing happened!
The truth is...I wanted to hold him from the beginning.
Strangely enough, I guess I thought it would be okay to hold his hand.
Oh! What about you?! Who is it? Is it someone from work?
I've got a can full of men!
Hey! Come on!
You're here? Oh, 8 c-cups of coffee.
Traitor...
You knew about Bo Nui and the CEO, didn't you.
H-How did you know?!
So you played with me?
N-No no that, I'll explain-!
I'll explain everything.
I won't forgive you!
Are you okay!?
- Are you hurt!?- You fell hard!- She's fine-are you okay!?
S-She's someone I'm close to! Move it!
Damn, man move!
What's wrong with me? I've gone crazy...
Okay, number 2, here we go!
Ms. Sim Bo Nui, congratulations! You've been chosen!
What! Why's it always me?
Excuse...What...Is it about lunch?
Y-Yes...
These people are asking for trouble!
You don't even remember the CEO's lunch!
And you just do "dalalala" by yourselves!
Oh...CEO, were you going to eat with us?
I have to eat!
Pick something from bread, rice cakes, and noodles. I'll buy.
- Bread?- B-Black bean noodles...
- Let's go with pizza.- Oh!- Wow!
If you give us your card, we'll handle it.
I can just order pizza, right?
It's done. Enjoy.
You ordered it? Did he already order it?
Napkin please!
- Wow, it's really been a while!- What's wrong with him, buying us pizza!
W-Why...Why's she coming?
I told her I ate already and she keeps...Yes, come in!
CEO, please eat this!
I thought I was going to die because I wanted to hug you so bad.
What are you doing?
Just one minute!
- Eat this first!- Dun wanna!
From now on, eat all your meals and have good nights of sleep, okay?
If you give me a kiss!
♬ Because I know you better than anyone else ♬
♬ Because I treasure you more than anyone else ♬
Ms. Bo Nui!
This one, I talked about this to you yesterday but you see how the sun is over here and the shadow's on this side?
The shadow being over here covers up the details.
I'd like it if you could move the shadow over to this side.
♬ One day, you came to me and showed me your heart ♬
Mr. Ji Hoon! Your phone seems to have shattered the last time I saw it.
- My phone?- Yes.
Wait just a minute!
So cute!
♬ I sent you away without saying a word ♬
- CEO!- Yeah.- I tried taking out the people when they mentioned it.
- Y...Yes, do it like that.- When I put in people, they said it was too cluttered last time.
Then...I think you can do it like that.
Wait, CEO, if we're indecisive about this...
Then! How about wearing this and doing it?
Alright...
- Woo!- Isn't it nice!?- As expected, the best is a party!
Music should be like this! Why take out the women?! The music should have this feel! CEO, you like this right?!
You're doing great!
♬ Because I love you more than anyone else ♬
We were totally secretive! Right?
Mhm. Aside from Dal Nim, I bet no one could tell!
I bet Ms. Dal Nim doesn't know either!
Hand it over-all of you, hand it over.
I mean, you bet on it not being Gary, not that she'd date the CEO!
Either way, you bet on Gary!
- But how could they be so obvious about it!?- It was really hard pretending I don't know...
- I guess they really think we don't know!- No way!
Just leave them be! This is probably his first time dating someone!
We're not walls!
Dal Nim, when did you first find out?
I don't know! Don't ask me such things!
Dal Nim! Wear slippers, you'll sprain your ankle like that!
An otaku is only complete...
when that person is happy...
End.
Are you okay?
- What?- We're at the riverbank.
I hate it! But what can I do, they told me it's the best dating spot.
- Did you search online?!- In summary,
after organizing 14,000 blog entries, the results are as follows.
The highest satisfaction rate of dating places was an outside picnic with 33%.
The highest satisfaction rate of clothes was blue-layers with 49%.
This is a turn-off, isn't it.
It's cool.
I like the place and your clothes are cool too.
This is so nice.
CEO, you've never been on a picnic then, have you.
I never had an interest for those things.
Hey, what kind of child would feel that way?!
Even when I was always alone, my heart would race when picnic day came!
From now, I'll be responsible for your picnics. And I'll make you lunch too.
But...how long are you going keep it up?
I'm sorry?
I mean...the sun is warm...and the grass is green...
but you keep saying "CEO, CEO", so I want to make you do work.
I call my CEO "CEO", what else would I call him...
I mean, a person has a name but if you keep calling him something about his work,
then I wonder if that's the right thing to do, Bo Nui.
Don't you think? Bo Nui?
Are you speaking casually?
You do it too, Bo Nui!
- Should I? Soo Ho?- That's not right!
I'm older than you!
Then what do you want me to do?!
I mean...use casual speech...
But...like "oppa"...
Huh? Or..."oppa"...
- Oh! That "oppa" word...exists...- I see...
Okay Soo Ho!
I gave you a good example. Why are you doing this? Don't do that.
- Mkay Soo Ho.- You're asking for trouble!
- Soo Ho, you're so scary.- If you keep this up, I'll really get upset!
Okay Soo Ho.
Faster!
Do you know what the shortest spell in the world is?
Are we doing this again?
They say it's your name. I hated and was so scared of my name being Sim Bo Nui. It felt like a curse.
But...
Hearing it from you, it sounds so nice!
Bo Nui! Bo Nui.
Thanks for being born, Bo Nui.
Thank you!
Gimmie. I'll take it as a celebratory gift.
It's not for you.
Then who? Ms. Dal Nim? Mr. Ji Hoon...
Don't tell me it's Gary!? Who're you giving it to, tell me!
This has nothing to do with you.
It's for my one and only fortuneteller classmate and is a response to her giving me gifts.
Do you...still stay in touch with my mother?
I haven't heard from her since that day. So I'm more worried.
I'm sorry.
What happened that day, it was my fault. All of it.
I won't lie to you ever again. I promise.
Oh! Excuse me, aren't you Gary Choi's GF?!
- Right?- You must be right!
Oh, we're totally fans of Gary Choi!
She's my girlf-my "GF"!
Don't you know me? Je Soo Ho? Damn Genius?! Don't you play cellphone games...
Don't you have a phone? Use the search engine!
We're going to fall!
Wait, wait!
It's okay! It's just as it was!
Why'd you jump in there!?
Hold...Hold my hand...
Shoulder, shoulder...shoulder!
Knee, knee! Hurry, hurry!
But about that prayer stick, should we give it to her right now?
Together?
I mean, you keep holding it against yourself...
But if I go, I might really fight again. But promise you won't be stressed!
The caller cannot come to the phone right now...
I don't think anyone's home. Even your mother won't pick up.
Should we try calling your father?
I don't know his number...
You're here!
Please come in!
- Let this go.- You brought this here to give it to me!
- Let go!- I can't!
Take it then!
I gave you a mild one. Should I bring a stronger one out?
What's wrong with you. Aren't you mad?!
I'm sorry...
People are really cunning.
They're fine with saying "thank you, sorry" to other people.
But when it comes to their family, they won't say a word.
You said so last time, that he was your baby.
That he was your baby no matter what!
How much have you suffered...
That man!
Gary! Aren't you in there!?
Are you really not!?
Seriously, he's driving me crazy!
The caller has powered off his phone. You will be connected to his voice mailbox.
Hey! You think it's enough to just send a text saying "getting some air"?!
This is getting off the map!
As soon as you get this message, call me.
Reports are coming in right now!
I said let's stay together a little longer!
We were together all day!
Exactly, we were together all day so we can stay together a little longer!
You have to hurry and get ready for your business trip!
I don't wanna go.
The business trip is 48 hours, if I add that to the time on the airplane...
I can't even calculate it. I really can't do it. I'm not going. I can't go on this business trip, I'm gonna call them and tell them i can't go.
It'll be over in a moment!
I'm going to miss you so much.
Me too.
But...you know you've never said "I miss you" before?
Do I have to say it for you to know it?
Soo Ho...
He was smiling.
Slowly!
I'm sayin'! What kind of game is fate playing!?
So when Gary and I came to Korea,
we were both utterly rejected by our first love from a decade ago!
I mean, exactly, you got rejected by someone else, why are you complaining about it to me?
- I!- You're grabbing my shirt.
- I couldn't even imagine it!- Okay, w-wait...
Soo Ho likes a woman...that isn't me...
Wait, my shirt...
I know I go off about saving Soo Ho and stuff like that.
But he's never opened his heart since then. For 10, no 30 years, he never took a step out of that cave.
The one who pulled him out of that cave, is Ms. Bo Nui.
Why!? Why! Why!? Why does that have to be Ms. Bo Nui?!
Why can't it be me!? When I'm so pretty!
When I see him next time, I'll be sure to ask why that happened.
You have a call.
Right. I'm sorry.
Just a minute.
Yes, Ms. Dal Nim, I'm a little busy right now.
Hello?
Ms. Dal Nim!
Cheers!
Cheers.
One of them has to die for this to be over...
Unnie, this is so unfair to me.
This hateful detestful guy totally teased me!
Why'd you tease this child?!
W-When did I do that!?
I never did that!
I-I mean...But how do I do this?
I have to go on a business trip with Je Soo Ho tomorrow!
Gimmie, c'mon, hand it over!
[ Expedia ]
T-This...watch me...
Click this. Okay?
Wow!
Then you slide and click-there! See?!
Wow, you're so fast! As expected of Zeze's ace!
If it wasn't for my CEO,
- I wouldn't have!- Even if you're rejected, you'll still keep your loyalty, is that it?
Hey!
You little-don't play lovey-dovey in front of me!
I mean...Ms. Bo Nui is a little...she's a little weird.
Shake shake shake...like putting salt everywhere...
Hey!
You-what'd you just say?!
My Bo Nui is what?!
- You little-just because I let you talk!- Wait, wait, you're really drunk!- You stay still!
You! I!
If it wasn't my Bo Nui, I wouldn't have given him up!
My 2 years of one-sided love!
The one I liked so much, I filled 3 notebooks without space to spare!
My CEO...I wouldn't have just let him go like that...
CEO?
Wait. Dal Nim. You liked him? My Soo Ho?
"My"?!
"My Soo Ho"?!
My Soo Ho!
Did you just say, my Soo Ho!?
No, my Soo Ho.
- Quietly, quietly!- You!
The crime of talking about my Bo Nui so lightly.
The crime of hurting my CEO's heart in the past!
In the name of justice!
I won't forgive you!
You! C'mere!
Ow! I'm older than you-wait!
Wait, wait! Let go-ow!
Ow!
Hot! Hot.
Sorry, but can you help me? The door is broken.
Ahjussi!
Wait, you can't go in there!
Give me your ID!
Hey! Ajusshi!
Hey!
ID!
Push.
What?!
Push! I said push it already! Hurry up!
- Oh, push?- Yes!
- Oh, thank you!- Right.
1, 2.
There we go!
- Ow!- Oh no!
- Are you okay?- Yes, I'm fine!
You're okay? Here, stand up!
Come on, ow! Ow!
Oh, why? What happened?
I have a disc right now!
Oh...you should've been careful!
But what are you here for?
Starting two days ago, I've been working on the electricity here.
Hey, we're going to be late! You have your passport, right?
Just get yours.
Oh, all of you are here to say bye.
I'll be back!
Yes sir! You have to hit the jackpot in Las Vegas!
We're not going to play. We're doing business! All of you are out of your minds!
Still, you were supposed to go for Genius 2 but we really got it for IF.
This is all due to the efforts and influence of the major sharedholder...
That's enough, let's go.
Finish the demo before we come back, okay?
Yes sir! Please be safe!
Please go safely!
I'll...I'll be back...
Give me your cellphone.
Why?
Hurry!
I made an app!Soo Ho Bo Nui Talk
You can just leave it!
You don't have to do anything!
Done.
Is it like a talisman?
I told you nothing's going to happen!
I mean, just trust me half as much as you do the Spirits.
Oh. Because I'm not here, don't cry because you miss me!
Stop doing that "tskkkk" thing and just go!
You say you're dating in secret and you're laughing all over the place! Are you going off to military service?!
Oh, Ms. Bo Nui, hello.
- Let's go. Hurry up.- Travel safe!
I'm going!
Ugh, you have to cry! Cry! Come on, cry!
Hey, hurry up! We're going to be late for the flight!
I'm really going!
As we are looking for a totally brand new video game.
Then IF is going to be a perfect choice.
So, is it correct that Gary Choi signed up for this game character?
Yes it is.
Sim Bo Nui/ It's lunchtime, isn't it?
Don't skip meals and remember to eat!
Sim Bo Nui/ Stop working and go to sleep!
Promise you'll at least get some sleep!
Yes, yes Princess!
CEO/ I miss you~
Me too.
Have you eaten?
Don't you miss me?
Not a bit!
Really?
You really don't miss me?
Jackpot!
Our PT was a huge success!
Really?! Really?!
Let me see! Come on!
"Zeze Factor is Flooded by Investment Requests"!
Wow!
If we have such secure investors, we'll be killed if something happens to the game!
Don't say such things! Ms. Bo Nui said to never voice such ominous things!
- She's right! Cancel it, hurry!- Cancel.
Hello? CEO?
Did you sleep?
No.
Are you getting on the plane now?
I miss you!
It's been 60 hours and 20 minutes of not seeing each other!
How can I wait 11 more hours?
Are you really not going to say it, even to the end?
I miss you. So very much.
From morning to night, all day.
I miss you. So much I might die.
Then...open the door.
What did you say?
How long are you going to keep me standing here?
I need to be more patient.
How!?
490,000 multiplied by 365 is 1,007,885 days.
Multiplied by 24 hours is
42,940,000 hours-ish.
It's not enough...
What are you doing?
Assuming that I'll be with you until I'm 80,
I finished calculating the time left with you, and it's not nearly enough.
Then...say it officially.
That it's yes.
- Excuse me?- Say it!
Yes.
What? I can't really hear.
I said Yes.
Yes. Yes.
♬ Like the sky of the night, like the air, I can't reach you ♬
♬ Don't hesitate any longer ♬