I will take...
all responsibility.
He's putting his everything into this,
so he'll lose everything he has.
I am dismissing myself...
from the president position as of today.
If he has fame, it will be tarnished.
I'll give up everything I have...
from my shares to my personal assets. Everything.
If he's wealthy, he'll lose all of his wealth.
When he loses everything from his fame to wealth...
and is left with nothing but his body...
Even that last thing he has will be destroyed by your bad luck.
Where have you been?
I met your mother.
She's very worried about you.
Thank you.
But I'll be okay.
Zeze Factory started in a tiny studio. It's okay.
We can start over.
You know I'm a genius, don't you?
It'll work out.
I really hope it does.
I'll make it happen.
Properly.
So...
Let's have fun today.
I realised that I didn't use any vacation days for seven years.
Today,
I'd like to have fun without worrying about anything.
Where should we go?
Wasn't that movie was really moving?
That's what you cried, right?
Not because of me?
I know you'll say it's nonsense,
but what if this is because of me?
What if...
this happened to you and Zeze...
because of me?
Bo Nui.
Are you an industrial spy?
- No.
-  Then...
you must've planted the ransomware.
Of did you pray for IF to be a failure?
You did none of the above.
How can this be your fault?
Look at me.
You're not allowed to worry.
You're not allowed to doubt.
That's a nice girl.
Let's have lunch.
Let me have the pizza.
Here.
It tastes better when you use your hands. Here you go.
Eat it all.
- Have another bite.
-  No.
This isn't your fault.
Never. It's not because of you.
This could be a coincidence.
It might not be my fault.
Bad things...
can happen all at once by chance.
If you don't give up an offering,
you will face bad luck for certain.
So you already gave your heart to him.
What should we do now?
- Really? Mr Je said that?
-  Yes.
The official statement will be released this afternoon.
He's even giving up his private property?
Why did he have to go so far?
I have no idea...
what kind of things were discussed among shareholders.
Dal Nim.
Don't frown. You'll get wrinkles.
I'm so troubled I don't know what to do.
I'm worried about Bo Nui, too.
Bo Nui?
Her prince has suddenly turned into a frog.
Knowing her, she'll be blaming herself for this.
I'm so worried about her.
This is my game. It's my life and reputation, and I'm fine.
Why is everyone else upset?
I know.
However, the company has no choice but to think about numbers.
Amy.
Gary.
The prize money you lost by missing games during the two-month break,
the profit that would've come with your ranking and now this...
We can come to the conclusion...
that this is a disgrace to the name Gary Choi.
- You're siding with the company.
-  Hey!
I drew blood fighting for you.
I tried saying we'd do anything if they dropped the lawsuit.
Then I tried threatening to quit my job.
I'm trying my best.
I want you to tell them exactly what I say.
I'm cancelling the contract unless they drop the lawsuit.
Gary.
This isn't something you can be so adamant about.
You might face a backlash.
The company could raise an issue...
about your vacation and your father.
They can do whatever they want. I'll pay for the damages.
Let's calm down.
Soo Ho is stepping down from his position and even giving up...
his private property to resolve the issue.
Once things quiet down,
you'll have the upper hand against IM Sports.
Who stepped down?
Soo Ho.
He's taking all responsibility of Zeze Factory.
It's a good move. I'll kill the buzz in the media.
He finds the right answer to problems faster than anyone else.
He must have weighed his options.
Then...
What will happen to Mr Je?
(Transferor)
(Share Release Form)
Is this really necessary?
This, too.
I should've given it to you yesterday, but forgot.
You're so stubborn.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I'm not the one making the share prices drop.
How would I know how much more it will drop?
Please, I've had enough.
(President Je Soo Ho resigns because of the ransomware.)
Will this resolve the issue?
It'll keep people quiet for now.
I want them to hurry up and catch the bad guy.
The police at the office scare me.
Does that mean Mr Je can come back?
The damage was already made and the lawsuit will be continued.
We still haven't found the passcode to solve this problem.
It can't be undone.
I feel like he's still in the office.
I know.
I am sorry.
Don't smile. It breaks my heart.
Right.
Please get rid of this for me.
Keep the car. You can do that.
I promised to give everything I own. I have to keep my words.
You...
are keeping it a secret, right?
What?
- About Mr Won?
-  Hey.
Okay. All right.
You're the one who cut me off first.
Make sure my team doesn't find out about it.
Especially Bo Nui.
You're unbelievable.
Gosh, we don't even have time to go out to eat.
I don't have any appetite.
Are you all right?
I will hurry out and buy something to eat.
Thanks, Bo Nui.
How can you clear up everything so fast?
Is your body the only thing you have now?
This is more than enough.
Stay here. I'll get my car.
- Hello?
-  Where are you?
I'm at the office. I wanted to see your face.
I'm outside running an errand. I think it will take a long time.
Is that right?
Yes.
Take care going back.
Okay.
Soo Ho.
Yes.
I'll put this at my place.
Soo Ho.
Je Soo Ho.
What? What is it?
Right.
You can't be yourself right now.
You never rested a day and spent all your 20s on Zeze Factory.
How would you have felt walking away from it voluntarily?
I am so sorry.
I am sorry that I couldn't protect you.
I should have sold my shares to...
Stop it.
Don't give up your place as the major shareholder.
You have to protect IF and my team.
- Soo Ho.
-  Stop it!
But I can't stop crying.
Why would you cry?
Stay with me for a while.
Please clean up for me.
No matter how hard I clean, it looks like a pig sty.
I won't go to a pig sty.
Just for a few days. I'm looking for a flat for you.
Don't waste your money on a useless thing.
Spend it only when I ask you.
Then where will you stay?
Where are you going?
Tell me where you are going!
Gosh, why did I cry for him?
Gosh!
He's completely mad.
Your company is bankrupting, you know?
- Who is it?
-  Your boyfriend.
- Mr Je!
-  Take my bag. Hurry.
What's going on?
It's nice.
What are you doing?
I sold my house, remember? I don't have a place to stay.
So?
- I'm staying here for a while.
-  What?
You know I'm unemployed now. I don't have a place to go.
You could go to Mr Han's.
I can't go there. I can't possibly live there.
It's a pig sty.
How about your parents' house then?
That's near the water.
I can't go near the water.
You went there with me before.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't have a car and it's too far.
And as a moral citizen, you shouldn't do that.
You should help the less fortunate.
Besides, it's your boyfriend we're talking here.
Your boyfriend.
I am your boyfriend.
- Are you serious?
-  I'm sorry. I can't accept you.
But it's not the first time.
- Still, you can't.
-  Then where should I sleep?
Come in.
Yes!
I will go to a sauna and sleep there.
Okay. You go in and sleep.
- Go in and sleep.
-  Okay.
Okay. Good night.
Bye. Sweet dreams.
- Bo Nui, wait! Bo Nui!
-  I am really sorry.
That's not it.
Why would you do it then?
What are you doing here?
I just dropped her off.
But I feel sorry to go home.
Gosh, I feel so sad. Bo Nui!
I am hungry.
- Enjoy.
-  Thank you.
Where's your father?
He's at the temple he's been staying.
I'm trying to convince him to go to Canada with me, but he won't listen.
You have a lot of time now.
You can go back and forth to see each other.
Thank you.
It's so hard to say that.
By the way, why did you quit Zeze Factory?
I had to.
They will still succeed to develop IF.
That was my condition for leaving.
You didn't have to bet your position.
It wasn't because of you, Gary.
I did that because...
- the original developer is pretty.
-  Gosh...
It's important for both you and Bo Nui.
Gosh, I really don't like you.
I need to see flaws in order to take you down.
But the more I see you, the more I think you're a good man.
I can't believe you realised that just now.
If you have nowhere to go, you can stay at my place.
I'll let you in.
Why would I?
I have a girlfriend. Why would I stay at your place?
I thought I'd pretend to be your friend. I don't like it, either.
Never mind.
It's just that I saw Bo Nui kicking you out a while ago.
You saw that?
Don't give Bo Nui a hard time.
When did I give her a hard time? I didn't do anything to her.
Then why would a kind girl like her kick you out?
Exactly. I don't know the reason.
If you know, please tell me.
Anyway, don't make her cry.
She cried enough.
You make sure...
You make sure to make her laugh.
Aren't you going to answer?
She will never cry because of me.
I would be the one crying because of Bo Nui.
It's good. Why aren't you eating?
I was going to eat it.
It's good. They have good noodles.
It's a complete defeat.
Game over.
Where are you?
(Where are you?)
(To Mr Je)
Did you find somewhere to go?
Would you like to come...
(Would you like to come...)
(To Mr Je)
- Hello?
-  Were you worrying about me?
I don't see any stars tonight.
Good night.
It's just for one day.
One day? Of course it is.
A day in the living room and another in your room.
The others on the bunk bed and in the kitchen. It'll be a month then.
No.
I'm sure you can find a place tomorrow.
Of course I can. That's why I'm not looking.
Look.
Do you not like being with me?
- No, but...
-  Okay, that's enough.
Four days.
I'll take 4 days and add 3 more. How about a week?
- Fine.
-  Really?
Yes!
You can laugh if it's funny.
You laughed.
Bo Nui.
Now,
let's go to sleep.
- Just once.
-  No, I don't want to.
- Please.
-  Go away.
Was this necessary?
Of course.
This is important.
It shows that this place is your home...
and that you feel totally comfortable, safe and free.
That's what it stands for.
You look gorgeous.
You look amazing.
Seriously.
Where do you think you're going? Sleep on the sofa.
- Sofa?
-  Yes.
I think you need to explain logically...
why I should sleep on the sofa.
Do you want me to kick you out?
You said you needed a place to sleep and you're trying to hit on me?
Come on.
Oh, my.
Are you serious?
Gosh.
I don't believe it.
You scared me.
No way.
You're dangerous.
You should've told me.
I had no idea.
If you wake up at night...
to get water or go to the bathroom,
I'll be right here.
Don't come and stare at my face...
or grab my hand.
Don't try anything silly.
Gosh.
You sneaky girl.
Why aren't you sleeping?
It's cooler on the floor in the summer.
If the bed gets too hot,
try sleeping on the floor. It's nice and cool.
It's so cool.
I'm sleepy. Good night.
Good night.
Even that last thing he has will be destroyed...
by your bad luck.
That isn't true.
Are you sleeping?
You must be sleeping.
Thank you for letting me stay here.
Sleep tight.
Good night.
Bo Nui...
Bo Nui.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
- I slept amazingly well.
-  Me, too.
It's even better seeing you in the morning. Do you want coffee?
Yes.
You should go in.
Should I walk you to work?
- Go in and look for a place.
-  Gosh!
Get plenty of rest here since you worked hard until now.
Take a nap and try to be lazy.
Come straight home after work.
I'm going to wait here like a puppy.
- See you after work.
-  Wait!
I forgot something.
I have my salt and red beans.
- You have to take this.
-  What?
Be safe.
It's me.
What happened?
I'll be right there.
Is it okay for us to continue developing IF?
I know.
Even if it's released again, nobody would care about it.
But still, Mr Je protected it with everything he had.
So we have to make it well.
Is Mr Je all right?
You can't dump him because he's dirt poor now.
The most miserable moment for guys is...
getting dumped for not having anything.
That's such an immature thing to say!
Don't worry about him.
That's the only way they can express how much they like Mr Je.
Okay. I will tell him that.
Don't tell him that I called him dirt poor.
Hello?
I am well.
- What?
-  I'm cleaning,
- and I'm washing the dishes.
-  You don't have to do that.
You could just leave them.
Except that I don't have you here, I am doing perfectly fine.
So don't worry about me and work hard. That's why I called.
- Bye.
-  All right.
Bye.
I wish you'd tell me when you're here.
I'm here!
You're so excited.
This place is empty anyway.
So I made a deal with the landlord and rented it for a month.
By the way, what is this mouldy office?
It used to be Mr Won's office.
What are you going to do?
Stake out? Are you planning to catch him yourself?
I'm going to destroy the ransomware.
- What?
-  Let's make a recovery software...
and distribute it for free.
We can't do anything about the damage that's already been done,
but it will start bringing up Zeze Factory's image.
Is that possible?
You should've mentioned it at the shareholders' meeting.
No, I couldn't have done it in the two days they had given me.
And I can't do it by myself.
Are you thinking of working with me?
I'm not good at this.
Maybe it's Mr Won!
- Mr Je.
-  Hello.
- Hello.
-  Did you order fried chicken?
I forgot.
- I should've brought some.
-  Don't worry about it.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for calling me.
What should I do first?
What are you here for?
They made it possible to check real-time.
I don't think we should touch this.
Gosh, they twisted it so much.
Knots are easy to make but tough to untie.
Let's eat!
Have some of this.
This type is not supposed to have a code, but this one does.
They changed an existing ransomware.
I think we can fix it.
You two are alike.
- Hey.
-  Blood-related families...
are not the only ones that can look alike.
You guys lack imagination.
By the way, you are still very good.
I just followed your direction.
This is fun.
It's looking good.
You're going to create something amazing!
Let me remind you again.
This is a top secret. Please don't tell anyone.
Of course.
There's no one to tell anyway.
Still.
- Secret.
-  Secret.
What?
You naughty boy.
Are you happy that you're staying at Bo Nui's?
Good? It's amazing.
You've opened up your eyes.
Your brake is broken. You'll get into an accident!
I have to stay there.
Of course. Your body and soul must be there.
I need to show her that it's okay for us to be together.
What are you talking about?
She's scared.
She must be really worried right now.
I need to stick close to her...
and show her that everything will be all right.
Wait. So you moved into her house...
just to comfort her?
Why? Why is Bo Nui so nervous?
She's going to think that everything is her fault.
If she blames everything that happened to...
me and the company on herself,
that fainthearted girl will leave me.
Is that why you made sure we never talk about Mr Won?
Once she finds out that the person she introduced made this happen...
Yes. So that's how it affects her.
If it hadn't been for her,
Mr Won wouldn't have worked for Zeze Factory.
I am going to figure out and fix everything.
Then I'm going to tell her that it was nothing.
I won't lose her.
Bo Nui.
Yes.
What is love?
Love?
It's something very precious,
happy and ardent.
It's a little terrifying, too. Isn't that what it is?
Bo Nui.
- You're really in love, aren't you?
-  Yes.
Never lose him.
Okay. Never.
I want to experience that kind of love before I die.
Why?
I'm not attracted to the most handsome man on earth right now.
I want him to look cheesier.
What's happening to me?
What's wrong with my eyes?
Don't do this to me! Don't!
He's ugly.
What should I do?
Did you eat?
You look so cheesy.
Why did I ask her that?
I am such an idiot. Why did I have to say that?
That was so not right.
I should've said it like this.
Is this an ordinary date?
I love it.
I will come pick you up every day.
- Bo Nui.
-  Yes?
You will continue to hold my hands after a month,
after two months...
and even after a year, right?
You promised me.
You don't need to wet it first.
It's better this way.
We look so stupid.
There's something I desperately want to believe.
Who's the sharpest?
I don't know.
I want to believe his words.
I want to believe his eyes.
This station is picture frame.
I want to believe the time I spend with him.
My back hurts.
I want to believe...
that it's going to be...
okay.
(She has a hard time swallowing food.)
(I hope every day will be like today.)
I hope every day will be like today.
Over here.
Why are you so late? Bo Nui lives right across the street.
You know how absentminded I am nowadays.
You look good.
Do I?
You look comfortable.
Start with IM Sports. What happened?
Well...
I was knocked out.
I got defeated.
So I'm saying goodbye to IM Sports.
You must've pushed too hard. You shouldn't have.
This is something Zeze has to handle.
You didn't have to suffer a loss.
What's wrong with you? You're being so nice.
Are you just pretending to be worried?
Cut it out. I can tell it's fake.
- Can you tell?
-  Yes.
- Do you think this is funny?
-  Yes, I do.
You see me laughing.
I can tell we're finally back to being friends.
Look.
I need to ask you something.
Soo Ho.
Did you hear?
Park Ha Sang was behind all this.
They are searching for him and everything.
It's a disaster.
- Is the Russian company behind him?
-  Yes.
No wonder why they brought up developing virtual reality games.
They're developing something that has a similar concept to ours.
Those scumbags.
They couldn't steal our game, so they ruined ours.
Do you know who that is?
He's the one who made you wear that rabbit costume.
Those sneaky jerks.
- The one who stole Genius?
-  Yes.
I don't believe he did it again.
How did Park Ha Sang even get in here?
He doesn't have the access, and we all know what he looks like.
- You won't believe this!
-  What?
A restoration file for the ransomware was posted.
From where?
It's an anonymous user, but it's for free.
You just have to download it to restore most of your files.
- This is probably a lie.
-  No, it isn't.
Can I test it out?
Gosh.
It's working.
- It's real.
-  It works.
It's working.
Good job. We made it.
- Thank you so much.
-  You're welcome.
This looks nice.
I told them.
Your father...
comes to the restaurant to get a drink from time to time.
He only drinks soda nowadays.
That's right.
He asked Yeong Il about how you're doing.
Then he pushed me to come here.
I'll give you two some time to talk.
- Take this.
-  What is it?
Your money.
Every time I came to see you,
you gave me money with your love.
I didn't spend any of it and saved it all.
I was planning to use it for your wedding.
I don't need it.
Your father wanted me to give this to you.
It's the register of our fishery.
He put it up for sale, so you can spend it when it's sold.
Take it back.
Please accept it.
We've done nothing for you.
Either when you were here or in the States,
we never did anything for you.
Please accept it, Soo Ho.
I really don't need it.
Don't sell the fishery.
You have to tell us when you need anything.
I'll do that.
Well, then...
At least, give this to Bo Nui.
The delicate and sweet Bo Nui...
needs something to protect her, so I got a tiger for her.
Wait! You're a tiger.
No wonder why you two make such a perfect couple.
Should you get married in the fall?
We can go to the fortune-teller to see how compatible you are.
- Mum.
-  I hear you.
Do you know how good he is?
He predicted that an evil raccoon was after you.
Hi.
- Hi.
-  Hi.
I'm here to say goodbye.
I'm moving out today.
- What?
-  What?
Thank you for everything.
Don't say that. We should thank you.
Even if you go to Canada, we'll annoy you for developing IF.
This is my last day in IM Sports.
- What?
-  Why is that?
Why? Did you get fired?
It was half my idea. I need a break.
Do you have a place to stay in Korea?
I'm thinking about it.
Oh, right.
Should I move into Saetbyeol Apartment?
It was a joke.
Bo Nui.
I'm sorry for everything.
I knew it, but I tried to ignore...
the fact that Soo Ho might find someone other than me.
I think that's why I was so mean to you.
I recently met Soo Ho.
My dad asked me to.
He asked me to bring Soo Ho with me to the States.
He wants to wrap up his 10-year-old research.
Guess what Soo Ho said.
I don't want to.
Right now,
I like being with Bo Nui.
Soo Ho...
looks very happy.
You're the one who brings him that happiness.
So...
I want you to be happy...
with him.
I always thought you're cool.
You're bright, bubbly and confident.
You're pretty enough...
to be loved by everyone.
I was jealous.
The person I'm most jealous of...
is telling me she's jealous of me.
Do you want to switch?
It's a joke.
Nurse Lee.
- Is something wrong?
-  Congratulations, Bo Nui!
I didn't know this day would come.
It's okay now. She's fine now.
(Contacts)
(Mr Je)
Bo Nui.
Bo Ra.
Finally.
Everything is okay now.
- Bo Nui.
-  Things will be better now.
Let's recover slowly and live together.
Thank you, Bo Ra.
The curse may have been lifted.
Bo Ra and Mr Je.
Everyone may be fine now.
Please feel free to take this if you need it.
Come here.
I'm so proud of you, Bo Nui.
Good job.
- I'm so proud.
-  Mr Je.
Bo Ra...
can talk now.
What?
She can only say my name so far, but what matters is...
that she started talking.
She recovered her voice.
Shall we go see her now then? Wait, it's late.
Shall we go tomorrow morning?
- I saw her.
-  Already?
Without your talisman?
Is today a special day or what?
Are you being reborn today?
Tell me that it's okay.
Say that it'll be okay and that everything will be fine.
It'll be fine.
Everything will be fine no matter what.
Tomorrow is the seventh day.
Are you really going to kick me out?
You can't live like this forever.
Okay.
If that's the case...
Let's go on a date tomorrow.
What's all this?
- It's so pretty.
-  Yes, indeed.
You'll have to dress up since it'll be a special date.
You know that I like hearing yes, right?
"Yes, yes." Like this.
Well, what I mean is...
When I say that we should eat, drink...
or do something,
you should just say yes.
Gosh, I'm sleepy.
I should get some sleep.
That means...
he's going to propose to you!
He asked you out on a date and gave you that dress.
He told you to say yes no matter what!
Today is the day.
I knew it. I was thinking you look prettier than usual today.
Mr Je is so good at dating.
I don't have to teach him anything.
I guess it's because he's a genius.
Sure thing.
Dal Nim.
I should be...
allowed to be happy now, right?
What are you talking about?
You must be happy.
Gosh, this feels so nice.
Do women like pink flowers?
- Yes.
-  I'll get this then.
Sure.
Mr Won, where have you been?
Bo Nui, please come here now.
Bo Nui. Bo Nui!
You let the suspect in just before the incident took place...
and resigned without giving notice after the incident.
The circumstances tell me that you must be his accomplice.
Tell me. How much did he give you?
What are you talking about now?
He just gave me a few drinks and coffee. Is that considered bribery?
Then tell me why you let him in when you aren't even his accomplice.
He said he was doing an electrical inspection.
According to the security camera footage,
it looked like you left him alone on purpose.
Was I supposed to poop there then?
I ran to the washroom because I had diarrhoea.
That's when he installed the ransomware or whatever it is.
Bo Nui.
He came to work on some electrical work.
Then why did you run away?
It must've been because of guilt!
I wanted to catch him myself.
I've been on a stake-out all this time.
I could've caught him by now if it weren't for you.
I should go catch him right now...
Bo Nui.
Bo Nui, tell him. I have no idea what that thing is.
You know that I'd never do such a thing.
Is the guy...
from that day the suspect?
I really didn't know.
Did you let him into the office?
Yes.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's not my fault.
It's not because of me.
I just started believing that...
the unfortunate incidents...
happened by pure coincidence.
But if it was you...
What can I do if it was you?
How can you do this to me?
How can you be like this?
Bo Nui, what's wrong?
You said you ruined Mr Won Dae Hae's life.
He got a really good job recently.
You said you're cursed with bad luck, but good things are happening.
I ran to see Mr Koo as soon as I heard the news.
He's saying it's the racoon.
The racoon got involved.
What a sad and wretched fate!
I see a deadly knife.
Its blade is thrusted in you.
No.
Your ferocious energy...
makes people suffer and bleed.
Who would want to be around you?
- No.
-  Don't blame anybody!
It's all because of you.
It's not true.
Bo Nui.
Ms Shim... Shim Bo Nui.
No, I should just call her Bo Nui.
Ta-da.
Ta-da! This is for you!
Bo Nui, where are you now?
Hello? Bo Nui?
Mr Je.
Did something happen?
I miss you.
I miss you so much.
Tell me...
that it's not true.
Tell me that it's okay.
Where are you now?
Bo Nui!
Yes, it's not true.
Look at him smiling like that.
If he is left with nothing but his body...
Even that last thing he has will be destroyed...
- by your bad luck.
-  No.
No.
No!
(He)
(Please feel free to take this if you need it!)
Thank you for everything.
I relied on you in times of distress.
But from today,
I'm going to lean on him.
I'll trust him and lean on his heart.
I want to live happily like that.
I...
can do that, right?