I missed you.
We only took a week-long break,
but I couldn't wait for our class to begin again.
How are you?
- Good.
-  Good.
I missed our pretty teacher.
I missed you, too.
- Me, too.
-  Me, too.
Today, you'll learn how to make video calls...
and how to use messenger services.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
Did you call him again?
I told you to stop bothering him when he's busy.
I didn't call him.
I set his place just in case he comes.
Why do you call Yeong Il all the time then?
Is he a spy or what?
Why do you ask him about your son?
Am I not allowed to even worry?
Here.
- Put that away.
-  Please, just once.
- No way.
-  Give it a try.
Soo Ho!
I couldn't ask for anything more.
When was the last time we gathered together for a birthday?
Has it been 18 years or 20?
It's been 21 years.
Let's celebrate birthdays together every year from now on.
Let's eat.
It would be great if she was here on this festive day with us.
I wonder how that small and fragile girl is doing.
How could she not call us even once?
Soo Ho, I don't go to the fortune-teller any more.
I got upset thinking about it.
He called that pretty girl a raccoon.
I can't trust him any more.
I don't believe what he says.
Good job.
Enjoy the food.
Congratulations, Min Jae.
Yes.
Congratulations!
He won the junior match and made a debut on television.
Everything is happening all at once.
I'm not sure if I should be taking gifts from you.
You're going to get busier from now on.
He's going to be so successful that you won't be able to handle alone.
Now is the time you should hire a professional.
What do I have to do for you to trust me?
The other companies are bigger...
Well...
This makes me sad.
I've told you this before,
but I am so much better...
than any other big companies.
If you could just talk to Gary Choi for five minutes,
you'd realise that.
You're lying, aren't you?
What did you say?
That you were Gary Choi's agent.
How many times have I told you?
I met him when he was so cheeky just like you now.
We made it to the top together.
Why aren't you working with him any longer then?
I read it on the internet that IM Sports fired you.
Hey!
I didn't get fired!
Min Jae has to first learn how to be on an interview.
Min Jae, if you talk rudely like that,
the news reporters won't like you. Do you know that?
Amy.
Gary!
Hey, how can you surprise me like this?
It's fun. I had a shooting here,
and you had a meeting here.
Anyway, that was perfect timing.
What are you here for today? Interview?
Yes.
You're now like a complete professional.
A year ago, you became shy...
doing a motion capture.
Don't even mention it.
When I think about what I did with Mr Je, gosh...
Why? You two looked good together.
There was a strange chemistry between you two.
How's work?
Well, working alone is...
really killing me.
I don't have any title or money.
It's really tough to find an athlete who will trust me for who I am.
Things will turn out well.
Whoever it is, the athlete who works with you is very lucky.
Hey. Don't do it.
I might really cry.
I cry whenever someone says something slightly touching.
You look good. Your face is glowing.
So do you.
How can you be so successful without me?
You won the Wimbledon,
and you were the cover model of "Time".
Congratulations.
I am so proud of my athlete.
Why are you like this? We talked about this on the phone already.
Oh, right.
You're seeing someone, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I can never reach you. Your phone is always busy.
Time's up. I have to go in.
Look at how you change the subject.
Anyway, wait for me. Let's go to Zeze Factory together.
You know today's the day of IF's re-release, right?
You go alone.
I don't work for IM Sports any more, and I'm no longer your agent.
Don't be like that. You've been there since the start.
I have a meeting with a promising swimmer.
He will get me a gold medal on the coming Olympics.
I'm leaving. Good luck with the interview.
Cheer up!
Mr Je.
I organised a list of game start-up companies.
Okay. Send me the file.
Here you go.
(List of Game Start-ups)
Did you hand-write all of these?
I wrote every word with love.
Properly!
This is unbelievable.
This is unbelievably useless.
As you know,
this is Daebak Soft.
This is Daebak Soft.
You can't become successful with this.
Right.
Okay.
- And...
-  Yes?
You should sign up for a computer class.
You should start learning how to use the tools. I will pay for it.
He's learning hard from me.
He's improving, so don't worry.
He's improving, and yet, he wrote all of these by hand.
Hello!
- This is a happy day!
-  Hello.
Hello.
It's been a year!
Finally, IF is out!
- Let's go.
-  Wait.
I...
thought deeply about it.
But as you know,
IF was first designed here.
No matter how much I think about it, I need to be there.
Why...
Why would he...
That's what I thought,
but I shouldn't probably go there.
Are you done planning for the new game?
- Not yet.
-  What are you going to do?
Gosh, time is ticking, and investors are very anxious.
Having heard that you are releasing a new game after a year,
everyone keep calling me. They're excited to see it.
Is that right?
You must have something in mind.
The largest shareholder of Daebak Soft is getting really excited.
There aren't any shares for it. How are you the shareholder?
- When you first began, I...
-  What?
Is this about how you paid the rent for two months?
That's not much. I already paid you back.
- I also paid for...
-  Electricity bills, right?
You don't even let us turn on the air conditioner. Gosh.
- I...
-  It's about Mr Won, isn't it?
That jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk don't cost much. Gosh.
Can you read my mind?
Anyway, once a major shareholder, always a major shareholder.
If Daebak Soft goes public, I will buy all the shares.
So this deal is really important.
You have to do well. Okay?
Okay? Answer me.
Answer me.
Oh, dear.
- Yoon Bal,
-  Yes.
How many hours have we been up?
It's 73 hours and about 30 minutes.
Oh, dear. I'm dying.
I need to watch my youngest child walk before I die.
Stop talking nonsense.
IF will be re-released today,
and Mr Je will return.
How nice is that?
I think I'm going to become neurotic.
Final check. Final check one.
Final check 1.1. Final check 1.2. Final check 2. Final check...
Why are there so many final checks? Am I "AlphaGo" or what?
But thanks to you, we released IF successfully.
How nice is that?
Hurry up and get out.
- No. I'm not going out.
-  Please wait a little.
- Mr Je is here!
-  What?
Go! Go!
Hurry up.
Gosh. Seriously.
Congratulations on the successful relaunch of IF.
Father of IF, Mr Je will give a congratulatory speech.
Here's the mic.
Because I'm your lady.
And you are my man.
I only came to congratulate you.
I came to applaud.
The candles are melting. Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
-  Hurry.
Okay.
It was very like Zeze Factory.
You did a splendid job.
All right. Let's blow it out on the count of three.
In 1, 2 and 3.
You're coming back, right?
Of course. He's the reason we stayed up all night.
- Come back,
-  Come back,
- Mr Je!
-  Mr Je!
- Come back,
-  Come back,
- Mr Je!
-  Mr Je Soo Ho!
- Come back!
-  Mr Je!
- Mr Je!
-  By the way,
I want to see the mother of IF, too. How is Bo Nui doing?
- Why? Why?
-  Be quiet.
Why?
Everyone.
I work for...
Daebak Soft now.
I will work hard so that it will pose a threat...
to Zeze Factory one day.
Okay. I look forward to seeing that.
I hope it thrives, Mr Je.
Okay.
- Let's eat.
-  Bring a knife to cut the cake.
Bo Ra.
(Bo Nui, I'm going to Seoul. Don't worry about me!)
Bo Nui, I am going to Seoul. Don't worry about me.
What's wrong with this?
Can you help me?
- Me?
-  Help me.
I'm sorry, but I can't go up there.
Can you push me from the back?
Is it your first time to see someone on a wheelchair?
Hurry up. I have to go.
Okay.
Thank you.
Are you alone?
Excuse me?
Are you not with your family or friends?
I'm not a kid.
I took a bus and a taxi alone to get here.
That's impressive.
By the way,
do you know where Zeze Factory is?
I heard it's around here.
Why are you going there?
I have to meet someone there.
It's close by. I'll take you.
Thank you.
Have we...
Never mind.
We couldn't have met.
Why does his voice sound familiar?
Could he be a voice actor?
Are you a voice actor?
I hear that a lot.
Dal Nim, I don't know what to do. Bo Ra disappeared.
Where could she be?
- Bo Nui.
-  I'm sorry,
but I'll call you back later.
She's here.
Your sister is at Zeze Factory now.
Shim Bo Nui.
(Shim Bo Nui)
Bo Ra, you should've called me beforehand.
Then you would have told Bo Nui.
You should come with Bo Nui.
It's dangerous to come alone.
This is my special operation.
- What is it?
-  Dal Nim.
Call Mr Je Soo Ho for me.
- Who?
-  Your boss.
I mean your former boss.
I came, thinking he'd be here on a day like this.
He came and left.
Really?
I was too late.
If I hadn't gotten caught in front...
What did you want to meet him for?
Did Bo Nui say something?
No, the problem is that she doesn't.
Bo Nui tells me everything.
She told me about working at the convenience store...
and what she had for lunch every day.
But she won't say a thing about Zeze Factory...
or Mr Je Soo Ho.
There are things you can't dare talk about...
because it hurts too much to even think.
That's why I can tell she's hiding something.
I wanted to meet him and find out what it is.
Too bad.
Is that so? Gosh.
- Hi.
-  Thank you.
What's this?
We should be giving you a gift.
You all worked hard.
You made my life look much better than the actual one.
The model is just so amazing.
I watched the Wimbledon game.
It was the best.
We got together to watch it.
I thought you were going to lose during the fourth match.
- My heart skipped a beat.
-  I almost had a heart attack.
- I'm not kidding.
-  Thank you.
I was able to win thanks to your encouragement.
People went crazy...
when the camera found your dad in the audience.
I cried a little.
As we developed the game, I saw things on your point of view.
It made me empathise with you so much.
Just the sight of your father brings tears to my eyes.
- He's overreacting.
-  You should look in the mirror.
That would surprise the tears away.
Why are you picking on him?
Hyeon Bin is nice and has a soft heart.
Isn't Mr Je here?
You just missed him.
You know that he's like the wind.
We could've taken pictures of you two if you had been here earlier.
- I know.
-  It must have been nice.
Hi, Bo Ra.
Guess where I am.
Where are you?
Gosh!
Hi.
What is Bo Ra doing here?
She came to visit.
Bo Nui will be here soon.
Can you stay with her?
I have a meeting with reporters.
Of course. You can go.
Wow, this is amazing.
It looks so real.
I felt like I was on a plane and in the sea.
My sister really made this?
- Bo Nui did?
-  Yes.
She made this, thinking about you.
You're the model.
But she thought about me?
She wanted to show you the beautiful things in life.
I didn't want to be the model, but changed my mind after hearing that.
So be nice to your sister.
Geon Uk, since I met you...
Can I get your autograph?
What?
My friends don't believe that I'm close to you.
Can I get 10 autographs?
- Is 10 enough?
-  Yes.
You look more handsome than before.
Even your autograph looks cool.
Thank you.
Hello?
In 1, 2...
Bo Ra.
- Did you call her?
-  I thought you told her.
Why aren't you answering your phone? You scared me.
I'm sorry.
You should've told me beforehand.
Are you okay?
She made it here safely and I'm here for her.
Bo Nui, I heard you made this.
I didn't know because you didn't tell me.
Did you really start making it because of me?
Yes.
This is unbelievable.
It's like a dream. A very good dream.
Thank you, Bo Nui.
I love you.
She drives me nuts.
Puberty must have hit her late. She keeps calling you, doesn't she?
It's fine. Talking to her on the phone doesn't bother me.
I'm proud of her. She made it all the way here alone.
I didn't know this day would come.
It's nice.
How is your dad? Is he doing well?
Yes, he told me to thank you...
for sending him food and clothes.
I should go see him in person.
Let's get dinner with my dad and Bo Ra later.
- Okay.
-  I told you to come to my match.
You wasted the tickets I sent you.
I'm sure there will be an opportunity someday.
You haven't been here for a while, have you?
No, I haven't.
Everything looks the same.
Are you going to live there forever?
I think Bo Ra is starting to feel suffocated there,
and it'd be better for you to work if you move to Seoul.
I might move someday.
You never know what will happen in the future.
I thought you left without seeing me.
What are you talking about? I want the wedding invitation.
You never disappoint me.
Ta-da!
Dal Nim!
It's so pretty.
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you.
This is all thanks to you.
It was your love that did all the work.
You're marrying the person you had a crush on for two years.
What crush?
- That isn't true.
-  You don't have to hide it.
I'm telling you the truth.
Did you have a crush on someone else?
Who?
No, don't tell me. It'll only concern me.
The person that makes you happy now is the best.
Have a happy life together.
Thank you.
You have to come to the wedding.
I'm not starting the wedding until you arrive, okay?
Is it because you might run into him?
Look, Bo Nui.
You can't avoid him forever.
People that are meant to meet will meet sooner or later.
I'll be there.
Really?
You promised me.
(Daebak Soft)
(Properly)
She will walk and run any time soon.
Good job, Bo Nui.
Here.
What's this?
Take it out.
I saw it when I went to Zeze Factory, so I took one.
Bo Nui,
apply for this contest.
Forget it.
I know you're developing a game every night.
To be honest, playing IF made me realise...
that you are the best.
I'm certain you're going to win.
Bo Ra, you're good at sweet-talking.
I mean it, though.
Never mind. Let's go in.
Okay.
Dal Nim. It's me, Bo Ra.
Did you give it to her?
I did.
But I don't know if she will do it or not.
Good job.
The winner gets 50,000-dollar cash prize.
People have to be free of...
financial problems to start seeing other things.
I hope she applies.
Bye.
Dal Nim, my darling.
Where is she?
She's in my heart
I'm here.
It's hot! It's hot!
Why did you come here again?
I came because I missed you.
I miss you whenever I turn my back.
What am I supposed to do?
Good job.
Did you give the wedding invitation to Mr Je?
I forgot. I am stupid.
That's not good!
Mr Je and Bo Nui are destined to reunite at our wedding.
You planned something really big, didn't you?
Why don't you plan our future first?
Don't you know how they feel?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
They miss each other terribly, but they're stopping themselves.
When they run into each other at our wedding,
their love toward each other will explode.
Why would they do that there? It has to be about us.
We might turn into supporting actors.
But everyone has to be happy on that day.
Do you want my best friend...
and your best friend...
to be unhappy?
No.
How can you be so considerate? You are so lovely.
You are even lovelier.
Wait. I brought a talisman.
It means you are mine.
(You're mine until the day you die.)
You are mine!
You're mine forever.
Habit is a scary thing.
It's been a year since I quit being your agent,
and I came because you called.
Did you sign with that rising swimmer?
Not yet. Why do you ask?
How about Min Jae? That little tennis player.
We're still negotiating.
I completely changed my mind about my ideal type of man.
I want him to be straightforward about expressing his feeling for me.
That little boy and his mother torture me together.
It makes me so dizzy.
So there's still no one.
Just wait. Soon, there will be news articles.
"Amy Han's sports management welcomes their first athlete."
Put my name there.
What?
Your first athlete will be Gary Choi.
Gary.
I'm no longer with IM Sports.
Hey.
You won the Wimbledon.
You're in your best shape, and you're the first on the ranking.
Why would you leave IM Sports?
You're not there.
There was no one to tease, so I got bored.
So?
Are you signing with me or what?
Of course, I will...
Gary.
I don't have much money for the down payment.
Can I pay you monthly?
That's a little...
Okay.
Gary!
- What are you doing? Wait.
-  I am so happy!
Anyway, thanks in advance.
My agent, Amy.
Let's do this, my athlete.
Hello?
Yes, I am Shim Bo Nui.
What?
I told you. You're going to win for certain.
I'm thankful that I passed the first round.
You are so humble.
You either make it or break it.
You either win or fail. That should be your mind-set.
- What is it about?
-  What?
The game. You've been preparing this for a long time.
What is it? Tell me.
There's nothing much to tell. It's simple.
Do you have a model?
I hope it will be someone handsome like Gary again.
I will play it every day.
My game is not like that.
Then what is it?
I haven't decided on the ending part yet.
I will tell you when I decide.
(Properly)
Talk to him about something.
What do you want me to do?
What exactly does the investor want?
Well... He doesn't like the part about the cave,
and he thinks the main character lacks charm.
In short, he wants us to fix everything.
- Let's end it.
-  What?
Let's not do this.
We will give up on this deal.
We can't. I disagree.
They say the one with money rules.
You need money for the rent and our payment.
You need to pay for so many things.
Let's try to give him what they want.
Let's do that, Mr Je.
When we fix something, he points out another problem.
When we fix it, he brings up something else.
People can point out problems endlessly when it comes to games.
Right.
Every person sees games differently.
Come on.
But without money,
we can't develop anything.
We have to make it somehow...
with our own design.
That's only easy to say. How can you make money without an investor?
He's not the only investor out there.
Yes, he is the only one.
He's the only one willing to invest on your idea.
If he doesn't like our game, I don't like him, either.
Let's fix it just a little bit.
Let's fix just a tiny bit.
I don't want to...
change even a tiny bit.
Gosh...
Then why don't you...
pretend to fix it and do what you want after you get the money?
No.
You...
I'm going to arrange a meeting for the last time. Do well.
He's about to open his wallet.
We will be just wasting our energy and time.
I'm going to book an appointment for the last time. Okay?
Okay? It'll be at 8am around Gangnam Station.
- I told you.
-  I can't make it.
- I'll see you at 8am.
-  I didn't hear anything.
See you at 8am.
(Wedding Invitation)
What is it?
It's white and square.
It's our wedding invitation.
Forgive me for getting married first.
(Han Ryang Ha and Lee Dal Nim's wedding ceremony)
Honestly,
you should buy me a refrigerator as the best friend.
Don't do that. I only run a small company, you know?
You're the major shareholder of Zeze Factory.
So go to the meeting and earn some money.
That will solve everything. Okay?
I will wait until the food goes bad.
Make sure to buy me a refrigerator with two doors.
Mr Je.
I think we should add this here...
and take this out.
This looks the best.
Bo Nui.
Thank you.
You have to eat.
Food is important.
I don't know what that is, but try it.
Gosh. I can't drink milk.
She was given a blade...
as her fortune for life.
Are you done?
Did you wake up?
Get more sleep.
Bo Nui, I had another nightmare.
It's just a dream. You'll be okay.
I'm right here next to you, so don't worry and sleep.
It's nice to hold your hand.
Bo Nui.
I was always waiting for you at the hospital.
I waited for you to come and hold my hand.
The nurse told me that you always...
stood outside my room.
So I waited.
I wondered when you'd come and hold my hand.
I wondered when I'd hear your voice.
I waited every day.
I didn't want anything bad would happen to you.
That's why I couldn't go in.
Why would anything bad happen to me?
I felt so much better after hearing your voice.
Didn't I start getting better after you visited me?
Since you came with that man.
Do you remember everything?
I don't remember his face.
But...
I keep replaying his voice in my head.
She tried hard to save you.
So hurry up and get better.
Tell her with confidence for me.
Tell her to be happy.
He told me to love the person I love with all my heart...
and hold tightly onto the hand I want to.
That's right.
He said that.
I have to thank him.
I should thank him for bringing you to me.
I'm sleepy.
Go to sleep.
I'll be here.
- Bo Nui.
-  Yes?
Thank you...
for not giving up on me.
Thank you for always protecting me.
Bo Nui!
Dal Nim.
How are you here?
Bo Ra called me.
She asked me to pave a road of petals for you.
I'm here to encourage you.
Thank you.
This reminds me of old times.
Don't you need the rabbit mask today?
Do you have your salt and red beans?
No, I don't.
Really?
I see. Now that Bo Ra got so much better,
you don't need any of that.
I'm a little nervous.
What can I do for you? Do you need a hug?
Yes.
Thank you for being my friend.
Thank you, too.
I have to go back to work.
I won't be able to stay for the entire presentation. I'm sorry.
I feel encouraged just by seeing you here.
Do a good job and win first place.
Buy me a wedding gift with the prize money.
Sounds good.
- Yes!
-  Yes!
(2017 Second Half Game Idea Contest)
The number you have dialled is not available at this moment.
Why isn't he answering the phone?
When did he leave?
I saw him when he left.
Where did he go?
I thought he was going to meet the investor.
Why would he go there when I'm here? This is driving me crazy.
I went through a lot of troubles to set up this meeting.
Why don't you print out the proposal and go by yourself?
That's a good idea. Where's the proposal?
Let's take a look.
What?
It isn't here.
It's not even in the share folder.
- That can't be true.
-  It's not in the hard drive.
- What?
-  What?
No way.
(2017 Second Half Game Idea Contest)
We will now begin...
the 2017 Second Half Game Idea Contest.
Next contestant should get ready.
Okay.
(2017 Second Half Game Idea Contest)
Hello, my name is Shim Bo Nui.
Hello, I'm Je Soo Ho of Daebak Soft.
- Do you believe...
-  Do you believe...
- in miracles?
-  In fate?
This game is about a girl...
who is the unluckiest in the world.
She was given a blade as her fortune for life.
She was born with the fate...
of hurting everyone she loves.
This game begins when the girl receives a letter...
after losing everything a year ago.
Goodbye.
Shim Bo Nui was my light, not a blade.
She held my hand in my times of need.
I didn't want you to see me like this.
Now, we're even.
She made me smile when I felt embarrassed.
You've done so much for me.
But this is all I can do for you.
She stayed by my side when I was sick.
When I lost everything,
she made me believe everything would be okay as long as I had her.
That light guided me out of my cave.
Shim Bo Nui saved the life of Je Soo Ho.
Thank you, my love.
The girl leaves on a long journey...
to reply back to this letter.
This game is...
about a boy trying to escape the cave he has been hiding in.
The cave is very dark, and he was so lonely in there alone.
However, the outside world felt unfamiliar and dangerous,
so he couldn't go out of the cave.
What does this boy need to escape from the cave?
He needs light.
The girl embarks on an adventure, and many hardships come her way.
At each of those moments, the girl reminisces the precious memories...
she shared with the person who led her to light.
(Medicine)
You seemed to be having indigestion.
Shim Bo Nui.
Mr Je!
Bo Nui...
Hello? This is the police, right?
The person saved her from danger...
and offered her an umbrella when she was getting soaked.
Bo Nui.
Let's go home now.
You said...
that I'm your talisman.
So what are you worried about?
He gave her a shoulder to lean on when she was frightened.
You're not allowed to worry.
You're not allowed to doubt.
The person smiled even when his world collapsed.
The person always...
embraced her with a big hug.
The same girl...
is called a blade by some...
and a ray of light by the others.
The miraculous light shines upon the boy who couldn't trust anything.
Then it comes down to this.
She now has to decide...
which side to trust.
The game is about his journey to escape the cave for the light.
The game is about her travelling on her own will...
to become the light herself after overcoming her unfortunate fate.
It's Miracle designed by Daebak Soft.
It's Will.
I'm sorry I took too long.
You're so slow.
You pretty fool.
Brace yourself.
I'm going to worry about nothing and only think about myself.
I'll only think about my happiness.
That's the right answer.
Say that you love me.
Say that once more.
Oh my gosh.
Yes, that's it.
Say.
That you love me.
Hey, everyone! Hi!
Hello.
Am I invisible to you or what?
What's up with your reaction?
You visit our office over a dozen times a day.
Do we have to greet you every single time?
Did I only visit a dozen times?
I'll come more often from now on!
I'll do better!
That must've been why.
I missed you so much.
Only you.
What are you doing this evening?
No, don't say anything.
You won't be able to do anything anyway.
Pick where you want to go for our honeymoon.
Shall we go to the Maldives or Hawaii?
- Hawaii?
-  The destination doesn't matter.
Wherever we go together becomes a paradise.
Yoon Bal, do something.
Ji Hoon, get him out of here.
You little kitty cat...
- Ouch, let go. Let go of me.
-  Get out.
- What an eyesore!
-  I won't let this slide!
I just can't take it any more.
Did Cupid put a love spell on this office or what? Everyone's in love.
Oh, that could be true.
My wife and I also met at Zeze Factory.
Goodness gracious, you guys are ridiculous!
Who's dating in the office?
If any of you get caught, I'll teach you a lesson.
You better watch out.
Love is such a great thing.
- I'll teach you a serious lesson!
-  Dal Nim!
(Daebak Soft)
How did it go?
Where did the other two go?
I need to tell you all officially.
They went to a meeting at the data centre.
They told me to call them with an update as soon as you get in.
It didn't go well?
Does he not want to invest in it?
Launching Will and Miracle together...
simultaneously as if they're twins...
It can be a burden to the investor.
- So let's launch Miracle first...
-  He said it's ingenious.
"The two games complement each other perfectly."
"This will be a hit, so I definitely want to invest on it."
- Seriously?
-  Yes!
That's so awesome!
Bo Ra kept telling me that it would go well.
She said that we'd get a lot of investments.
Bo Ra must be waiting. Let's go.
(Saetbyeol Apartment)
We're here.
Hold on. Wait.
Let's hang out here for a few moments.
Put me down over there.
Sure.
All right. Be careful.
I'm really home now.
Hi, Saetbyeol Apartment.
(Saetbyeol Apartment)
Go in.
It's been three years for you and Bo Ra.
I'll be at the rooftop.
It looks a lot like when we used to live together.
I know. He prepared all this for us.
From our beds...
to my desk, everything looks the same.
Bo Nui. This isn't a dream, right?
That drawing!
That's still here, too.
Do you remember?
What you said to me as you were putting that up...
after our parents passed away.
I said that we aren't alone...
because Mum and Dad are watching over us.
And there are 5 of us now, not 4.
(Mum, Bo Nui, Bo Ra and Dad)
Thank you.
I'll be really good to you from now on.
Even that's not enough.
It's not.
Do you know how much dust I inhaled while cleaning there for a week?
I appreciate it so much, so we should...
eat now!
Here.
How can you be like that?
What did I do?
Well, I heard that you did all the work on our place...
without telling Bo Nui.
I'm pretty good, right?
Aren't I cool?
You pretended not to know me then, too.
Gosh, you have a sly side.
You're the one who didn't recognise me.
What? My memory can be bad at times, so you should understand.
Gosh, your memory is what?
Let's memorise the multiples of 19 together.
That's the best exercise for your memory and brain.
No, I don't want to. I hate maths.
How can you hate maths?
Mathematics is a beautiful subject.
It's a subject that needs to be vanished from this planet.
- Cancel what you just said.
-  No.
- I don't want to.
-  How could you...
Take that back at once.
- Take it back.
-  What's going on? Are you arguing?
No, we're not.
- We're so close.
-  We're not arguing.
Soo Ho.
- Soo Ho.
-  Oh, it's you.
Congratulations on moving back.
Now that you're back, we have to celebrate with you.
I ran here as soon as my game ended.
Did you call him?
No, I prefer spending time with just you two.
Geon Uk! Come in!
All right, I'm going in now. Excuse me.
Bo Nui, your sister is cool.
- Hey, Soo Ho!
-  Gosh!
I told you not to come.
How can I not be here?
We need to celebrate your new beginning.
Come on! Move over.
Gosh, this apartment is so tiny.
- I need more of this.
-  Thanks.
- Have some fruit.
-  They look so pretty.
All right, everyone!
Attention, please.
We have something to give you.
First off, Seol Hui.
- Geon Uk!
-  Geon Uk.
- What's this?
-  We're getting married.
- Dal Nim! Why didn't you tell me?
-  I'm sorry.
We didn't have a chance to tell anyone.
These two are busy talking. I should go over there.
Hey, Geon Uk.
- Geon Uk.
-  Yes.
Give us a wedding gift. You make a lot of money.
Hello? Are you ready now?
Not yet. Take your time.
Gosh, it's a beautiful day today.
I'm in a great mood, too. It's a perfect day.
It's perfect for a picnic.
Oh, right. I put tuna in gimbap.
Gosh, fish! I love it.
Drive carefully.
I'll see you shortly.
No, don't worry.
It'll be okay.
Whatever. Let's forget it. No picnic for today!
Let's just do it. Who cares about getting soaked?
What matters is that we're together.
- In 1, 2 and 3!
-  In 1, 2 and 3! Run!
Nothing has changed.
We don't know what future has in store for us,
and our fate will present cruel moments at times.
So we have decided...
to live in the moment.
We won't miss what today's happiness brings to us.
(Epilogue)
The rain has stopped.
I'm glad we decided to stay.
Getting rained on was fun.
Do you want to get rained on with me again?
You know I like yes, right?
My answer is yes, of course.
Would you...
marry me?
I thought hard about it and realised...
that it has to be you.
I'm saying that it must be...
you.
Yes!
Everyone! I'm getting married!
(Thank you for watching Lucky Romance.)
(We're rooting for all of you who do your best regardless of your fate.)
(We hope your will and luck will create many miraculous moments.)
(Lucky Romance)
I'm your boyfriend.
What are you doing this evening?
Do you want to go to Wolmido with me?
You don't have to risk your position.
Oh, no! Your head!
What's wrong?
Dal Nim, my darling.
It's sweet potato cake.
How will we cut it? Where's the knife?
Sweet potato!
Come and eat with us.
Whatever, you pig.
Pig?
Shall we bet?
The one who arrives at the finish line first... What?
I didn't do anything.
Please approve this.
Stop it already.
Are you planning to slip away?
This doesn't fit in my mouth.
Hey! No!
You could die!
My tiger!
Hold on a second.
- Hey, come over here.
-  No, hang on.
You have to pull me towards you.