What happened?
It's okay. Stay calm.
Find a man born in the year of the tiger, and spend a night with him.
Otherwise, she'll die.
I can do this.
This body will rot away when I die anyway.
This is nothing.
You're not supposed to save your body,
but your money.
It's not like I'm going to love him. I can't fall in love with him.
I won't even see him again after this.
Hi!
How long has it been?
Hi, it's good to see you.
I'm sorry.
How have you been?
Good.
Look.
You were born in 1986, right?
- The year of the tiger. - Yes.
That's right.
Sleep with me tonight!
All I need is one night.
Just one night. Nothing more.
Please...
Bo Nui. Shim Bo Nui.
Oh, right.
Let me have a drink before I start talking.
What did you want to say to me?
You're making me nervous.
Excuse me.
Is it you?
Hello?
What's this?
Wait a second.
What happened?
Look, I...
I need another drink before I can say this.
Bo Nui, do you...
have any kind of insurance?
You know how scary this world has come to.
Listen.
Listen to me!
I...
I have a favour to ask.
I must be out of my mind.
I don't have money for insurance.
(Insurance Policy)
Gosh.
Where's my phone?
What in the world happened?
Dal Nim!
Hi, where are you?
Why was it so hard to get a hold of you since yesterday?
I don't know. I don't remember anything.
Did you get drunk?
Yes.
I woke up and found my place a total mess.
What? Are you okay?
Did anything happen to you?
Something should have happened.
Born in the year of the tiger?
I don't think anything happened.
Wait. Wait.
Oh, my!
Why did you call?
I have to pay you for the work.
Send me your bank account and a copy of your ID.
It's going to take around two weeks.
That long?
I need approval to give you four times the regular pay.
How much do you need urgently?
I'll lend you some.
It's okay. I know the situation you're in.
Thanks, though. Bye.
What should I do?
Hi.
I still have a day left.
Did you change your mind? I'll get paid soon.
I'm sorry about that day.
You could've told me about your sibling.
Oh, did you find out?
Every family has a problem they can't talk about.
Look.
Don't worry about the rent and take your time.
- Really? - Of course.
You know how soft-hearted I am.
Thank you.
Blessings to you.
I'll pray for you to be showered with blessings.
Thank you. Go in.
Bye.
Oh, right. Don't light candles in the room.
Of course, I won't ever.
Thank you!
You're giving me a break, aren't you?
What did they say? I'm healthy from head to toe, aren't I?
I didn't need a check-up.
You need to get checked up before Wimbledon.
You know it's less than a month away.
I'm not participating.
What?
Give me some vacation time. Just two months.
What are you talking about?
Tennis players don't get vacations.
Tennis players are human, too.
Gary.
This is Wimbledon we're talking about.
What about your score and ranking?
You're not getting a vacation. Don't even dream about it.
The association won't approve of it, either.
- I can if I do poorly on the test. - What?
Did you already ask?
- Yes, I told them. - Gary!
Amy.
Use me as an excuse and take a break.
You don't have a boyfriend because you work too hard.
I'm not done talking to you. Why do you keep running away?
- Why? - What are you talking about?
- It's the first time I'm out. - Are you sure?
Who was the one called me...
in the middle of the night to pay for his taxi?
You haven't told me where you spent...
all the money you exchanged at the airport.
I spent it on something very nice for someone in need.
What the...
Where did she go?
(Mum, Bo Nui, Bo Ra and Dad)
It's really her, Bo Nui.
Unit 401's overdue rent is all settled now, right?
Of course. It's all settled.
Anyway, I didn't know that she had a handsome brother like you.
By the way, please don't tell my sister...
- that I paid for the rent. - Why?
Is there a secret behind your birth? Is that it?
Yes. She might be shocked.
Gosh, don't you worry about that.
As long as the rent is paid on time,
- I won't have to see her. - Thank you.
Is it because you look kind? I already feel close to you.
You are a decent man.
Did she just not recognise me?
Hello.
What? Is it already out?
It's not. It's not out in the store.
I am sorry.
Where did you download the game?
Gosh, we are in trouble.
Oh, gosh.
Is it really what I think it is?
How are we supposed to solve this problem?
It was released in Russia yesterday at midnight.
It has already been downloaded five million times.
Genius Two was scheduled to be released after a month. What now?
- Did you find out where they are? - Yes.
They left the country on that day. They've been planning it.
I can't believe it. Aren't they industrial spies?
Let's sue them all! Let's report them to the international police.
She's right.
Attorney Park is here.
So going to Russia now is not going to help.
Recently, they are tightening regulations.
But they're not interested in cases against their national interest.
Up to this day, the country stands as the capital of software piracy.
Mr Je.
Newspaper companies keep calling.
They're asking about what happened.
Gosh, this is crazy.
It is not officially released. How many times do I have to repeat?
- We have nothing to say about it. - Gosh!
We will give up...
- the release of Genius Two. - What?
- Mr Je. - Even if we sue them,
we will just waste time, and they'd only grant us an injunction.
Moreover, we cannot release a copycat in the market.
- But ours is the original. - No.
The first released one is the original.
It's our fault that our security had a loophole.
So we must take the responsibility.
I cannot resign. I have three kids.
- You're having a third child? - Yes. It just happened.
- When is the deadline? - The sooner the better.
Bring me a new game.
What?
All right. Let's organise teams.
Dal Nim and Dae Kwon. Lead one team each, and bring me an alpha version.
We will have a demonstration event for the new game after a month.
We will showcase a totally new game, even greater than Genius Two.
I will give you two days.
- Mr Je... - Two days?
How can we do this?
Right. If any of you want to resign,
I will accept the resignation letter after four weeks.
Four weeks? Is this a divorce procedure or what?
- Gosh. - Gosh.
This is a real crisis.
How can we come up with an idea and work on graphics in just two days?
Perhaps, that's his way of dismissing us?
You still don't know he doesn't beat around the bush.
We're in an emergency, you know?
We have to bring our heads together and come up with ideas. Right?
- Cheers, everyone! We can do it! - Yes. She's right.
- This is an emergency. - Mr Han!
Why don't you help us brainstorm...
- Never mind. Bye. - Can you deliver coffee here?
I am a major shareholder.
I hold the biggest share.
I hold a very high position. Do you know that?
- Let's go, Attorney Park. - Yes.
- So can you deliver it or not? - Come on.
Sew it along this line, okay?
That's not how you do it.
- You should hurry up. - I'm back.
- You're here. - You're here.
- You're here, Bo Nui! - Hi!
- Gosh, Bo Nui. - I'll do it.
You are so punctual.
Please check it.
I know how good and meticulous you are.
Look at this. You've done a beautiful job.
How much do you want this time?
- I'm going to stop for a while. - Why?
Are you doing another part-time job? Do both! You do this at home anyway.
Some things came up.
Bye.
- Take care. - Take care.
- Take care. - Bye.
I have to find the tiger right away.
There are only girls here.
- Hey! Stop! - Stop it!
Turn it down.
I'm listening to an exciting song to feel better and brainstorm.
Can anything come out in just two days?
There is someone who has been staying up all night...
- for two days. - He's coming out.
- The meeting is at 3pm, right? - Yes.
- Yes. - Yes.
Submit your work by 2:30pm.
Please check the sources I sent. Hurry.
Stop drinking coffee.
- Give it back. - How long have you been up?
For 42 hours and 30 minutes. Give it back. I have a meeting coming up.
If you die, my shares will worth nothing.
Have some fruits. It gives you vitamin C. How great is that?
Here.
When you sit down for too long, you will get constipated. Drink it.
More. That's it. Good boy.
How are the new game ideas? Is it good or bad?
Please don't talk.
- Please show me your ID. - What?
- Even when I'm buying these? - They're changing the law.
I will check it quickly.
Please show me your ID.
Do I look that young?
I am from Class Fruit of Saetbyeol Kindergarten.
I am seven years old, and my name is Ji Yeon Woo.
You were born on the year of the tiger.
Good luck. Here.
It's 20 cents.
Statistically, 1 out of 12 people should be a tiger.
Why can't I see any?
You are adorable.
Hey. Can you get me one of your cousins?
Thank you for listening.
Thank you.
That was okay, right?
Three-match puzzle for killing time is addicting and nice...
except that the other companies already came up with it.
How many of those games disappeared just this year?
Honestly, what do you expect us to do in two days?
Are we here to create a work of art?
Am I supposed to extend the deadline as long as you want...
and beg you to come up with a masterpiece?
Or has Zeze Factory become a charity organisation without my knowledge?
A charity organisation...
Everyone, this company...
is Zeze Factory.
If you could give us a little more time,
we'll come up with a revised plan.
I'll give you four days.
You don't need to work too hard. Just do a proper job.
- Yes. - Understood.
- Gosh. - This is crazy.
Here it is. I hope you enjoy it.
Sir, you've been running this pub since the IT Centre opened, right?
Yes.
Your customers chat a lot, don't they?
Have you heard any good ideas?
It could be ideas they decided not to pursue.
A hidden gem might be found among them.
Why do you need ideas? You guys are the best in the industry.
Please ignore him. He's just babbling.
I'm not babbling.
I'm concerned about the company as the main shareholder.
I heard you caused another ruckus today.
- Me? - Yes.
You're the only one who doesn't remember.
Don't be harsh on them, please.
What are you going to do if they quit?
If we line up those who want to join Zeze, the line will be so long.
And will any of them be able to satisfy you?
How many times have I told you? Not everyone is like you.
They had to let go of the game they worked on for months.
Restarting from the scratch isn't easy.
That shouldn't be an issue.
They should stop and go when they're told to do so.
Right, you live in a world where everything is either 0 or 1.
That's why you are so decisive.
You'll figure out this one as well since you're so smart and shrewd.
What is that?
(Open Competition for New Game Ideas)
The first round is already over.
Only the presentation is left, so I'm taking this off.
Hey, how about that competition?
It'll be so amateur. It'll be like a kindergarten talent show.
Kids in kindergarten are very creative.
Let me see that poster.
I'm filling up your car!
Your total has been charged.
- Hello! - Sir.
We're doing a daily giveaway event.
What is your Chinese zodiac sign?
My zodiac sign is the ox.
Oh, I see.
That's too bad.
Today, we're giving away gifts to customers whose sign is the tiger.
Your car has been filled up. Thank you!
Drive safely!
(Is It the Miraculous Medicine?)
Oh, Bo Nui. You're here.
Please have a seat.
I brought coffee for you.
Bo Nui.
You have my car registration, right?
I'll give it back when you pay me.
Are you going to pay me now?
Do you want to keep the car?
Go ahead. Keep it.
- No. I'll get going then. - Bo Nui! Hold on.
You'll regret if you leave now. Have a seat.
Mr Won.
My life is full of regrets.
Stop! Hold on.
Don't say that and just hold on right there.
Don't say things like that. Do you remember this?
The game we planned together last time.
That game. Look at this!
(Open Competition for New Game Ideas)
- We submitted it here, right? - Yes.
It passed the preliminary round.
- Seriously? - Yes!
Why would I lie to you about it?
We have to prepare the presentation. The winner gets 30,000 dollars!
Think about winning it and signing a contract.
We'll make a huge amount of money! It'll be huge!
- We'll make it big! - That'd be amazing!
They say that every dog has its day!
- Let's prepare the presentation. - We should.
- When is it? - Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
(Daebak Soft)
Bo Nui, go in. Let's go in.
Gosh, this office has become a mess...
since you stopped coming to work.
I couldn't come to work because I had to catch you.
Goodness. How could we prepare for this presentation in a day?
My phone is suspended as you know. I found out late.
It's impossible. We don't have anything to demonstrate.
We can't complete it in time.
Bo Nui. Don't say it's impossible.
Don't even think about negative things.
This is a huge opportunity for us.
Bo Nui, think about it. We worked so hard.
We poured our hearts into making it.
Bo Nui, we'll win.
We will definitely win and get that 30,000 dollars.
With that money, I can pay you...
and complete IF.
Let's make some money. All right?
Gosh.
We've been neglecting our baby.
- Shall we revive it? - Yes! Let's get to work!
I'll go pick up the most expensive vitamins and supplements.
- All right. - Bo Nui, do you have money on you?
- Goodness! - Sorry, I'll be back. Wait for me!
We can do this!
(Daebak Soft)
Goodness.
Gosh, I must say...
this is a miracle.
You're the best. Great work, Bo Nui.
You're so awesome!
I hope we didn't waste our time.
The quality isn't up to my standard.
Don't say that. This is amazing.
If we submit this, we'll definitely win the competition.
Mr Won, I'll stop by my place first and meet you there.
We're presenting in the second half, so we have some time.
- Okay. - I'll see you later!
- Wash up and get changed! - I will! Oh, right.
Mr Won, go get changed into a suit. You have to wear a tie.
And keep memorising the script!
Okay, I will.
(Open Competition for New Game Ideas)
(Presentation for New Game Ideas)
You must be hot.
I know because I've done it before.
You can do it!
What's taking him so long?
The second half is starting now. Please get ready.
- Okay! - Okay!
(Presentation for New Game Ideas)
The next presenter is KG Network.
(Network Game)
(Social Network Game)
Hello, I'm Jin Seon Woo from KG Network.
We'd like to take social network games to the next level.
All right. I don't need to hear any more.
We'd like to take the notion of war games to the next level...
- by incorporating... - Whatever.
It'll allow you to experience speed in a totally different way.
- With a fresh take on... - Yes, it's different.
It's childish in a very different way.
The next team will present an idea about a sports game.
Let's welcome Mr Won Dae Hae of Daebak Soft.
(Sports Game)
Mr Won, please come up on stage.
- Mr Won Dae Hae? - Yes, I'm here.
Hello, I'm from Daebak Soft.
Are you Mr Won Dae Hae?
What are you doing right now?
It's a part of our presentation.
It's not against the guidelines.
We should let her start the presentation. It's fun.
- Thank you. - Shall we do that?
Please start your presentation.
Then I'll begin now.
I'll use the racoon mask for just 30 minutes.
I'm sorry.
Well...
How much do you know about racoons?
- What kind of animal is it? - Why is she talking about racoons?
Is this a quiz about animals or what?
Wearing this mask...
is making me realise how racoons may view this world...
- and how people treat racoons. - What is she saying?
Things that I couldn't normally notice...
started becoming visible to me after I put this mask on.
And it made me think.
Could we make people enjoy sports games in the same way?
You are no longer the person visiting the zoo,
but the raccoon locked up in the cage in this game.
Look through the eyes of the player, and play sports with their body.
This is "IF", the experiencing game by Daebak Soft.
(Look through the eyes of the player and play sports with their body.)
(You no longer watch they play, but you play it yourself.)
You play IF through the first-person perspective.
For example, it's easy to create games that are played alone...
like ski jumping.
Or the games that require only two players...
like kendo.
However, sports that require more players...
can be very dynamic as well...
as long as you focus on the game's characteristics...
through the first-person perspective.
I know there have been console games...
that allowed you to enjoy sports by using movement sensors.
However, we've added one more thing!
What if you can become Kim Yuna...
or Park Ji Sung?
You can not only play sports through their perspectives...
but also live their lives...
through the perspectives of the star athletes.
Virtual reality?
This was IF, the sports experience game by Daebak Soft.
Thank you.
Actually,
Mr Won should have been here...
for the presentation.
(Won Dae Hae)
However, I spoke in his place because he had an emergency.
I'm Shim Bo Nui, an employee of Daebak Soft.
- Shim Bo Nui? - What should we do about this?
Shim Bo Nui?
She's my friend.
She wouldn't call me like this if she's one of them.
- Hey, Bo Nui. - I'm Shim Bo Nui.
- Hey, Bo Nui. - I'm Shim Bo Nui of Daebak Soft.
(The cleaning lady, the bunny, the drunk girl...)
(and the presentation raccoon are the same person.)
I know it's against the rules...
to have someone else stand in for the presentation.
However,
I thought it was a waste.
I tried hard to design this game.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
Ms Shim Bo Nui?
You were the bunny at the demonstration, right?
Did you torture Dal Nim to find me?
I'm really not an industrial spy.
Also, I don't have the strength to talk to you right now.
You acted suspicious.
Of course. I'm sorry.
I guess you love animals very much.
Or is it more like an obsession?
- A rabbit. - I said it's not!
Take it off!
A bear.
A raccoon and a tiger.
Were you born in the year of the tiger?
Were any of you born in that year?
How is your bear? How about the tiger?
- Did you find your tiger? - Well...
How did you know?
Do you remember what happened that day?
I'm not asking for you to be grateful.
I'm not asking for an apology, either.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't you remember what you did to me when you were drunk?
No, I don't.
I have plans. I should get going. Bye!
Wait a second!
I think she remembers.
Gosh. Why did I give the presentation?
My life is full of regrets.
- Gosh. - Where were you, Mr Won?
I fell asleep at the sauna.
How did it go? Did you give the presentation?
Yes, I did. I wore this during the presentation.
Did you do a good job? I know you did.
I would've stuttered the whole time.
You did a good job, right?
Like I said, it was impossible to finish in a day.
I thought this would work.
I'm sorry you had to miss your part-time job for this.
It's okay. I'll look for something else.
I have your car registration,
so get it when you have the money.
How much was it?
- I was joking. I know. - I should get going.
Can you take this back to where they have children's plays?
- Thank you. - Got it.
Bo Nui, I have this with me. It's the idea box.
I'll come up with something, so good luck until then!
Good luck.
Let's see.
Excuse me.
- Me? - Yes.
What is it?
Oh, right.
You're moving in. Which apartment are you?
It's 402.
Don't you recognise me?
You might have seen me on the news.
Are you...
a reporter? You don't look like one, though.
I don't watch the news. They talk about too many crimes.
I can't afford to shoulder the suffering of others.
Good luck on your move.
- Wait. - Oh, right.
This is nothing, but it's a welcome gift.
It's nice to have a candle. It's pretty useful.
Gosh.
Mr Je?
Did you want to talk to me?
- About Ms Shim Bo Nui... - She really isn't a spy.
She's not the type to be a good spy.
She hasn't even met Park Ha Sang and Go Su Wan.
She's busy working part-time jobs to pay off her rent and all.
She can't come even if I asked her to.
Does she work at Daebak Soft?
How did you know?
Did you do a background check on her?
No.
I found out by accident.
She doesn't work there since her boss ran away without paying her.
She developed the software, did the sales and did everything.
She looks like she doesn't even know how to turn a computer on.
Do you think I asked anyone to help us?
She wasn't able to graduate, but she majored in computer science.
She was the top of her class and received a four-year scholarship.
Wait. When did you see her face?
She was wearing a bunny costume that day.
It happened by accident...
several times in a row.
I only saw weird sides of her.
- So she isn't computer-illiterate? - What are you talking about?
She almost became one of us at Zeze Family.
What do you mean?
She made it to the final round at the first recruitment.
What?
She was the first one to fix the bug.
(2014 Recruitment Final Interview)
It's been four hours.
How can they even think to apply to Zeze Factory with those skills?
How can anyone catch a bug you created?
Giving up quickly is a wise thing to do. Another one is leaving.
Anyone with an IQ of 100 or higher can solve it.
They can solve it if they take time with it.
They should be diligent if they aren't smart.
Poor kids.
Do they know? The genius, Je Soo Ho, whom they worship...
is actually a total jerk. They probably have no idea.
- Let's give up. - Why?
No one will be hired.
It's our first open recruitment, though.
Let's wait a bit more and see.
Not a single person will be hired.
Come on, Soo Ho.
- An applicant solved it. - Really? Who did it?
Who solved it?
Who is it? Who solved it?
Who did it? Who caught the bug?
No, it's not me.
Whose seat is this?
Did this person leave?
- Yes. - Sorry?
Why would the person leave after solving it?
(Application)
(Applicant Name, Shim Bo Nui)
(Dal Nim)
All the spirits in the sky.
I know that luck doesn't exist in my life.
I know I shouldn't expect to be lucky.
I was foolish to get my hopes up once again.
Please forgive me.
I'll wake up from my foolish dreams...
and do as you say.
Please send me a tiger.
It's okay even if I can't get rid of all the misfortunes in my life.
Please.
Please save Bo Ra's life.
If you can make Bo Ra regain her consciousness,
I'll be okay even without seeing her again.
Is someone knocking my door?
Who are you?
I'm your next-door neighbour.
Do you have a hammer?
She turned out as a nasty tempered girl.
Be careful with it.
Thank you.
I can recognise her face as a kid the more I see her.
By the way,
how can she not recognise me?
I'm the cutie-pie, Geon Uk.
You can just leave it in front of the door.
She won't even open the door for me.
Could I also borrow plasters from you?
Did you get hurt?
Gosh!
I told you to be careful!
Hey.
Give me your hand.
Are you okay now?
You should be careful.
You should be extra careful...
since you live next door.
I'm not supposed talk to or open the door to strangers.
I can't really lend things to strangers, either.
They say neighbours are like your family.
No one thinks like that these days.
Anyway, if you need anything from now on,
ask other neighbours or just buy it.
What is it?
- Let's go out for food. - Pardon me?
You opened the door for me, lent me your hammer and put this on as well.
You said you never do things like that.
I'll treat you to thank you for your special favour.
Thank you for the offer. I'll just accept the gesture.
I'm too busy these days.
Hold on.
No matter how busy you are, you still eat, don't you?
Well...
Please don't mistake my kindness for flirting.
You should respect your neighbours' preferences.
These days, people don't like to become close to their neighbours.
Gosh, what is wrong with me today?
I'm actually quite famous.
You might regret this later.
My life is already full of regrets.
Whether you're famous or not, I'm not interested at all...
unless you were born in the year of the tiger.
What if I was?
Is your Chinese zodiac sign the tiger?
If it is, would you go out for a meal with me?
Of course!
Let's go for food. I think I qualify.
You're serious, right? Your sign is really the tiger?
When shall we go? How about now?
You should repay kindness as soon as possible.
I have to unpack and organise my stuff today.
How about tomorrow? When do you get off work?
Don't worry about that.
I won't go to work at all. I'll stay at home all day long,
so we can go out for dinner or lunch.
Would lunch be weird?
Then let's go for dinner tomorrow.
You'll be surprised.
Okay!
Oh, right.
Bring your identification card.
My goodness!
You sent the tiger to the flat next to mine.
Don't be too surprised and run away!
Okay, that was good.
This time, try moving your right arm all the way.
You saw that, right? When you serve,
you should stretch your left arm from here to all the way up.
Please let me know when the article is ready.
Sure, I will.
Stretch your arm all the way.
Okay. Do that again.
Good.
All right.
- Goodbye, Mr Choi. - Goodbye, Mr Choi.
Bye. See you later.
- Gary Choi, you're the best! - Thanks!
Where are you staying now?
What?
You didn't think I'd find out if you didn't check out from the hotel?
How did you know?
Why are you really being like this?
You dropped the bomb on me and even ran away.
Staying at a hotel is no fun.
I'm back in Korea after living abroad for so long.
Let me have some fun.
You used to hate it whenever I brought up anything about Korea.
I knew it.
I thought it was strange that you accepted the sponsorship.
You saw it the other day.
All those fans were going crazy for me.
Had I known how popular I was in Korea,
I would've visited a long time ago.
Tell me where you're staying now!
You don't even know anyone in Seoul.
By any chance...
I've launched a boat on the ocean.
Is it that place?
That old drawer works better than I expected.
No way.
Hey, you can't live in a place like that. You're Gary Choi.
I've been away for 15 years.
I'm back in Korea after being away for 15 years.
Give me some time. I won't cause trouble.
Just give me two months, okay?
I'll take that as a yes.
Goodness. Is he kidding or serious right now?
Yes, two months.
No, it won't take that long.
He's used to playing tennis weekly.
How could he possibly take a rest...
for such a long period of time? Two months?
I think it's impossible.
Well, no. It wouldn't happen because...
he'd be very nervous.
I'll just wait and see. Yes.
The coach has agreed.
Okay. Bye.
I have no idea.
Well, I've never been on a date with a guy before.
Can't the spirits also tell me what to wear?
Oh, right. My lucky colour.
(Today's Fortune)
Sorry, Dal Nim. I have to take care of something urgent.
I'll call you back later. Sorry!
(Today's Fortune)
Goodness.
I'm not interested.
No, thank you.
I won't change it!
(Today's Fortune)
(Your lucky colour is pink today.)
Pink. Pink.
Do I have pink clothes?
Gosh, who is it?
Is he already here?
- I'm not yet ready. - Gosh.
Why are you here?
I couldn't reach you no matter what I do.
- So you were calling me? - Yes.
- You have my number and address? - Well...
I really am not an industrial spy!
About what happened last time...
Actually, I remember it.
I also know that you're upset because I got you into troubles.
But isn't it too much to come to my place?
First, I got your number and address from your application form.
Second, it is true that you've caused me troubles.
But I am not here for your apology.
How far have you gotten with IF?
IF? What?
Welcome.
- Do you have an investor? - No.
- Did you decide on the platform? - No.
I'll offer 300,000 dollars and 1 percent incentive. What do you say?
Why? Do you want more incentives?
Are you telling me you want to buy IF?
- Yes. - Why?
We can't make a business deal here.
- Let's talk somewhere else. - No!
I am just an employee. You should talk to my boss about it.
I have a very important meeting right now.
I am sorry.
I can't reach your boss no matter what I do.
I tried his mobile phone, house phone and email but no answers.
He's hounded by creditors, so he doesn't answer strange numbers.
Then you could call him.
He doesn't answer my calls, either. He owes me a lot of money, too.
Gosh, it's so messed up.
Yes, it is. Anyway, I have a very important appointment.
I will call him up later. Okay? I am sorry.
Decide it right here. Is it yes or no?
I will tell you honestly. I cannot trust either of you.
Think about it. If you were not going to join Zeze,
why did you spend time to crack the bug?
If you're not going to sell it, why did you give the presentation?
It's beyond my understanding. So how can I trust you?
I guess you're the boss, so you don't know how it goes.
Even the applicants evaluate companies.
Whether I join the company or not is up to me.
I just chose not to join Zeze. That's all.
Zeze...
You chose not to join Zeze,
and you chose to join...
Daebak Soft.
That can happen.
Isn't it the same even now?
Whether you pay 100,000 dollars or a million dollars,
Daebak Soft determines to sell IF or not.
So call that boss of yours,
and ask him to decide whether he will sell IF or not.
- What are you doing? - Quiet.
Unit 401. I'm here.
(That night)
I need to go home.
Why is it so heavy?
It's too heavy.
Gosh...
I'm too tired.
Sit here.
Why is this doll so heavy?
I can't do it any more.
I am done fulfilling the duty...
as a member of the society.
Oh, no.
It hurts!
What is this girl?
- What? - What?
Pretty tiger...
- Why would you... - Where are you?
- look for a tiger at this hour? - A tiger...
I have to find a tiger.
Tiger!
Where are you going?
I won't let you go.
(Lucky Romance)
My rationality is paralysed. Totally paralysed.
- There isn't anyone. - There is someone.
- I said there is no one. - How dare you talk back?
There is one for certain. And he's very near you.
Why can a bug cause a malfunction in my sympathetic nerves?
The boat you launched after 15 years is the girl next door?
Mum, did you know that Dad struggled after quitting his job?
Do only one thing. If you'll insist that I'm your son, take money.
If you will insist I'm not your son, remove me from the register.
You ride a bike well now.
- Who are you? - I am Seol Hui. Amy.
Did something significant happen between us?
Or maybe something really bad happened.
I forget bad memory quickly. I am efficient.
I was surprised, too. I couldn't believe Je Soo Ho called me.
Please wear off all the evil from me.
Put everything back to normal.
Please make me lucky.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
Wait for the full moon. Don't go past that month.
I have three weeks. I have to succeed no matter what.