Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
CEO... you're a kinder person than I thought you would be.
W-What kind of crap is that?
It's true!
You thought I was terminal, so you even decided to let me put a ridiculous clause in the contract.
So you knew it was ridiculous?!
You were worried so you even bought me medicine.
And in the off-chance that it might've been a pervert, you got involved even though you don't know how to fight.
Looking back on it, you're really cool.
If CEO said things a little nicer, I think you'd be a 100 points.
Ah... we went over 1 hour and 20 minutes.
We'll cancel tomorrow and add an hour and a half to our meeting next week Saturday.
See you next week.
About that.
Can't we spend it now?
- Pardon?  -The hour and thirty minutes.
Let's spend it now.
Today...sleep with me, Mr. Je Soo Ho.
What did you say?
What did you...say just now?
You said... that you didn't have any time.
If you stay the night with me, let's have the contract dating called off.
There's no need to forcibly meet anymore. So-
Wait. Hold Up. One Moment.
So you're saying, not "sleeping" but as a man and woman...
Hotel accommodations cost, nightview, was it all excuses for this?
Was that your objective from the beginning?
That's right.
From the beginning when I asked to date, I thought this... was included.
Then making a fuss about going on dates or not, forcing yourself on me after drinking, was all because of this I see.
Are you crazy for men?
You said you didn't like me. That it was a fake relationship.
But you're saying you want to sleep with me? From the first day? Out of the blue?
Yes.
Then why didn't you say so from the start?
Then I wouldn't have engaged in a labor contract like this with you.
Can't you... think of me as someone you don't know?
Just...as someone you met at a bar or at a club.
Men think of that kind of stuff as a sporting event so...
Look here, Sim Bo Nui!
I am not joking nor playing around right now.
I'm being sincere.
It's possible whether you like someone or love them,
and to simply satisfy a carnal desire, without those feelings is not even the least bit shameful in today's society.
Whether you're crazy or addicted to men. I know full well I'm not in the position to criticize you.
But, leave me out; however you decide to live your life doesn't matter, but that's not who I am.
I'm begging you.
Is it still a no if I ask you like this?
I'll do anything, I'll do everything you tell me to do!
I mean...why are you being like this?
You're not terminal and you said it wasn't your dying wish either.
If it's really because of your sexual frustration, then look into someone else.
The world's filled with men willing to sleep with women they've met for the first time!
It has to be you.
It must. Be you.
♬ Tell me. Tell me with your lips clamped shut ♬
♬ Tell me with those fond eyes ♬
♬ When did it start? ♬
♬Because I myself can't know my own heart.♬
♬ Did you perhaps know? ♬
♬ That we're looking at the same place. ♬
♬ Tell me. (Tell me). ♬
♬ Tell me with your lips clamped shut. (Tell me). ♬
♬ Tell me with loving eyes ♬
♬ Say you also feel the same as I do ♬
It has to be you.
♬ I love you ♬
It must. Be You.
♬ The words I utter for the first time: I love you (I love you). ♬
♬ There are no better words than these. ♬
♬ Hurry and tell me those words. ♬
Are you crazy for men?
however you decide to live your life doesn't matter but that's not me.
I want to date normally with a person I like, and live like that too.
It's true!
I saw it! I really saw it!
Oh man! You really came!?
He's my friend. He's uglier than me, right?
Hey, it's loud and it stinks in here, isn't there some place quiet?
There isn't.
Later, we can go to a place and-
no, no wait, wait there!
I'll be right back!
-What is it?-What, it's not like we only meet because something happens.
Hey, go fool God.
You suddenly call asking where I am, then come to a club, which you hate so much,
and a guy who only sips on soda is-look at you! You're drinking alcohol! This is a signal saying something happened!
What signal, what's a signal!
-Is it because of Seol Hee?-No!
For a girl from your past to suddenly appear-of course it's nerve-wracking!
I said that's not it!
-Never mind.-You're so damn hesitant-fine! I won't say anything either!
Why do you think a woman would ask to sleep with you?
How could she do that? I can't understand!
Y-You...
You slept with a woman?!
-You slept with a woman-!-You're crazy!
-This Soo Ho-!-I said you're crazy!
You had your first night-!
S-So, you're saying, a woman offered a hot night...
and you refused, you idiot, what do I do with you!
W-Why's that being an idiot! Doing something like that with someone you don't like is just being an animal...
Wow, coming onto the almighty Je Soo Ho,
this is fun!
-But was that girl really drunk?-No.-Then was she high?
-No.-Or, is she pretty?
Yeah-ugh!
You've hurt a pretty lady.
-Me?-Yeah.
Look,
look at all those beautiful women-no matter how drunk they are, no one will take the initiative.
It doesn't matter if they say the world is more open now,
it isn't easy for women to go into a full-body attack first, sober at that!
Sleep with me tonight, Je Soo Ho.
She was sober...and she said it easily too.
Really? Wait, but is it really not Seol Hee?
It's not? If it's not then who...
Don't tell me, it's Bo Nui?
We said she was terminal! That was her dying wish?
She's not a terminal, you stupid fly!
She's not? Then that's a relief!
Wait but why'd Bo Nui do that?
I said it's not Sim Bo Nui!
You can be scared.
I was scared in the beginning, I got scared too! Seeing like-wow, like I was scared!
The first is always like that, what's wrong with you?
This hyung is always praying for your beautiful first night.
Stop-it's hot, let go.
What, should I give you some tips?
Stop! Stop! Stop!
What are you doing here?
Just to get some air.
-Did that person leave?-Yeah.
Why? Did he yell at you? Did he pick on you?!
-He said something worse after I left, huh!-No!
What do you mean "no", it's written all over your face.
I said it's not.
I must've been to hasty, only thinking about myself.
That person, does he have the sign of a tiger?
-How did you know?-What is it?
What are you supposed to do with a tiger that you're clinging on like this?
-I have to sleep with him.-Stop making jokes.
I have to sleep with that person, that's how my Bo Ra will wake up.
What are you saying?
What's this about Bo Ra waking up and what's you having to sleep with a tiger?
Did the shaman say that?! That doesn't make sense-
You think...I'm delusional too, right?
I know, no matter who looks at it, this is crazy.
But I can stay still because of that?
How can I ignore that when Bo Ra's life is on the line?
I ruined everything again.
My head's going to explode,
thinking about where to find a tiger and how to start this again.
Let's go.
-Where?-A good place.
It has to be you.
I said...it has to be you.
She made it clear from the beginning, she doesn't like you.
Where are we going!?
Hurry up! Come on!
You hold a racket,
from here and straight...
Hey! I've never played this before.
I'm going! Focus!
What are you doing-hey!
When your thoughts are cluttered, there's nothing better than moving around.
Seriously, trust me!
Nice!
You're good!
♬ Will you smile for me whenever you see me ♬
♬ The one full of sunshine, ♬
Like you did just now!♬ full of hope ♬
♬ the person who found their way to me ♬
It's good, good!♬ That's you ♬
Okay.
♬ Casting a spell onto you ♬
-Hey!-Sim Bo Nui, you run great!
You're making fun of me, aren't you.
You're dead-c'mere.
No, you said you've got a lot on your mind,
-so when you move around and sweat, people--Come here!
You're dead!
♬ I want to fall ♬
♬ into the eyes that stare at me ♬
♬ Hey, you, my only love ♬
Noona! Are you okay!?
Yeah, I'm fine.
-Let me see...-No, I'm fine.
-Still, come on--No...no.
What's wrong?
Noona.
That's right, cry it all out.
You're angry, agitated, and frustrated too.
Cry all you want until that frustration is gone!
Yeah, scream it out,
Sim Bo Nui! You frustrating thing!
Choi Geon Wook! You ninny!
Mr. Choi Ho! Where are you!?
Bo Ra!
Wake up...
Wake up!
You're coming back now? You've got a package from Jemulpo!
From Jemulpo, carp juice, fragile!
You can have it.
Again? Thank you, rest up!
It has to be you.
That scared me!
Hurry up and go! Okay!?
-Do you feel better?-Yeah.
Don't you have those times? When you want to go back to the past.
The night before I went to Canada.
Dad said we should sleep together one last time, but I said no.
Noona, what time do you want to go back to?
That day 2 years ago, the day Bo Ra got into that accident,
if I could go back to that morning,
I would do anything.
Oppa!
You rascals!
-Oppa! Oh my gosh-please sign this!-I said get away!
I'm sorry!
This is my youngest daughter and she plays tennis!
She said she'll look just once from far away!
It's okay.
Oppa you're so handsome!
Thank you!
We love you Gary Choi!
Study hard!
Gary Choi?
Gary Choi?!
You...
you're Gary Choi?!
Excuse me! Room 402!
With that man, I have to...safely sleep...
He's like a younger brother, just overreacting because we grew up together!
I'm not overreactive, get out of the way!
I mean, how could to fool me so perfectly?
I told you, I'm famous.
How am I supposed to know when you say it like that?
You just don't know because you have no interest.
Noona, you haven't asked once about what I've been doing with my life. I don't know who's sad about who.
Of course I thought you were unemployed! Always wearing a hat and dragging around slippers.
I did that on purpose because if word got out about me, the neighborhood would get crazy.
You saw that today right? You don't know how hard it was for me to hide this.
Hey!
But how can our Puccu be Gary Choi?
If I gave you an honest serve, you would've been taken to the hospital.
-Just keep that in mind.-Thanks!
It's not that big of a deal...
For growing up so well.
Why am I so proud? Our Geon Wook, you've grown up so well!
I made a buttload of money too,
so don't worry! From now on, I'll be your support system!
If you have anything you need, tell me all of them!
It's fine!
What? What should I do for you?
The Canadian tiger you talked about last time...
Never mind.
Let's go inside!
Je Soo Ho, 86, tiger Xno tiger! fail
Resignation Letter
-Hello-Good morning!
Miss Bo Nui! Look over my graphics, please?
Of course.
How is it?
Miss Seung Yeon, have we seen Gary Choi's face before?
What are you talking about? We've seen so much of him!
This, this, and this too!
Why? Is the synchronization off? It's weird?
No! Not that,
-but Gary Choi--CEO!
-O-Oh, CEO, you're here!-We'll pass on the greetings!
Keep working!
Okay. That was smooth.
Why're you coming!?
Does that make sense!?
No-I mean, why's the service so faulty?!
Who made the damn thing, huh!?
That was smooth.
Mother
CEO!
Yes?
I have something to tell you.
I have a meeting I need to get to so...
-CEO!-Yes?
But the meeting room's this way.
Yes.
Name tag...
I'll look at the e-mail.
-Are you looking for someone?-Sim Bo-
Are you...avoiding me?
No. Why would I?
This whole day...
It felt like we kept missing each other.
I don't understand at all.
You said you have something to tell me right? I have something to tell you too. Come in.
About yesterday...
I'm sorry.
-Are you saying you have nothing to do with this place anymore?-No.
After yesterday, how could I possible see your face.
Why can't you? Nothing happened.
Do you...have lingering feelings? Or a different plan?
No! It's definitely not that!
I...It's because I was so desperate,
I made a mistake.
So you're running away?
I'm saying I'll take responsibility.
Why didn't you tell me?
Gary Choi. He's the little brother living next door to you, right?
-How did you know--Would you look at that? You knew all along.
-No!-For someone with such a strong conviction for accountability,
how could keep crucial information a secret?!
Yes, well, I know you have no affections towards IF,
but still, IF was a game that started from you.
You know how important Gary Choi is to our development and you-
No! I found out yesterday night too!
Whatever! When you found out, whether he's your little brother or your dating partner, it doesn't matter!
Get Gary Choi.
-Excuse me?-Get him to agree to be our model.
That's how you take responsibility, got it?
-Are you okay, CEO?-What.
Seeing me.
Isn't it...uncomfortable?
I said yesterday that I respect your private life.
It's something that has nothing to do with me anymore anyways.
Yes.
I understand.
About Gary Choi, you can go through the process on your own.
The company will be going through the formal process on our own.
Yes.
CEO,
I like IF.
I made it, how could I not care for it.
But, this is Zeze.
Everyone is so great and skilled,
I thought it was beyond my place to tell them to do this and that.
But, more than anyone, I want IF to succeed.
I want someone to be able to experience a life they've only ever dreamed of.
And that's the heart,
I started with.
I'm glad there's a place for me here.
I'll...try my best to persuade him.
Be careful of the edges!
This is the last of the luggage, right?
You can move all of this to the 4th floor!
Got it.
Oh, I'm in the lobby right now!
Where are you? I'm...right in front of the screen door.
Which floor are you going into? The 1st or the 7th?
Here!
Here he comes.
You can come this way.
Why are you putting these here? You have to take them all up.
-I can only bring it here-You can't enter without an entrance pass!
-Please work hard.-Please get in safe.
No, what am I supposed to do with all this-hey, ahjusshi!
Wow, this isn't going to be easy. You're going to have to tell your employees to get down here.
We...don't have employees yet...
What should I do?
What's this? You're calling me?
Geon Wook, are you busy right now?
-Yeah, seriously busy.-Oh, should I call you later?
I'm ironing my super important red underwear.
The winning charm. Symbol of good luck, you know?
Of course, you're doing something very important.
But why?
Did you get fired?!
No...I was just wondering if I could see you when I get off work.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
How can I get in here?
No...you said...you were here for the 4th floor...this is the 8th...
I have to give out rice cakes!
Move, it's iris identification.
Wow, you have full clearance here!?
That's so cool!
I'm a major shareholder...damn...
-Hello!-What-how did she?!
Did you let her in!?
-She's new to the 4th floor...-IM Sports?
I'm the director of IM Sports's Korea branch, and also the one that just moved into the 4th floor, Han Seol Hee.
-How did she get in here?-That's what I'm wondering.
But why did the head of coffee carry that?
O-Oh...exactly...why-why did I bring this?
They said you're supposed to pass out rice cakes when you move in in Korea.
I was curious about the people who worked with CEO Je Soo Ho,
I'll be seeing all of you often, I'm in your care.
Oh y-yes...
Come in.
O-Oh...S-Soo Ho! The thing is...
See me!
Ow! Ow, why are you pushing so much!
Ow!
You're a liar!
W-What? Liar? Why am I a liar?
You said you knew everything! That you were his guardian angel!
Saying femme fatale and acting like you knew her face and everything!
I just pretended not to know! I'm his friend,
you think it'd be okay for me to go around talking about the CEO's private life!?
Liar! I saw your face and everything!
You did that!
When did I do this!
That...was because she was so much prettier than her old pictures-
but Dal Nim...why are you arguing about that to me?
Looking at it again, back then you ran till you ran out of breath too!
That...was me, as his willing assistant,
trying to check every little change during a crucial time like this!
Me, I'm a person that adores every kind of love out there,
but there are just two that you have to be careful with.
Affairs and loyalty.
Don't be so loyal! Work as much as you receive!
Like...get a hobby and date around!
And, and when do you get rid of this, the wire bunch.
I'm not taking it off until I die!
Oh! It's horrifying! Ugh! It's going to come out in my dreams!
Wow, this is some top of the line, trendy designing, from a baby who only knew books.
-What in the world are you doing?-Oh!
Do that for me too, the thing where the door opens when I show my eyes.
Have you received Gary Choi's agreement?
Mmm, I will soon. You know a lot of people want Gary, right?
I'll make sure you get a lot from me.
Why did you move into the 4th floor?
For business, I need an office,
and with my timing, the monthly rent was in range. It's also close to the sub-contractor, isn't it perfect?
Why? Did you think...that I moved here because of you?
As Zeze, I'll interpret it as determination from IM Sports.
Since the feedback was taking so long, we've taken a different route in contacting Gary Choi.
What is that supposed to mean?
No, how can you contact him when I'm the management?
You said the athlete's agreement was of utmost importance.
I handle Gary's contract, from a business to a business, this is rude.
Then what are we supposed to do? We're desperate and his management is taking their time.
We can only take the direct route.
Soo Ho, trust me.
You and me meeting again, being connected through Gary,
I don't think it's a coincidence.
Soo Ho!
We have something to talk about, hmm?
You're probably busy, you should head down.
Promise me, if I give you Gary Choi then you give me a pass to here.
Gary first.
Okay! Then, let's meet again soon, CEO Je.
She really does whatever she wants...
Mother...
Yes Seung Yeon?
Come down for lunch, we're on the 1st floor right now.
Oh! Okay, I'll go right now!
Je So Hoo, now I'm under you.
Amy
Please check it.
We've made the name and number of the finder private,
we also put in the picture of the owl you told us about.
Yes, it's good. I'll leave things in your care.
Work hard.
Searching for a person.But since it's a recent picture, there's probably going to be a lot of people who recognize him, right?
Yeah. They said it was way better. It's all thanks to you.
-Here.-I'll eat it on my own.
Hurry up!
This!
To be honest, I was in such a hurry because I had no time.
But, this time, I think I might be able to find him for real this time.
I just have a feeling.
When you're done with your break, are you going to Canada?
Why? Are you sad already?
Geon Wook, you got a proposal to be a model for a game, right?
How'd you know? This noona is suddenly so interested in me!
I got one but I said no. I'm a little too expensive.
But can't you do it?
The company I'm at is Zeze Factory.
Then...that tiger CEO guy is trying to get me as the model?
-What's "guy"!-Well between two people who've used their fists!
...call each other "this guy" and "that guy"...
That game is my project.
The CEO picked up what almost got thrown away.
It's a really good game. You're giving other people the chance to live a great life as you!
Sorry, I can't do it.
Look for other people, not me.
There are so many great people in the world, what can you get from living as a person like me.
What's wrong with you?
I'm...
a son that's finding his dad after 10 years.
It's not great at all, it's not good.
Hey! You can find him now! You can meet him.
Yeah. I'm going to.
So I don't have time. Sorry Noona.
Oh you're at it again! The smell will get onto me again!
Be quiet.
You...tell the truth. Are you supporting two families?
What are you saying?
You make that carp juice with all the care in the world,
you don't think I'd notice you take out a box every single time?
They say carp is great for getting rid of bloating for pregnant women.
You're really spewing nonsense!
You need to be on the same wavelength for jokes, ugh!
Where are you going?
Where would I go! I'm going to give my son-
I said don't go!
What do you expect from a kid who can't even treat his parents right!?
Maybe for you because you make a mess after you're drunk!
But I'm treated like an elegant madam!
As if!
You're smart, graceful,
as expected from Je Soo Ho's mother!
I can't even go into my son's company when I want to!
Miss! The wall talisman miss, from last time?
Yes! Hello.
Are you really sure? You put it in well?
Yes, I hid it well in the book furthest in the corner.
But why's he like this?
Mother.
That one,
it's a talisman that wards off raccoons and let's him get closer to women.
He said that Soo Ho would be good to me too because I'm a woman.
A raccoon?
They said a wicked raccoon's attached to Soo Ho!
My goodness-he said it constantly makes my child miserable!
How much do you understand raccoons?
Because of that raccoon, my child,
Bunny stop right there!
gets hurt, collapses,
I said it has to be you.
and is mentally worn out by it.
Isn't there anyone that's been making CEO Je miserable, or anyone that's been clinging to him these days?
That raccoon...it must be me.
Huh?
Oh, I wonder.
I'm on contract so I don't really with the CEO.
A really persistent one must be on him.
Mother, I have something I need to do quickly, so I'll be leaving first!
Miss, give me your number.
I-I'm only on contract,
I won't be here after 3 months!
That's then!
I don't want to wait around every single time I come here.
A kid who knows stuff
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
♬ Yesterday, yes a day like any day ♬
♬ Alone again for every day ♬
♬ Without making love in the shadows ♬
♬ Today, I know ♬
Young Il...
Op...pa?
I just need one person.
Just one right tiger.
What is this?
Your post has been deemed inappropriate and following the online cafe's rules...
immediate deletion?
What did I do?!
All I did was ask for tigers to confirm with their I.D. cards and meet them offline!
I don't even have time, it's not like I can go through people one by one.
Have you eaten?
I have something to ask.
When you asked me to sleep with you, was there really no emotion behind that whatsoever?
I'm working so hard with a tiger right in front of me.
Ask away.
That...is it tuna?
No! It's ham and cheese! Eat-no, would you like to eat this one?
I'm fine.
After we've gone through the Q&A session, we'll proceed with cleanup.
But if there's anything we're lacking in, you can say so and we'll compensate.
Dal Nim...
Yes CEO.
Why's Sim Bo Nui acting like that?
Did she do something weird to you again?!
What.
No, it's nice!
Why won't you hurry up and send me the copy file?
I...think I told you multiple times to send it to me.
I told you...that we already sent it.
Ham and Cheese Sandwich! It's because you skip meals that you feel collapsing. Please eat it no matter what!
Why is that woman doing this?
2 servings of spicy rice cakes, blood sausages, and kimbap please!
Okay.
Oh! The fried ones too!
♬ Homage to the Perfection of Wisdom ♬
Yeah Dal Nim?
Oh, Bo Nui! Did you do something to the CEO?
Why? Did he say something?
What is that, what is it this time!? Did you throw salt?
Did you throw scallions? Or,
did you spray chicken blood!?
Geon Wook!
Noona! Noona, is Chun Nam far from Seoul?
-Chun Nam?-Yeah, I got a call and they said they found where my dad is!
Oh!
Cheo Nam! It's not far, Geon Wook, this is good news!
Th...How do I get there?
The plane...Noona, should I go to the airport?
It's not that long by train, it's close.
Should I go with you?
No ghost, no ghost, no ghost,
Miss Sim Bo Nui!? What are you doing here?!
It's my first day!
With a heart that's clean and tidy...the corners here and there...
Oh! This was your room!
What are you doing?
Here!
Go safely.
Thank you!
Why? Are you nervous?
What do I say first?
Would he even recognize me?
Of course! He's your dad.
Let's go, okay?
Is anyone home?
Is no one home?
Who is it?
Hello!
We heard someone by the name Choi Ho lived here?
Who?
Mr. Choi Ho. This...he looks like this.
Hold on.
Oh! It's Choi!
Where is he right now? Is he inside?
He's not here anymore. He doesn't live here.
When did he leave?
Wait a minute...
I think it was around mid-January.
He's always been so diligent and quiet, I didn't even know he'd been coming and going.
But he just cleaned everything up,
and left without a word, leaving all his stuff too!
Geon Wook, we'll be outside.
Boss, it's not a good time for me right now.
Oh, Bo Nui, do you have some money?
What is that supposed to mean?
No no, it's because I'm short on cash right now,
I'm about to lose a really good item!
What's this about an item all of a sudden, what are you doing?
Is it stolen goods this time?
No no! It's not like that.
Bo Nui, you got your salary from Zeze right? Just send me $1000 right now,
as soon as I buy the item,
I'll get money-I'll give you the money back by tonight!
It's night right now. And I don't have money, I also can't pick up calls from now on.
B-Bo Nui! Don't hang up and just listen!
The people of our country these days have deteriorating health!
Stay healthy boss.
Man! If you're worrying about my health you should lend me some money...
What should I do. Should I use my organs?
2002, May 11th. I talked with Geon Wook over the phone,
he said he skipped his tennis lesson lying that his stomach was hurting.
As two men, I promised him to keep it a secret from his mother.
He knows how to get out of doing work. He's grown so much.
Geon Wook won at the North America Open Jr.!
Yeah! That's right!
Because Park sent me the footage, I watched it in good quality.
Despite that it was a match from 5 months ago.
I've started to write down the world rankings that come out every week.
Until the day that the three words "Choi Geon Wook" are written,
I must live with the heart of rooting for him.
Yes, yes! It's the substitute driver! Yes!
I sold the last room and bought a plane ticket.
No...he's never come to Canada...
The 15th North America Open Jr. Champion, Gary Choi!
My son!
He looked happy.
That's enough.
You should've told me if you came!
You should've seen me!
Don't cry.
He's probably fine, safe and fine somewhere.
Get some sleep, I'll wake you up when we get there.
Here!
Resignation Letter
Zeze Tiger
Development Impact Team
Je Soo Ho, 86, tiger Xno tiger, fail!
Oh! Then, at least take this! It's a talisman that welcomes gold!
She uses talismans on a daily basis.
Folk belief,
in other words, she's an ardent believer of superstitions.
I'll never let you go.
She's...looking for a tiger.
Sleep with me tonight.
She doesn't like me but has to spend a night...
Talisman -> Superstition -> Tiger -> One night
It has to be you!
It has to be you.
Sacrifice
You went through a lot today because of me.
Go on inside.
Thanks Noona.
Hurry inside and get a lot of rest!
CEO
CEO!
-From now on, answer honestly to everything I ask.-What?
Promise me!
That you'll tell the truth about everything.
-Yes.-That day,
you told me it had to be me, that it could only be me.
-Yes.-Because I have the sign of a tiger?
So...during those barbaric times,
how a paying guest would offer a woman,
the way you offer up an animal,
did you use me as an offering because I had the sign of a tiger?
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry-I should've told you beforehand,
but if I said that, I thought you would treat like a delusional person-
You're more scary than I thought.
Is it fun using people?
When did it start? The casino? The demonstration? The recruitment!
It's not a game and it's not a joke? I'm a nice person?
What's the reason you're like this, why are you doing something as crazy as this, why!?
I was listening and figured you were crossing the line.
Geon Wook.
Leave. This is between us.
So what. It's not like the two of you had a one-night stand and it's not like the two of you were dating,
why are you so mad?
Don't tell me...did you think she loved you?
Let's go Noona.
Wait, wait!
You go ahead.
-Noona!-That person,
I can't send him back like this.
I want to go back and explain to him. That it was to safe Bo Ra, that I'm sorry.
And if you do? Did that person say he'd do what you wanted?
You saw how he cornered you! No matter what you tell him, he won't understand.
If you go back, you'll just hear worse things, don't go.
I'm going back to hear those things.
How surprised do you think he was? How angry?
If he can forgive me just a little bit by screaming at me and pouring it on me,
that's fine. "Crazy bitch", "Delusional", "Screw loose", I've heard those things countless times,
so go inside, you must be tired. Don't think about anything today and get a lot of rest!
It's not like the two of you had a one-night stand and it's not like the two of you were dating,
why are you so mad?
Don't tell me...did you think she loved you?
Meaning of the Talisman
Secluded Evil
Butterfly Talisman
Meaning of the Talisman: Secluded EvilWarding off evil spirits from interfering with what you desperately wish for Desperately wishing...
Meaning of the Talisman: ButterflyReferring to flowers seducing male butterflies with their sweet honey, a talisman that seduces men.
A talisman...that seduces men?
♬  Tell me ♬
♬ Tell me through those pursed lips ♬
♬ With those fond eyes, tell me ♬
♬ That you feel the same way ♬
Let's be honest, even if he can't understand, he'll listen♬ I love you ♬
Let's talk. I have something I want to ask.♬ I love you ♬
-Have you seen it?/-What.
-Have you heard?/-And if I have?♬ These words I'm saying for the first time, ♬
What is that woman trying to do?♬ I love you ♬
You have something...with Sim Bo Nui, right?♬ I love you ♬
-Of course I do./-Do it the way I want,♬ There are no words better than these ♬
and instead, I get to choose.♬ There are no words better than these ♬
I have no time, it's the end on the day of the full moon!♬ Hurry ♬
I was misunderstood. I still thought you were a good person.♬ Tell me ♬
I don't know what she'll do if I leave her alone.
Hey-are you...worrying about Miss Bo Nui?
This is the first time I've seen you worry about someone.
What, you think this doesn't affect me?! I'm afraid, I'm nervous and I want to run away,♬ Should we start from now ♬
but I won't.♬ I don't care who's first ♬