Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Oh my, Miss Bo Nui? What brings you here at this time?
- Bo Ra...- She's stable.
She was fine today, why?
Today and tomorrow, please take good care of her.
And if anything happens, then give me a call right away.
That's what I always do. Did you come because you were worried?
I'll leave everything in your care.
Even for the smallest changes, please. Please let me know.
I got it. Don't worry.
Miss Sim Bo Nui!
Hanguk University Hospital
I'd rather this all be a dream. I wish all of this was just a scary dream.
♬ Tell me (Tell me) ♬
♬ Tell me with your lips clamped shut. (Tell me). With your loving  ♬
Just think of me as an utility pole.
♬ two eyes, tell me. That you feel the same way ♬
♬  I love you ♬
♬ These words I'm saying for the first time, I love you ♬
You told me I was a talking utility pole,
I talk, ♬ There are no better words than this ♬
I walk,
I put an umbrella over you.
You know I'm a genius right? I have a lot of functions.
♬ Should we start now? ♬
♬ I don't care who's first ♬
♬ I like it even if you say it until you’re sick of doing it ♬
♬ Love is something which is always expressed ♬
♬ Tell me  ♬
What's the problem? ♬  (Tell me) ♬
♬ Tell me with those lips clamped shut. (Tell me) ♬
♬ Tell me with your two loving eyes ♬
The customer is not answering at this time...
What is it? What is it that you have to do with a sign of tiger that you're groveling like this.
I have to sleep with him.
You're crazy, Choi Geon Wook.
It's not it. It won't be.
Let's have another shot, fighting! fighting! fighting!
Let's have another shot!
- Bar maid give me some more chairs. - Fighting!
How much is all this?
- We'll have to go a second round! - You don't even let me have a word...
Pardon? You don't want a second round?
Get back safe!
Miss, are you here alone?
Do you want to come with us?
Do you think you'll be able to handle me?
I...This Sim Bo Nui is...
The world's most unlucky person.
If you stay by my side,
you might die.
What?
Mister, do you have the sign of a tiger? If you do, then yes to a one-night stand.
You're forward. Do you want to move to a different place?
Let's go, come on, get your stuff.
- Just a moment.- Who are you? - Just
What are you?! What! What is this, let go! Let go!
What are you!? Who are you!
Je Soo Ho. Don't you know? Genius. But forget that,
if you want to mess around you should at least put in the effort.
Your company id, your ring, you're real lazy there Mr. Married Man.
What...was the managing director's number again?
- Why can't I remember?- No! No! I'll go! I was just about to go!
- That's right? Go.- Sorry!
- Run.- Yes sir!
Why isn't he coming?!
You're scared aren't you. A cowardly tiger that can't even match up to a kitty.
Meow! Meow! Where's that damn tiger?
Stop this.
It's not your business.
- I said stop this!- Who are you to do this. Give me that!
She's not dead! I checked her myself.
Your little sister, she's fine.
So what? Should I dance in joy?
Because she hasn't woken up.
That's not what I'm saying!
- What are you doing?- I told you to stay out of it.
If you're going to help, then you should've helped when I needed you. What's the point of you doing this now?
I begged you,
I begged you to help me just once, if you just did that, if you did!—
If I did then what do you think would've changed!?
Do you still not understand?
This ridiculous superstitious act is over, it's past 12 and there's no full moon,
-so please, just logically!—- Stop. I said stop!
What were you going to do, if you got caught by those crazy bastards, and they recorded you?
How did you know that?
- The emergency call...was that you, CEO?- It was good that I did this, at least—
Why are you doing this to me?! CEO, what are you that you can do this to me!?
What about that!? What about a hidden camera, who cares!
There was a person's life on the line, our Bo Ra! I could've saved her.
Let go!
Let's go. The sun's not up yet, I'll fulfill that wish for you.
I'm a tiger.
Morning Star Villa
Gary!
Oh my god...
Gary?
Yeah, Noona?
Amy...
What are you doing not changing your clothes?
How long were you like this?
Thirty minutes? One hour?
We can't do this, you should go to the sauna.
Calm down. This much is nothing.
I came because your voice over the phone was weird and you're out there looking so sad in front of someone else's house.
Do you want a can of beer?
Do you like Ms. Bo Nui?
Me?! Like Noona Bo Nui!?
You've been with me for so many years and you still don't know my type?
It's late and it was raining.
-And she wouldn't even pick up?-Mhm.
She didn't go to the company dinner and didn't even come home?
Gary, this...
-She's with a boyfriend.-Huh?
I'm sure!
I said let go. That none of this matters anymore, I said let go!
Listen well. One,
if you don't grab a tiger then your sister will die,
two, you didn't do that crazy act,
three, your sister is fine and alive,
what these results show is that superstitions are wrong.
Sim Bo Nui, please come out of that fantasy and see...reality.
Reality?
Do you want me to tell you what reality is?
If I love them, they all leave. I gave my parents a funeral when I was 16.
There were only me and Bo Ra left in the world, but-
But now I have to let go of the one little sister I've got left.
That...
What do I do with that?
I'm so scared, it's all horrible,
that I'd rather die off first.
Every day is like stepping on thin ice and because I don't know when disaster might happen, every minute, every second is Hell!
This is my reality, got it?
She's alive today? If it's not today then it'll be tomorrow.
If it's not tomorrow, it'll be the day after!
Why in the world do you think of it like that?!
I'll cancel it.
When I said it was because of you, CEO, back then...I lied.
At least with that,
I wanted to run away from the guilt, it was all my fault.
Why is that your fault?!
It doesn't make any logical sense!
CEO, even if you die and come back to life, you won't understand.
So instead of following me, just go.
Again! Look at you! Walking off again!
Yeah I'm done with this! If I had any more patience to explain this to you, I'd be Buddha!
I've wasted my time well! I'm going too! I'm going!
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Sim Bo Nui.
Let's go home.
I don't like home. I can't go.
I can't bear to see it.
Bo Ra's bed, Bo Ra's desk.
Bo Ra's things...how could I look at all of that?
What right do I have to see those things?
You're disqualified.
If you can't find Dad or Noona, what's the point of you!
Still, I'll leave them in your care, Owl.
Here!
Covers.
Towel! Towel!
Oh why's the towel here!
Pillow! Pillow!
Pillow...is it weird to give my pillow?
Oh, a blanket!
What is it?
Oh Soo Ho! Where are you? You're home, right?
Hey, your team members,
are rioting about barging into your house!
No! They definitely can't!
I know! I know! I know no one can go in except me!
-You know where it is!-Be quiet-bang!
Oh! But on a day like this,
they're upset you're not here!
If by any chance, they're in my sight,
whether it's overtime, penalties, or pay cuts, tell them they'll have to pay the price.
Hey! Hey! If I gave you a joke, then take it as a joke!
If you take it as education what am I supposed to do!
I'll leave everything in your care, Hyung.
Did you...just call me hyung?
I trust you, I'm hanging up.
♬ Why didn't I know you? ♬
♬ I trusted that you would stay ♬
♬ Time is thoughtlessly flowing by ♬
♬ All that's left is late regret ♬
Exactly what kind of life did she live? This girl...
Where is this?
My house.
Why am I here?
You should get checked up for alcohol-induced dementia.
You seem to comfortably forget everything when you drink.
Oh, I slept well.
I'll make your wish come true.
Sim Bo Nui, let's go home.
How did you know about the hospital?
How should I say I knew about it for you to stop thinking stupid things?
I told you yesterday. Today if not tomorrow. If not tomorrow, then the day after.
Do you really think it's a matter of time?
I seemed to have bothered you again. I don't know why I keep doing this to you.
No, no, I'm okay.
No. There's no reason for you to be okay.
Because of me, you were bothered, frustrated and bewildered.
While you are irrational, at least you're aware of your actions.
Yes, you're right. Because of you, I was bothered, frustrated and bewildered.
- So from now on--During this time,
I was thankful.
There will be nothing like this from now on. I promise that.
Stay healthy.
What is this? This ominous respect?
Superstitions are a virus-no, what am I saying, superstitions are a virus.
I mean, if she's grateful she can just do well from now on. Why'd she say "stay healthy"?
Her additions and subtractions don't compute!
Anyway... That Sim Bo Nui. She's a weird woman.
What is this?
Went to pray.
Shaman Sir?
Sir Shaman!
The phone is turned off. You will be connected to voice messaging-
Sir Shaman. What am I supposed to do?
You should tell me what I'm supposed to do now...
When did I get so old?
Look at all these wrinkles. It's not like I'm stressing my body but it keeps forming-oh my gosh.
What am I going to do about this v-line?
You have a lot of gray hairs too, darling.
Bo Nui Noona? Noona!
Noona!
Geon Wook!
You're coming now? You didn't see me?
You must have come out to exercise. Go run.
Wait a minute. Is Bo Ra okay?
Yeah. She's fine.
Were you at the hospital all night?
- No. - Then where-
You look tired. Go in.
Okay.
So. Where did you sleep?
With who?
I have to sleep with that person. That's how our Bo Ra will wake up.
There's no way that would happen.
Even if noona is reckless, if Je Soo Ho is Je Soo Ho, he wouldn't do such a thing.
But Noona is too pretty and that guy is a man too.
Here! Coffee is here. And for Seung Hyeon, a special size.
Thank you. I thought I was dying of thirst.
Oh Dal Ddong!
What did you say?
How are you swollen to the point where it's fascinating?
Did you drop anything yesterday?
No, I didn't.
Oh, really? Wait a moment. It looks like you dropped your heart and left though.
Mother!
No! Absolutely not. All of you go home!
Let's go together!"With you my heart shakes as well"
Are we going to Je Soo Ho's house!?
Let's go to Je Soo Ho's place!
These people!
Go to the house!
Come follow me!
Third round! Let's go a third!
Hurry and leave.
Oh, that scared me. I thought I stepped on a mine or something.
What is this?
Who leaves their stuff around, J's story?
Wait a minute!
"Though you stand furious as thunder, with the betrayal of your colleague"
"The solitude that came with enduring that alone"
Oh! Wow! These words! This must be why Zeze's storylines are so good, right?
That's not mine!
If it's not yours, why are you trying to steal it back?
J-Just listen to it! Listen to it. The real thing starts from here!
"You, who stays unmoving while the days and nights pass, my darling, the workaholic"
Wow!
"If only I could massage your stiff shoulders, how nice would that be?"
Oh, I'm getting chills! Chills!
"I don't expect any compensation in return, I'm simply grateful that I can like-"
-Stay still!-I'll find the owner for you!
-I can find the owner too!-No! I will!
Wow. Everyone wants Je Soo Ho!
Just take all the women in the world!
Wow, hey, I like that sentence. "You my darling, the workaholic"!
Oh god! That was childish. Childish poop panty childish!
D-100
Let's start working on the scenario now.
Yes! We just have to run in order!
We're not just running, the problem is we have to keep sprinting at 200km/h!
I'm so freaking thirsty!
Wow, the respectable Mr. Lee Hyun Bin!
- But, what about Bo Nui and the CEO?- Don't know.
Hey, they weren't at the company dinner either and now they're late together too! What if they have something between them?
Oh! It's a mystery!
-Right?-What are you talking about? CEO's already here.
Did she faint?
I mean, she slept fine all through the night!
Seriously, she requires so much care, making the CEO get her personally.
I'm going to give her a stern talking to when I see her!
"Unexcused absence! This is absurd!"
Ah, you have a meeting today, right?
I came to see you.
- Where were you yesterday?- Huh?
I'm asking where you were last night, and with whom.
Why are you curious about that?
Damn...he keeps making me ask.
Were you with Bo Nui Noona yesterday?
I told you. I'm no different from her younger brother.
As her little brother, I have to know.
As her little brother, ask your biological older sister Sim Bo Nui yourself!
I don't want to share my employee's private life with outsiders.
What? Right now, Noona is-!
Anyway, it's because something's happened.
It's because something's happened that she's clinging onto nonsense signs.
I mean, Mr. Je Soo Ho, if you're sane, you can't complain about what's right or wrong when you're facing off between men!
I know it's because of her little sister.
Noona...talked about Bo Ra, to you?
You talk like you're the one who knows Sim Bo Nui the best in the world, but I know what there's to know.
And, we'll handle whatever happens between us.
"We" two?
Anyway, I'm disappointed.
You meddle in the private life of the noona next door.
Right now, Gary seems like a puny kid from the neighborhood, that's sticking his nose in where he isn't needed.
I'm saying as a character, you're getting less charming. Then.
We aren't open yet, we start at 4...
Oppa Yeong Il, right?
Oppa!
-Are you busy?-Thinking.
You have nothing to tell me?
Hm? Huh?
-Ugh this is no fun, I'm leaving.-"Stay healthy".
-I'm going to be more healthy than you!-What do you think that means?
"Stay healthy".
It's a positive remark!
Bye bye! Sayonara, Jai Jien! Ahnyoung! Why? Did the hot woman tell you to stay healthy?
You were dumped! Dumped! Damn kicked off!
Ow! Ow-wait! You're being so rough with a major shareholder!
Wait! Wait! The kids are watching! I'm embarrassed!...Good meeting!
Moon, moon, what moon, round round round moon,
where have you risen? In Dede you've risen!
Miss Bo Nui!
Oh, Bo Nui!
I'm sorry for being late. I'm sorry.
Are you sick? You don't look so good.
I'm okay. What about the CEO?
He's cry-I mean...thinking?
Nothing's happened, right?
What the heck? She's fine.
Ms. Sim Bo Nui, please see me for a moment.
I'll be back.
- You...- CEO Je. Oh, Bo Nui.
- Hi.- Hello.
Did your date go well yesterday?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Excuse me?- Gary waited so long for you.
Ah, I saw him this morning.
-The morning?-You're here for the meeting, right?
You said we'd meet today. Let's get some tea, I have something to say.
You don't remember? You promised me after the event yesterday!
Ah, seriously! Let go! Let go!
Oh, you're all here.
-Oh Je Soo Ho's first love and Je Soo Ho's bundle of luck--Hey!
CEO Je's too cruel to his first love.
I'll say this officially. She's not a first love and she isn't a bundle of luck.
Of course you'd say she isn't but according to my interpretations, she's your first love.
- Let's go. See you later.- Yes.
- Work hard.- Yes.
-Our bundle of luck! Bundle of luck! -Stop it. Come on, hurry up.
Why! Why how nice is it!
-With your bundle of luck and your first love!
- It's not! She's not!- Stop pushing!
It's so nice to see you, this is fascinating! Do you live in this neighborhood?
No! My son's company is this way, Zeze Factory.
Zeze? I know it! They have a lot of dinners here, they're regulars!
Is that so? Zeze's CEO is my son.
Wow. I see.
You really raised your son well.
Oppa, how about your kids?
If they're like you, they must be very smart.
I'm alone. I failed with my business a long time ago and we split then.
I thought it was good I didn't have a kid but now that I'm old, I regret it.
Oh, I see.
Then, I'll start.
What's with the dramatic intro. Someone would think we had something happen between us.
I didn't run away from you, I ran away from myself.
I was scared. That I might keep using you.
I didn't approach you with the purpose of the thesis.
I was just curious...
Who it was my dad chose instead of my older brother.
- Older brother?- Yeah.
An oppa that wasn't as bright as you, but still was called a prodigy.
There was an accident, my dad lost a pupil that was a son,
and my mom was depressed with nervous breakdowns.
And his little sister, was caught up in guilt that wasn't necessary,
so she majored in physics, which didn't even fit with her aptitude.
Just, a predictable story.
Why didn't you tell me?
I must have saved it to tell you now.
And that thesis, I took it back right away. Though you were gone because you'd already left for Korea.
Soo Ho, I know it's shameless but I'd like you to understand,
the selfish and immature me, from 2004,
even if it won't lead to forgiveness,
2005.
It's not 2004, it's 2005.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Since I've tied one knot, it's the start again.
Yes! That was good!
Yes! Just a moment!
Please come in!
Huh? Ms. Dal Nim? What brings you here?
CEO told me to pass this on to you.
This...is that, right? Free Pass!
It's a temporary entrance pass for the project.
Thank you.
Je Soo Ho!
Thank you!
I think we need to make the size a little bigger.
Who put this here?
Oh...I think Ms. Bo Nui put that there.
Oh, she gave all of us one too! It blocks out electromagnetic waves,
and if we put thorny plants up then...
-What did she say? The bad things...-Evil Countenance!
She said it'd block out that stuff.
- Oh yes. -Where is she? Ms. Sim Bo Nui.
This jump and then we'll calculate it all through here.
And the aspects that've been modified from the initial plans.
What are you doing?
Oh, CEO!
Ah, Ms. Bo Nui had organized all the information from the first plans for IF, so I was listening to her explain that.
Are you trying to give up your position?
What? No! It's not like that!
Ms. Sim Bo Nui. Respond.
Mr. Hyun Bin, could you give us a moment.
Oh, yes!
-CEO--Are you going to say nonsense like "I'll quit" or something like that again!?
I just got a call from the hospital!
-They said patient Sim Bo Ra is really doing fine!-I know.
I call every 10 minutes to check too.
I mean, for a person who knows that-are you still going to talk about evil spirits and countenances?!
They do exist.
I mean, do you not remember?!
That astrology, physiognomy, all of it was a sham!
Whether it's talisman or a thorny plant, whether it has an effect or not,
I'm saying I trust and depend on it, is that so bad?
It's bad!
I know.
Now, Ms. Sim Bo Nui, it's because you're so invested in a phenomenon that you're not accepting reality.
It's a psychological error!
CEO, by your standards, I'm filled with errors.
I'm afraid to clip my nails at night because I'm scared, I don't even whistle,
and I don't even write my name in red pen because something bad could happen.
Okay! I'll give you an orderly explanation about your error.
There's things called "evidence" in science, Ms. Bo Nui, I'll try to prove your faith with science.
Hypothesis, if you write your name in red pen, something bad happens!
-Don't.-I wrote it.
Did something happen? The roof didn't collapse, I didn't get hit by a thunderbolt, and heart attack-!
It doesn't happen. My heart, is incredibly healthy.
Oh! I can even write my parents' names. Here...
Don't! I said don't!
Give it!
Why are you doing this? You really can't do this!
What's there to not do? My father, Mr. Je Mul Po,
he's anatomically healthy, his voice is loud,
he's very healthy, just wait and see, nothing will happen.
If your parents die because of you,
do you know how hellish that life is?
Ms. Sim Bo Nui...your parents...died because of you?
Thoughtless acts like these, don't ever...ever do them.
No, I just wanted to prove...
I just...
Did he go on a show or something?
They said there was an article-!
CEO's Mother
Hello.
Yes, it's me.
Excuse me?!
I mean, why would a tiny man like him be back there!
When I got the call, I was so shocked that my blood pressure just dropped!
He'll be okay.
Are you sure you don't have to give the CEO a call?
Don't don't! I tried calling him a couple times and then called you.
Still.
I'm sorry and grateful to you, I'll put in a good word for you to Soo Ho later.
It's okay, this is a given.
Honey! Honey! Honey!
Be quiet!
-Your head! Oh my gosh-what do I do, are you okay?!-It's fine!
-Do you have a hole!?-Move your hand! I'm fine!
It's a relief!
It's really a relief!
No, I'm really okay-I'm not hungry at all!
What are you saying! You came all the way here, of course you have to eat!
Sit, sit!
But how do you have such good intentions? You're not like people these days,
-I knew from the moment with the talisman.-Take this.
Now, eat up!
Thank you for the food!
It's a relief that you're safe.
It's a relief that the CEO won't have to worry either.
Oh my...even loyalty!
Since you came all the way here, tell us. How is our Soo Ho at the company?
-Stop that.-I'm just curious!
He's always like...ill-tempered and stuff, right?
He's cool.
And because he's a genius, he's very very good with his work.
And even though it doesn't seem like it, he takes good care of every single employee.
And when there's something wrong or an aspect we're lacking in, he tries to help fix it.
I'll be leaving the company soon, that's what I wanted to tell you when I picked up.
Why!? A competent person like you has to be right next to Soo Ho!
Ah!
Unni, I'm hungry. Shall we have some ramyon, or if not, ddokbeokki (spicy rice cakes)?
Unni, why are you so tired?
Smile. Do it like this!
I have to take care of my little sister to the end.
Oh, you're coming in late.
Ah, you've arrived.
What are you doing here?
- Yes?  - What's going on in this place?
Oh, she came with us at dawn and clean up everything!
-And she apologized for everything.-She told us to stay healthy.
Where did Dal Nim go?
Oh! She went outside with her to help carry stuff.
What is it? From a girl who wouldn't even let me step into her house!
Just because, I wanted to eat a meal with you.
Eat some of this.
I'll enjoy the meal.
But are you really quitting?
All that's left is development, you'll all be fine without me.
And Bo Ra's hospital bills?
Those are okay too.
What do you mean okay?
There's always money going out every month, you should just stay.
Did the CEO hint at you?
No, nothing like that.
Please give this to the CEO.
Do me this favor. It's because I feel so sorry.
Bo Nui said to give this to you.
Did she say anything else? Like, she was different from always?
No. We just ate together,
and she told me to do well with the diet I'm on.
Did she...tell you to stay healthy?
Yes. How did you know?
You really aren't going in?
I'm grateful to be even be here.
It's all done now. Bo Ra will wake up soon, do you have to take it this far?
You never know, you have to avoid and be careful about things that they say aren't good.
Then...you haven't seen Bo Ra's face once since the accident?
Go see her! I'll be with the doctor!
Bo Ra, your oppa came. Remember? Oppa Puccu.
This is harder than I thought.
Open your eyes. I've become really handsome.
You'll have to wake up
for thick-headed Sim Bo Nui to finally live like a human being.
-Have you really decided?-Yes.
I don't know when it will be,
but I want to be with her at the very end.
Thank you for everything.
It's unexpected, I didn't think you would ever discharge her.
I must have been too selfish all this time.
I understand. Then.
What did the doctor say? She'll be okay, right? She'll wake up soon, right?
A little kid that would cling to the edge of your dress grew up to be a lady.
-She was pretty, she looks exactly like you.-Really?
Her skin is clear and her complexion's nice,
she looks like she'll be up soon.
Of course. She will.
In the end, it's you that saves Bo Ra.
That would be nice.
When Bo Ra wakes up, I'll tell her to treat you well for as long as she lives!
Thanks. Let me hug you once!
It was really nice meeting you again.
It was really nice for me too.
Work hard until the end and you have to be nice with cooperating on IF.
As long as you're there, I'll give an OK to everything.
Even if there is someone I don't really like, I'll have to be patient.
Despite the way I look, I've been a professional for 6 years,
-I'm a far superior sunbae to you when it comes to society.-You're messing with me again!
Let's go.
CEO, I'm giving you a proper message.
Through all these times, I've been both grateful and apologetic.
You've been patient with so much.
All of it is my fault.
I'm the source of all the evil spirits.
And I was like that with you too.
Even so,
you're the first person to have ever put an umbrella over me.
That day, it was because of you I didn't feel as cold.
That memory, I'll keep it safe as it is precious.
I just ask, that you stay healthy.
CEO Je! CEO Je! Wait! It's been a while!
-Oh! Daebak Software.-Sim Bo Nui is upstairs, right?-No, she isn't.
-Wait wait! She can't not be here! She hasn't picked up the phone for days, she's not at the office-who am I supposed to get the money from?-What money?
Oh! The employee's not here so I can just get it from the employer. The water, 5 bottles.
-$550.-I don't know what you're talking about.-What's wrong with you, you're the employer--Talk to Ms. Sim Bo Nui personally.
No! I have to know where she is to talk to her-I don't know where she is that's why I'm talking to you!
Sim Bo Nui! Sim Bo Nui!
- What are you doing?- Sim Bo Nui!
Noona's not here. She left.
-When? -We went outside together and went separate ways, as if she has anywhere to go.
Are you saying you just let her go?
-Where did she say she would go? Did she say she would be anywhere?-What's wrong with you?
I don't think Noona and you have a relationship for you to overreact like this.
What does it matter what kind of relationship I have with her!?
Haven't you seen her face?! She's completely pale,
and completely lifeless, you just let her go like that?!
She was laughing when we were talking,
we went together to see Bo Ra too!
Would a person going to die, tell the world they're going to die!?
Why would Noona die?
We just have to wait for Bo Ra to wake up now!
-When she did that with you!-Nothing happened.
That day, nothing happened! So that woman,
she's completely sure her little sister is going to die.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Korean University Hospital
I've confirmed the transferring patient with SI Rehabilitation Hospital.
Where did she go? Why won't you tell me!?
Patient information can't be shared with anyone except the guardian.
Ms. Bo Nui also told me to make sure.
I'm no different from family with Bo Ra, you saw me earlier too!
Where is Sim Bo Nui?
She said it had a very nice view,
that she would spend the last days there, together.
♬ When I saw ♬
♬ Your silhouette walking away ♬
♬ I still won't ♬
♬ Call this moment  ♬
♬ Farewell ♬
♬ It was so sweet ♬
One Night with the TigerTruth or Dare♬ Our two hearts ♬
♬ That were completely immersed in those memories ♬
♬ How could we possibly forget ♬
♬ You will come back ♬
♬ You won't make it through the loneliess ♬
♬ To my side ♬
♬ You will return again ♬
♬ But in that time ♬
♬ When I meet you again ♬
♬ Will I be able to love you? ♬
♬ With the times that pass ♬
♬ How much will I  ♬
♬ shed tears ♬
♬ I wonder ♬
♬ Lean on me ♬
♬ Have you been waiting? ♬
♬ To me it's you, ♬
♬ but it's taken so long ♬
♬ I say with my heart ♬
Lucky RomancePreview♬ That I'll protect you ♬
Please watch over Bo Ra to the end, that she won't be in pain.♬ That I'll protect you ♬
After watching over Bo Ra well, I'll go with her.♬ I'll stay by your side ♬
What can I do? What should I do?!♬ I'll stay by your side ♬
Have you heard of any other luck premonitions, what can I do!♬ Even when I close my eyes ♬
I don't know what you're going to do next. I keep thinking about you.♬ I see you ♬
Because of you, I'm worried and it's driving me crazy!♬ And my heart flutters again ♬
When you worry about someone, and you keep thinking about them, it means you like them.♬ A love I can't believe ♬
Now, you won't have to worry because of me.♬ Has come to me ♬
As I promised, I'll disappear from you.♬ Has come to me ♬
"When a man likes a woman, they are always curious about what she is doing."♬ Lean on me ♬
Ah! What! Why are you coming here! Don't you know where this is!?♬ Can you feel it ♬
Legs, come to your senses! I wonder if she's eaten?♬ Can you feel it ♬
That woman, she's a bug. A bug.♬ Lean on me ♬
♬ Like this forever ♬