Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Episode 9
♬ I’m smiling, and without me knowing ♬
♬ I’m loving you ♬
See? It’s fine.
♬ Like that warm sun that shines on you ♬
Ms. Bo Nui?
♬  I want to watch over you  ♬
Thank you.
Thank you…so much…
♬ Lean on me, forever like this ♬
Whenever you miss her, tell me.
♬ We can’t turn back the times that have passed ♬
I’ll come with you.
♬ The times we didn’t know were love, lean on me ♬
Korea University Hospital
No matter what, tell me it isn’t true.
Is…this a dream?
I’ve imagined Bo Ra waking up, hundreds of thousands of times.
But I was never selfish about wanting to see her, not even in my dreams.
From now on, let’s come to see her. Hundreds of thousands of times.
I must’ve done great things for you in the past life!
But I won’t wish for more.
I thought I’d never see her for the rest of my life. But I saw her once.
Thank you so much for today. Please get back safely!
Wait! You're just going to leave?
Excuse me?
Let’s go in the car.
It’s close, I’ll walk! I have a conscience too, I won’t bother you any more!
Fine then…
Let’s eat! Let's eat...
What?
I mean, from morning until now, I drove you, I was your talisman. Are you running now that you’ve used me all up?
You said you were thankful.I don’t believe in the past life so pay me back in this life.
No, I said I was going to go see my parents and you forced me…
I don’t know-I don’t know what you’re talking about!There’s a restaurant right here!Let’s go here to eat!
Let’s leave, please?
We can go after we eat.
Eel, flatfish, salmon, nigiri, fish-covered rice-there’s nothing for you to eat!I’ll buy next time, okay?
Excuse me!
Yes?
Oh-sorry, we’ll come next time!
We’ll be ordering now.
Unfortunately, there are things I can eat.
You’re right…
You were happy there was nothing for me, right!?
No, it's not like that!
Thank you. I’ll eat well.
Did you have stomach problems after eating seafood once?
I heard from your mother that you were a fish maniac when you were young.
Nevermind…
I almost died. Because I fell into the sea.
I told you before, I have a great sense of imagination. My memory is even better.
The saltiness that passed my throat. The smell of the sea in my nose.
It's all vivid.
After that, I stopped eating fishy food. It’s a trauma with a clear cause that reaped results.
Hurry up and eat! So that we can have coffee too.
Yes!
You're good.
Boo!
What are you doing?
It’s just, I remembered when we first met.
You were really flustered that day because of me, right?
Constantly, always, you fluster me, every single time.
I’m sorry…for constantly, always, giving you trouble, every single time.
I guess that’s why they say you can’t fix the life you’re given. I'll be careful.
You said…your parents passed away when you were 16, right?
Yes.
Do you think that…that’s your fault too?
With the blade, destiny, that sort of thing?
I didn’t know it then.
Only my baby chick died, only my seat partner got hurt, and my mom and dad…
Even when they died getting tickets their daughter wanted, I thought it was all a coincidence.
If I knew earlier, it would’ve been better. If I knew, I’d have sent Bo Ra away to be adopted…
Why would you say such things? Says the person who gave up her life for her little sister.
Money is something I could make and food was something I didn’t need, but that was the scariest thing.
The thought that they could take my Bo Ra away from me.
I’d wake up multiple times, to touch her face again and again…
Should I try guessing what you’re thinking?
Let’s see…“Oh, how pathetic, how naive-this woman really…never changes”
Am I right?
You must have had such a hard time.
A little kid feeding, dressing, raising a little-er kid…
It must have been hard for you.
Let’s go now, I’ve taken too much of your time.
You’re being disrespectful in the middle of a devotion, thinking of such things!
I only think of Bo Ra, no matter what!
Please watch over her, from her fingers to her toes, and wake her up.
I don’t want anything else.
Boo!
♬ That day when we first met ♬
Whenever you miss her, tell me.
♬ You must have thought it was a joke ♬
♬ I’ll show you the truth ♬
Did you sleep well?
Is that too greasy?
Are you up? What are you doing?
How do you use pretty words-did you eat? I don't know anymore...
Hello! Please have some of this!
Oh my!
Why did you bring so much!?
How is my Bo Ra today? From now on, I want to journal every single day!
Bo Ra? She’s busy right now! Very busy!
She’s meeting with a handsome man. The man you came with last time!
It was you?
Why? Is there anyone else that would be here besides me?
No!Nurse Lee told me that a handsome man came.
That’s me!
How is Bo Ra? She looks a lot more lively, right?!
She must be sleeping. I just quietly said hi and came out.
Noona, you want to see Bo Ra too, right?
Geon Wook, I saw Bo Ra’s face! With my own two eyes!
When? How?!
Yesterday. It’s all thanks to the CEO!
CEO Je…?
He told me to think of him as my talisman! He said he’d come with me whenever I wanted to see her.
My CEO hates superstitions and any signs!
I thought he’d be really feisty, but the more I get to know him, I think he’s a really good person.
That’s good.
Wait!
Why did he come again? Without even contacting me?
Who?
It’s the CEO. Has he been waiting long? He should've called!
Does he still burst into your room?
Sometimes he stops by when he’s in the neighborhood…
That person has a really messed-up personality.
Last time he came by without notice, he kept droning on about ominous things like you would die and stuff.
And then he just wandered around the house all night.
The CEO did? When?
The day Bo Ra woke up!
Noona…you didn’t come home that day…
This has to end. I'm going to tell him to remember boundaries.
Hey! Hey, Geon Wook! It's not that!
Geon Wook! Hey!
Look here, CEO Je...!
Oh! It really is you! Player Gary Choi!
Hello, I'm Reporter Choi from Women's Sense. I heard that you were looking for your father. Is this true?
What?
Excuse me! What do you think you're doing all of a sudden?
What are you doing!? You can't take pictures! Don't take pictures!
It's okay, you just need to say a few words!
Wait! Wait, please! Wait!
That inquiry office, detective-whatever it is, that's the only place the information could've leaked from.
Hurry up and give me the number!
Don't worry. We have all the original files and we signed a penalty agreement should any of the copies surface.
Should we just sue all of them?!
There's no need to fight the medium itself. You'll only increase the gossip.
Amy, let's do a broadcast.
What?
We blocked it by force this time, but once word gets out, it'll be in the blink of an eye.
After the broadcast, there won't be a problem with the game either.
You don't have to push yourself. If Gary doesn't want it, we won't impose it on you.
Gary. People are cruel.
They might be at your feet in praise but just wait until they find a trace.
"He's the worst bastard", "What a pitiful child",
all sorts of things will run from their mouths.
I'll brace myself. As long as I can find my dad, everything's fine.
Broadcasts are good for impact.
On top of that, because it's Gary, it'll get around faster, further.
Okay. Let's try this.
I'll make it according to the concept we want.
I won't let our Gary be cursed and shredded by anyone.
Zeze will also support you as much as we can. Tell me if you need anything.
How'd it go?
The best defense is going on the offense. We decided to go with what I wanted.
Let's make a beta version before the day the athlete leaves.
We're cutting it too close!
Gary is the main character, we'll need his confirmation. The person-in-charge of the scenario will be Ms. Sim Bo Nui.
After the broadcast on Saturday, please come up with the story for his parents.
Yes! I understand!
In a month, we'll have the open beta. In three months, we'll have the official release.
What!?
What about our workshop!? It's this Friday! It can't be cancelled!
I wanted to eat meat! Meat!
No matter how I look at it, the workshop this time around...
It'd be best to go, right?
What?!
Go and play no matter what. You'll have to clear your minds to give it your all.
Yes!
Yes. We understand!
Go have fun. And eat meat.
Yes, yes.
I understand!
I was going in.
Yes...Excuse me, CEO! Thank you.
W-What for?
For being considerate towards Geon Wook. Now just accept that you're a good tiger.
I mean, what's there about me being a good tiger to Gary, not even you.
And why would you be thanking me for that?
Because he's like a little brother I like and cherish.
Wow, you must like him and cherish him a lot.
Then...
Food!
Let's eat. You said you were thankful.
If you're thankful, you have to buy food.
Oh, sorry, I have an appointment today.
With who...
Fine, go ahead.
Why does he keep asking to eat food?
That's amazing.
How...is he beautiful down to the bone?
I don't even need chocolate for my blood sugar, you know what I mean?
Yeah, he's definitely top-class among human beings.
In other words, women lose their minds when they see a good looking guy...
Can you be quiet?!
I need to appreciate a handsome man.
Though he's incomparable to the heavenly-class.
Shaman Sir! I'm here!
Hello mother...
They say maybe not for enemies but grace should always be repaid.
No! I'm okay...
Come in!
We came for another talisman!
This is a miss who knows a few things. She's an employee at my son's company. Isn't she pretty?
Have you been well, Shaman Sir?
The talisman for joy, I use that one often too.
I'm sorry for not telling you earlier.
What if we were married couples in the past life!?
How could this be! Shaman Sir! Please look at our matrimonial harmony! I think it'll be killer!
Don't worry about me and please see your fortune. I'm here solely as a delivery girl!
First, please do my son's first!
What happened to that raccoon? Is it still on him!?
No! No! Please don't!
No! No!
I told you, right? The frivolous raccoon!
Yes! That damned raccoon!
How is it?
It's hanging!
The waves are coming in.
If he keeps dipping his ankles,
the moment he realizes it,
he'll be under!
Thank you!
Nothing's been going on at the office? Like the roof is leaking?
Or the bathroom floods? Or the water fountain in CEO Je's room is broken?
Our son can't ever be near water.
He fell in and almost died when he was a kid!
Oh! I see...
I'll watch over him well!
I can't believe it. Of course the ignorant being would drop the kid in the sea, as if that would teach him how to swim!
Someone...purposely dropped him in there?
The man who knocked his head falling backwards!
Is he the raccoon on Soo Ho?
I'll put this talisman in your care too.
Give it to him personally this time! And while you're at it, you can see his face too.
I don't want to see him throw it away in front of me. It feels like he's crumpling my heart.
Ms. Bo Nui!
Oh! Hold on!
Hi Boss!
Are you on your way in after lunch?
Yes! Have you eaten?
I'll have to eat when I head in. I've got a lot of side dishes!
She's our CEO's mother! I had an errand to run for her!
Hello.
He's the boss of the chicken place our office goes to often! He's very kind!
I see...Ms. Bo Nui, I'll be going.
Please go safely!
I'll be going! Please work hard!
What is this!? This! What happened to this?! Can we fix it!?
What's with this, seriously?!
Who was it! Who did this?!
Oh! It looks like you pressed the wrong button!
Mr. Ji Hoon?!
No, no! It's not me!
We were all just on our way in from lunch. Why take it out on us?
Then who was it?! Being so childish?!
How should we know!?
Seriously.
Bones...a person's nose bone, chin bone, forehead bone-they're all the same...
Beautiful...tsh...right...
Sim Bo Nui, look at you. In every single corner-you scaredy cat!
Dal Nim!
Why aren't you going, why!?
I have to check on Bo Ra every day. What if I go with you and we get into an accident along the way?
Even in college, you couldn't go to MT's because you had to work. The only countryside you've ever been in is to work until your bones ache!
Now Bo Ra's awake, you can whistle some tunes and have fun!
I want to too. Go to a nice place and see pretty things, eat yummy food.
Then you can! Let's go...Bo Nui, let's go!
That day, the day Bo Ra got into an accident. I thought that if I gave it one more minute, I could find the bug.
And like that, I kept getting greedy for one minute, two minutes...and my Bo Ra's surgery got delayed.
Like you said, after Bo Ra woke up, a breeze keeps tickling my heart.
But...that's being selfish.
You know well that I can't do that.
It's not selfishness...
Are you ready?
Ms. Bo Nui! Here!
I put in a special word at a place I worked a long time for.
For now, save up bit by bit and we can talk about it later.
- Ms. Bo Nui, you want me to give you that?- It's better for two people to hold blank paper too.
Ms. Bo Nui, I'm so grateful. So grateful. I'm only living because of you. Thank you so much.
Don't say stuff like that! It's a lot better when you're yelling in a loud voice!
Thank you-Won Dae Hae, you can do it! Loud voice!
- Thank you.- This is for lunchboxes!
- Ma'am! What about tomorrow's lunch?! How about a lunchbox?!- Please find us next time!
- Hello! This is "Lunchbox Today Too"...- I'm okay.- Okay!
Mother! Hello, this is called "Lunchbox Today Too". We promise fresh ingredients along with much care.
Please find us regularly!
- Hello sir!- Forget it.
Thank you.
Aren't you working? Give me a sheet.
In exchange for not paying the water off, I found him a part-time job and I'm just helping him.
Did anyone ask?
What...are you doing?
I'm receiving flyers. From the most naive one of all the naive.
I'm partially at fault for Boss Won turning out this way.
Again? The blue blade? And you've got a rough fortune? That thing?
After he hired me, orders from all over the place got cancelled!
I don't care!
- Thank you!- About the workshop...
- How...- CEO Je! What brings you here?! It's been a while!
CEO Je, I've got a killer project.
You know AlphaGo? The future will be a generation of robots and artificial intelligence. I've got a superior at the Blue House...
Boss! L-Let's...Go there! Get back safe...
Hurry!
I got it! I got it!
You can do it to me but don't do that to CEO Je, please!
Okay!
Ms. Bo Nui. The two of you have something, don't you.
What?
I smell it. When I see one, I know ten.
Then you would've either been an exorcist or hit jackpot! We don't have anything!
Oh, if it's not, then why's CEO Je standing around there? Not going home and just wandering here and there?
Now he's going! It's nice! That pink atmosphere, it's good!
I said it's not!
What do you mean 'not'-what's wrong with that between a man and a woman!?
Hello?
Oppa. It's me, Hee Ae. Sorry about before, something must have come over me.
It wouldn't be that great to recognize me in front of an employee. I understand!
It's not like that! That child is a subordinate working directly under my son. I thought she might tell.
I'm sorry, Young Il Oppa.
Oppa! Remember to drink the carp juice! And tell me when you run out, okay?
Alright. Thanks!
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Here! A beer and a coke, right?
Huh? Why, is something going on?
Sim Bo Nui...
It's Sim Bo Nui.
What's wrong with Ms. Bo Nui? Did she cause an accident?!
No, I'm frustrated. Did she say weird, delirious things when she worked here too?
She's just worrying!
What am I going to do to her?
Not because you're going to do something to her, but because she might do something to you.
Ms. Bo Nui taped that up herself.
To make sure I wouldn't get hurt. She never let me go on delivery routes and
anything that required a knife or boiling oil-she did all the dangerous things by herself!
Because she was afraid I'd become unlucky from her.
I'm partially at fault for Boss Won turning out this way.
After he hired me, orders from all over the place got cancelled!
Whenever I think of Ms. Bo Nui, I feel bitter regret.
She should be having a fun time at her age. But all she does is work without rest, while doing all sorts of dangerous things.
Oh baby! I heard you're going on a workshop! When? Is there a date-oh, hello!
Welcome!
Agh! This is annoying!
But fine, I'll go and buy for you guys, as the major shareholder! Bang!
Where are you going?
I have some place to go...you can have all of this.
Did I do something wrong?
Welcome! Have a nice day!
Welco-!
Boss!
Oh! Ms. Bo Nui! Hello!
What happened?
Huh? Oh! Last night, CEO Je came by, begging that I help.
Security guard?
Yeah, we just happened to have an empty space.
So...you'll get four of the major public insurance, bonuses for the holidays and pay for overtime.
Still! We made a contract as employer and employer. Wouldn't it be weird for me to work under you?
If you don't want it, fine.
No! No! I don't not want it! I'm just asking if it's weird...
Is that okay? Then when should I go to work?
This is good! I feel like I've dropped some weight off my shoulders!
Oh! You're here!
- Bye! Ms. Bo Nui! Fighting!- Fighting!
That-wow, it's so weird!
Sorry?
The...your boss, Won Dae Hae, the one who failed because of you. I heard he got a job at a nice place!
You said you're unlucky but good things happen!
It's so weird!
You stopped by the hospital on your way back from work!
I want to keep seeing her!
You feel uneasy because you're leaving for the workshop tomorrow, huh?
Geon Wook, I'm not going.
Why? Did CEO Je tell you not to come? Is he discriminating against contract-workers?!
No! I have to watch over Bo Ra. What time do I have for anything else?
Oh yeah. Are you ready for the broadcast? Don't be nervous and do well!
About that, I wanted to ask you.
What?
Noona. Can't you go with me?
I feel like if you're there with me, I'll have so much strength!
What if you get terrible luck because of me?
I'll passionately support you from home.
You can do exorcisms! I'll take salt bottles!
You know how important this is to me.
It's because I know that I can't go even more.
If you can't find your father because of me,
you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
Oh Gary! What's up in the middle of the night?
Amy. I think I might cancel training tomorrow.
Training?
Did you forget!?
No! Of course, there's no need to exhaust yourself before the broadcast.
I actually have something important to do tomorrow too.
Gary, take care of your face and your heart. Okay?
Okay.
Nice!
The weather just had to be nice. If only the rain came I would've...
Setting, check!
Ticket, check.
Noona, go on a picnic with me and accept my request.
♫ The world seems to look different ♫
♫ Look at that sky, the blue sky makes me smile ♫
♫ I thought it was love ♫
♫ I thought you liked me ♫
♫ I thought this was the beginning ♫
♫ I thought you'd cling to me ♫
So you really won't come by all means?
Go have fun! And tell the team members that I had stomach problems.
Don't you have to report to the CEO?
He's not going anyways.
I'm going to send a ton of pictures! So that you can be jealous!
Play nice! Bye!
I even got the salt and red beans ready...
Dal Nim! Hurry!
Yes.
- You packed everything up?- Yes! We're all ready, right?
- Wait! Wait, wait!- Hello.
I'm not late, right? I'm just in time!
Hello...
- What is this?- What's all this packed stuff?
Shall we go?
W-Wait! Where? Head of branch!
Yeah, Geon Wook?
Where are you? You're not home?
Yeah. The thing is...
Let's go. To the workshop.
- They said you weren't going.- Yes. That was the plan.
- They said it was right by a lake!- Ugh. The worst!
Then why?
There's one employee that requires a lot of care. She's not even a child but she can't go anywhere without me. So what can I do?
For the well-being of my employee, I must sacrifice this shell.
- No...- Let's go. And don't worry.
I'll be your talisman.
It turned out that way. But why? Did something happen?
No...you said you had the day off. I thought we could eat spicy rice cakes together.
Let's eat spicy rice cakes next time. I'll buy!
Have a good time.
Rest all that you can today! I'll call you later.
Do they have some deep resentment towards spicy rice cakes or what?
W-Wait! No, no! Agh!
I just cleaned everything.
Sorry. It's a long way, I felt paranoid.
Your living talisman is right here!
Without a doubt, I assure you.
No matter how many hours we're in this car alone, nothing will happen!
- Music...- Agh...- I just wanted to listen to some music...
- Then at least the water...- Agh...
I'll drink it! Please!
O-Open this...for me...
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Here. Put this on.
Feel the sun, get in the mood. When you go to play, you're supposed to wear things like this.
Says who?
Han Yang Ha. There's a punk that doesn't lose to anyone when it comes to playing around. So it's probably right.
CEO. Do you by any chance...like me?
What?!
It's not, right?
What are you saying all of a sudden?! I almost got into an accident!
Well I didn't have a choice! You keep coming to my house,
and a person that doesn't eat often keeps asking me to eat with him.
And you hired Boss Won as security.
You're even going to a workshop you don't have to go to because of me.
Above all, you became my talisman too.
It's not! Tsh! You've misunderstood everything quite well!
Ms. Sim Bo Nui, you're just a bug to me. A bug that has a deadly superstition virus.
As a citizen with a conscience...and your superior with moral values. I only did that...because I couldn't just...stand by...
I knew it. I mean, Boss Won kept saying it!
No, that Boss Won...is seriously...
So...hmm? What about you, Ms. Sim Bo Nui?
Excuse me?
Do you hate me? Or like me.
♫  Warmly, for us ♫
That's enough! If it's not 0 then it's 1! What are you so...
Fine! Just hate me all you want! Yeah!
Both of us! We can just...be open! And hate each other! We're on the same page!
It's so hot...
♫ Just you and I, Shalala Romance ♫
It's nice!
If it's like this,
you can't say it's "all members attending". When CEO Je and Ms. Bo Nui aren't here!
I'm here! Welcome!
Is CEO Je here too?
He'll either come or not later, however he feels.
For the greatest beauty in our building to be here...I'm honored.
What are you doing here?
Me? As a major shareholder! Of course I have to be here for the sake of boosting the employees' morale!
I was hiding like a bear-oh my, I thought I'd turn into a bear!
Seriously...
Gary?!
Welcome! World famous-!
Gary! How did you come here when your broadcast is tomorrow?
What are you!? You said you were resting!
Y'all did rugby, didn't you?
Then what about you Amy? You hate the countryside. Is this "important"?
Of course!
What's more important than a get-together with the people creating the game for my athlete!
Hey, it's Je Soo Ho!
It's so fun.
Who is this!? Isn't it our Je Soo Ho!
- Je Soo Ho!  - Bo Nui!
Dal Nim!
Oh! Bo Nui! How did...the two of you?
You said all members should attend!
I'll hurry and change the room arrangements. CEO, it's really good that you came!
Bo Nui! You did good coming here!
Come on! Let's play! Yeah!
Huh?
Why are you here!
Can't I come? IF is my game!
No! I mean your broadcast is tomorrow!
What are you going to do if something happens to you going back and forth long distances, when you don't even know roads well?!
I came to ask you one more time. To me, you're not someone that brings misfortune!
From the first day I landed in Korea. More than the red underwear and the owl, you were more...
You were my lucky charm.
So please Noona, come with me.
Sorry.
Noona, you seriously...
- What? What?- Oh wait!
He keeps saying weird things!
Let's ride today!
- Yes!- Fighting!
- Hyung...why...- Why are you here?
I thought you were a German soldier!
Let's ride today!
Why are you here?
Take it off! Take it off!
It's Je Soo Ho!
Stop it...
Hey-are you going to ride this?!
What are you going to do if you get hurt?! You can't have injuries!
Then what, do I just drink after coming all this way?
Oh he's here!
- He's here.- Oh, were you shocked?
Oh, is there something you can pull on?
I know...I know.
I'm going to fly today!
Let's ride today!
Go!
Wait!
We can't go yet! Hold on!
Oh...you're like Crayon Pop!
Jumping! Jumping!
Call me oppa!
Everyone get some salt!
You really can't get hurt! Tomorrow's the broadcast!
Should we do a bet too? First one to the finish line gets a wish.
What guys give each other wishes?
We're doing it.
Go!
♬ Now put all those tears behind you ♬
♬ Goodbye to the endless sadness, hello blue tides ♬
♬ I can do it again ♬
This is great!
♬ With the hope that makes my heart burst ♬
♬ I want to let myself reach it, flying through that sky ♬
♬ To that dream ♬
♬ No one else can find ♬
♬ To the dream that's ours ♬
What about Gary?
This is so fun!
Give me your license. Where in the world did you learn to drive!?
Then what about you? Are you so good that you slam your bike into that ditch?!
The machine didn't listen to me! I told you the wheel didn't move!
Machines have souls too.
How cheeky must you have been for it to break like that!
Y-You...You're saying that I'm cheeky, right?!
As expected! Your memory, imagination and sense of understanding is perfect!
Is that a compliment...?
Why are you last?!
What about Noona? I was looking for Bo Nui Noona. Is she here?
Let's ride again!
- I want to ride again! It's so fun!- Then we can ride again!
That damn...
Yeah! Let's ride again!
I'm crazy. I'm delusional, as if there's anything to do.
All I do is meat-wait!
Wait bundle of Dal! Can't you stop eating?
- Don't touch me.- Let me grill!
To be honest, it's time!
I'm just thinking about the possibility of him getting hurt!
- He won't get hurt!- We could seriously die.
Then we can die!
We have to dunk him when he's here, when else would we get the chance!?
Ahem-! CEO! You're here!
Pour him a drink.
Soo Ho!
I don't drink alcohol but you poured alcohol.
- Give him some coke!- Now since our CEO is here, it's time for the long-awaited Game of Truth!
Yeah!
- Spin the bottle!- Okay!
Sim Bo Nui!
Sim Bo Nui! Sim Bo Nui!
- If you can't answer in 3 seconds, you have to down the mixed drink!- Okay!
- Start!- Zeze Factory was all hype!
No!
CEO Je's got a dirty attitude!
- Yes...- Right!?
- You're happy these days! -Mhm.
Oh!
You're dating someone?
No!
You have a crush.
Oh! It looks like she does@
- What?- We got her!
I don't! I don't have anyone I like, I don't have that luxury either.
Hey, Je Soo Ho. Let's talk. Did I come here to grill meat?
How can no one ask me to play with them.
Am I supposed to grill meat for hundreds of thousands of days?
Wait! Ms. Bo Nui! Be honest! You're secretly dating the CEO, right?!
No! That's just trouble!
Hand it over, come on! Hand it over!
These people-did you bet again!
Give me mine first.
Ms. Seung Hyeon always wins!
Where are you going?
Just...walking...
Are you okay? In America, just being at the riverside was hard for you.
How many years ago was that.
Wow, my Soo Ho is all grown up. He's an adult!
I'm not the puny kid from your memories.
Then why don't you date anyone? Yang Ha said so.
That he taught you about everything but women.
How about me? It was only me back then.
No?
It's not that big of a deal. I already confirmed the questions and format too.
You're trying to find your father!
Am I not allowed to?
Of course you can't! Just to find that person, you want to destroy your reputation, all you've done!
All in one blow!? No! Never!
Nothing will be destroyed. Mom, please.
I'll start with Amy. And cancel the contract with IM.
Geon Wook!
Noona...
Your mother, is she really angry?
It's my first broadcast.
So she's probably worried about this and that.
Tomorrow...
What time do I have to be there by?
Noona.
You're going up tonight, right? I'll leave early tomorrow morning.
Then let's just go together!
I have to at least get to the end of today.
And if we go up together...you never know...
I'd feel better going separately.
Thanks Noona.
I feel like I can finally breathe.
Mommy! Momma!
- Why? Why?!- It keeps following me!
Ow.
It left. It's gone.
- It's gone?- Yeah, it's gone.
- Really?- Yeah.
I really hate moths the most in the world.
I really hate the countryside!
So why'd you come...
- Why?!- Stay still.
Why?! Why! Why?!
Why?! Ah!?
- Is it gone?!-It's gone.
- Really?- Mhm.
Hey! It's gone. It's gone!
It looks like I should head in now.
Be careful on your way up. I'll call you.
What'd they say? The company is out of control, right?
Don't worry about it. I'll get you on-air no matter what and take all the responsibility.
Just now...with CEO Je...
I'll damn kill you!
I mean...James is just egging me on, it's infuriating.
He's stick skinny, he'll be light!
Between the four of us, we can definitely carry him!
No what if he gets...
Gets hurt?
Dal Nim!
What are you doing?! Are you okay?!
Hey hey, this way, not there.
Look at her!
Bye Dal Nim!
Oh!
The CEO, the CEO is here!
- Mission launch!- Go, go!
Dal Nim, what do I do.
My heart is weird.
Ms. Bo Nui, I'll show you something fun. Come here, hurry!
Where are you going?
Have you had a lot?
CEO, let's drown in alcohol together!
- No, I don't drink alcohol...- Let's go!
I said I don't drink!
I guess those people intend to live only to today.
They said they're going to dunk the CEO in water.
What?
We've been through more than enough. Times like these, you go crazy just once.
Ms. Bo Nui! You want to help them?!
I almost died. Because I fell into the sea.
No. No!
Please! Do it right! Please! Do it right!
-No, no! Wait! No! No!- 1, 2, 3!
CEO! It feels great, doesn't it!?
You look great!
What are you doing! This is dangerous!
The CEO...we just wanted to pull a prank on the CEO...
Is there a reason to kill someone by playing in the water tonight?!
No, it's shallow here so it's fine. It only comes up to the waist!
Are you okay?
Don't overreact.
No, is this really something to get that mad about?
He's fine. What are we supposed to do if we can't even do this at a workshop?
Exactly! If he came to the workshop, he should be dunked at least once!
It should feel cool.
I told you we shouldn't do it.
- What's the point in saying it now.- You should've said something!- We're all in the same boat now.
Leave. I just need some sleep.
Don't go back there. I don't want my employees knowing.
Let's go to the hospital...
I said I'm fine!
Why are you like this, seriously!? If you're hurt then you can say you're hurt! Why do you hide it!? Why do you pretend it doesn't hurt!
Why do you try to carry everything on your own?
CEO, the way you held an umbrella over me, the way you became my talisman and held me...
Let me do that for you.
Which one would you like?
I need to check your driver's license...
How can you say something like that at a time like this?
I'm making this clear. This is my trauma. Not something you caused.
Do you...still hold a grudge against your father?
Mother...
I didn't know anything and I went on and on about being good your parents...
I'm sorry for sticking my nose in...
10 years.
Since I went to study overseas when I was 11 years old, I lived with him for 10 years.
Well, even if it wasn't that, there wasn't much for me to look back on.
You went to study abroad alone? An 11 year old? That's a baby!
But here or there, it's all the same. In the end, all people who I can't communicate with.
Wherever I was. I was always a monkey.
Fascinating and strange, something fun to watch on the other the side of the fence.
It wasn't bad. I hate dealing with people who smile at my face,
then talk trash about me behind my back.
You must have been lonely.
Like being stuck in a pitch-dark cave, the little kid must have been scared and felt dreary.
Why do you put a person that says he's okay, in a cave?
I thought that you were someone that was born with all the luck in the world.
You're smart, you have skills, you're charming...
And your parents are healthy.
So I thought you were a completely different human being from me.
You thought...?
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just go.
I barfed on you. This much is nothing.
You smiled! You're feeling better enough to smile, right?
I'm showing you sides that shouldn't be seen...
People all live the same way. Now we're even!
Puccu: New Message
♫ Tell me (Tell me) ♫
♫ Tell me through those pursed lips ♫
♫ With those fond eyes, tell me ♫
♫ That you feel the same way ♫
♫ I love you ♫
My heart hurts so much,
but I don't know where it is, so I can't write it.
♫ There are no better words than these ♫
CEO, you've done so much for me.
But this is all I can do for you.
♫ Tell me ♫
♫ Shall we try starting now? ♫
♫ I don't care who's first ♫
Remember what you asked before?
I don't...
hate you.
How could I hate such a good person?
No matter what anyone else says. To me,
you're affectionate, kind, and warm-hearted.
It'd be nice if I could be that kind of a person to you...
But I can't...and I shouldn't.
♫ These words I'm saying for the first time, I love you (I love you) ♫
♫ There are no words better than these ♫
So...don't be in pain.
Don't go. Stay by my side.
Do you believe in destiny?Truth Dare
♫ Why didn't I know you ♫
Is anyone there?! Anyone! Zeze Factory!
♫ Time passes by without fail ♫
If that thing called destiny really exists,
then go ahead and save me.
I caught it from Sim Bo Nui-I'm telling you, this is a virus!
♫ Please remember ♫
♫ I was genuine to you ♫
CEO! Are you okay?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
♫ I need you ♫
♫ Just a bit, won't you open up to me? ♫
What? From both of them at the same time!?
Are you maybe thinking about dating?
Dating...that sounds pretty good.
If you have time tomorrow, do you want to date me?
She's the person I like. That's why I don't want to hear it.
There's something there. There is!
Don't you...have anything to say to me?
Dating is a luxury I can't afford!
Are you crazy!?
You confessed!?
It'll probably last a moment. When this passes, I'll reminisce. That the breeze was so warm, so kind. I can remember it in happiness.
What exactly is that person? Who is that person to you that you push me away!
What are you doing tomorrow? If not much, then let's eat.
♫ It's you ♫