Subtitles by DramaFever
[This drama is based on psychology.
All cases and treatments are fictitious.]
Oh my god!
Who... the hell are you?
Let go of that hand right now!
- Mr. Soo Hyun?
- Professor Choi?
Let's go!
Professor Choi!
What are you trying to do here?
You two know each other?
[Episode 7]
How do you know Professor Jo?
We're just acquaintances, but he
has a lot of interest in fortune telling.
That's the only reason
I introduced him to you.
All you did was introduce him to me?
Then why did he ask me out on a date?
How am I supposed to know?
I guess his ideal type
is fortune tellers.
Then, why did you chase us?
I was afraid that you might
fall for Professor Jo
since he's so handsome
and chivalrous.
But you decided to go on a date with him
within a day of meeting him?
How could you be so... fickle?
Why?
Why can't I see other men?
Are the two of us in a relationship?
Did we ever go out, or anything?
No, we didn't!
So what business of yours is it?
Don't you remember?
I clearly told you that I like--
Oh. You mean what you told me
while sending me those flowers?
I didn't realize
that was actually genuine.
I thought you were just messing around.
Who would mess around
with something like that?
Oh, really?
Then I'll give it to you straight now.
My answer is "no."
It's not because I'm mad
or because of your excessive jealously,
or because I'm giving up.
It's just a sincere "no."
I don't have any feelings for you
whatsoever.
Ms. Hye Rim. There are times when humans
are not aware of their true feelings.
The way I see it, you're in that--
Also, I have some work that came up.
I'll become quite busy from here on out.
What kind of work?
Are you saying that some kind
of project came in, or something?
Yes. I've been tasked with being
a part of efforts
improving international
relations with China
as well as the unification
of North and South Korea
and achieving world peace.
So representatives from all these
countries will be meeting in one spot?
That's really none of your business.
Anyway, I'll be busy because of all this
so I don't think I'll even be able
to see your face anymore.
Goodbye, Mr. Choi Soo Hyun.
Can I have the check, please?
I came to reclaim what I left here.
(in French)
The clothes have been ruined.
It wasn't like this at first.
(in French)
I'm telling you there's a date tomorrow!
Take responsibility!
(in French)
What, is it something bad?
No, that's not it, but...
I'll give you a little extra, so
please try to convince that French lady!
Please?
50,000 won.
This money is the same as four hours
worth of part-time work
and could pay for three containers
of sugar syrup!
Is that not enough?
Would you like a bit more?
Um... it's not something that can
be solved by trying to convince her.
All she's doing is telling you
what'll happen in the future.
She said that it's important
to respect your child's opinion.
Marie Antoinette went through
something similar, you see.
She didn't want to get married
but her mother forced her to
get married to a French royal.
And thus, that ultimately
led to her demise.
Yes... I did force my child to major
in medicine when they didn't want to.
See? And his grades weren't
that good either, because of that.
It's his life.
Please respect his opinions.
How much did you say your fee was?
With a base price of 50,000 won
and travel fees of 50,000 won
it's 100,000 won in total, ma'am.
There were some tiny errors
this time around. I apologize.
What kind of errors, exactly?
That's confidential, so I can't
volunteer that information.
Why did you say, "get your hands off her"
when you appeared suddenly?
Very rudely, at that.
My experiment does not allow for the
subjects to touch each other.
I know that you did it as a
defensive maneuver to protect Ms. Go
but I had to stop that as quickly
as possible, through any means necessary.
And I'm still sorry about the fact
that I spoke to you so disrespectfully.
It seems that the liberal arts
are quite complicated.
The natural sciences are much easier,
with everything being calculable.
Anyway, have you heard
from Ms. Go Hye Rim?
She's been texting me, asking to see me
since this morning.
She's trying to confirm her suspicions.
She's realized that the two of
us know each other, which is why.
If you do meet her,
please tell her this.
Welcome!
I'll get straight to the point.
What kind of relationship do
you have with Mr. Choi Soo Hyun?
We're just acquaintances.
And the reason I met you
is because I asked him to recommend
a good fortune teller to me.
I heard that you were a
professor of mechanical engineering.
I didn't know people in the sciences
believed in fortune telling.
That's just my personal preference.
But, why did you go with
Mr. Choi that day?
Go on the offensive. Ask her why
she went with Choi Soo Hyun.
I'm the one who asked to see you.
Did our date mean nothing to you?
That's because I had to talk to
Mr. Choi about something...
You could've done that later, though.
It was kind of an urgent scenario, so...
I'm disappointed.
I never would've expected you
to be such a person.
I am sorry about that.
But how did you get to know Mr. Soo Hyun?
I told you.
I've taken on a project that
is relevant to psychology--
Mr. Choi is from Stanford and
you're from Dong Ah University.
So how did you two...
I'm saying that the two of us
are working together on this project.
And what's the objective
of this project?
To find out more about
a woman's way of thinking.
Professor Choi is supervising
and participating in an experiment
related to female psychology, so...
An experiment regarding
female psychology?
He's supervising and even participating
in such an experiment?
How strange.
What did I do to deserve this?
I'm the one who was rendered
a fool by you two
so why are you treating me this way?
I don't get it.
I'll be excusing myself now.
He's both supervising and participating
in the experiment?
Currently, the experiment is in
quite a dangerous state.
Due to Subject A, which is me,
having acted brashly
the subject, Go Hye Rim,
has made a declaration of farewell.
If things keep progressing this way,
my hypothesis will not be proven true.
It's commonly said that a woman's "no"
is similar to her "yes".
However, that is completely false.
One must gauge the true meaning
behind a woman's words
while taking the circumstances
into account.
If that is the case, what are
Ms. Go Hye Rim's circumstances?
It's not because I'm mad, or your
jealously, or because I'm giving up.
It's just a sincere "no."
The fact that she said something
like that is a significant sign.
In reality, she could've said no because
she became angry and wanted to
trigger jealously in me to test me.
Therefore, rather than
making uncalculated moves
more data collection regarding the
subject takes precedence at this point.
Yes, Professor Choi.
Hello.
Yes, hello, Ms. Yoo Rim.
Are you available to talk right now?
I have something to ask you,
you see.
Ms. Hye Rim seems busy as of late.
Did something happen?
Oh... yes, but...
If it's something complicated,
you don't need to tell me.
But we're neighbors.
She's just busy because of work,
is all.
It's not easy to pay
for a child's tuition.
Oh, yes.
You studied abroad, right?
How much does it cost for a high school
student studying in London?
Well, things are
more expensive in London
so it'll probably be at least  2 million
won per month, not including tuition.
Why?
Oh... It's nothing.
Studying abroad in London?
Is she tight on funds
because of Do Kyung?
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
- Thank you! Goodbye!
- Yes! Goodbye!
Ms. Hye Rim.
How much is it
to rent this place out for a night?
Why?
What's the occasion?
I'm having a get-together with
some people I know
and I was thinking that I'd
like to have it here.
No.
Find somewhere else.
It'll be a small cocktail party.
About 3 million won
should cover it, right?
3 million won?
No... even 2 million won
would be more than enough.
Does it... cost more than that?
3.5 million, then?
I'm sorry, but I pick and choose
my customers.
Your guests aren't welcome here.
So, considering the factor that they're
my friends, I'll give you 4 million.
That's fine, right?
With that much, I could pay for 2 months
of Do Kyung's living expenses in London.
No. If I'm too greedy,
karma will bite me back later.
I don't know. If you're so desperate...
How about... 2.5 million?
You have to prepare canapes
and champagne, so won't you need more?
I don't have to prepare expensive
caviar or anything, right?
Then 2.5 million should be
more than enough.
Okay. Then it'll be 7 p.m. tonight.
I'll leave it to you.
Oh, yes.
A lot of my friends are
interested in fortune telling
so they will want their fortunes told.
That's okay, right?
Of course!
Welcome!
You're Professor Choi's guests, yes?
Right this way.
It's important to have an
"I can overcome anything" attitude.
Have strength.
You'll get through this.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Thank you. I'll use it for a good cause.
Yes.
Welcome!
I have someone
to introduce to all of you.
Please come here.
She's this cafe's owner
and a counselor at our center.
Please give a warm round of applause
for Ms. Go Hye Rim!
Sorry, we need more starters here.
Okay, wait.
- Sorry!
- Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Did you hurt your hand?
I'm fine. Don't act like you're helping
me, and go mingle with your guests.
No, you go and rest.
I'll clean up here.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you mingling?
I greeted everyone.
She's still a bit angry.
Do I have to use this trick up my sleeve?
Thank you.
You've worked hard today.
Keep up the good work, then.
At this rate, my tricks will backfire
and I'll end up falling for her.
I can't let myself be shaken up now.
I'm not done with my plan yet.
Have a good night.
Oh, hello Professor.
Did something happen at the cafe?
I had a get-together, so I
bought out the place tonight.
And it'd be better for Ms. Hye Rim
to get many customers at once
as opposed to getting them one at a time.
Wow, you're being way too considerate,
Professor!
No, that's not true.
Neighbors should help
each other out, after all.
What? Choi Soo Hyun did?
Yeah. I think he bought out the place
tonight for your sake.
Aren't you grateful?
I don't know if I should be grateful
or be even more suspicious.
All right... one, two, three!
Two, two, three!
Put some strength into it!
One, two, three!
Two, two, three!
All right.
One, two, three!
- Two, two, three!
- I'm sorry I'm so late!
There were a lot of materials
for me to organize.
It's fine. Are you sure
you're not too busy?
No! I made a promise, after all.
Did you decide on the machine
you want to work out on?
When you do, I'll help you learn the
exercises on it that are right for you.
That one.
You're doing well!
Just five more minutes, okay?
I can't... I can't do this.
I want to buy something else!
A bit faster!
If you really want a good workout,
you'll have to go faster than that.
Geez... I don't think I can do this.
My legs are shaking...
I think they're going to fall off!
Then do you want to have something
to eat first, Doctor?
Ta-da!
It's been three minutes!
Put this in too, and try it.
It tastes a lot better that way.
Oh my, so you could do that too, huh?
It's my first time
eating at a convenience store.
If you keep following me around, you'll
have a lot of interesting experiences.
Yeah... that'd be nice.
I feel like I'm young again!
But, Doctor...
You've never worked out before, right?
All you ever did was study, right?
Yes.
You can't do that! If you want to live
a long life, you have to work out.
Ah yes, of course.
I'm going to live a long life.
So teach me some easy
workout moves, okay?
There's no such thing, really...
Do you want to work out with me
every day, instead?
Really?
Starting tomorrow,
we'll go hiking at 7 a.m.
Don't forget, okay?
Sounds good.
Um... then... what can I do for you?
Is there anything that you want,
in particular?
Something I want, huh?
I'm not sure.
You?
Me... you... want to... have me?
Yes. Please be my mentor.
Both of my parents live abroad
and I quit baseball, so I have
nobody to really talk to.
And you know
how my brother's personality is.
I didn't know that you were so lonely.
I'm not lonely...
well, maybe a bit.
If you have any worries, tell me.
Is there something you're having
a hard time with?
What do you think about psychological
experiments, Doctor?
Well... I do believe they are necessary
if they are for the sake of research.
Why do you ask?
Actually... about Hye Rim...
she's a part of a psychology
experiment right now.
Doctor!
I made some cookies.
Would you like some?
Um... do you know where
Doctor Choi Soo Hyun is?
You made Ms. Go Hye Rim
a part of your experiment?
How dare you!
It's an experiment that was cleared
by the IRB, Doctor.
It's not even the real thing;
it's just the preliminary experiment.
Even so, how could you deceive
someone you work with like that?
Doctor.
Do you remember what I asked you
during my time as an undergrad?
You said that your "heart"
is actually your brain
but love is a wondrous and beautiful
emotion that transcends all science.
And I said that I don't believe love
to be that, but rather
a byproduct of irregular neural activity
within one's brain.
I do remember.
You kept arguing with me,
even after class was over.
That's the fundamental basis
of my experiment.
I still believe that love is nothing more
than a type of irregular neural activity.
But...
I keep having the thought that
that isn't all there is to it, somehow.
And as I worked on other experiments,
I kept becoming curious about this.
Could love be a form of insanity?
Or a divine entity's gift to humanity?
Love is something that I want
to study forever, as a psychologist.
And this experiment is like
the starting line, in a way.
Please understand where I'm coming
from as a fellow scientist, Doctor.
But... was there no other way than this?
This is an experiment that took me
a very long time to develop.
And what's your hypothesis?
There is no greater factor influencing
a woman's love than material goods.
Therefore, women do not truly love.
That's your hypothesis?
That's how you see women's love?
Considering my past experiences
and results, yes.
Do you want to receive a
consultation from me some time?
It's something I've always
thought about
but I think that you're
seriously deficient of something.
And women are somehow related to it...
what could it be?
Aren't you curious yourself?
What? My brother decided to be
Male Subject A again?
Yes. Maybe it's because of his break,
but he seems to be going all-out.
What do we do now?
This won't do.
We can't let him have Hye Rim.
You go and make sure that
he can't contact Go Hye Rim.
In the meantime, I'll be working on her.
Okay!
If anything else comes up,
please visit again! Goodbye.
Yes, goodbye.
Huh? What is it?
Want coffee?
Ta-da!
You like magic, right?
Want to go see a show with me tonight?
Hey, I secretly stole
Doctor Choi's cellphone...
A magic show?
I really do want to see it, but...
I'm really busy as of late.
You can work hard later.
I'll even help you out.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, coming!
You're coming with me, okay?
Your cellphone, Doctor.
Why do you have this?
Doctor. Seung Chan is going to see
a show with Ms. Hye Rim.
He's totally going all-out right now.
Where are they going, exactly?
A magic show.
Thank you.
I really wanted to see this.
Thanks, Seung Chan.
Oh, it's nothing.
Even so... you're always looking
out for me and helping me out.
Do you remember the first time
that you saw me?
Huh?
- Hey!
- Hello.
I'm Choi Seung Chan, and I'm
a new employee at the center.
I wanted to formally introduce myself.
Yeah. Of course.
You helped me with my laundry
back then, too.
And you went to the supermarket
with me, and helped me with the cafe.
And you even helped me out today, too.
I feel like you're the only one who
looks out for me when I need help.
I'm really grateful, Seung Chan.
No need for that.
I don't think it's a normal
magic show today.
I heard they're doing something special.
So there's been rumors that it'll be
even more special because of that.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It'd be cool if 50,000 won bills
fell from the ceiling or something.
You know when they ask for volunteers?
Let's both volunteer, okay?
What if they put me in a box
and cut me in half?
If it's something like that,
I'll go up instead...
Mr. Soo Hyun?
Brother...
How did you know...
I actually quite like magic.
It's funny to watch people be amused
by such obvious tricks.
The psychology behind people enjoying
being tricked is quite interesting.
Hye Rim.
Switch seats with me.
This is my assigned seat.
If you're a law-abiding citizen,
you should--
Whatever.
Hi there.
Want to link arms?
Thank you.
Are you all right?
N... no...
You look like you're not well.
If so, I could escort you...
No, that's fine.
Sorry for the trouble.
Don't worry.
Don't be so amazed.
It's really a simple trick.
The secret's in that fabric.
Once they lift it, he--
I never asked you.
Hello! I'm Magician Lee Sang Gook.
A lot of people are here today.
What was the name of my show again?
- Loveholic!
Yes, it's "Loveholic."
To tell you the truth,
today is a special day for me.
I'll be getting married soon.
Are you all right, ma'am?
And now, let me introduce
you to her...
my lovely fiancee.
First we have to check her breathing.
Please call an ambulance.
Hey. What are you doing?
Damn this girl...
she wore such tacky clothes.
But... where is this?
What is this place?
It's a magic show.
Are you feeling all right?
Geez... magic show.
This girl came all the way here?
So pathetic...
She drives me crazy!
Damn it...
What's with her, all of a sudden?
Is she crazy?
Ms. Yoo Sun. Do you remember me
picking up your phone for you before?
Yoo Sun, my butt...
I'm Emma.
I'm fine, so go about
your own business now.
Where's the exit?
Over there?
Ms. Yoo Sun, no...
I mean, Ms. Emma.
Does this happen often?
If you have some free time,
how about talking with me--
Who the hell are you?
What are you trying to do?
- I'm someone who can help people like--
- Don't mess with me!
You're trying to get rid of me.
No, I'm not.
I want you and Yoo Sun to
be able to live together peacefully...
We already are. So back the hell off
while I'm still saying it nicely, okay?
Are you really feeling all right?
I told you I'm fine!
What the hell is with you?
What was that?
Is she really crazy?
We'll have to do a detailed test
to be sure
but I think it's DID
(dissociative identity disorder).
What? DID?
That really exists?
Isn't that really serious?
Is it okay to send her off like that?
There's nothing we can do right now.
Her other personality
is dominating right now
so she'll think we're trying to
get rid of her no matter what we say.
Then, what do we do?
Just let her leave, like that?
We'll have to wait.
If we're lucky, Ms. Yoo Sun will wake up,
see my business card, and come see me.
And if not...
How was that?
Is this good enough?
It's perfect.
You're doing really well.
That's good.
Then Ms. Hye Rim will like it too, right?
You... still like my older sister?
Of course.
Then what am I to you?
You even kissed me instead of her!
Yes... isn't that what we agreed on?
Just plain smooches
and kisses are different, you know!
A kiss is the same as saying,
"I like you. Let's go out!"
You mean that this physical action
is the same as words?
You're studying psychology, and yet
you know nothing about people's hearts...
This is the first time that you've
visited the center in person.
I figured I should confirm that
everything is going smoothly here.
You left it in the hands of a pro,
so you should have more faith in me.
I know, but I've been backstabbed
many times before.
Oh, yes.
That woman who won't listen to you...
what does she do when you have clients?
Do you lock her up or something?
There's a dark cave
in the basement of this building.
I chain her up there
and only give her water.
And sometimes I beat her
with a whip.
Someone else might think
you were being serious!
How many people have you fixed
with consultations?
People aren't machines.
You don't "fix" them.
All I do is help people living irregular
lives live more regularly.
You sure are giving a complicated answer
to a simple question.
But even so, you've "fixed"
at least...
I mean, you've "helped people
live more regular lives," right?
Due to my values,
I can't answer that question.
There is no such person as a perfectly
normal person in this world--
But there should be some
symptoms they've had.
I'm asking you how many people's symptoms
were better when they left this place.
Is that so difficult to understand?
I don't know.
But I'm quite quick when it comes
to my diagnoses.
I see a couple of symptoms
in you right now.
You're displaying free-flowing anxiety,
agitation, and hints of anxiety disorder.
And it seems that you have a bit
of hypochondriasis, as well.
And of course, you definitely seem
to have narcissistic personality traits.
I also see some mood lability as well.
With all this difficult terminology
you're throwing at me
you really do seem like
a legitimate professor.
People's hearts are so cunning, right?
If you're so curious about the work I do,
why not get a consultation?
No, it's not for me...
Hey, let me ask you something.
What kind of disease
is dissociative disorder?
Is it that hard for them to act normal?
Why are you curious about that,
all of a sudden?
My friend's in-laws are concerned
with it, so I was curious.
There are many different kinds
of dissociative disorder.
Loss of memory type, fleeing type,
mood-changing type...
Anyway... is it something
that's really serious?
It depends on the situation,
but it is a serious condition.
It's something that develops
as a form of escaping severe pain
when reality becomes
too much to bear, after all.
Severe pain?
Yes, welcome!
Hello. This is the psychological
counseling center Madame Antoine, right?
Yes, it is.
This was in my bag, so...
[Choi Soo Hyun, Ph.D]
I passed out?
Yes. You don't remember any of it?
Oh... I wasn't really
in the right state of mind back then...
But... what happened at the magic show?
Did Sang Wook... I mean....
didn't the magician
announce something?
Yes, he did. He announced
that he'd be getting married.
Did you know him?
We were engaged once.
But one day, I suddenly
couldn't get in touch with him.
So I looked into it, and he
apparently left for England...
and then I suddenly heard
that he was getting married.
I couldn't believe it, so I felt like
I had to confirm it with my own eyes...
but I was too scared to go confront him.
So I went to his magic show...
I'm sorry.
Does Emma know about this?
You... met her?
Yes. But she seemed to really hate me.
Then I'm sure you're aware
of my condition, too.
Just the gist of it.
You've gotten treatment
for DID before, right?
Yes, in junior high school.
But I don't want to receive
treatment again.
I only came here to find out
what happened at the magic show.
Why don't you want
to receive treatment?
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I'll go pay the consultation fee.
No need for that,
but please tell me...
Geez! Ugh, I'm so tired,
I could die...
Can you meet me
where we kissed last time?
I have something to ask you about the
correlation between actions and words.
I'd have to be crazy to go!
Hey. This is our spot!
Piss off while I'm still
saying it nicely.
High schoolers shouldn't be smoking.
Who the hell is this jackass?
Do you need a beating to send you away,
or are you going to leave?
No. I have to meet someone here, so...
The hell are you looking at,
you bastard?
Hey, take his money since
you're beating him up anyway.
Sure.
Can you move?
I have business here.
So do we, all right?
Just go back.
Ji Ho!
You're not going to move?
Are you talking down to me?
Just piss off!
Hey.
Hey!
Ji Ho, are you okay?
I have a third-degree black belt
in Hapkido and Tae Kwon Do!
Excuse me! These high schoolers
are beating people up! Run!
Hey, you punks.
What are you doing?
Ji Ho! Are you okay?
Get up.
Are you okay?
Goodbye.
Can we have some band-aids
and ointment?
Do you want something
to calm your nerves, too?
You don't need to buy things like that.
I'm fine.
Please give us
a nerve-calmer, too.
How much is everything?
Ointment, 3,500 won. Band-aids,
2,500 won. Nerve-calmer, 5,000 won.
All together, that's 11,000.
You can't even do such easy math?
Why are you getting so mad?
I'm embarrassed.
I couldn't even protect a woman,
much less avoid getting myself beat up.
Woman? Am I a woman to you?
Are you a man, then?
Since when did you think of me
as a woman?
Yoo Rim. Are you really a third-degree
black belt in Hapkido and Tae Kwon Do?
No. Just in Hapkido.
Where are you going?
To learn Hapkido!
[Name: Lee Yoo Sun]
Hello?
- Is Ms. Yoo Sun...
- There's nobody like that here.
Hello?
Emma... I need someone
who can get along with Emma.
Someone who is sharp-witted
but can be sensitive.
Hello.
My name is Go Hye Rim.
If I just ask her to come with me,
she'll refuse.
Doctor. My phone died...
could I borrow yours?
Sure. But what is it?
Please enjoy!
I have to meet a client outside
of the office, but I need your help.
Could you come with me?
We're going to meet Dr. Bae
on the way. Get in.
You're going, too?
She's my client.
Of course. Let's go.
Yes, Doctor?
What? You can't make it?
I guess it can't be helped.
The two of us will go.
She said that something came up
and she can't come.
Liar.
You were lying
from the start, weren't you?
She wasn't coming from the start, right?
I guess you've caught me.
Well, you're free to think
as you please about it.
Let me off right now.
Is your project going well?
I'd like to contribute to the cause
for world peace, too.
You already know, though.
What do you mean?
Is there something you're hiding from me?
Since you're helping me with my work,
I want to help you.
How much would be enough?
Your stores earnings for one day?
No, give me double that.
But, who's this person we're meeting?
The person who passed out
at the magic show before.
The person with DID?
She came to the center?
Yes. Ms. Yoo Sun came to see me.
But Ms. Yoo Sun is skeptical
regarding the treatment.
I guess she doesn't really want
to get rid of Emma.
Then... how would it help
if she meets me?
You were hiding behind Seung Chan
at the magic show.
I'm sure she didn't get
a good look at your face.
Then give me three times
my daily earnings.
If I have to convince someone when I'm
not sure it'll be Yoo Sun or Emma...
- I think it's only fair--
- Just a second. I need gas.
Yes, here you are.
Goodbye.
Wait.
6,000 won is enough for a car wash!
Let's get your car washed!
I... don't do that myself.
I can tell Ji Ho to do that
for me later--
Is he your slave or something?
Also, these will expire tomorrow!
Come on, let's do it.
It'd be a shame to waste them.
The car isn't really that dirty...
Don't you see the rain stains
on your window?
Also, if you have 6,000 won
worth of tickets
You can get a car wash for 4,000 won
and spring for water and tissues, too!
Get your car washed
and get the free stuff too!
A thrifty life is a happy life!
What's the matter?
Do you have a water drop allergy,
or something like that?
It's not an allergy, but...
when I get hit by drops of liquid,
it's extremely painful.
But they're not really falling right now.
They're just falling outside.
Does that affect you too?
That's just how it feels.
That's why you made Ji Ho
get your car washed...
I'm sorry. I was being stubborn about
it, and now you're so uncomfortable.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
I'm sorry I told you to quit your job
as a counselor before.
Why... do you think I did that?
Because you grew to like me
way too much?
So you wanted to cut me out?
Yes.
I'm being honest with you.
People tend to become more honest
when they feel that their
lives are being threatened.
Do you think I'll forgive you
because of that?
It doesn't matter if you do or not.
I just wanted to tell you how I felt.
All right... we're done
getting a car wash
and I'm done making my difficult apology.
Let's go.
Who do you think will be there?
Yoo Sun? Emma?
There might be another
personality that comes out instead.
Really? Oh my goodness...
Be strong.
I'll give you more money.
I'll give you three times more than
your daily earnings.
Who is it?
Hello!
You're here again, you bastard?
How did you know my address?
Did Yoo Sun tell you?
First, please calm down...
Hello! I'm a representative
from a cosmetics company.
Oh my... you have such great skin!
But I see a few freckles.
If you cover it up with this,
they'll be gone in a flash!
You're not with him?
No. I don't know who he is.
If he's a problematic person,
want me to call the cops for you?
You can't just open your door
for people like him!
Something terrible could happen!
But first, take a look at these products!
You don't need to buy anything.
I'll just do your makeup and go.
Piss off while I'm being nice about it!
What are you doing?
Nothing, really.
I sold a lot already,
so this is all I have left, but...
I'll give you a special
70 percent discount.
Look. It's pretty, right?
But... you have such a cool
sense of style.
But... isn't this one used?
It's one that I carry around as a sample.
Come over here. I'll transform you
to suit your style.
How is it?
You like it a lot better, right?
You look a rock singer, right?
It's all right.
Want me to make you up, too?
How is it?
It's cool, right?
Wow, it's so cool!
Just use informal speech!
We're both getting old together anyway.
I feel like I'm getting
good vibes from you.
Want to go shopping with me?
I'll buy you makeup, too.
Okay!
Should we?
I'm clothes shopping with Emma.
What should I do now?
Was there anything unique at her place?
There were a lot of paintings.
I took a couple of photos.
Send those to me, and just become
closer to Emma for now.
And ask her about her relationship with
Yoo Sun when you get the chance.
All right, that's it!
How is it that your sense of style
is the same as mine?
I'll buy you this entire outfit.
Excuse me.
This, please.
Is it okay if you use all this money?
It's fine. It's actually my friend's card
but my money is hers,
and her money is mine.
Oh... do you live with her?
Yeah... a really quiet chick
named Yoo Sun.
Actually, she's kind of an outcast
and I'm the only friend she has
so she can't live without me.
But Ms. Yoo Sun is quite
skeptical about the treatment.
I guess she doesn't really
want to get rid of Emma.
Then... did your friend
paint the paintings in that room before?
Yeah, probably.
Hey, let's stop talking about
boring stuff and go shopping, already.
I met Ms. Yoo Sun while I was
publishing a book three years ago.
She was the illustrator, but her
drawings were so good
so I started seeing her more often.
Eventually, we started dating.
I heard that you two
really loved each other.
So what broke you two up?
She came to see me
and broke up with me out of nowhere.
What reason do you need?
I've just grown to dislike you!
Ms. Yoo Sun! Even up until the
day before yesterday, we were fine...
so why are you acting this way now?
I didn't really like you,
I just tolerated it up until now.
So get what I'm saying through
your thick skull, and piss off.
If you don't, I'll report you
to the police as a stalker!
It was way too strange.
It was as if she had suddenly changed.
I kept on going to her place,
but she wouldn't see me.
It was Emma. It wasn't Yoo Sun
who asked to break up, but Emma.
So I decided to go study abroad.
I'd originally planned to go
with Ms. Yoo Sun, but...
So that's how it was. She talked as if
she was really close to Yoo Sun.
So did Emma dump the magician
out of jealousy
because she didn't want to lose Yoo Sun?
Yes. It seems that way.
But... did you get a bit more
friendly with Emma?
Yes. A lot.
She's quite liberal when it comes to...
[Incoming call: Choi Seung Chan]
Oh my. Seung Chan is calling.
I'll talk to you later.
Yeah, Seung Chan?
What's up?
Go Hye Rim!
Are you good at drawing?
What are you doing?
You're here?
First, put this on.
This spot is where my kids rest
while playing baseball
but the wall is too blank, so I wanted
to draw something pretty here.
I even got permission from the principal.
Want to draw with me?
Really?
I can draw whatever I want?
Hey!
What the hell!
- Get over here!
- Oh no!
Hey, stop it!
It's pretty.
I'm sure it'll look even cooler
during the daytime.
Huh?
What's that?
I don't know.
What could it be?
[I like you]
That's some great lettering, isn't it?
I was going to draw your face too
but I was afraid my kids would see
and be like, "it's a witch!" so I didn't.
Seung Chan.
You don't need to give me
a reply right now.
I just... felt like I couldn't
keep it inside anymore.
So I let it out, is all.
All right. Shall we go, then?
Hey, you're not going
to erase that?
It's not like I specified who it is,
so why does it matter?
You're going to get in trouble for
writing nonsense on the wall!
That's my problem, not yours.
Hey, what if you get fired?
Who'd fire the Rookie of the Year?
- Wow.
- It's so pretty!
I wonder who drew this?
- Wow, so pretty!
- Wow! I wonder who drew this?
- It's pretty, right?
- Yeah.
You're positive?
Seung Chan really wrote this
and showed Ms. Hye Rim?
I'm telling you, yes!
I even saw him bring
the spray paint in yesterday.
He's such a terrible guy.
He always uses me and then does
this kind of stuff in the meantime...
His tactics are way too immature.
Is he a kid? Vandalizing walls...
Right?
Should we erase it with this?
Where is he right now?
What, I'm not allowed
to write on things?
I even got permission from the principal.
So what?
What did Ms. Go Hye Rim say?
Why do I have to answer that?
You're my competitor!
I'm asking right now as the
supervisor of this experiment.
What did she say?
Was it a yes, or no?
Hmm... a tentative yes?
When she saw the writing,
she laughed like this.
Isn't it over at this point?
Game, set.
Where is Ms. Go Hye Rim?
She went out to meet someone.
And she told me to give this
to you if you came by.
I got a call from Emma,
so I'm going to meet her.
It's my second time seeing her so you'll
give me double my daily earnings, right?
Ta-da!
Awesome!
You look so cool!
If we both got these,
I bet people would think we were twins.
Should we start a band together?
It's so fun to have met a friend like you
after hanging out with
Yoo Sun all the time.
Me too.
But, about your friend, Yoo Sun...
it seems like she's
really good at drawing.
Yeah, she's an illustrator.
She's so quiet that she never goes out
and just draws all day.
Yoo Sun was a very quiet child.
She didn't talk much and was really shy.
It might be because she was in an
accident when she was young.
An accident?
When she was in first grade,
her family went to a river
but there was an accident there.
Yoo Sun fell into the water,
and her father died trying to save her.
Oh... so that's why she painted
a picture of a river.
When Yoo Sun was young, water-related
accident occurred; father passed away.
So the people who passed
away back then...
Were her mother and father.
Her mother, too?
Yes. Her father was swept away
by the waves
and her mother managed to save Yoo Sun
but didn't have any more strength
so she drowned.
Have you been well, my daughter?
Yes, Mom.
So Ms. Yoo Sun's only friend is Emma.
It's different from other cases since
the personalities are coexisting well.
It won't be easy.
Wasn't Emma the one who made
Yoo Sun break up with the magician?
If Yoo Sun knew that,
wouldn't that make things different?
You'll have to tread with caution
with that, though.
Right now, Ms. Yoo Sun considers Emma
her closest friend.
At any rate, good work.
No, not really.
I got to have a great time with Emma
thanks to all this.
Things are busy at the cafe,
so I have to go.
Can you tell Mr. Soo Hyun
about the situation?
Of course.
Oh, yes... Ms. Hye Rim.
Actually, Hye Rim is a part of a
psychological experiment right now.
Did Professor Choi, by any chance...
ask you to be a part of an experiment?
Yes. Something about ideal types.
Why?
Did you agree to do it?
I'm already a part of it.
Why, Doctor?
Do you know something about it?
Actually, that is...
I'm sorry I'm late.
Ms. Hye Rim, you said
that you had to go, right?
Go ahead.
I'll tell Professor Choi
about Ms. Yoo Sun.
Okay...
Ji Ho. I'm going clothes shopping.
Want to come with me?
Yes.
How is it?
Which one suits me more?
Both of them. You look good
no matter what you wear.
Then I'll try on both.
Say "ah!"
But, Ms. Hye Rim... why are you
being so nice to me today?
Don't think about it too hard.
Does there need to be a
reason to eat and hang out?
Just enjoy it.
Say "ah!"
Wow! Our Ji Ho is so good
at drinking, too!
Yes. I'm good at everything that doesn't
require physical exertion.
Since we're drinking,
want to play the Truth Game?
Okay. Ask me anything.
Don't think too hard
and answer right away.
- What's your height?
- 185 centimeters.
- Weight?
- 65 kilograms.
- Favorite color?
- Blue.
- Jjajjangmyun or jjamppong?
- Jjamppong!
- Favorite season?
- Autumn!
The title of the experiment
being done on me?
Madame Antoine.
I thought it was one
based on ideal types.
That's just what we call it,
among us.
The real title is too long, so...
What's so long about saying
"ideal type experiment?"
Um... even so...
Your cafe's name is Madame Antoine
and that's the center's name, too, so...
So you're saying that the experiment's
name is Madame Antoine, huh?
And what are the details
of the experiment, then?
You already know.
The relationship between your ideal type
and your immune system...
I need to use the bathroom.
Ji Ho!
Hey, Won Ji Ho!
Ms. Hye Rim.
Can you tell me my fortune?
Yes.
Of course.
Madame Antoine.
Did Professor Choi, by any chance...
ask you to be a part of an experiment?
Actually, that is...
I'm asking you this as the
supervisor of the experiment.
What did she say?
Was it yes, or no?
A tentative yes?
When she saw the writing,
she laughed like this.
So I heard Seung Chan confessed to you.
Confessed?
Well, I don't know.
Does that count as a confession?
I don't know.
But what does that have to do with you?
What was your reply?
- What did Seung Chan tell you?
- He said that he was rejected.
Why is it that only lies
ever come out of your mouth?
I have good feelings toward him
and not so much toward you. Satisfied?
Are you saying that you like him
more than you like me?
What can I do about the fact
that I can't trust you?
I already apologized to you!
Did you think that everything
would be fine with just that?
All of your words and actions
are suspicious to me!
You have a supernatural
sense of perception, right?
Here. Scan me all over
with that sense of yours.
Dig out what's so
suspicious about me, then.
Is there anyone in the bathroom stall
next to me? (in French)
There isn't any toilet paper here.
(in French)
Can someone give me some toilet paper?
All I have is my sock!
(in French)
What did Marie Antoinette say?
Did she say that she'd bring you
toilet paper?
She told me that you're doing an
experiment called "Madame" Antoine on me.
It's an experiment where
three men are made to approach a woman
to see who she'll fall in love with
and this is currently the second
preliminary version of this experiment.
The participants are Seung Chan,
Ji Ho, and you.
And you're supervising the experiment
while taking part in it.
It's incredible, isn't it?
But it seems that you've
come across an issue.
You've begun to actually like me.
The supervisor is supposed to be
completely impartial and unbiased
but that has become impossible now.
So you, Mr. Choi Soo Hyun,
who became flustered
told me that you'd see me
and then said you wouldn't.
Then you told me to quit my job
as a counselor at the center
and then took back what you said.
What a mess this all is.
Right?
Tell me it isn't true.
Tell me that you didn't pretend to
like me because of the experiment
but that you actually really liked me.
You're not saying anything.
All right. Don't even think
of talking to me ever again.
You really...
are a fortune teller.
But you're only half right.
What are you talking about?
So you're not doing a terrible
experiment on me?
No...
I like you.
Subtitles by DramaFever
What are you trying to do, exactly?
I'll stop that experiment right now.
Then... we're actually dating now, right?
Should I reciprocate his kiss
this time, or not?
Please get rid of Emma.
Now, you will reawaken as Emma.
You want me to disappear, too?
You won't disappear.
I'll remember you.
Go Hye Rim!
Go ahead and try confessing.
I can never see you
as a man.
What's the matter, Mr. Soo Hyun?
What happened?
I remembered the time I was
separated from my mother.
Is there any way I can help?
Can't you see that
I'm working right now?
Good luck!
I'd like it if you would
just leave me alone.
I think Ms. Go Hye Rim heard
while I was counseling you.
The human being, Choi Soo Hyun
must now dominate
Male Subject A Choi Soo Hyun.
I love you, Ms. Hye Rim.