(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 11)
(ID card: Kim Gil Do)
Kim Gil Do?
How do you know this name?
Don't say that name...
ever again.
What if I keep talking about the name?
You!
It wasn't a lie?
It's his real name.
Mum?
Mum.
I will be there soon.
This is just between the two of us.
Don't tell anyone.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
And Ms Ko told me to keep an eye on Da Hae.
I'm being a spy for both you and Ms Ko.
Figure out what Ms Ko knows about Da Hae.
By the way,
when will you crush Ha Jung Tae?
Remember that I've been working here...
for the past 10 years to finish him off.
It already began.
We are almost there.
Do your best.
If you don't do it right,
I will make you regret it.
(DNA Parentage Test Report)
Kim Da Hae is...
Ha Jung Tae's daughter.
But it is a secret that no one should find out.
Did she try so hard to come to Goongnakwon...
because of this?
Or is there another reason?
Why did you want to see me?
It's not like there must be a reason.
It's been a while since we met.
I thought we saw each other for a reason.
Do you know how many cheques have been issued...
with a false issue number?
It's been taken care of at our branch so far.
I'm not sure if you remember that.
I paid you for that.
By the way,
did I tell you that my son is going abroad to study?
It costs a lot.
It cost as much as an annual salary of a manager in a major company.
And the plane ticket is very expensive.
I didn't mean to tell you that.
It's hard to live your life as a breadwinner.
Don't you think?
Mr Park will be in the car park. Give this to him.
What is this?
Don't ask questions. Just do as you are told.
Yes, Sir.
Are you Mr Park?
What took you so long?
My goodness, how cheap of him.
Why does he have my mum's picture?
Why does he have the keepsake from my mother?
He abandoned us.
He's the one who made us tremble with anger.
Are you all right?
You are not supposed to be here.
I was just...
Do you want me to shout?
Actually, I work here.
I'm a driver.
Only kitchen staff are allowed in here.
Sorry.
Wait.
I'm done crying.
Oh, okay.
You said you're a driver. Who do you drive?
Mr Ha.
Okay. You can go.
I wasn't going to say this, but I must.
You have flour under your eye.
Stand still.
There.
I'll go now.
I told you all my secrets.
It's all over if they find out we're from the same orphanage.
What are you doing here when you know that?
Before I went to prison,
I thought I just had to do my time and start over.
But now that I'm out,
I feel worse than when I was inside.
I was flailing in a swamp I couldn't get out of,
and I got sick of it.
I'm here for myself.
I want to be acknowledged by whoever needs me and succeed.
- That's all.
-  You don't mean that.
I know you.
You wouldn't do something like this for yourself.
Tae Ha.
You don't know me.
Just like how I don't know you.
Do you know what I regret the most?
Going to prison instead of Yeo Kyung.
What you just said...
Do you mean it?
I meant everything I said.
I've changed, Myeong.
Just like you have.
(ID card: Kim Gil Do)
(Photos saved)
I gave it to Mr Park.
Unless I give you a job,
watch labourer Kim Da Hae.
Do you mean, I should protect her?
Just keep an eye on her.
Do not let her come into my office.
Yes, Sir.
I mentioned the matter to my husband already.
I invited you over to ask for your opinion.
About what?
I'm going to promote Kim Da Hae to join the noodle department.
You can't.
I said it's too soon.
How strange.
The ice-cold man gets all worked up whenever I mention her.
Is there a reason?
Ever since Myeong solved the broth problem,
sales have been soaring.
I don't see why Da Hae can't do the same.
What do you say?
Nothing is more entertaining than watching a fight.
But I've seen you two fight so often. It's almost boring.
You asked for my opinion, so I'll give it to you.
I'm all for it.
Speak up if you will.
But the decision will remain the same.
You are making a mistake.
I thought...
it could be a mistake.
But your reaction tells me...
that it's not, after all.
Noodle department, Kim Da Hae.
Yes?
Did you just say "noodle department"?
Of all the labourers who worked in our kitchen,
you were the best.
I bet everyone will agree. Well done.
Go to Mr Ha's office. He'll give you a new name-tag.
Thank you.
Noodle department, Kim Da Hae.
It's like a ceremony.
I affix all the name-tags on our workers.
And I'm the one to take them off.
I hope...
I won't have to take this off.
Kim Gil Do.
Is that your real name?
Don't go too far.
My office is fine.
(Kim Da Hae, Noodle Team)
My mum.
Did you love her?
But not the secret room.
Stay away.
Kim Da Hae.
Congratulations.
You climbed up a stage.
Keep climbing.
Show him.
Thank you.
We should celebrate over a drink.
You know I can't drink.
Oh, yes. I remember now.
You passed out after two cups, right?
One cup.
I was out by the second.
You have something for me.
There's a safe in the wall.
I couldn't open it because of the passcode.
It's more dangerous than I thought.
What do you mean?
You don't have to know. Are there any other photos?
Mr Ha almost caught me.
That's all I was able to take.
Can I trust you?
You don't trust anyone.
Doubting is your hobby.
Okay, I'll trust you this time.
But I expect something more detailed next time.
It's too hard. I might get caught.
Don't get caught.
Goongnak Foundation and a safe for the cash.
I can think of only one thing.
Money laundering.
I knew he was up to something, but I wasn't expecting this.
Nothing works like money when trying to make connections.
Especially dirty money.
They won't turn against each other that easily.
As soon as one does, they both perish.
That's it.
I don't want to expose Goongnakwon to such dangers.
I feel the same way.
Let's find a solution.
That's enough for today.
Da Hae...
got promoted.
Whose idea was it?
It was Ms Ko's. I just went along with it.
What's her logic?
I guess she thinks Da Hae's loyal to her. Although she's mistaken.
The chefs...
have to be in the kitchen at all times.
- Naturally.
-  Then she can't see the old man.
She has no excuse to be anywhere else.
She had Da Hae promoted...
so she can't go to the other building.
It can't be.
That means something's going on.
Something no one can know about.
You won't have time to come here.
I wanted to thank you.
I owe you for the promotion.
I didn't get to congratulate you properly.
It's all you. I didn't do anything.
It was a unanimous decision, so that means you did well.
Did no one object?
Even Mr Ha acknowledged you.
So...
how is your father?
He won't even blink for me.
Da Hae.
The only person I can trust in Goongnakwon...
is you.
You're the only one I can tell how I really feel.
I sometimes wonder how nice it would be...
if you were my daughter.
I worry how I'd feel...
if you let me down after trusting you so much.
But then again, we can't control our emotions, can we?
That won't happen.
Do you mean that?
Can you promise?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hearing that melts my heart.
Excuse me.
Yes, Sir?
Sir.
He said the noodles are soft and that they fall apart.
It's the third time today.
Okay.
Apologise to the customer.
We'll serve a fresh bowl.
Yes, Sir.
What's wrong?
The bittern's different.
Compare it.
It lacks sodium.
What's the matter?
The bittern's salt concentration is different.
Today's supply is weaker.
It was watered down.
The glutinosity of flour drops on humid days.
That plus the weaker bittern explains the noodles' texture.
The bittern is a serious problem.
A restaurant like this should be making your own supply.
That takes a lot of time and effort.
Dose that mean...
we should give up?
It should be spot in the sun, but with no direct sunlight.
This spot should do it.
Put that there.
First, put the sack of bay salt on top of the crock.
This is common practice.
Even I can do this.
Do you know about adding Chinese yam powder?
Chinese yam powder?
That increases the stickiness of the dough.
For every bowl of bittern, one tablespoonful should do.
This is how I make bittern.
It sounds like a secret recipe.
Why are you sharing it?
So that we can make better noodles.
Do I need another reason?
Very well. Let's give it a go.
But if it fails, we're going to give up.
Sir.
We can use shrimp eggs instead when making wheat vermicelli.
It improves the stickiness and texture.
I've been making dough for 15 years.
I've never heard of anyone using shrimp eggs...
instead of bittern.
Just because you haven't heard of it doesn't mean it doesn't exist.
I've tried it.
It's delicious.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Okay, then. Let's try both.
I'm willing to try anything.
Something's bound to work.
I've never heard of the shrimp egg technique.
Didn't you tell me not to talk to you?
Noodles are an exception.
I don't know much about noodles.
I hadn't tasted many kinds, and no one taught me.
So I gave anything a go.
I got lucky with the shrimp eggs.
It was really delicious.
The shrimp egg flavour fills your mouth with each mouthful.
It would be perfect with beef brisket broth.
How do you know that?
A mix of beef and fish broth was the best combination.
- The ratio was...
-  Was it 5 to 1?
Hey.
- Isn't it odd?
-  What is?
We lose track of time talking about noodles.
You're right.
Try your best...
to survive the hazing.
I could do with a break.
It's nice.
Especially the shrimp egg noodles.
I like the flavour and clean aftertaste.
I didn't know you were so imaginative.
Did you happen to add Chinese yam powder...
to the bittern?
Yes.
It improves the dough.
That's the bittern...
Chimyeon Restaurant used in the past.
Not any more, though.
It really does improve the noodles' texture and flavour.
Did you decide to take out the powder?
We had to keep up with the demands.
I quite liked...
the shrimp egg noodles.
Are you trying to get promoted?
Well done.
Sales are going up again.
I see you...
in a different light now.
You can leave.
The Chinese yam powder in the bittern...
was Myeong's idea.
The shrimp egg noodles was Da Hae's suggestion.
I can't take the credit.
All I did was prevent their creative ideas from being ignored.
You're a hardhead.
You're very stubborn.
I apologise.
It's a compliment.
You could have taken all the credit,
but instead you told the truth.
That's not easy.
You can leave.
Thank you.
I think we can promote him.
He seems to have the respect of his team,
although he lacks the skill.
He can make up for that through leadership.
What do you think?
There's no need to rush.
You waited this long. Put it off a little longer.
Is this about Myeong?
Wake up.
Even if he becomes the head, that doesn't make Goongnakwon yours.
How interesting.
It sounds offensive,
but it makes me want to give it a shot.
Sales are rising because Myeong solved the broth problem.
He is well qualified. No, he's more than qualified.
He just recently joined the noodle team.
Now you want him to be the head?
Things don't go that easily in Goongnakwon.
The Moon family will...
make an issue out of it.
That family likes people who brings in money.
Don't you know that already?
Let's think about it.
That's enough...
for today.
No.
Since she brought this up, I'd like to finalise the issue.
Deputy Head of Noodles and Moo Myeong...
Let's make them compete for Head of Noodles.
Don't be ridiculous.
You startled me. Why is it ridiculous?
If you keep rejecting, I will have the Moon family interfere.
You have only three months left. Let's wait and see how it goes.
Do you really want to do this?
I will make a formal suggestion for the competition.
I know Ms Ko will go against the idea.
So it depends on you.
Please give me some time to consider it carefully.
I will tell you tomorrow.
Ma'am.
Da Hae. Go bring Deputy Head of Noodles to me.
Deputy Head of Noodles is in Mr Ha's office now.
What?
A competition for Head of Noodles?
Moo Myeong will compete against you.
He just joined noodle department.
I've been Deputy Head of Noodles for five years.
If you give up,
you will be Deputy Head of Noodles for 10 years.
It is your call.
Listen.
I will let you...
win the competition.
You will never lose the competition.
But...
you have to promise me that you will be my person.
I will play fair and square.
I don't want to be dishonest.
You are too inflexible.
You are stubborn.
This is not a compliment.
If Moo Myeong becomes Head of Noodles, you will have to resign.
Do you want the past 15 years to come to nothing?
Play fair and square.
You won't lose.
I'm just...
being supportive.
I'm not rejecting...
to be your person.
But I don't want to be Head of Noodles with your support.
If I do, the past 15 years will come to nothing.
I may not be good enough,
but I want to do it on my own.
Don't you get it?
If you become my person,
I will make you become Head of Noodles.
If you reject,
I will make you leave Goongnakwon for good.
Your eyes will tire out. Take it easy for a while.
We ransacked a private loan company. But the accounting is perfect.
No unlawful connections.
No circumstantial evidence for illegal contract.
Take a look at this.
16 people got arrested for illegal gambling.
Small business owners, lawyers and bank managers are involved.
What is this?
That bank manager works at Naegok branch of Gwangmyeong Bank.
The bank manager bet 480 thousand dollars.
And he had a few cheques.
Do you know whose name was used to issue the cheques?
Goongnakwon?
You just got lucky.
Who do you want to summon first?
For running an illegal gambling place,
they arrested Mr Yoon who was in charge on May 31.
Among the 16 people who are involved,
there was a bank manager, a national athlete...
Did you know Mr Park was gambling?
I was not interested in his private life.
Did you ever give him money without me knowing?
He whined about his son studying abroad,
so I gave him some money.
Oh, my goodness.
We will be examined by the prosecution. What should we do?
Goongnak Foundation is on a tight budget.
If they find out, all the money will disappear.
Why are you being so cowardly? I didn't think you were like that.
What?
It's not that I'm being cowardly.
It's that you are being too bold.
Do you want to know how to be bold?
I know.
I didn't know he gambled.
What are you talking about?
Just come and have some coffee with me.
The prosecutor in charge is newly appointed.
I will take care of it.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, then.
I will go have some coffee with you soon.
Okay.
How many times did I tell you?
Don't worry about it.
Just mind your business.
You see,
there will be search and confiscation.
They will desperately try to find your fault.
How can I not get worried?
You may be able to make Mr Park not speak about it.
But what about Mr Choi?
There will be no way out when the prosecutor starts investigating.
That won't happen.
If it does,
I will stop it.
I will take care of it.
Are you busy?
No.
Come see me out.
Is everything okay?
I'm just driving.
If you just drive, there will be no problem.
Oh, no.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Should I pretend not to know him like this?
Yes.
That's easy.
Tae Ha.
Listen carefully.
Mr Ha and I are already in a pile of mess.
There is no way out for us.
Do you know how people who are in a mess...
make friends?
They involve...
their friends in the mess.
Mr Ha will give you a job soon.
If you want to do it, make sure to do it right.
If not, you should quit immediately.
I'm telling you again.
You can't hesitate...
even for a second. Do you understand?
I'm not going to look back.
That's why I'm worried about you.
You should look back from time to time.
You are not a turtle. You should look back sometimes.
You failed to protect my father.
But I will protect my friends no matter what.
Your friends?
You have other friends?
You must be busy.
Are you a honeybee or what?
(Mr Ha)
Yes, Sir.
I will be right there.
Where would you like to go, Sir?
To Seoul Central District Prosecutor's Office.
I'm sorry, sir?
Why?
Do you have a problem going there?
No, Sir.
Why do you need to go the prosecutor's office?
I'm sorry.
It's all right. You can ask that much.
I'm going to get some coffee.
I see.
Hello, Mr Ko.
I heard Ha Jung Tae was summoned.
I tossed the ball.
She's good at hitting them right into court.
Mr Ko, listen to me carefully.
Do not take a part in this case.
Just watch.
I want to see how well Ms Chae takes care of this.
You know how I am.
When I want to make use of someone,
I make sure I use them fully.
Is Mr Park still keeping his silence?
He's just killing time. I think he has some connections.
He said that he borrowed the money, but he won't say from whom.
We'll have to meet his connection.
Also, summon Mr Choi, who works for Mr Park.
We'll find out something if we ask the right questions.
Ms Chae's office.
Yes, Chief.
Yes, Sir.
Ms Chae, it's the chief.
(Chief Prosecutor's office)
Hello, Chief.
Hello, Mr Ahn.
Welcome, Ms Chae. Introduce yourself.
This is Mr Ha of Goongnakwon.
This is the prosecutor in charge.
Nice to meet you. I'm Ha Jung Tae.
I am Chae Yeo Kyung.
Take a seat.
I'm sorry, but I'm not allowed to speak in private with...
Nonsense.
Are you saying that the chief privately called you here?
That's not what I'm saying.
But I don't think this is reasonable.
Ms Chae, no one asked for your opinion.
I just said what's wrong is wrong. Do I need to get scolded for that?
Hey!
You can leave. I don't want to be misunderstood.
I'm sorry if I was impolite.
My goodness. She must be out of her mind.
This doesn't seem like a place for a cup of coffee.
Today's last order is cheongmyeon.
It's our tradition to let the person in charge...
make the last order of their first day.
Can you do it?
Oh, well...
You must be talking about the dish made by...
mixing mung bean powder and water. You sift it through a thin cloth...
and cook in a double boiler and serve it cold with omija tea.
Is that the right?
It is.
Da Hae, can you make it?
Yes.
- Take it.
-  Okay.
Let's call it a day. Good job, everyone.
Great job.
What's with you?
You were cold, then you became nice again.
What's the real you?
You're starting this again.
You should thank me first.
Oh, sure. Thanks.
I'm really thankful.
I'm so used to living alone,
so I feel thankful whenever I am treated nicely.
I was going to be strong here.
I shouldn't let my guard down.
Don't worry. You're doing fine.
I'm sure...
your father will be proud, too.
Let's not talk about that.
Didn't you tell your parents about getting promoted?
Stop it.
I'm sorry. I was really busy.
It's all right.
Aren't you hungry?
I am. I haven't had anything to eat.
I am not hungry.
You do understand that there were Goongnakwon's cheques...
among the cheques used by Mr Park when he gambled, right?
My friend once had...
a lighter from a club in Jeju Island.
But he's never been there.
If even lighters can cross the ocean,
why not a cheque?
Isn't it an abuse of authority to summon someone like me...
for an incident like this?
I caught the tail. So at least let me see what the body looks like.
And it's not an abuse of authority. I'm just doing my job.
When did you last meet Mr Park?
The last time was...
I'm not sure what you mean by the last time,
but frankly, I do not remember.
It's been so long.
This will take a while.
This will end late at night. You should call home and say,
"I'm not at a bar, so don't nag at me."
Is there another reason why you're doing this?
There is.
Don't ever think about using your connections again.
Next time you do, I will break off that connection for good.
Wow, you're scary.
I just got the chills.
I guess people really do rise up from a humble family.
You got all the way here from an orphanage.
Do you want to make a bet?
Ms Chae, you'll be removed from this case as of today.
So don't make this hard on me.
A prosecutor is...
an independent government administrative office.
You can't get to me.
I could get to a first-year prosecutor...
as much as I wanted to even 10 years ago.
Even someone like me.
Go to Ahyeon-dong.
- Mr Ahn.
-  Recite...
the principle of uniformity.
Why do you want...
Recite it!
All prosecutors must obey prosecutors in a higher office...
with the Public Prosecutor General as the top office,
and all must work in uniformity.
Forget about this case,
and wait for another one.
I can't do that.
What?
I will investigate more into the cheques,
and I will also summon Mr Choi, who works for Mr Park.
Also, I will bring in Mr Ha for a second questioning...
Are you...
insane?
I'm glad...
you figured it out.
The chief said that...
I am a perfect candidate to work in this special branch...
because I have zero connections.
I should live up...
to his expectations.
Zero connections?
I know that you got here with your connections.
Who are you trying to fool?
Please take back what you said.
Remember this.
No matter how good your connection is,
no one can say anything about the orders of this institution.
Once the orders get destroyed, so will the institution.
You can try as much as you'd like.
Let's see what'll happen to you.
I will show you myself.
Don't ask a thing,
and jump right out when I tell you.
I already made the decision.
So don't make any decisions of your own.
Let me tell you again.
If you hesitate even for a second,
you'll be done with.
Do you understand?
It's what he gets for his beating.
I shut his mouth with a beating,
and I stop him...
from talking with money.
This is my way.
Make sure you beat him...
just until he can barely walk back home.
Go.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Oh my gosh.
Don't do this.
Spare me.
I'll give you anything you want.
Let's go.
I want to be left alone.
Just leave me.
Didn't you hear me?
Go away.
I didn't hear you.
So try screaming louder.
Get out of here!
Louder.
I can smell oil,
blood...
and...
old letters.
It smells like a piece of memory.
Thankfully, it still smells much stronger than the bad smells.
If I were you,
I'd quit before it gets worse.
Thank you.
Do you always hold girls' hands like this?
Do you always get away with this?
Cheer up.
(To Park Tae Ha)
I will hold a contest in the noodles department.
Your opponent will be Deputy Head of Noodles.
It's impossible for you to become the head without a contest.
I'm sure you can definitely win against Deputy Head of Noodles.
How does it sound? Don't you think it's fair?
I accept.
You will begin appearing on TV shows...
after you become Head of Noodles.
All right, it's my turn now.
When can I meet...
Congressman So Tae Seop?
Declare...
the contest first.
I always...
keep my promises no matter what happens.
My promise to let someone live,
and my promise to kill, too.
How does tonight sound?
(Top Secret)
(Defence Industry Corruption)
Mr Choi...
got admitted to the hospital.
He said he fell down the stairs, but I doubt that.
So he can't come in for questioning?
- That's right.
-  What happens if...
I go on investigating...
a case I was told to close and ignore?
You'll be suspended and disciplined for insubordination at least.
Also, it'll be difficult for you to survive in the organisation.
- What else?
-  You might lose us, your staff.
And I'll probably waste my work hours away without a single case.
Or you could end up with dozens of cases a day.
Either way, you won't be able to survive.
I want some noodles.
What about you?
You know how crazy I am about noodles.
Hello, Sir.
Hey.
You were born to make noodles.
You look very nice.
Come inside.
Are you involved in any social movements?
Do whatever you want. Beat him up if you have to.
If you fail, I'll kill you.
Nice to meet you, Sir. I'm Ha Jung Tae.
I'm So Tae Seop.
Come with me.
A table for two? Come this way, please.
Forget the noodles. Get Mr Ha.
It's an honour to meet you.
It's an honour for me. I got to meet a famous chef.
Tae Ha, see what the problem is.
(Master of Revenge)
You know nothing.
You saw nothing.
My gut tells me that you're hiding something.
You always did anything I asked.
Quit working there.
Don't say you saw me.
It's best if we ignore each other.
Find out about Kim Gil Do.
You'll learn more about Ha Jung Tae.
It really exists.
In small amounts, it's a medicine.
In large amounts, it's a neurotoxin.
The old man.
Ha Jung Tae. Do you know why I'm here?