(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 12)
When you are faced with a monster,
you shouldn't express your true intentions.
If you express your desire,
it will take advantage of your desire.
If you expose your weakness,
it will pounce on that weakness.
Take your time and don't throw yourself.
Hide and pretend not to know.
You must hide your claws...
as if you've never met him before.
This is how monsters fight against each other.
This is how...
monsters fight...
against each other.
I asked for Mr Ha.
Who are you?
I'm his personal assistant.
How can I help you?
I need to ask him a few questions for the investigation. It is simple.
He doesn't need to hide.
He is having an important meeting.
He isn't hiding.
Bring him here, right now.
Do you have a warrant?
You can't meet him without a summons or an arrest warrant.
A request for him to accompany you will be rejected as well.
You should know that you are interrupting the business.
Please leave.
You said you found a job you liked.
You said...
you'd buy a heavy vehicle and operate it.
Is this why...
you told me to drop the case?
To work at Goongnakwon?
To become Mr Ha's personal assistant?
Is that why?
Tell me.
Why are you here?
You are the one who told me that he was a dangerous person.
- Yeo Kyung.
-  Tae Ha.
What are you doing? Why are you lying?
Right now, you won't believe anything I say.
There's a reason I had to work here.
And I can't leave now.
What is that reason?
Someone dragged you in here. Why can't you tell me?
You can't manage.
He's not someone you can take on alone.
Sometimes you have to fight, knowing you will lose.
You won't just lose. You could end up dead!
Thanks for the advice.
Don't come here again.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Tae Ha.
You...
always did everything I asked.
Do me one last favour.
Quit working here.
I didn't do anything for you.
It was the debt.
The debt I owed you for what my father did.
I think I paid it in full.
I guess you disagree.
Yes.
The debt.
That debt.
It's still as huge as a mountain.
You aren't done paying me back.
Mr Ha got to where he is...
by committing crimes.
If you work for him, you'll have to do bad things.
I did nothing wrong.
You know that.
Go.
Let's not meet like this again.
If you leave like this,
we're done being friends.
Skipping one meal...
is all it takes to feel hunger.
And air?
It's hard to last over a minute without it.
Friends?
I didn't see mine for six years,
and it wasn't too bad.
Friends...
mean less than you think.
Go.
Why did you want to see me so badly?
You move our country.
I've respected you for a while now.
Nonsense.
If our country was a plane,
I'm probably just one of those small screws.
Mr Ha.
You look familiar.
Have we met before?
This is our first meeting.
Is it?
I'm pretty sure I saw you somewhere.
I cannot beat around the bush.
People who wish to meet me...
all have a reason or a motive.
I only meet people who are worth my time.
I just...
wish to be of some help...
to the work you do and...
Do you know what the word "noodles" means?
It means "to absorb water".
Politics and noodles both have to retain water.
But...
can you do so with bare hands?
The water just drips through your fingers.
Even if it takes time,
you have to cup your hands to hold and move water.
Then, one day, you will be able to cook rice and noodles.
How touching.
I would love to quote it one day.
I feel hungry now.
Myeong, let's have some noodles.
What would you like?
This is a special day.
We should have janchi guksu.
I'll make some.
I enjoyed the meal.
I hope to see you more often.
I heard you're hosting a competition for Head of Noodles.
We'll meet then.
I'd like to see what the competition is like.
Do you mind?
You are welcome to come and watch.
But...
I'm only free the day after tomorrow.
That's too soon. We need time to prepare.
Haven't you ever taken a test?
Procrastination...
never works.
Your everyday skill is the real thing.
I don't mind.
I'm not sure if the deputy head of noodles will be okay, though.
We'll host it that evening, then.
Such an important event must be fair.
If you use tricks to pick your favourite...
or try to change the rules, it'll ruin your business.
Your job is to hold a competition where the two young men...
can show off their skills.
Of course, Sir.
I should leave.
See you in two days.
Go home safe, Sir.
I can't use tricks or change the rules...
of the competition.
It seemed like he was saying...
what you wanted to say to me.
I doubt that.
Why would he care for the likes of me?
I tried to make an ally and got a mother-in-law instead.
It's not the picture I imagined.
Erase it and start over.
Or paint over it.
You will be able to draw...
whatever it is you want.
Are you sure it's not the drawing you want?
Stand next to me.
Only my enemies stand before me.
Stand in my way,
and I might crush you without mercy.
You wouldn't.
I'm not foolish enough...
to take you on.
We shall wait and see about that.
We shall hold the competition tomorrow.
It will begin at 10pm, after business hours.
The judges will be me, Ms Seol and my wife.
It will be a blind test.
Name the dish.
You shall cook...
medicinal herb noodles.
You have to get rid of the offensive bitter taste,
but leave some flavour behind.
It's very hard to create a delectable dish.
If the broth, noodles and topping do not go perfectly well together,
it will be impossible to eat.
There is no definitive guideline,
which is why I thought this would be a perfect theme.
However, you must use at least five medicinal herbs.
You can each name one assistant.
I pick Kim Jin Hak.
I pick Kim Da Hae.
Speak up if you have objections or questions.
If not, you can leave.
Do you have more to say?
That's enough...
for me.
Now it just has to be fair.
Don't worry.
I will monitor everything from start to finish.
It will be very fair.
Mr Ha.
You look familiar.
Have we met before?
You can't go in. Who are you?
What is it?
Wait here.
I can't sleep out of fear that you'll hurt me.
What wouldn't a kidnapper do?
I mean nothing?
If you're a father... No.
If you're human,
you shouldn't have said that.
Don't worry.
I will monitor everything from start to finish.
- Ms Ko.
-  Who are you?
I'm Mr Ha's assistant.
Oh, you're his new hire.
I don't have a title yet.
You're tall and handsome.
Don't be scared. I won't bite.
Is Mr Ha in?
No.
You're his assistant.
What are you doing here if he's not here?
He told me to wait here.
Okay, then.
Sorry.
What is it?
I'm here for my belongings.
I will get it for you.
Do you know what it looks like?
Step aside.
He opened his eyes? Are you sure?
Stay outside.
Are you going to follow me around like a puppy?
Don't mind me.
How odd.
You look like a rabbit, so why do you work for a snake?
Silly me. I'm so scatterbrained.
Where did I put it?
Sir, are you awake?
You should have given me a hint.
You scared me.
Who else knows?
Your daughter? Or Da Hae?
Tell me.
I heard you opened your eyes.
Why now?
You did this when we moved to Gangnam.
Why do you do this whenever I plan something?
Do you want me to fail that badly?
Do you? Is that it?
Open your eyes!
Why is there a remote control when there's no TV?
It's real.
Mr Ha.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
He's only skin and bones.
I massaged him, and that's all I felt.
What's this?
It looks like a bruise.
You strangled him.
I saw it with my own eyes.
What nonsense is this?
Nonsense?
It's not nonsense. You're feigning ignorance.
Do you call yourself human? What human being does this?
I've had enough.
You say what you want and blame me for everything.
Shut your mouth!
Wait.
What did you see?
I was here alone.
Father.
Father!
Father. Father.
Father.
Is he awake? Dae Cheon.
Dae Cheon.
How is he?
His consciousness comes and goes.
What if he never wakes up?
That won't happen.
He's a strong man. He will wake up.
It's almost a miracle that he regained consciousness.
But his vital signs aren't encouraging.
He is is under severe stress.
What's strange is that...
he shows symptoms of poison in his nervous system.
What do you mean?
He is severely paralysed.
Nothing showed up on the toxicology screen,
but he has been poisoned.
Then...
what should we do?
Have him admitted.
Ms Ko.
I won't do that.
If he's admitted, I can't stay by his side.
If I'm not there,
he could die at any time.
Until he makes a full recovery,
I will eat and sleep here.
If that is what you wish, then I can't force you.
In case of possible emergencies,
I'll send someone over, so don't worry.
Goodbye.
Can you leave?
I want to talk to my dad.
Father.
I have evidence...
to crush Jung Tae.
He can't get away this time.
Burn it.
You know nothing.
You saw nothing. Do you understand?
Detective Park, it's me.
You need to come over.
It's not about the hit-and-run.
It's still urgent, though. See you soon.
Please stay here.
Okay.
Who told you to let her in?
No one is supposed enter my room without my permission.
Do I have to tell you that every time?
- I'm sorry, Sir.
-  "I'm sorry."
"It is my fault."
I hate those words.
How many times did I tell you that?
I already watched what you did.
You can't erase my memory.
You look startled.
Of course.
You should be startled this time.
Don't you think?
What are you doing?
What do you think you are you doing?
- Honey.
-  What?
Don't call me that.
I haven't heard that word in so long that I forgot.
Ha Jung Tae.
Do you know why I'm here?
I'm here to kill you.
Detective Park.
What happens if someone installs...
a surveillance camera with no permission?
It is against the privacy protection law.
And if you violate the people's basic human rights,
you will receive a criminal penalty.
Take a look at this carefully.
Watch what he's done.
Did you do this?
If you are talking about channel management, yes.
You have a good assistant.
You changed it so soon.
Do you want us to investigate further into it?
Never mind.
I just became the crazy person.
Excuse me.
Earlier...
It was my mistake.
I would've been angry if I were you.
No one will enter this room without your permission from now on.
How did you change it?
I got a license for Engineer Information Communication in prison.
I didn't know I'd make use of it like this.
Well done.
You may leave.
Mr Park.
Spend all the money...
in this wallet within today.
- I'm sorry, Sir?
-  Spend all the money inside.
There is no surveillance camera around Mr Choi's house.
There is one across the street, but it is broken.
He said he fell down the stairs.
According to the ambulance workers who'd gone there,
there was a lot of blood around this area.
Was there a black box?
There must've been cars that were parked around the area.
Ask the car owners for cooperation.
Okay.
Once a day, exactly five grams at a time.
Feed it to him after mixing it with water.
Don't use more or less of it.
Never eat it.
If you do, you won't feel anything even if your body burns in fire.
Hey, Gil Yong.
You're here.
Don't talk to me.
Ms Ko won't be happy if she finds out about this.
We share the same family name. I don't know why she's so mean to me.
Do you want a noodle expert to make you some noodles?
No, I'd have to get paid to eat your noodles.
Did you say, "noodle expert"?
Good for you!
Congratulations!
How dare you hug me?
I was just excited.
When you become Head of Noodles...
Go away.
I'm leaving.
Myeong?
You...
It's been a long time.
Why? You should try harder to hide from me.
You'll keep coming here to deliver vegetables anyway.
I was bound to see you some day.
If so, it'd be better if I had control over when and where.
The more you talk, the more I hate you.
Do you know how hard I tried to find you?
I traveled all over the country to find your body.
Let me ask you a question.
Are you guys having a meeting at Goongnakwon all together?
Why are you all here?
We all have our own reasons.
Just like how you come here to deliver vegetables.
You're the one who told me to come here.
You're the one who made me deliver vegetables to Goongnakwon.
What about Yeo Kyung?
Yeo Kyung?
Do you even think of her?
You seriously shouldn't be like this.
Yeo Kyung has been worried sick about you.
She is devastated.
Don't tell her that we met.
It will break her heart.
It's better if she doesn't find out.
So let's keep it like that, okay?
You want me to keep it from her? How?
Since the day you got stabbed,
Yeo Kyung has led a miserable life.
She never...
passed a day comfortably.
I'm doing this because I know how she is.
Yeo Kyung will be in danger if she finds out that I'm here.
Don't tell Yeo Kyung that I'm here.
You should go tell her yourself.
If you can't do that,
just give her a call.
Do you understand?
(Yeo Kyung)
Darn it.
Who are you?
Please don't do this.
My gosh.
Did you find anything?
Not really.
Nothing was recorded.
That's too bad.
That's our only evidence.
What are we going to do?
Well...
maybe we should do some legwork.
There might be a witness.
Okay. I got it.
(Delete)
(Are you sure?)
(Congressman So Tae Seop)
Yes, Congressman.
Did you wait for long?
No, Sir. I had a chance to get some fresh air.
It looks like you've been through a lot.
It's not easy to do planned investigation as the first-year.
I understand.
You may come across some obstacles.
That's the crossroad.
Some give up,
and some either punch though or jump over that wall.
Thankfully, you're the latter.
I like that about you.
I may collapse because of the wall,
but I'll never give up.
Do you know...
a man named Kim Gil Do?
I've never heard of him.
Look him up.
You'll find some interesting things.
(Kim Gil Do)
Let's see.
Among people born from 1955 to 1965,
there is a total of 461 people registered under Kim Gil Do.
Let's narrow it down.
Can you sort out special people like people on prosecution suspension,
ex-convicts, missing people and wanted criminals?
From 1989 to 1995.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
But who is this Kim Gil Do?
- Is he...
-  Are information prior to 1995...
also stored in the computer system?
It's probably not accurate.
Even if you find some on the system,
you have to go to the branches and check the information yourself.
It'll take only 2 to 3 days for us to go down and look for them.
First of all, please sort out special persons.
Okay.
Let's do this. We're almost there.
I thought you were going to destroy him. What happened?
How is he?
He fell asleep.
He doesn't pay much attention to me.
My goodness, Father. You are so cold-hearted.
How can you...
never even call my name after waking up?
Ms Seol, please do me a favour.
Can we stall the competition...
until he wakes up again?
When will that be?
I'm not sure when that will be.
Do you know?
Will you be like this?
You're the one who is misjudging the situation.
It's not the time to be greedy. It's time for you to make a choice.
Will it be me, or Mr Ha?
Ms Seol.
- Father.
-  Dae Cheon.
Father.
Mr Ko.
Father, it's me, Gang Sook.
I'm listening, so please speak.
Da...
What?
Da Hae.
Da Hae?
Ms Ko.
Ms Seol.
Sit down.
Sir, it's me, Da Hae.
Did you want to say something?
Why?
Do you want me to leave?
We'll be outside.
Let's go.
Sir, you can take your time.
I'll wait for you. Don't make it too hard on yourself.
Cho...
What?
Cho, and what else?
Help! We need help!
Dae Cheon.
Father.
- Father.
-  Dae Cheon.
It was a light stroke.
Right now, he needs to rest.
What did he say?
He was about to say something, but he had a stroke.
Is that true?
Yes, Ms Ko.
Don't push her. She has no reason to lie.
I'm just curious.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Ms Ko.
See you later.
Da Hae.
It looks like...
he's only going to speak to you.
Did he really say nothing?
You can tell me.
No.
You have to tell me.
I told you, he said nothing. How many times did I tell you?
At times, there is something...
called an instinct, which can't be explained logically.
We call that our gut feeling. You know that, right?
That's how I feel right now.
I can feel that you are hiding something.
I am also speculating that you and Mr Ha must have a past, too.
Stop it.
I am sick of your suspicions.
Suspicions don't go away until they become confirmed.
That day will soon come.
And if I confirm that my feelings and speculations were correct,
you will have to...
pay for it.
I warned you before...
that this is a fight between adults.
It's a war, so it won't be weird to see someone die.
Do you know why people begin to take sides?
It's because they want to live.
They can't stand out on their own.
There will come a time when you'll have to make a choice.
So I hope...
you make a wise decision.
Ko Dae Cheon regained his consciousness,
and he began to talk, although he's still inarticulate.
That's an unexpected variable.
That's what I hate the most.
Unexpected variables.
They're unpredictable,
and you never know what they'll lead to.
In that case,
Ms Ko will try to stall the competition.
I did stop it.
But...
Mr Ha will want to do it quickly...
before Mr Ko fully regains his consciousness.
But you know what?
There is another variable.
It's Kim Da Hae.
She's on special terms with Mr Ko.
And there's something between her and Mr Ha, too.
I put her in there, but I'm not sure if she's on my side.
- I will try to find out.
-  Focus on what she's hiding...
instead of what she knows.
That'll be faster.
Okay.
One more thing.
What will you do after you become Head of Noodles?
I will go on TV shows with Mr Ha.
I will tell the world about how unsubstantial...
Mr Ha and his skills are on TV.
I will make him lose his job,
and then think about what I'll do after that.
Your next goal must be...
Goongnak Foundation.
Mr Ha's hideous crimes are...
swarming in that place.
Fine.
I don't mind losing Goongnak Foundation.
I am...
only interested in Goongnakwon.
Cho...
Do you know about the competition tomorrow?
- You'll be fine.
-  I picked you as my assistant.
What?
Who says that you can do that?
It's hard enough for me since I'm preparing for my test.
How can I assist you?
I need your perfect sense of smell.
If I can't get the smell right for medicinal herb noodles,
it'll be a failure.
I'll help you through your test in return.
You do know that...
you will be disapproved...
if you can't make the order, right?
Jin Hak was disapproved only after two orders.
He couldn't make baby octopus noodles.
I will teach you...
difficult recipes when someone orders them.
How does that sound?
Well, I guess that's fair.
What should I do first?
Sleep well.
That's the first step.
What are you doing?
Sorry?
You were looking around like a baby who lost his mum.
It's nothing.
Stop.
I haven't seen you before. Which department are you in?
I am Assistant Park Tae Ha.
Assistant? Assistant to who?
To Mr Ha.
Oh, really?
You should've told me.
Who are you looking for?
It's nothing.
Tae Ha?
You found her.
You found who you were looking for.
I am such a lonely woman,
but I guess some of us aren't.
You're dating at work.
Don't worry about her. She's like that.
What's up?
Right.
Thank you for the other day.
What are you doing after work?
Are you asking me out?
No.
I just asked you what you were doing.
I was just curious.
What's your plan?
I just...
eat, wash up and sleep.
My goodness.
Just dine with him.
You two will never get anywhere.
Hey, come on.
I'm sorry, though.
I have to prepare for the competition tomorrow.
What's the competition?
It's to get the head of noodles.
Deputy Head of Noodles and Myeong are competing tomorrow.
I am Myeong's assistant,
so I don't have the time today.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry to bother you.
How is your hand?
It's fine, Sir.
Did you use up the money?
People say that we use money like we use water.
Money is very easy to use.
It's not easy to use someone else's money like water.
It's easier with someone else's money.
I've never done that, so I wouldn't know.
I don't like...
people who aren't flexible.
It's the worst when someone is single-minded...
and dull.
I'm sorry.
But...
it doesn't seem so bad now.
That means the person is honest.
It's a compliment.
- Thank you.
-  These are important times.
I won't accept any small mistakes...
or unseen variables.
Are you referring to the competition?
That man named Myeong of the noodles department...
keeps on getting on my nerves.
I can see right through him,
and he has sharp teeth.
It's not easy for me to shun him nor take him in.
He's very different form you.
I need his background check.
Keep an eye on him,
and report to me if anything seems suspicious.
Yes, Sir.
Welcome, Congressman.
I hope I'm not interfering with your affairs.
Of course not.
This way, please.
Can you smell the broth?
Guess what it is.
Milk vetch root, acanthopanax,
kudzu root,
lycium fruit, date...
and Chinese gooseberry.
Wow, you really do have a perfect sense of smell.
Do you know...
a medicinal herb that first smells like Jerusalem artichoke,
then milk vetch root with...
a hint of bitterness at the end?
Any ideas?
My nose isn't that good.
I guess no one could be able to make sense of that.
What makes you so curious?
I smelled that herb on three people.
It's not a common smell.
Isn't that strange?
Who are they?
We shall begin the competition for Head of Noodles.
You already know what to make and what the rules are.
Congressman So Tae Seop has graced us with his presence.
I hope you make a lovely bowl of noodles...
befitting of Goongnakwon's fame and reputation.
You may begin.
So I said,
"You have a rock for a head and an ugly face."
"All you're good at is tell lies, so what will you grow up to be?"
Do you know what he said?
He said, "I'll become a politician."
He's now our prime minister.
My goodness.
No wonder.
There are many people like that.
Who would've known you'd become a politician?
Didn't you study history in college?
I did.
Ms Ko studied fashion design,
and now she runs Goongnakwon.
Don't you think modelling would suit your figure better?
Mr Ha, what must a man do to gain the love of such a beauty?
Things just happened, in my case.
Are you unwell?
No, I'm fine.
I'd like to ask you something.
You went to Seoul National University.
You must've been busy studying and falling in love.
When did you learn to make noodles?
I didn't do all three at the same time.
Forget about falling in love.
It was an arranged marriage.
Oh, was it?
Could you excuse me?
Why did you decide to make five coloured noodles?
It's the only dish my mother made me.
What's that?
A medicine and poison.
It's the last thing I add to the broth.
A medicine and poison?
A small amount is a medicine, but a large amount is a neurotoxin.
I wanted to show someone who used this as poison...
that it can also be used as medicine.
What is this herb called?
"Cho". It's the root of the alpine monkshood.
It was used to kill people in the Joseon Dynasty period.
Mr Ko.
(Seongbuk-dong Robbery Homicide, April 30, 1980)
Yes?
I think I found something on Kim Gil Do.
I'll fax it over.
Okay.
I hate to do this.
But...
I hate the idea of going back even more.
Gil Do.
Stop it.
(Thief and murderer wanted, 3,000-dollar reward)
(Master of Revenge)