(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 13)
Look.
How many are there? Count them.
There are 46 crocks in total.
People get wrinkles as they grow old,
and trees get growth rings.
Right?
These crocks are like my wrinkles and growth rings.
With 46 crocks, I'd say you're still young.
Jung Tae.
Yes?
You can use these as a stepping stone...
to make them into 200 crocks. Okay?
The base of all dishes is the sauce.
You need a good sauce to make a good noodle dish.
Whatever happens,
don't ever forget this, okay?
Of course. I will keep that in mind.
Look at you. You're now part of the family.
Don't you think?
That stupid old man.
He shouldn't have done such a thing.
What are you thinking about?
About your father.
That's weird.
You say that you're thinking about my father,
but it sounds creepy.
Gil Do.
That's enough.
Did you...
just call me Gil Do?
Why do you call me Kim Gil Do?
The person who made that small Chimyeon Restaurant...
into the grand Goongnakwon in Gangnam is Ha Jung Tae.
The person who turned you into the master of...
royal pheasant buckwheat noodles is also Ha Jung Tae.
And the person who worked around the clock...
being held in contempt by the Ko Family is also Ha Jung Tae.
But why do you call me Kim Gil Do?
Why is that?
Why?
Kim Gil Do...
is a murderer.
I'm not the only one who killed someone.
You killed the only person I've ever loved.
Did I startle you?
I have more.
The daughter of the woman you killed...
Do you know who that is?
She's Da Hae.
Stop... Stop lying.
That's... That's a lie.
Do you know why I've kept you alive?
If you die now,
your daughter, Gang Sook, will get all your shares.
Goongnakwon...
is mine.
I sacrificed my life on building it into what it is now.
No one can touch it.
If you do,
both you and your daughter, Gang Sook,
won't be able to get away with it.
So let's make a deal.
Hand your shares over to me.
And all you have to do is to...
just keep breathing as if your neither dead nor alive.
Anything other than that is unacceptable.
Kim... Kim Gil Do.
You.
(Thief and murderer wanted, 3,000-dollar reward)
Is this the man I'm thinking about?
Who else knows about this?
Now you know about it.
Why are you...
telling me about this?
You deserve to know...
if the person next to you is a human or a beast.
Leave it here.
If you overlook it, I will expose it to the world myself.
He is a murderer.
Stop it!
Sir, are you all right?
Sir.
Was Mr Ha here?
I can smell the wolfsbane powder. He was here, wasn't he?
What did he do to you?
Da Hae.
Yes, Sir. I'm listening.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
really sorry.
Yes?
Did you check the composite sketch?
The case is from 34 years ago.
And the statute of limitations has expired twice already.
Isn't it just a common murder case by a robber?
The address of the incident is 387-18, Seongbuk-dong.
The owner of the house hasn't changed for the past 34 years.
Do you know who the owner is?
It's Congressman So Tae Seop.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
Okay.
Come back to the office.
What is this?
It's obviously the skill of making a request.
Explain it so that I can understand.
People of the highest ranks like him never assign you to a case.
That could get them into trouble later on.
If he wants you to scratch his back, he'll let you scratch his leg first.
Then you will end up scratching his back some day.
So that's why he trying to get me involved in the case?
You had dinner with him.
He wants you to pay for it.
(Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung)
Excuse me.
It's me.
The murder case of Seongbuk-dong took place in your house.
Your housekeeper was murdered, and Kim Gil Do is the murderer.
That's right.
Did you want me to investigate the case for your personal grudge?
The case has expired already.
What are you talking about?
What does Kim Gil Do...
have to do with Ha Jung Tae of Goongnakwon?
They have something in common.
You should get to the bottom of the case before making a snap decision.
Hello? Sir?
Where have you been?
I had something to take care of.
- I see.
-  Let's go in.
Okay.
Instead of milk vetch root, add mountain ash.
To that, add white tuckahoe.
That will counter the bitter taste of camphor.
It's a secret recipe that only I know.
It cannot get out.
I apologise. It was an urgent call.
You're a busy man. Can you spare the time?
You're sweating.
Do you feel unwell?
No. I feel fine.
A bamboo leaf?
Okay.
Let's eat.
What a lovely combination of lilies and camphor.
You must know a lot about medicinal herbs.
I'm impressed.
Forget everything else. The noodles taste delicious.
I enjoyed it.
What did you think, Sir?
I felt like I was in a mountain surrounded by the scent of camphor.
Let's taste the next dish.
This is interesting.
It has a zing, but also a nice flavour.
It's a great dish overall,
but the noodles could have been better.
I think you boiled the gardenia noodles first.
Unfortunately, they were a little soggy.
I agree with Ms Seol.
Let's read out the scores.
Before we do that,
I'd like to hear about how they made the broth.
It's getting late.
And Congressman So is busy. Let's make the decision.
I don't mind.
What do you think? Can you tell us the recipe?
Yes.
Then let's go with the five-coloured noodles first.
I used milk vetch root, acanthopanax, kudzu,
boxthorn, dates, silvervine fruit and...
wolfsbane powder.
Wolfsbane powder?
It was the poison given to people who deserved the death penalty.
A large enough dose can even kill an ox.
Did you poison our food?
If you wanted to kill us all,
you could have.
Wolfsbane can be a poison, but also a medicine.
It eliminates a herb's bad smell and improves the flavour.
It is also good for arthritis and diabetes.
That's why I used it.
Adding poison to food...
is something only a monster would do.
Myeong's not that kind of person.
We're all fine,
so let's consider this as a good experience.
What goes in the broth of the lily and camphor noodles?
I added camphor, boxthorn, Korean angelica root,
liquorice root and milk vetch root.
That should have answered your questions. Now let's...
I don't smell milk vetch root.
They used mountain ash instead.
And white tuckahoe, too.
Da Hae.
You should learn when not to speak.
Wait. I remember...
- that recipe.
-  Stop being obstinate.
Mountain ash and white tuckahoe are often used with camphor.
I'm pretty sure the deputy head was so focused that he forgot...
what he used. Am I right?
I'll ask the deputy head one last question.
Your honour is at stake, so please be honest.
Were you mistaken,
or did you not use mountain ash and white tuckahoe?
I...
did not use...
mountain ash and white tuckahoe.
Whatever the reason, I made a crucial mistake.
I will forfeit the challenge.
I apologise.
Ingredients he didn't even use...
ended up in the noodles.
The deputy head of noodles admitted his mistake.
It's time to decide.
He cheated.
Therefore, he loses...
the right to compete.
Our new head of noodles is Moo Myeong.
Thank you for your time.
Mr Ko Dae Cheon.
He is fully conscious.
I'm telling you since I thought everyone should know.
I told you that being hardheaded is not a compliment.
I will study harder so that being hardheaded...
becomes a compliment.
Thank you for everything.
Studying won't help you.
You've reached your maximum potential.
Your father-in-law is awake.
Shouldn't you go and see him?
You're my guest. I should see you out.
I didn't attend the competition to see Myeong.
I wanted to see your character.
But seeing...
how the competition went...
worries me a little.
I treat any bowl of noodles with utmost sincerity.
I did so far, and I will do so forever.
I hope you do.
By the way, do you hit balls?
If you're talking about golf, then yes. I play a little.
Let's play one day.
We can talk in the open.
Give me a call.
Goodbye then.
I don't believe it. Is he really conscious?
Am I dreaming?
He can't sit up yet. He can only speak.
He's weak in the body and mind. We'll have to wait and see.
Does that mean that...
we'll have to serve two bosses now?
What?
My goodness. One is more than enough.
How can we deal with two?
Can't they play rock-paper-scissors to decide?
Don't poke me.
Oh, my gosh. Mr Ha, I'm so sorry.
I ran off my mouth.
Why didn't you tell me he was here?
He has regained consciousness,
but he is extremely weak.
One positive aspect is that his cognitive ability is perfect.
Have a lawyer...
draw up papers to declare that he is fully competent.
Make sure he gets some rest.
You gathering around him like this could also be stressful for him.
Make sure visiting hours are strictly kept.
I should go.
Father.
It's me, Gang Sook.
Say something.
Why won't you even say your own daughter's name?
Father.
Gang Sook.
How have you been?
I've been miserable ever since your accident.
Mi Ja.
I'm right here.
Look after Gang Sook for me.
I will.
The kids from the kitchen.
Are they outside?
Yes.
I want to talk to them.
Send them in.
Come on in.
Mr Ko.
It's me, Kim Jin Young.
Do you recognise me?
You little brat.
You gained even more weight.
I'm all skin and bones.
Don't say that.
Moon Bok.
Yes, Sir.
You've grown old, too.
I'm already 50.
Won Sang.
Do you still...
pretend to be dumb?
I'm a chatterbox now.
Cheo Nyeo.
Are you still not married?
If I did, I'd have to change my name, then.
Cheo Nyeo means "single".
Jin Hak.
Yes?
Do you...
still slack off at work?
I work hard now.
In the kitchen,
the head of noodles is always the boss.
Help him.
And have fun...
making noodles.
You don't make noodles...
with your hands.
Noodles...
are made with your soul.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
-  Yes.
This is my will.
I woke up just so...
I could...
tell you that.
What did you do to Mr Ko?
What do you mean?
Wolfsbane.
I smelled it from day one.
I could smell it from Mr Ko's mouth and Dong Bae's hands.
It was an unfamiliar smell, so I thought it was medicine.
But earlier this evening, you reeked of the smell.
You fed it to Mr Ko.
That's why he was paralysed.
Because you can't let him wake up,
you drugged him so you could kill him.
To me,
Mr Ko...
was the father I never had.
I was a nobody.
But he let me work at Chimyeon Restaurant.
He made me his heir...
and let me marry his precious daughter.
Did you say...
I wanted to kill him?
Would I...
kill the only father I ever had?
Wolfsbane.
It's poison.
But it's also medicine.
It works wonders on people who suffer from a stroke.
That's why I gave it to him.
So he'd wake up.
So he'd...
knead dough again...
and make noodles again.
I want to be alone.
What an act that was.
I almost fell for it.
You left during the competition...
to see my father, right?
Did you go to feed him wolfsbane?
I just explained.
It's medicine.
He was paralysed and unable to speak until now.
It was because of the wolfsbane powder. It's no medicine.
You can't lie forever.
The truth will come out.
Don't waste your time here.
Spend what time you have with your father.
You might regret not doing so.
As of this moment,
don't you dare approach my father.
You put him in his current condition.
The least you can do is let him die in peace.
Okay?
Calm down.
I told you that...
you and I...
should tiptoe around each other.
That's best for us both.
Shut it.
Stay away from...
my father.
If you do,
I'll act my part and pretend to be...
a good wife.
(Born in 1966, Head of Dokku Gang)
(Gilsung Gang)
(Born in 1961, Seoul)
If I look into Kim Gil Do,
I'll get to Ha Jung Tae.
(Gangnam-gu San 323-37)
Ms Kim.
Yes?
Gangnam-gu San 323-37.
Tell me the current address of that place.
It used to be a mountain.
Ms Chae.
Gangnam-gu San 323-37 is currently part of Ilwon-dong.
Do you know what's there right now?
Goongnakwon.
Ha Jung Tae bought the land that used to be Kim Gil Do's house.
The land itself is registered under Goongnakwon.
But this red section.
This belongs to Ha Jung Tae.
He bought it 20 years ago.
Yes.
He planned to build Goongnakwon there since then.
He bought over 9000m² of land just so he could buy 65m²?
Why do you think he's so fixated on that land?
Ha Jung Tae and Kim Gil Do.
They're both the same person.
I am Moo Myeong, the new Head of Noodles.
I'm sure you were briefed on what happened.
Please continue to do your best at your work stations.
First, we need a deputy head of noodles.
Mr Park, the head of broth will fill in.
What? But I...
I need your help.
I don't think I deserve such respect from the head of noodles.
Well, I may not be good enough,
but I will make sure to try my best.
Good for you.
Mr Ko Dae Cheon said we should make noodles with our souls.
I will also try my best with a sincere heart...
to make noodles.
Okay, then.
Let's start with three portions of royal pheasant buckwheat noodles.
Let's begin.
- Yes, Sir.
-  Yes, Sir.
Mr Kim Jin Hak.
What you're doing will make the meat tougher.
Hit the body once and the legs twice.
I'm sorry, Sir.
I'm sorry about Deputy Head of Noodles.
But it is nobody's fault. Don't feel guilty about it.
I...
need your help.
I'd appreciate your cooperation.
Thank you, Sir.
Gil Yong.
You seem happy now that you've become the head of noodles.
Yeo Kyung is still investigating Goongnakwon.
- What?
-  You said it was dangerous.
Shouldn't you stop her?
Father. Father.
Are you feeling better now?
Da Hae.
Gosh, you're saying her name again.
Why are you so obsessed with her?
Let me talk with you, too.
Father.
Listen carefully to what I have to say.
You should give me your shares for Goongnakwon.
If something goes wrong, Jung Tae will take over the restaurant. Okay?
Father. Are you listening to me?
Ha Jung Tae...
is the one who made you this way. I will make him pay.
But I need power to do that.
Father.
Lawyer Park.
Bring him here.
Okay.
(Yeo Kyung)
You are the first one to come and the last one to leave.
When do you get to sleep?
We don't have a labourer any more. So I should do all the work.
We should hire a labourer.
I appreciate your hard work.
It's your day off tomorrow. What's your plan for tonight?
Well, nothing special.
I'd like to have a small celebration party. Will you join me?
Let me apologise first.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Was it because of the wolfsbane powder?
I thought Mr Ko was in danger.
So...
It's okay. You prevented a big accident...
instead of helping me.
Where will you have the party?
At the fish noodle restaurant?
Where are you going?
Me? I have a plan.
Aren't you tired?
It's dangerous to ride a scooter at this hour.
Get in.
You go first. I will be right there.
There's plenty of seats here.
Do you want to join?
No, thank you.
What kind of music do you like?
Anything. What about you?
Me, too.
Do you remember? I was going to leave through the window.
How could I forget that? You also left your scooter here.
That's right. I did.
The police was here when I came back to get my scooter.
Your friend is just like you.
She is inflexible and stubborn.
My friend?
The female prosecutor. She also came to Goongnakwon once.
Didn't you see her?
What? She didn't even know your phone number.
Is she really your friend?
Yeo Kyung is still investigating Goongnakwon.
You said it was dangerous. Shouldn't you stop her?
Have some.
Wow.
It looks very delicious.
I don't need to worry about getting fat as it is devil's-tongue jelly.
What is that?
Gosh!
I've been looking for this.
Did you have it all this time?
You bought it, didn't you?
Smell it.
It's mine!
It's no fun to just drink.
Do you want to play Truth or Dare?
If you can't answer a question, you should drink.
Okay. But I will ask first.
Why...
did you join Goongnakwon?
Why did you join Goongnakwon?
How do you get into the secret room?
That's cheating. It's my turn to ask a question.
What was in the secret room other than a safe?
No, it's my turn.
Under Mr Ha's desk,
there is a button.
If you press it,
the wall rotates.
It rotates.
What did you do?
She got drunk on her own.
Don't imagine things.
Don't do this again.
Don't use innocent bystanders.
I didn't.
Tae Ha.
What... What are you doing?
Stop it.
You smell nice.
Tae Ha's smell.
Why did you drink so much when you can't take it?
I can walk just fine.
Watch out.
Gosh.
I forgot. I should take a photo.
I have to take photos and report back.
Stop it.
Report to whom?
Hey.
Stop taking photos.
I like your smell.
I really do.
(Yeo Kyung)
Sorry for calling you out.
- Sit.
-  No thanks.
I'm here to talk.
And then I'll leave.
I know that...
you're going after Mr Ha...
and that no one can stop you.
So I made up my mind.
I will stop worrying,
and I won't try to stop you.
- Yeo Kyung.
-  Stop.
I'm not done talking.
Mr Ha was involved...
with my parents' death.
I will get to the truth.
You and I...
share a common enemy.
I'll get to the point. The only way...
to get you and Tae Ha out of Goongnakwon...
is to crush Mr Ha.
Let's join forces.
Let's crush that monster...
and go back to how we used to be.
Stay out of it.
I can do this alone.
With what power?
Can you ruin him...
by becoming the head of noodles?
I...
can't let you get hurt.
I can't even worry about you getting hurt.
So stay out of it.
That monster...
is out of your league.
Have you...
killed someone?
I have.
I killed a man...
and did nothing as Tae Ha took the blame.
I'm a murderer who goes around as a prosecutor with a clean past.
A monster?
Who's the real monster?
I am.
Can you say...
I'm not a monster?
Listen carefully.
Once this is over,
I will quit my job.
I will clear Tae Ha's name and pay for my crime. So please...
Please...
Please don't run away from me.
Let go of me.
Why do you think I ignored you?
It's because I knew you'd get involved.
That's why, Yeo Kyung.
That's why.
Let's do it together.
Let's stop...
running away.
Let's make something clear.
I take the lead. You stay behind me.
Don't do anything alone.
I won't work with you unless you promise me that.
I promise.
There's a secret room in Mr Ha's office.
He uses it to launder cash,
and I found a way to get in.
I'll go in soon.
Get me enough for a search warrant.
I need something concrete. Once we begin,
I'll go after Goongnak Foundation, too.
You should get back to work.
Look after yourself.
Mr Ha.
It's your big day.
Get on Congressman So's good side and fly high.
Take me with you if you can.
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung, was it?
Is she still on that case?
I tied her up for now.
She won't cause any trouble.
Good shot.
Do you work out?
Thank you, Sir.
Your ball goes way farther now.
You hit that too hard.
Prosecutor Ahn, can you go to the toilet?
What for? I just went.
Go again.
Sure.
Congressman Choi told me.
I'd like to invest.
If you take my money,
there's both a huge strength and a small problem.
No one can touch an investment that my money's in.
Isn't that a strength?
What's the small problem?
I heard it takes a year to launder money.
I'm too impatient to wait that long.
I want it back within three months.
That is the small problem.
Realistically speaking, that's impossible.
Make it possible.
The motto exists for a reason.
Let's go back to playing golf.
Isn't the weather lovely?
I, Ko Dae Cheon...
have in my name...
Did he make many changes?
It's practically a new will.
Did he mention me in...
I cannot answer any questions right now.
- Mr Park.
-  I apologise.
I'm obligated to keep everything a secret.
Goodbye.
Mr Park.
Mr Ha.
Why are you here?
Mr Ko called me.
What for?
To write a new will.
I see.
Have a nice day.
You fool.
The mill goes round and round
And round and round
- Come with me.
-  What for?
- I'm not done.
-  You're so slow.
- We need to leave.
-  You and your temper.
What are you doing?
You scared me. My goodness.
Are you all right?
Of course I am.
That's good.
I got a little too drunk last night.
I don't remember anything. Did something happen?
Not at all.
Of course not. Nothing could have.
Oh, Mr Ha wants to see you in half an hour at the annex.
Be there on time.
Mr Ha?
What for?
I don't know.
Bye.
Oh, dear.
Did I wake you?
Sorry.
I meant to come and go unnoticed.
What do you want?
I told you to make things right,
but you messed things up even further.
So this time,
I will make things right.
Wouldn't my shares...
naturally go to you?
Is that why you called your lawyer?
If you were going to leave the shares to me,
why did you meet Mr Park without me present?
Why did you?
Why...
Why is that in your hands?
I wonder. Why do you think I have this?
Now,
it will go to Da Hae.
She will be here soon.
You two can have a lovely chat.
Gil Do.
Kim Gil Do.
No.
This is wrong.
This...
Is there anyone out there?
Follow me.
Myeong, step back.
This is wrong.
This...
Mr Ko. Are you okay?
This is wrong.
Mr Ko. Mr Ko.
You can't...
What?
Why do you have this?
Is this yours?
I... I...
Did you kill my mother?
Tell me. Did you kill my mother?
Help! Can anyone help us?
Mr Ko. No.
Don't die. You can't die.
Sir!
Oh, no. Mr Ko!
Tell me. Tell me why you killed my mother!
I'm...
sorry.
Please don't die. Mr...
Mr Ko!
No.
You can't die.
(Master of Revenge)
Your father-in-law just passed away.
Thank you for letting me know by now.
Do you know how I became successful?
It's because I don't have friends.
Don't come in here ever again.
Mr Ha's shares have suddenly reached 50 percent.
I'd like to see Ha Jung Tae being suffocated.
That doesn't mean that I forgive you.
It still doesn't change the fact that you abandoned me.
Tell me. Why are you betraying me?