(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 14)
Tae Ha! Tae Ha!
Hurry up and leave.
Go.
Sir.
What happened?
Did you break down the door?
I thought you were stuck inside as the emergency alarm rang.
Any intruders?
I looked, but no one was there.
That's not possible.
You have to press the button to ring the alarm and shut the door.
I'm sure there's someone inside.
Ha Jung Tae!
What's going on?
Your father-in-law...
just passed away.
Tae Ha.
I didn't do this to save you.
I would've gotten in trouble if Mr Ha found out you got in.
That's why I did this.
Mr Ko just passed away. So Mr Ha...
will be at the annex, and I won't be around all the time, either.
You might think of this as an opportunity,
but don't even think about it.
Don't ever come in here again.
Next time you do, I won't let you loose.
The prayer beads.
You put them on his wrist.
Thank you...
for letting me know by now.
Father.
What am I going to do if you leave me like this?
How could you leave me alone like this? What am I going to do?
I'm sorry.
I still have a lot to tell you.
Dae Cheon.
My poor father.
Oh my gosh.
Dae Cheon.
Dae Cheon, how can you leave like this?
Gosh.
Dae Cheon.
Father.
It's a typical post traumatic stress disorder.
It's as if the incident keeps happening over and over again.
Your arms and legs are still feeling the burning pain from the fire.
And you still feel the knife stabbing you on your side.
Father.
It is so hard to make Ha Jung Tae trust me...
and to pry into his secret.
He is...
the only person who knows your real name.
But I can't get any closer to him.
The only thing left is the secret room.
I must break into the room.
I must do it at all costs.
Are you all right?
No, I'm not.
What happened to Mr Ko?
He was holding on for so long. I can't believe he left like that.
Where is he now?
I should go see him.
That's not why I wanted to see you.
We have work to do...
during the period of the funeral.
What?
I'm...
sorry.
Puppy.
Are you all right?
Your face looks emaciated.
- Uncle Dokku. - What?
It was Mr Ko.
He killed my mother.
What?
I'm going to ask you one last time.
Did you know about that?
I really didn't know that far.
I mean it.
I didn't even get to ask him why he killed my mother.
I wanted to ask him why he had to kill my mother.
I always thought about yelling and spitting at...
whoever killed my mother.
But do you know what I did when I found out it was him?
I asked him not to die.
I asked people for help to save his life.
Puppy.
I don't know what to do now.
I don't know why I should stay...
at Goongnakwon any more.
How are your shoulders?
They're fine, Sir.
There was a sign of an outsider having broken into the secret room.
That's why I changed the access system. It was like a trap.
And someone fell into...
that trap I set up.
Who was it?
Tell me the truth.
Then you have to take responsibility only for that.
But if you lie,
you will never...
be able to deal with it.
Was it Da Hae?
You told me to protect her.
So I did.
I told you to watch her.
Can't you tell the difference?
I apologise.
She's going through a tough time.
From now on,
protect her instead of watching her.
Yes, Sir.
(Condolences to the late Master Ko Dae Cheon)
Thank you for helping out.
But why are you taking away...
more than what you're bringing in?
Get some rest.
You might collapse next.
My husband who's supposed to be the chief mourner...
hasn't shown his face even once.
I have to keep my father company.
I know you're upset, but try to keep it in.
Let's just wait until...
the funeral is over.
That's why...
I'm clenching my teeth...
and waiting for time to pass.
Did you call me?
As you know, my father-in-law has passed away.
In mourning,
I plan to close Goongnakwon for three days.
Tell the kitchen staff.
I also have a personal favour to ask.
I have a TV interview the day after tomorrow.
I don't want to do it while I'm in mourning,
so I want you to do it instead.
It's what you wanted, so I'm sure you'll do well.
Yes, Sir.
He finally woke up after six years in a coma,
but he only lived 10 days.
Something similar happened to a friend of mine.
He fell off a cliff,
but survived miraculously.
Then one day, his young son played with fire,
which led him to his death.
Life can be so futile.
Don't be so sad.
Life is like that. Everyone dies.
I think everyone's here.
Read out the will.
I can't until everyone is here.
Please call Kim Da Hae.
What for?
Mr Ha wants to see you.
I won't go.
You have to witness the reading of Mr Ko's will.
You're mentioned in it.
Why me?
See for yourself.
Everyone has to be present for the reading.
Everyone's waiting.
Have a seat.
Everyone's here, so I'll begin.
I, Ko Dae Cheon,
leave all my savings and the land on which...
Chimyeon Restaurant stood in Masan...
to my daughter, Ko Gang Sook.
I, Ko Dae Cheon, leave the title of Noodle Master...
that was handed down four generations...
to my son-in-law, Ha Jung Tae.
I, Ko Dae Cheon, leave the 20 percent of...
Goongnakwon's shares that are in my name...
to Kim Da Hae of the Noodle Team.
That is all.
This makes no sense.
Why are his shares going to her?
What did you do to my father?
Did you cajole him while pretending to nurse him?
Calm down.
How can I calm down?
You're in this with her.
One of you drugged and confused him...
and the other coaxed him.
Why don't you try and explain?
Stop it.
Do you feel guilty?
Do you even have a conscience?
Watch yourself. We have a guest.
I have no reason to stay.
Do excuse me.
Stay right there!
You can't toy with us...
and then leave.
I'm not the one who toys with others.
You are.
You hurt people beyond healing...
and think money will clear things up.
That chills me to the bone.
Kim Da Hae!
Stop right there!
I must've looked like a lunatic.
I understand how you feel.
I would have done the same.
He left his shares to a stranger.
I don't understand what he was thinking.
There's no point in wondering or regretting now.
It's all over.
It's not over yet.
There must be a way to get the shares back.
We will get it back.
We can't.
It's spilt milk.
Give me time to figure it out.
Da Hae...
is my husband's daughter.
My goodness.
The two will gang up against us.
We can't beat them.
That little witch.
She played us all.
I'll have to do something.
We have to teach her a lesson to show her how things work.
I know how you feel.
You got your shares out of nowhere,
but people treat you like a thief.
You never asked for it,
and you don't think it belongs to you.
I don't care about the shares.
You aren't on great terms with Mr Ha,
and you've gone way beyond the point of no return with Ms Ko.
I'm saying I can help you.
You're talented.
You have a great sense of smell, you're passionate,
and you love making noodles.
You don't have to fight over the shares.
If you trust me,
I'll help you achieve your dream within Goongnakwon.
I don't even know what my dream is.
Do you?
All I learned from you is to doubt others.
It feels odd hearing you asking for my trust.
I'll think about the shares.
I still think they don't belong to me.
Bye.
Tell us the secret of your dough.
It's not hard at all. It's all about the push and pull.
For example, it's like me telling you...
that you have a pretty face, but an ugly personality.
That really is a harsh example.
Sorry. I was trying to think of an example.
That's all right. But what does that have to do with kneading dough?
It's the same principle.
You have to put love into it as you beat it down at the same time.
I see.
Pat it.
- Pat it. - And knead it.
And knead it.
- And again. - Okay.
- Pat it. - Pat it.
- And knead it. - And knead it.
Pat it.
And knead it.
And knead it. It's so easy.
Noodles have to be quick and simple to make.
If noodles were hard to make, they wouldn't be so widely loved.
What a great answer.
Next, I'll show you how to make a broth.
Are you trying to host my show, too?
Shall we change places?
I suddenly feel threatened.
He isn't too bad.
You pulled out at the last minute, and he saved the day.
I can't smile on national TV when I'm in mourning.
The ratings doubled compared to when you were on.
He's pretty to look at and tall,
and he makes me feel good.
He might even have an online fan forum.
You need to smile more.
I'll teach you how to smile in different situations.
What about crying?
Did you ever cry?
Tears pooled in my eyes just once.
I was incredibly sad, but the tears wouldn't fall.
Let's give it a go.
Though I can't imagine you crying.
What are you doing?
I'm going to make noodles.
Who gave permission?
Scream if you want to. You're good at that.
Do you even know how?
Anyone can cook noodles.
Where are the somen noodles?
Don't you know that our noodles are handmade?
Oh, I see.
I didn't know that.
How about sujebi, then?
Are you...
trying to cook for me?
Can't I?
Do you know what?
It's the first time you smiled in three days.
Why were you counting that?
I don't know. I just was, I guess.
Taste it.
Hey, you aren't too bad.
I'm just asking because I'm curious. Can't you speak freely to me?
I can.
Don't people say you're uptight?
Especially women.
No woman has ever said that.
Really?
Do you expect me to believe that?
I've never had a girlfriend.
You sweet potato.
What?
Sweet potato?
My goodness. This is incredible. It really is.
Did you see the long line?
I bet it goes all the way to Daejeon.
It can't possibly reach Daejeon.
It must reach Busan at least.
You're right.
Look at your handsome face.
Just a few hours in the spotlight, and your face is shining.
You're embarrassing me.
Our daily sales doubled since you took over.
Don't feel embarrassed.
That's not all.
Mr Park doesn't nap now that he's Deputy Head of Noodles.
He's so alert now.
How can I nap when my boss glares each time I blink?
I have such a hard time working under an evil superior.
Stop it.
Da Hae would've been so happy if she were here.
She stays in her room all day instead of coming to work.
I feel so bad for her.
She was given 20 percent of Goongnakwon's shares.
Would you want to work if you were her?
- What did you say? - 20 percent?
- Yes. - What?
How much is that worth?
But why her?
Did you know about this?
- Mr Ha and Ms Ko were furious. - Well...
My goodness. Forget about it.
Let's get ready before the customers flock in.
- Okay. - Let's get to work.
Gosh, 20 percent?
Stop it.
You don't seem surprised. Did you know about it?
I suspected something,
though I didn't know they were related.
Mr Ha now has half of Goongnakwon's shares.
We might lose everything we fought for.
I think your father will be proud of you.
Let's not talk about him.
Don't you tell your parents that you work here?
I said stop.
There's no guarantee that her shares will go to him.
It is likely, though.
We had a chat, but I couldn't get through to her.
Let me talk to her.
Someone else is working his arms off while you're enjoying a holiday.
It's killing me.
I want to get out of here, but I have no place to go.
Are you free?
Shall we go out for some noodles?
You haven't had any in a while.
My hands shake if I don't eat noodles for even a day.
It's so strange.
The broth was made with anchovies, large-eyed herring and kelp,
and you just boiled store-bought somen noodles.
But how is it so tasty?
It's in the hands.
Are you really going to quit?
Is there talk?
You own 20 percent of the shares.
You're rich now.
I'm trying to get on your good side.
Just like someone said, it was given to me so suddenly.
I don't know much about shares,
and I don't really care.
Mr Ha, Ms Ko and Ms Seol...
all want it.
Just pick someone and give it all away.
Now, I'll talk to you as the head of noodles.
We need you in the kitchen.
Mope and wander all you want as long as you promise to come back.
I'll wait for you.
You said you have nowhere to go.
You can stay here. I can stay at Goongnakwon.
You'll be able to think here, and no one will bother you.
You can use anything you find in the fridge.
I have to go back to work.
Sir.
Thank you.
He should wash it.
Prosecutor Chae.
While investigating Ha Jung Tae, I found this.
His whereabouts were unknown while he was wanted.
But soon after the case expired,
he renewed his resident and family registration...
and even his seal impression all at once.
Where is his residence?
It's in Bongpyeong, Gangwon Province.
You are Myeong's friend, aren't you?
Why are you here?
Well...
Because...
Please don't get me wrong.
I'm staying here for a while for personal reasons.
I mean, we didn't stay here together.
Excuse me. Let me explain.
Hey!
(Kim Da Hae)
The number you have dialled is not available at the moment.
Da Hae is doing well. Don't worry about her.
- Where is she? - She will be back soon. So...
I told you before.
Don't involve innocent people.
Then you should take better care of her.
Can't you reach Da Hae yet?
- I'm sorry, Sir. - Never mind.
I will see her today anyway.
I'm sorry.
I should have been here sooner.
I'm sorry being so late.
Da Hae finally...
found out about your death.
I told her.
If she didn't find out that Ko Dae Cheon did it,
she'd never let it go. So I told her.
I couldn't see my daughter mourning over...
the death of the murderer who killed her mother.
I can't approach Da Hae.
But I can't stay away from her, either.
I don't know what to do.
Please tell me.
I now understand how actors feel.
Sorry, Sir?
I mean their tears.
I'm not sure...
if your tears were true or false.
They were false tears.
Why would you shed false tears?
I heard about the 20 percent share.
How did you feel?
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
(Kim Seon Joo)
I couldn't see my daughter mourning over...
the death of the murderer who killed her mother.
Mum.
Today is a special day.
You look so beautiful in the picture.
And you've got the fur gloves to keep you warm.
You must be happy.
Hello?
Da Hae.
I need to see you.
I'm sorry...
about the other day.
My father...
passed away so suddenly.
I was out of my mind.
I apologise.
Please accept it.
I guess I really like you a lot.
I thought you were betraying me with your father, so I was upset.
Da Hae.
You know that you are like a daughter to me.
Nothing has changed.
I care about you that much.
And I really like you.
So you should...
remember the promise...
between us.
We can count on each other...
when we have hard times in Goongnakwon.
Right?
I'm...
not sure about that, Ma'am.
Da Hae.
I can't make any decision for now.
Please understand me.
Hey.
I'm not asking you to help me.
I'm just saying we should be on the same side.
Don't you understand?
I shouldn't have come here.
How you not understand what I'm saying?
If you keep acting like this,
I won't let you get by so easily.
Do you understand?
People never change.
I almost forgot about that.
Right. People never change. How can people change?
They say the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
You are...
just like your father.
Do you even know...
who killed my mother?
I don't think you have the right...
to say that to me.
Aren't you going to eat?
I will, Sir.
I've been coming to this place for 30 years.
There are many restaurants who serve better dishes,
but I feel really comfortable here.
The food is delicious.
That's good.
The dumplings remind me of my father.
My father was a drunk.
Whenever he hit me, he bought me a pack of dumplings that night.
My lips and mouth were all sore,
but I couldn't stop eating the dumplings since they were so good.
Sometimes, I even made him mad on purpose...
to eat some dumplings.
I wanted him to buy me dumplings.
Tae Ha.
Yes, Sir.
Do you know how I became successful?
It's because I don't have friends.
The moment you run out of money, your food runs out first.
After that, your friends walk out on you.
You should...
live for yourself, too.
You're the only one who can save yourself.
Do you know how I became successful?
It's because I don't have friends.
This place looks neater than before.
Are you keeping a secret maid?
What are you saying?
It smells different, too.
Something is fishy.
I thought you were going to show me something.
Yes.
Kim Gil Do.
He's the suspect of the...
Seongbuk-dong murder case from 34 years ago.
(Police report)
This is Kim Gil Do's past addresses.
(Address: Gangnam-gu San, 323-37)
And this is...
Mr Ha's secret chamber.
He bought Kim Gil Do's old place...
and built Goongnakwon on top of his old house.
It's impossible for this to be a coincidence.
Ha Jung Tae and Kim Gil Do are the same person.
Ha Jung Tae and Kim Gil Do.
Ha Jung Tae was wanted in college for violating National Security Law.
He went low for a while.
Then he reregistered as a citizen and came back to life...
in Bongpyeong, Gangwon Province.
Bongpyeong?
Isn't that your hometown?
Yes, Bongpyeong.
Anyway, I think Kim Gil Do stole someone else's life as his own.
What about the secret chamber?
I failed.
He must've noticed something. He changed the security system.
Do you think you can go back in there?
I must go in at any price.
Everything about him is stored in that place.
(Congressman So Tae Seop)
Yes, Congressman.
How's it going?
Isn't it about time you raided Goongnakwon?
I only have circumstantial evidence.
A search and seizure warrant won't be issued with this.
Is that so? Then I should corner Mr Ha a little more.
Once he's cornered, he'll gasp for air.
That's when you'll find his weaknesses.
Please do that.
I'd like to see Mr Ha gasp for air.
Give me some time.
You're here.
Have a seat.
Have you thought about it?
It was an unexpected offer, so I need some more time.
Why?
Do you think I'll eat you alive?
Pardon?
Come on, I'm just joking.
How can someone like me eat up someone like you?
But don't make me wait too long.
It might not end up as a joke.
How can you make me wait this long?
It's been a while, Mr Park.
Yes.
Let's go.
It's nothing to ponder about.
It's a cable show, but you'll be the host of the show.
You can be on TV to advertise yourself once every week.
(Proposal for TV appearance)
I don't like the fact that I'll be with Head of Noodles.
Also, I hate this father and son concept.
Isn't it wonderful?
Your image will change from a scary CEO into a loving father.
By-election districts will be announced in just three months.
You'll be on TV 12 times in until that time.
Give me more time.
Are you afraid that Head of Noodles might do much better than you?
Nonsense.
It must be true.
Goongnakwon's sales went up after he appeared on TV.
If he goes on more TV shows, the sales will go up again.
If that happens, my management rights will be lost forever.
Anyway, what happened to Chimyeon Restaurant?
The construction is already over. It looks like a hotel.
If you're going into politics, why do you keep expanding your work?
I'm preparing myself just in case I don't get the management rights.
When the worst case happens, I'll need something to depend on.
What happened to Da Hae?
These kids are very tough.
If I beat around the bush, they beat around it together.
If I push her down, she pushes me down even lower.
This won't work on her.
Everything is over.
By the way, have you looked into our sales?
I'm not in the mood to do that.
My goodness, look at you.
The sales went up by three times after Myeong went on TV.
The elderly of the Moon family are very excited.
Wait and see.
Something interesting will happen.
I doubt that.
Hey.
I told her something interesting will happen,
but she won't believe me.
If he decides to be on the show, it'll be bad for his reputation.
If we keep up our sales...
and gather support from the Moon family...
We may be able to take him down from his place.
Why are you so late?
I'm sorry, it was hard to anything other than this.
Is that okay?
The air is fresh.
All right, let this begin. Ready, action.
Mr Ha made wild pine mushroom royal bibim guksu.
Mr Moo made kkolttu guksu.
Now, should we let them taste each other's noodles?
Please, evaluate.
Kkolttu guksu is also known as the nose-hitter.
When you slurp the noodles,
it must be chewy enough to hit your nose as it goes into your mouth.
You can see that he left marks with his noodles on my face.
He did the least he can do.
Wow, I can really see that on your nose.
Yes. He passed.
Head of Noodles.
This is the best bowl of bibim guksu I've ever had.
Then should we just leave it as a tie?
That's no fun.
Let's pick a winner.
That's great. Let's continue.
What is that?
This is yi gen mian. It's made with one strand.
Chinese people eat it as a token of long life.
You have to make it as long as you can without breaking it.
That's very interesting.
How do you feel, Mr Ha?
Will you accept the challenge?
It has been so long.
And I've only made traditional Korean noodles.
There are references to yi gen mian in our history books.
It just never became popular.
I can't help it if he denies it.
My goodness, that was a strong blow.
All right, I'll do it.
Let's film that again.
All right, let's roll again.
Mr Ha, we'll just finish up with a few final words.
Make it friendly, okay?
Yes, sure.
My goodness, I guess I've aged.
I can't do this any more.
But I will prepare a secret recipe...
to beat you next time.
I will wait for you.
Cut. That was good.
Hyun Jeong, finish it up.
That's awful.
They didn't edit anything out.
My gosh, look at him.
It does feel great,
but I'm afraid of what people might think of Goongnakwon.
We have Myeong.
Mr Ha is nothing but an old melody.
No one wants to hear that.
The VIP room is booked three months ahead.
Our sales are at the highest.
Come on.
You can smile now.
(Ha Jung Tae)
(Moo Myeong)
(Moo Myeong Chef)
(Moo Myeong defeats his teacher! Mr Ha became an embarrassment.)
I'm not his teacher.
(Goongnakwon's Mr Ha is a professional at breaking noodles.)
What does it say?
I'm a professional at breaking noodles?
This happened because you're competitive.
If you lost in that match,
you should've praised your student for doing well.
If you did that, you would've been acknowledged...
as a generous adult.
It's easier said than done.
Don't compete with him. Use him.
It's what you're good at.
Don't keep that popular boy only inside of Goongnakwon.
Let him volunteer for good causes,
and you can go with him.
You couldn't have a better election campaign.
Feed him well before you eat him.
That way, he'll have a lot to eat.
- You're not bad. - You're the teacher.
(Goongnakwon's New Adventure)
Make Goongnakwon's name smaller.
Goongnak Foundation invested everything into this.
We don't need Goongnakwon.
You'll face oppositions.
I can break them, too.
Why are you in such a rush?
I can go into politics...
only after I clear this problem.
Also,
there is someone I must send away.
Our last episode received great attention.
It's all thanks to you.
That's why it's important to have a loser.
It brings out the winner.
I know that you did that on purpose to help me stand out.
Thank you.
Stay outside.
Why are we here?
Please take care of this place.
I am Goongnakwon's head of noodles.
Are you doing this because of the rise in sales?
Is this because of your management rights?
Goongnak Foundation will fully invest in this place.
We'll split the profit in half.
This is very generous,
but I can't leave Goongnakwon.
Let me make a proposal.
I will run this restaurant three days a week.
I will remain there as Head of Noodles.
Also, I want to be publicly recognised as your successor.
Is it my turn to answer?
Resign from your post...
as Head of Noodles.
The moment you resign, you'll earn my trust.
That's how you'll become my successor.
I promise.
I can't approach Da Hae.
But I can't stay away from her, either.
I don't know what to do.
I really don't.
Please, tell me.
(Gil Yong, Mr Ha, Myeong)
I loved coming to this building.
A man who lied in there would listen to anything...
and everything I had to say.
But...
I misunderstood you and thought that you killed my mum.
I came here to apologise.
I still don't forgive you, though.
The fact that you abandoned me does not change.
What will you do from now on?
You can become a director...
of Goongnakwon with the shares you have.
You don't need to wander off.
What brought me here was...
my mother's death,
but what kept me going was making noodles.
I like noodles.
I don't really care about those shares.
Unbelievable.
We can barely keep Goongnakwon going.
What is this sub-brand about?
Also, how can you send him away?
You're trying to ruin Goongnakwon in order to make it yours.
I won't approve of this.
Also, you can't make such a decision...
with your shares. Not a chance.
This is a power of attorney...
that allows me to exercise Da Hae's share.
What?
I have 30 percent of the shares, and Da Hae has 20 percent.
That's 50 percent in total.
I don't think we'll lose.
What about the Moon family?
Us two and the Moon family...
adds up to another 50 percent.
Will you push ahead with this?
I will...
resign.
What are you talking about?
I resign from Head of Noodles...
as of now.
You.
How can you do this to me?
How can you abandon Goongnakwon...
just to go work for Chimyeon Restaurant?
Are you insane?
What happened?
Tell me.
Why are you betraying me?
Tell me, you little jerk.
Everything I say right now will sound like an excuse.
But I will promise you this.
I will make sure Goongnakwon falls into your hands.
Shut it.
I am determined...
to destroy you from now on.
So...
try to hold out.
(For Ko Gang Sook)
Congressman So Tae Seop, this is Gang Sook.
I must become his successor...
to win back your name, Father.
If he wants,
I'll even have to be able to give him my heart.
That's the only way he'll trust me.
Only then, will he tell me his secrets...
including your name, Father.
Mr Ha.
Congressman So is here.
Congressman So?
You could have called ahead.
I did.
But I came here myself since you did not respond.
So tell me.
Did you think about it?
Three months isn't enough time.
If something goes wrong...
How will you get into politics with such a weak determination?
Did I ever tell you that I wanted to go into politics?
You seem to assume that I want to be a politician.
It's as if your script has a conclusion.
(DNA Testing Centre)
(Ha Jung Tae is Kim Da Hae's biological father.)
You seem to assume that I want to be a politician.
It's as if your script has a conclusion.
Anyone who doesn't take you seriously is in for a huge shock.
You should play nice.
What if I were to bite you?
Pour me a drink.
Pour me a glass, you jerk.
You're a beast who killed a woman with an ashtray.
Are you trying to pretend to be human now?
(Master of Revenge)