(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 18)
Oh, no. Tae Ha!
No!
What are you doing? Go take care of her.
Yeo Kyung.
Take her to the hospital first.
I will take care of the rest.
Dokku, you jerk.
Why are you here?
Gil Sung.
What's wrong with you?
How dare you mess with a prosecutor?
Listen to me.
You better hide yourself no matter what.
You don't need to care what Mr Ha says.
If you show up here ever again, I will kill you.
Do you understand?
If I don't get to take care of this right,
I will be dead anyway.
There are a lot of congressmen...
and prosecutors involved in this mess.
If you think there could be a way out,
you are totally mistaken.
Just take this money...
and back off.
You can't even handle me.
Do you understand?
Come in.
Take a seat.
I will tell you why I called you first.
Da Hae is exceptionally kind towards you.
Is there a reason why you approached her?
I don't understand what you mean.
She was like that when we appeared on TV together.
And even when we elected the new Master of Noodles.
I believe...
you're behind all of that.
Are you saying that out of concern as an advisor?
Or are you saying that as her father?
Did you know that?
It is an open secret.
Everyone knows that but pretends not to know.
Stop having any influence on Da Hae.
Make sure to keep your distance from her.
I can't do that if you are saying that as an advisor.
Da Hae has a talent to run Goongnakwon.
I will stay close to her and help her out.
If you're saying it as a father, I still can't do that.
You have no right to say that.
Do as I say.
Don't let things get out of hand.
Now, I will tell you why I'm here.
I want you to empty this office.
This office is not for an advisor.
I will give you three days to do so.
And stop visiting...
the kitchen.
I don't want the kitchen getting involved...
in your political affairs.
You act as if you've got the world in your hands.
If we think of Goongnakwon as a small world,
you're not mistaken.
Since I won the position, I should take my trophy.
And you are my trophy.
You said you wanted to take back your father's name.
I have a name to take back as well.
Once I take it back,
things will become more interesting.
I don't need any trophies.
I will just smash everything.
I will give you three days.
Vacate the office completely.
Anything remaining will be thrown away.
You should sleep more.
You didn't collapse because you got hurt.
The doctor said it was because you were too tired.
What a mess.
You and I were lucky.
It was Mr Ha, wasn't it?
He'll try again when he finds out that they failed.
There is no guarantee that we will be lucky again.
I have you.
You will stop them.
Yeo Kyung.
I'll show them what happens...
if they mess with a prosecutor.
They will do the same thing again if I let it slide.
I will wipe them out.
I feel dizzy.
Get some sleep. I will be here until you fall asleep.
(Identification Card: Park Tae Ha)
Is she all right?
What about you?
Are you worried about me?
You almost got stabbed. How can I not worry about you?
The only problem with you is your concentration.
Is it true...
that Mr Ha ordered my father to kill?
It's true.
He probably didn't say it out loud.
But he did give your father drugs and a knife.
That's practically telling him to go kill someone.
Tae Ha, get away from Mr Ha...
if you're not planning on killing him.
He has a talent for...
ruining people.
You will be used and discarded...
just like your father.
I can't get leave right now.
Why? Is it because of that friend of yours?
At first it was because of my friends,
but now, I have someone else I need to protect.
Please take good care of Yeo Kyung.
(Mr Ha)
It's Mr Ha.
Hey, let's quit while we still can.
(Dokku)
- It's Ha Jung Tae.
-  Hi, Jung Tae.
How are you?
Don't hang up.
I have something to say.
After seeing what you did yesterday,
I'm thinking that you're pretty desperate.
Yesterday?
Gil Sung and his boys...
have disappeared and won't take your calls.
So there's no point in trying to find them.
This is your last warning.
I didn't kill you...
because I didn't want to make Da Hae an orphan.
But if you keep causing trouble,
I'll go back to Goongnakwon.
And when I do,
you will really end up dead.
Do you understand?
What happened to your face?
I got drunk and fell, Sir.
How did you afford the drinks?
See if everything's still there.
Thank you.
You can go.
What is it?
I think Mr Ha knows about us.
It's because you misplaced that photo of us.
No.
Maybe you gave it to him.
Do you think I betrayed you?
How did you find out?
It was Mr Ha.
He showed it to me himself.
Why are you still with him?
I know why you came here,
but it doesn't explain why you're still here.
Leave.
Then I'll trust you.
I will leave when everything's done.
End whatever revenge it is that you want.
I think you and Yeo Kyung...
are both in danger.
Mind your own business.
I can take care of myself.
Don't be so sure.
That's what Yeo Kyung said.
Go and see her.
Bye.
(New Health Hospital, Room 230)
Are you looking for someone?
Yes, Chae Yeo Kyung.
She was in Room 230, but she left.
Shouldn't you stay for longer?
I have no time to.
Where are the men?
They're...
(Myeong)
I sent them on their ways,
so don't look for them.
Poking a dying fire will only...
spread the embers.
Should I let them off when they attacked a prosecutor?
This time around, I think...
they were just trying to kidnap you.
But if you corner and threaten them,
they'll bring weapons next time.
They won't care who you are...
if they feel their lives are being threatened.
Just focus on getting Mr Ha.
Did you send...
the witness application?
It's because he said he's ready to give a statement.
Ignore the form if you don't need it.
Are you sure that he will give a statement?
Human beings can be very fickle.
So I can't really be sure.
But I think he will.
Look after him.
I'll subpoena him soon.
It's fun to hang around with a prosecutor.
What will you do now?
Hello.
Why are you acting like you're guilty of something?
Prosecutor Ahn, what are you doing here?
I'm Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung.
Prosecutor Chae.
If I'd known you were so pretty,
I'd have come in for questioning.
I think we'll be meeting often anyway.
Your aide wasn't enough to arrest Mr Ha.
I think I need to take you down...
to make the arrest.
What in the world is she saying?
Prosecutor Ahn, translate for me.
Are you deaf or what?
Sir.
You can pick 1 of 2 options.
You can go in for breaking tax laws...
and pay a fine.
It will be embarrassing,
but you can stay in Congress.
If you refuse to cooperate,
as soon as the provisional session ends,
I will have you detained.
A minimum of 3 and a maximum of 5-year sentence.
That's what you'll get.
Why are you being so harsh?
Are there any other options?
No.
I choose number one.
Under one condition.
I want you to give me Mr Ha.
I'll pay you well.
I'll think about it.
Go on.
It's about Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung.
Yes, I heard she came to work today.
I need you...
to put more pressure on her.
She should be suspended or dismissed,
but I think someone on the inside is helping her.
Aren't you the one who caused the trouble?
Why are you asking me...
to clean up your mess?
You gave me a lot of money to put into the foundation.
I gave you an extra amount of shares.
Can't I even ask for a favour?
Then do something in return.
You have cash in your own safe.
Sir!
I apologise.
If I touch my clients' money,
I die.
You know that.
That's why everyone wants this badge.
Once you have this,
it's no longer embezzlement.
It becomes an investment.
Leave for now.
We'll talk again.
Must you suck the marrow out of my bones, too?
People who crave meat just aren't full enough.
You can finally say you're full when the marrow's gone.
Do you understand?
Get rid of this first.
It's darkens the room.
What are you doing?
Hello.
You're here just in time.
The couch won't fit in the annex.
No one's going to the annex.
You gave me three days.
I changed my mind.
I wanted to get things over and done with.
We're planning to get rid of the secret room.
My gosh, you even fitted a rotating wall for a door.
What was that for? You're so weird.
Are you a spy or what?
We'll suspend the company card you have.
What else was there? That's right.
I fired your henchmen.
It doesn't look so nice to have...
burly men in suits running around the place.
And are you anticipating a terrorist attack or what?
Why would you need a dozen security personnel?
Am I wrong?
You really seem to be enjoying this.
Can you tell?
Oh, dear. I should try harder to hide my feelings.
Do you know how I feel?
I think I'm floating on cloud nine.
It's thrilling, and I can't get enough of it.
You better stay on that cloud nine.
Because I'll drop you from it.
My gosh, you're so scary.
I'm so scared that I feel like crying.
Watch out.
He will stop at nothing to get back...
what he lost.
Gang Sook's a formidable woman.
She wants me to sleep...
where her father died.
Does she want me to have nightmares?
Shall I find you a place to stay outside?
That's what my wife wants.
If I leave now, I'll never be able to come back.
- Mr Park.
-  Yes, Sir.
Do you think it's over for me?
I can see you're cornered.
That will soon change.
I'll win the nomination and become a congressman.
Then I'll get everything back.
The one who laughs the most now...
will shed the most tears then.
(Making the broth)
Why are you telling me this?
Royal pheasant buckwheat noodles.
Mr Ha stole the recipe my father perfected.
Was it Mr Ha again?
Well...
It's nothing like that.
Come in. We need to talk.
Okay.
Do me a favour.
I hope you'll say yes.
I want you to stop Mr Ha from doing...
any more bad things.
And stop getting hurt yourself.
Promise me.
Go to sleep.
It's late.
(Connecting)
Please sign the receipt.
We'll send you a team of bodyguards if you wish.
No thanks.
Sir.
Hello.
(Top Secret)
Put it in there.
Where's the confidential document?
(Defence Industry Corruption)
Where's the original copy?
You'll have it...
once I get nominated for Congress.
That would be fair.
What's that, Sir?
Answers to the questions you'll be asked.
You're practically a member of Congress already.
Even a corpse would get elected in your constituency.
Memorise those answers and pass the screening.
Yes, Sir.
And...
until your candidacy is confirmed,
do nothing but breathe.
You cannot do anything.
If you...
go after someone like you did with Yeo Kyung,
it'll be over for you.
I'll remember that.
You will soon see...
why people go crazy for a small gold badge.
You will experience it for yourself.
For the peace of our nation,
and the happiness of its people,
I will...
I will... I will strive hard.
You look like you're exiled.
She really locked you in here, didn't she?
I can go wherever I want to.
Just not to the kitchen.
Guess what we call people who can't enter the kitchen.
"Outsiders".
You're being treated as an outsider now.
I'm just leaving it to her for a while.
I will take it back later.
How?
How will you do that?
I'm out of Goongnak Foundation because of you.
I have nothing to rely on right now.
Are you just going to stand by and watch?
The most brutal revenge...
is to make a person miserable at their happiest moment.
Let them be happy for now.
I will make them miserable pretty soon.
Give me your shares of Goongnakwon as you promised.
I think I'll feel more relieved...
if I had that with me.
I already told you.
I need to get nominated first.
Then I'll give you the shares.
Mr Ha.
Don't pick a fight with me.
What will you do if I turn my back on you, too?
Just wait.
I never...
go against what I promised.
Top Head of Noodles...
Do you know who Myeong really is?
(Operation Record)
He's the one who spoiled the 100th anniversary banquet.
I found him.
The person who spoiled the banquet.
No, Choi Soon Seok.
I...
found him, Sir.
Choi Soon Seok?
The reason he joined Goongnakwon was to get you.
He came here to seek revenge for his father.
That's Moo Myeong.
The hospital records of him with a stab wound.
The invitation list for the 100th anniversary banquet.
Everything is in there.
(Invitation List)
But...
how do you have these files?
I was planning to take you down...
by working together...
with Myeong.
We were accomplices.
You're...
Choi Soon Seok, aren't you?
You're not Moo Myeong.
You're Choi Soon Seok, Ha Jung Tae's son.
And you're Kim Gil Do.
Gangnam-gu San, 323-37.
It's right here.
This is where you were born.
Seongbuk-dong, 387-18.
It's So Tae Seop's house...
where you committed your first crime.
And...
Gangwon Province, Bongpyeong, Yupo-ri,
802-2.
It's where you killed my father...
and my mother.
On top of that,
you even stole my father's name and entire life there.
And here,
Choi Soon Seok will steal everything from Kim Gil Do.
Right where you were born!
Shut your mouth.
If I wanted to kill you,
I could have killed you a thousand times already.
Do you know why I kept you alive all this time?
I kept you alive to take everything away from you.
Ha Jung Tae...
gave birth to a monster.
I'm not done yet.
I have one more thing to take from you.
So wait for me.
I'll take the one thing you'll never want to lose.
I'll cruelly take it away from you.
Jung Tae.
Look at your son.
He's become a monster like me...
just to kill me.
Ha Jung Tae.
Just wait a little more.
I will...
send your son to you.
My goodness.
I love this place.
We can shoot a TV programme here.
Why did you want to see me?
I don't think you wanted to show off your restaurant.
A live show?
Yes.
Viewers can participate in the show.
It will be a new venture.
I agree.
But it takes a lot of time...
to shoot a TV cooking programme.
There are also a lot of variables to consider.
Congressman So...
Is he doing all right?
Sorry?
Well, yes.
He talks about you from time to time.
Drop by Chimyeon Restaurant with him sometime.
It would be nice...
if Mr Ha could also join you both.
Okay.
I will give it a try.
Since we're on it, we might as well make it very big.
Mr Ha...
should appear on the programme no matter what.
And this is...
not my plan.
It's yours.
Do you understand...
what I mean?
Of course I do.
Just make sure to keep your end of the secret.
Then I will work on it.
Didn't he go crazy yet?
It must be hard for him to stay sober.
Mr Ha?
Why are you asking me about him?
I thought you were his best friend nowadays.
I heard you guys stick together like glue. Am I wrong?
What are you talking about?
I'm planning to appoint Top Head of Noodles...
as Master of Noodles.
He only recently became the successor.
We left...
the head of noodles position open for three years.
We should be more careful for Master of Noodles.
If I leave that spot vacant,
Jung Tae will watch for a chance to take it back.
Can't you see that I'm trying to end things properly?
Top Head of Noodles...
can't become Master of Noodles.
Why not?
Are you jealous of me getting things my way?
Top Head of Noodles...
has taste blindness.
He's lost his sense of taste.
How can he become the master of noodles...
when he can't even taste things properly?
- Don't you think?
-  Are you sure?
Why would I lie to you about something like this?
If the Ko family finds out,
it'll be hard for him to remain as the successor.
So stop talking nonsense.
Wow, he's like Batman.
He is amazing.
Don't you think?
He cooks noodles so well...
even without a sense of taste.
He's like Batman, don't you think?
Gang Sook!
Ms Seol.
Listen to me.
You've lost your means, so stay out of it.
Stop poking around here and there...
with your petty share of Goongnakwon.
Goongnakwon is mine.
Don't you get it?
If you don't,
just memorise it.
Put it in your head.
Put that here.
- Yes, Ma'am.
-  This way.
Make sure not to scratch the floor.
Okay.
Father.
This is where Kim Gil Do's desk used to be.
Here, he used to sign papers using your name.
I took it back.
This is where Kim Gil Do lived his glory days.
He got all this with your name and cooking secrets.
I erased them all.
And this is...
where he was born and raised.
I will destroy everything so he can never come back.
Please wait a little more.
Just a little bit more.
It's not about the law but its enforcement.
We'll discuss these important problems...
regarding enforcement.
Steal and change.
Then imitate.
I don't need to try hard to be creative.
I'll steal, change and imitate.
You're right.
Did my car change, too?
I'm fine.
Today's the screening day for the by-elections, right?
Yes, Prosecutor.
There must be reporters here.
There probably are.
Do you want to go and watch?
(By-election nominations screening)
Mr Ha.
(Korean Liberal Party)
I am Ha Jung Tae, a potential candidate.
Even the great Master of Goongnakwon...
gets nervous sitting here, right?
There isn't a single person here...
who never had a bowl of noodles there.
Just think of this as one of our casual lunches.
Thank you, Sir.
Shall we begin?
No one would believe that this is your first election.
You look relaxed as if this is your third election,
and you're very opinionated.
Also, I like how persuasive you are,
how humble you speak...
and how comfortable you are around people.
You're a natural.
You're too nice.
Good things will happen as you partner with me.
I trust you, Congressman.
It's been a while,
Congressman and Master of Noodles.
What brings you here?
Master of Noodles, I request you to voluntarily...
follow me for Congressman Choi's case.
Why does this have to be now?
Why does this have to be here?
There are reporters here,
and I thought you'd lay low in sake of your nomination.
I think this is a great timing.
I reject to go with you.
I think people will talk.
Follow her before this gets too big.
Mr Ha, what's going on?
Prosecutor Chae, tell us something.
Will this affect his nomination?
Are you following her?
- Tell us something.
-  Tell us.
- Will you say a word?
-  Sir, please.
I think you have something to say.
- Did you keep your promise?
-  Will you go?
How long has Mr Ha been in the interrogation room?
It's been seven hours.
Leave him there.
He's probably going insane.
Congressman So saw this,
and he knows about Congressman Choi's case.
He's probably deep in thought.
The results are obvious.
They'll call me after they talk.
If you witness,
they'll let you off with a fine.
That's what they say,
but I can never trust the prosecution.
Many men's lives were ruined...
after giving into the prosecution's request.
If you don't, you'll definitely be put into prison.
Well, that's why I'm saying this.
If they look deep enough,
they will find Goongnak Foundation.
I'm afraid you'll get lured in, too.
That'll be bad.
That's why I ask...
to be acquitted.
It'll be great for both you and me.
You can go and witness.
Make sure it doesn't go to Goongnak Foundation.
You must stop them.
Instead, sell Mr Ha in return.
What will happen to his nomination?
He must've paid...
a fortune for this nomination.
I didn't ask him to pay me.
He paid me because he wanted to.
Call the special department and put an end to this.
Some of us will die, and some of us will live on.
Yes, Congressman Choi.
That sounds great.
You may go home.
Did you get what you wanted?
In a way.
What about you?
You couldn't even make a scratch on me.
Mr Ha.
Congressman Choi is here.
Congressman Choi?
Nominations for by-elections are reported today, right?
Yes.
You must be nervous.
I remember when I first walked...
into Chimyeon Restaurant 30 years ago.
I only trusted the royal pheasant buckwheat noodles...
when I went in there.
That young man with bad hair became who I am today.
Who I will be in 30 years will be...
decided today.
You asked me if I was nervous.
To be honest, I am more nervous today...
than I was 30 years ago.
I am going to the special department.
Even the most powerful people get ruined...
when they go to...
the special department.
That department was set up to catch men like us.
Even Dokku who received money was released.
They can't press charges on lost money.
Mr Ha.
Don't think ill of me.
What do you mean?
Things don't always go our way, right?
It's not like...
I wanted things to be like this.
Anyway, we should get a drink later.
Thanks for the noodles.
(Professor Lee Geon Sil nominated, Ha Jung Tae fails)
I feel so refreshed.
I don't need anything else.
I didn't know they'd drop him for something like this.
A prickle under my nail hurts...
more than a spear in someone else's body.
They obviously didn't want Mr Ha and his problems.
This is why politics is scary.
When will Congressman Choi come?
Tomorrow.
You never know when he'll change his mind.
Don't let your guard down until then.
Yes, Sir.
Anyway,
how much further are you planning to go with Mr Ha?
Foreign exchange control law? Tax law?
I'm going to add murder and murder instigation charges.
Make sure you do it right.
The harder you try, the harder he'll resist.
Tae Ha.
Mr Ha.
Do you want a drink?
Yes, Sir.
I know that you killed my father.
But I won't kill someone like my father did.
Instead,
I will watch you go down...
as I stay next to you.
Did you know?
Your daughter...
asked me to stop you from sinning.
But I know that I can't do that.
The only person who can stop you from sinning...
is yourself.
It's me, Congressman.
Did you get a good night's sleep?
Thanks to you, I did.
I give up on the nomination.
I will no longer bother you...
regarding that issue.
You make me feel so sorry.
But...
I can't go to prison.
I gave up on my dreams,
and I gave up Goongnak Foundation.
I don't think I deserve to go to prison.
I want to meet you...
and Congressman Choi.
Please intervene.
It's not too hard for us to meet,
but it won't be easy...
to persuade the prosecution.
I will...
give you a little gift.
I can't leave you like this if you're so persistent.
Let's meet up.
We'll find a way...
between the three of us.
My house?
Sure.
Okay.
I'm so sorry, Prosecutor Chae.
I can't be there because I have an emergency.
Excuse me, Congressman Choi.
I won't let you get away with breaking this promise.
I'm so scared.
I just got goose bumps.
I wish I can show you.
Anyway, I'm a bit busy. Goodbye.
(Dokku)
It's me, Mr Lee.
May I meet the one who wrote the witness application?
I will wait for you.
There are disappointments
But there aren't much of them left
How much will he bring? I have to make it even.
I still walk down the road
Of the life I have left
Gosh, Mr Ha is really not sensible.
After I'm done walking down this road
I'll drive.
You can go and rest.
Give me the keys.
I'll accompany you, Sir.
Do as you're told.
I'm the one who decides.
Please give it another thought.
Welcome, Mr Ha.
Take a seat.
You made a wise decision.
This isn't the only election in your life.
And things don't always go...
the way we plan them to. I hope you understand.
I'm sorry for making you worried.
My goodness.
I have a weak heart.
Don't you have something to give to us?
Come on.
Of course.
My life depends...
on what you'll say.
We all have to help each other out.
And even if you get elected,
there are people who get dropped later.
What do they call it?
Oh, right, it's "vacancy".
They call those empty seats "vacancy".
I'm trying to say that there are other opportunities.
Sure.
You seem determined to witness. I will trust you.
Let's begin with our basic investigation.
What's your name?
Hwang Sung Rok.
What was your position at Goongnakwon?
I was Ha Jung Tae's personal assistant...
and the operational manager of Goongnakwon.
For which crime of his will you be witnessing?
Murder, murder instigation,
numbers of embezzlement, breach of duties,
fabrication of the official documents,
assault, threat and much more.
I will witness on all of these.
I guess you haven't quit smoking.
I smoke from time to time...
when I get frustrated, like now.
Are you going to smoke?
Don't do it, Gil Do.
I'll put it back.
- Then...
-  One.
nothing happened, okay?
Do you understand?
One.
You're scaring me.
Is something wrong?
Two.
Kim Gil Do!
Three.
Are you crazy?
What have you done?
We now have...
a vacancy.
Can I...
take that spot?
(Master of Revenge)