(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
We now have...
a vacancy.
Can I...
take that spot?
(Episode 19)
Did you know?
I also started politics with a vacant spot.
Gil Do.
Stop living like a beast as of today.
If you keep living like one, I'll destroy you.
I asked if I could take the spot.
Sure, go ahead.
How will I stop a beast like you?
What is your name?
Hwang Sung Rok.
For which crime of his will you be witnessing?
Two cases of murder instigations,
numbers of embezzlement, breach of duties,
fabrication of the official documents,
assault, threat and much more.
I will witness on all of these.
Wait here.
Please spare me.
- Please.
-  Go apologise to Mr Ha.
No matter how much you beg, there's nothing I can do.
You can't kill a person.
But if you send me to Mr Ha,
it'll be the same thing as you killing me.
What would be the difference?
Shut his mouth.
Kim Da Hae! Kim Da Hae!
Let him talk.
Why did you just say Da Hae's name?
What do you think will happen if Congressman So...
finds out that Kim Da Hae is Mr Ha's daughter?
Do you think he will keep her alive?
How would So Tae Seop know about that?
I set things up so that...
everything will be revealed as soon as I die.
Are you telling me to believe your lie?
Whether you believe me or not...
is up to you.
But if what I said is true,
Kim Da Hae will die.
Mr Ha.
It's not...
over yet.
Something doesn't feel right.
Never mind.
Nothing will happen, right?
Stop imagining stuff. Everything will be fine.
Then I'm going to take my hands off now.
Let's go.
From instigation of murder to money laundering.
I can be a witness to everything.
Of course,
I have relevant evidence.
Tell me your conditions.
You're smart.
Dokku...
I mean, Lee Jeong Beom.
You dropped his charges.
That's why I surfaced.
I want full immunity...
on everything I did in the past.
Then I'll give you a statement.
I once sent a parcel to Ms Ko Gang Sook.
She didn't use it wisely.
I hope...
you don't make the same mistake.
I need time to think.
Take all the time you need.
But I'd rather you not take too long.
Where's Congressman Choi?
I haven't been able to reach him for three days.
He hasn't shown up in Congress...
or at his office.
I can't tell if he disappeared or if he's missing.
His aides also seem to be wary.
He must have gone into hiding.
Too bad we can't arrest congressmen during congress.
You scared me.
There's something you must see.
Based on trace evidence of burned charcoal...
and statements from family that he'd been under stress,
the police suspect the congressman took his own life.
A source close to Choi said his aide...
was jailed for violating foreign exchange laws...
and that the prosecutors were closing in on him.
- Yes, Chief.
-  They say this could've...
had an effect on his suicide.
I'll be right there.
Choi Sung Do was So Tae Seop's right-hand man...
who had secured his third consecutive term...
with a huge margin in the previous election.
This incident means a by-election must be held...
in Choi's constituency.
He wasn't my right-hand man.
You can't ignore the importance of experience.
It's only hard the fist time.
It becomes familiar the second time.
It's nothing the third time.
I didn't think you'd clean it up so nicely.
You'll be nominated immediately.
A lot of people are watching.
Lie low for now,
and prepare to be elected.
Don't you think I'd need something...
to prepare myself with?
My money and gold bars. You took them all.
Give me back...
what you haven't spent.
Right now.
That way, I can prepare.
You really don't know when to stop, do you?
You and I are in the same boat now.
We will either both live or both die.
I would rather we both live...
for a long, long time.
Bring me the original of the confidential document.
Then I will give you what I have.
I will think about it...
once I join Congress.
If you get it before then,
you'll chew me right up.
Why should I fill your greedy belly?
You already ate so much that...
you're full right up to your throat.
Am I wrong?
Do as you're told.
I'm the one who decides.
Please give it another thought.
Do me a favour.
Mr Ha.
Stop him from doing anything bad.
Focus.
I apologise.
Mr Park.
Do you want to study?
Pardon?
Night schools or online degrees.
You can study on the clock.
I'll make you my aide once I win the election.
Be prepared.
Are you listening?
Yes, Sir.
Sir.
You got ordered to stop investigating.
I will be transferred soon.
It'll be settled as soon as they find my replacement.
A criminal case that involves politics...
always gets messy like this.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
You're right. It's all your fault.
I worked so hard just to get here,
and you ruined it all with one case.
So get rid of Mr Ha once and for all.
What?
Cards are scary whey they haven't been shown yet.
Do you watch football?
Before the referee brings out a card,
the player will plead to stay in the game.
But once the red card comes out,
they curse as they walk off.
Why?
What's there to fear when they're out anyway?
That's me right now.
Sort it out fast.
You have until they find my replacement.
Thank you, Sir.
I'm closer to injustice than justice,
and I value personal revenge over public order.
So don't thank me.
Then why...
Try getting bibim guksu all over your face.
Then you'll understand why.
How do you like your job?
It's not bad.
I got fired after just three years.
Why is my face up there?
But still, you're the one...
who made Goongnakwon into what it is now.
I don't want to leave any trace of me here.
Take it down.
Yes, Sir.
- Right now.
-  Sir.
Do it.
Wait. Let me do it.
I'm slightly taller than you are.
Your name is...
Gil Yong, isn't it?
Yes, Sir. I'm Ko Gil Yong, the dishwasher.
Take it down, and put it at the annex.
Yes, Sir.
This cuts years off my life.
I thought it would stay up there for decades.
Why does he want it gone already?
You scared me.
What's this?
It's nothing, so don't bother.
(Defence Industry Corruption)
Who gave you this?
Don't ask. Give it back.
Was it Yeo Kyung?
Yes.
I'll keep it.
You can't leave it around.
I never left it lying around.
I tore my hair out trying to find the safest spot.
And I gave Yeo Kyung my word...
that I'd keep it safe.
I can keep it safer.
How can I trust you?
You work for Mr Ha.
What if you give it to him?
Gil Yong.
I don't know what this is, and I don't want to know.
But I know that this is very important to Yeo Kyung...
and that I must keep it safe no matter what.
So stay away.
Listen carefully.
Whoever has this becomes a target.
They could end up dead.
No. They will die.
If you have it, you'll die.
If Yeo Kyung has it, she will.
What if you have it?
Hi, Yeo Kyung.
Of course it's safe.
Now?
Okay.
She wants to see us.
All of us.
Congressman Choi killed himself?
That would never happen.
Cockroaches never commit suicide.
Kim Gil Do has to be involved.
No. Is it both So Tae Seop and Kim Gil Do?
The man who made Tae Ha's father a murderer...
is Kim Gil Do.
We can put pressure on him with the secret document.
If it goes to Congressman So,
he'll no longer need Kim Gil Do.
But that means we have no way of convicting him.
If Congressman So gets it,
he'll try to cover his tracks.
That includes Yeo Kyung.
Fortunately, I'm still a prosecutor.
He can't do anything to me yet.
I'll offer a deal.
It's too dangerous.
Let's summarise.
We make a deal with So Tae Seop before Myeong's show.
We'll arrest Kim Gil Do after the TV show,
and then see to it that he rots in jail.
Yes, let's do that.
Until now,
we fought the same enemy separately.
In our bids to keep the others safe,
we fought separately from the inside and out.
Let's stop doing that.
Do you want some noodles?
Three, four, five...
Gosh.
Just look at this place.
They treat you worse than a useless old man.
What brings you here?
Now that you got the nomination, we should get to work.
You can find an office and hire the campaigners.
That's nothing.
Why don't we do a live show?
Let's not waste your last TV appearance.
We can bring a panel on board...
and let the public join in live.
Korea's first ever live cooking show...
should create quite a buzz.
I'm no longer Master of Noodles.
It could look bad.
Shall I tell you how to do well in politics?
You must be good at pretending.
Pretend to be just, pretend to care for the weak...
and pretend to be sincere.
You're a natural at that,
so I'll just set the stage for you.
Have some fun. Don't waste a great opportunity.
Let's do it.
We got him.
He'll go on the live show.
Good. Well done.
(Top Secret)
(Congressman So Tae Seop)
Prosecutor Chae.
What do you want?
You want to see me?
Is there a reason we should meet?
I have something to explain and show you.
Do you still have something I'd care about?
K120-17.
What do you say?
You said you couldn't find it.
Why do you have it?
Did you deceive me?
Isn't it more important that I have it now?
Let's meet up. Come over.
It's been a while.
Yes, it has been a while.
But am I the only one happy to see you all?
Why did you want to see us?
As you all know, I am running for Congress.
I'll be busy and unable to care about Goongnakwon.
I called everyone here because I thought...
it would be better to entrust someone with my shares.
Just keep it instead of causing us more trouble.
He wants to erase Goongnakwon from his identity...
at least until the election is over.
I wouldn't do that. Goongnakwon is my root.
We'll see about that.
Let's see what happens after you transfer your shares.
Don't be too afraid. I won't bite.
We can't stop him from exercising his rights.
Let's hear who you'll entrust them to.
Ms Seol, I hope you'll run Goongnakwon well.
This is unexpected.
Why did you choose me?
You are the only person here that I can trust.
Now that you have a share of 40 percent,
if Top Head of Noodles wavers, teach him well...
until I return.
Then I won't wait to say this.
Here's what I think.
I cannot...
accept you as Mr Ha's successor.
There are rumours that you can't properly taste food.
That's impossible. Don't say such nonsense.
He cooked royal pheasant buckwheat noodles perfectly.
Don't get so upset. He just has to prove me wrong.
Isn't this show going to be live?
Yes.
I'd like you to cook royal pheasant buckwheat noodles.
Prove yourself without any editing or tricks.
Then I'll believe you.
Very well.
But if I do prove myself on live TV,
accept me as Master of Noodles.
Of course I will.
(Defence Industry Corruption)
Where's the original?
You'll have it...
as soon as I get nominated.
How dare they.
They tried to play me.
Come in.
Aren't you Ha Jung Tae's man?
I'm Park Tae Ha, Sir.
What are you doing here?
What do you want?
This is the confidential document you wanted.
Am I right?
It's the original copy.
Why did you bring it instead of Mr Ha?
What do you think you're doing?
I didn't come here on behalf of Mr Ha.
I've been keeping this, and I always will.
Don't even try to take it from me.
If you try to take it,
I will leak it to the press.
You are begging me to kill you.
Do you know that?
I don't know politics.
So threatening or appeasing me will be useless.
I will just say what I wanted to say.
It's up to you to decide.
Go ahead.
Just do whatever Prosecutor Chae asks you to do.
If you do that,
the documents will be yours.
What's the relationship between you two?
I won't be answering any questions.
Please do what I just told you to do.
Then I'll make sure to keep my end of the deal.
How dare you try to make a deal with me?
I can...
because your life depends on what I have.
What else do you need?
Yes, you're right. You are.
But the probability is that you'll end up dead.
This isn't a deal. It's you playing your last card.
When you die,
you'll think of what I just said.
I'm sure I'll think of someone when I die,
but it won't be you.
Forget it.
I know you won't lie to me.
What exactly do you want?
I have a witness to accuse Kim Gil Do.
I need your help...
to have the witness testify.
Are you listening to me?
You guys are too ignorant about the world.
But do you know what's funny?
That is what scares me about you guys.
Did you just say "you guys"?
Try to catch Kim Gil Do.
This is your last chance.
You may go now.
Yes, Sir.
How did it go? What about Yeo Kyung?
Did you do something wrong?
I took care of it.
Yeo Kyung will be fine.
Are you sure?
Can I trust you?
Yes.
Just make sure to keep it to yourself.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Do you have time right now?
I'm not sure.
I'm off now, though.
I'll see you in the parking lot.
Hey, I said I wasn't sure. Don't you get it?
It could mean that I don't have time.
But the probability is that you'll end up dead.
When you die,
you'll think of what I just said.
Get in.
Am I your boss or what?
That's okay.
Where are we going anyway?
You'll see.
Why aren't you eating?
Now I believe that...
you've never gone out with a girl.
What does that have to do with dumplings?
Forget about it.
It is delicious.
I ate...
dumplings with Mr Ha a while back.
That was the day...
I saw you at the charnel house.
I found out...
you were his daughter that day.
I don't want to talk about it.
My father was a murderer.
He killed two people.
Then he was executed.
I'm a son of a murderer with bad blood.
I wanted to escape from that fact.
So I ran away desperately.
And now I'm here.
I don't want to run away any more.
And I don't want you to run away, either.
No matter who your father is...
or what he does,
it is not your fault.
Just endure it from where you stand.
I wanted to tell you this.
What if I still run away?
Hold onto me so I won't.
I had a good time.
Do you know what you smell of?
You smell of sweat, car...
and...
dumplings.
I'm sorry.
But when all that combines together,
do you know what it smells like?
It smells like Tae Ha.
I thought you've never dated anyone before.
You're right, I haven't.
This is my second kiss, though.
You probably don't remember because you were drunk.
You were my first kiss.
Good night.
Make is short.
- Like this?
-  There will be less people here.
- Can you edit this part?
-  I'll edit this.
Yes, that's a bit different now.
Da Hae.
You look good in the uniform.
Thank you.
What brings you here?
How are you?
I mean, your sense of taste.
It's not back yet.
But it's getting better.
I can help you with the live broadcast.
Let's make signs for salty, spicy and sour tastes.
We'll sign the measurements with our fingers.
There's no need for that.
I will do this alone.
But...
Thanks for your concern.
However, I can't let anyone help me with this.
I have to deal with this on my own.
My goodness, isn't your makeup artist here?
I guess she can't find this rusty old place.
Give it to me. I'll help you.
Are you nervous?
You've been on a number of TV shows.
I've never been on a live broadcast.
Just relax.
I'll give you a chance to look back on your life...
and to talk about your future during the show.
Don't miss that opportunity.
That's why I agreed to do this show.
I won't miss it for the world.
Just do whatever Prosecutor Chae asks you to do.
If you do that, the document will be yours.
Prosecutor General, it's me.
Come on, I wasn't the only one who was busy.
I have a favour to ask.
Will you do it?
I will owe you one if you do this for me.
So please help me out.
I guess you are really good.
What did you do to get this?
It's an emergency arrest warrant...
and a non-indictment order for Hwang Sung Rok.
(Emergency arrest warrant, Non-indictment order)
This had to be the prosecutor general.
Even Congressman So probably had to ask for a favour.
This is the final battle for Mr Ha and me.
Inspector Kim, let's go.
Yes, Prosecutor.
Do you want me to come along?
Have you seen the cue sheet?
The competition begins after 20 minutes of talking.
You have to make 3 types of noodles in 20 minutes.
Did you prepare the doughs?
Yes, they are matured, too.
Great. Let's do this.
Take a question from the spectator in the red shirt.
There won't be any problems, right?
Promise me.
What?
Promise me that you won't run away.
I promise.
Let's begin.
Cue.
They probably began, right?
They just began. It'll take us another 10 minutes.
Step on it.
I guess stealing, changing and mimicking...
became a trademark for Mr Ha.
I didn't know you had such a story.
All right, I'll take a question from our audience.
I wonder what kind of questions...
you'll have for these noodle experts.
Yes, the gentleman in a red shirt.
No.
Will you give him the microphone?
What's your question?
I have a question for Mr Ha.
Yes, I'm listening.
How does it feel to murder someone?
Hey, take the microphone from him.
You murdered a man,
and you instigated murder, too.
I want to know how you felt at that time.
What is he saying?
(DNA Test result)
I need some manpower.
No, not gangs.
Yes.
Find me a few men who can do some work.
(Ha Jung Tae and Kim Da Hae are biologically related.)
Ha Jung Tae.
I'm sorry for the disturbance.
You have too many enemies.
What are you going to do?
Should we stir things up a bit?
Why don't we listen to...
Myeong's story about when he first made noodles?
I learned to make noodles from my father.
He lived his entire life for noodles.
When he finally made royal pheasant buckwheat noodles,
he was betrayed and killed...
by a trusted friend.
Wait, excuse me.
Isn't Mr Ha the first man to finalise the recipe...
for royal pheasant buckwheat noodles?
Is that so?
Stop it.
Nothing will change.
No, things will change.
At least the world will know...
if you're a man or a beast.
Are you saying that...
Mr Ha killed your father and stole the recipe...
for royal pheasant buckwheat noodles?
He also killed my mother.
And he even stole my father's name.
The name Ha Jung Tae...
belongs to my father.
Don't run away.
If you run away now,
you'll run for the rest of your life.
Kim Gil Do.
This is that beast's name.
Gangnam-gu San 323-37.
His current office is where he was born.
Yupo-ri, Bongpyeong, Gangwon Province,
house number 801-2.
That's where I was born,
and it's where Kim Gil Do killed my father.
Mr Ha. Mr Ha.
He killed my mother, too.
On top of that,
he stole my father's name...
and his entire life.
What went wrong?
Since when...
did it all go wrong?
Why is this happening to me?
All I did was try my best to live my life.
Why?
(Emergency arrest warrant)
Choi Soon Seok.
Choi Soon Seok!
Stay still.
I'd just look out the window if I were you.
When you get there,
you'll never be able to come outside ever again.
I have a question, Prosecutor Chae.
I'll take your question once we're there.
When you arrest someone,
you bind up a person, right?
Shut up, Kim Gil Do.
But why do you...
leave one's head to move freely?
No.
Goongnakwon's advisor Ha Jung Tae was...
arrested and charged with various accounts...
including a violation of exchange control act, tax law,
murder and murder instigation, but he fled on the way.
Ha Jung Tae was arrested...
around 4pm during Goongnakwon's live broadcast.
- How's Yeo Kyung?
-  It's said...
- She's okay.
-  that he fled from the vehicle...
when the guard was low.
What will you do now?
The prosecution will arrest him soon.
He'll come to me.
We'll put an end to this.
You got what you wanted.
Everyone knows about him now.
He's completely finished.
You don't need to deal with him any more.
Tae Ha.
I want to see...
Kim Gil Do's face when he loses everything.
I will watch him with my own two eyes.
That's the end of my revenge.
Fine.
Do what you have to do.
I'll do what I have to do.
And you can...
protect Yeo Kyung from now on.
What do you mean?
I'm dumping her on you.
I've fully paid my debt...
to Yeo Kyung.
(Da Hae, Do Hyun Jeong, Dong Bae)
(Da Hae)
Your call has been forwarded...
(Unknown number, Hang-dong 7-ga 25-2, Jung-gu, Incheon)
Bring me the confidential document.
If you do, I'll let Da Hae live.
You have to come by yourself.
Yes, Mr Ha.
Wait, should I call you Kim Gil Do now?
Where are you hiding?
I want to make a deal.
I will give you the document right away.
Can you do something about this situation?
Where is the document?
How can you give me something you don't have?
Did you know?
The whole world knows except you.
There has to be another way.
There will be a way to turn things around.
Listen carefully. I'll tell you how to sort this out.
Your daughter, Da Hae,
is with me right now.
You're lying.
I just spoke to her.
Did you really?
That's strange. I have her gagged.
(New message)
(From So Tae Seop)
Let her go.
She has nothing to do with this.
Of course, she does. She's your daughter.
Let her go!
You just have to exchange your life for hers.
Isn't it simple?
There's a warehouse in Incheon.
I'll send you the address. Come right over.
If you die to save your daughter,
wouldn't that be a fair trade?
This should be fun.
Will her dad come for her,
or will Mr Park show up instead?
You have some guts.
Give me the document.
I don't have it.
I'll check to see if Da Hae's safe,
then I'll tell you where it is.
How can I trust you?
I'm here alone.
What more do you need?
Hello?
Are you okay?
Tae Ha?
Where are you?
Are you okay? Are you safe and sound?
Nothing's wrong.
It'll be fine.
It'll all work out.
Da Hae.
Go on. I'm listening.
Next time, I'll take you somewhere nice for a meal.
That still bugs me.
Why are you saying that?
I liked it.
Don't be silly.
Do me a favour.
Don't forget...
my smell.
Listen carefully.
I don't know what you're about to do.
Don't do it.
Don't. You can't do it.
If you hang up on me now, I'll hate you forever.
Are you listening?
I'll hate you until I die.
Tae Ha, what's going on?
Go to Da Hae right now.
What's wrong?
Is she in trouble?
Protect her.
Tae Ha. Tae Ha!
Let's end things here.
(Master of Revenge)
My friend died trying to...
bring Kim Gil Do down.
It's your revenge.
Do not involve us.
My friends are in this nightmare because of me.
You can pick 1 of 2 options.
Fire me.
Yeo Kyung wishes to see you.
Kim Gil Do will definitely show up.
Even if someone has to die, that's when it'll end.