In Dodo Group's...
Strategic Planning Department...
is a man called Byun Il Jae.
He's Congressman Hwang's son-in-law.
I was investigating him for embezzlement...
when I realised that money...
was going from him to Congressman Hwang.
That is how I first found out about...
the deep-set corruption surrounding the defence industry.
Gun Woo betrayed you.
Sir.
What is going on?
I didn't do it. It wasn't me.
No! Don't come to me!
I didn't do it! I did nothing wrong!
Go away!
I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
Can a person suddenly become schizophrenic?
It may happen when one is exposed with severe impact.
- When will he be diagnosed?
-  We'll begin as soon as...
he calms down.
It's not me. I didn't do it.
Please, no.
No.
Congressman Hwang, please say something.
What is your relationship with the defence industry?
Do you agree with...
- Get these reporters away.
-  the given charge?
- Sir, please.
-  Say something.
- Congressman.
Is it true that you are Chairman Do Choong's second son?
Please say a word about these rumours.
We won't take any private questions.
Please move.
I'm sorry, please move away.
Great job, Vice Chairman Do.
Forget about everything else...
and just focus on keeping the company profitable.
Yes,
Father.
What did he say?
Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo, who exposed this incident, was...
the second son...
- of Chairman Do Choong.
-  Idiots.
Mum! Why are you taking this out on me?
My goodness!
There are rumours that Do Gun Woo will become...
a candidate for the next chairman in place of Do Gwang Woo,
who's serving a sentence for creating slush fund.
Do Gun Woo that scumbag!
Darn it!
Let go of me!
I'm going to kill him! Do Gun Woo!
Let go!
What happened?
What do you mean that he's mentally ill?
He was shocked deeply after watching the hearing.
You should see him.
Are you sure Il Jae turned crazy?
We'll see when the results are out.
What about Choong Dong?
We searched his place and anywhere he might go to,
but there's no sign of him.
Why hasn't he shown himself to Il Jae?
It's weird.
I asked Cha Woo to check on the departure list with immigration.
Don't worry.
In Il Jae's state, nothing will change even if Choong Dong shows up.
Don't come near me! It's not my fault!
Don't come near me!
Honey, it's me. What's wrong with you?
- Don't come near me!
-  Be careful, he's dangerous.
Let me go! He's my husband.
Honey.
Honey, please put this down.
Don't be like this.
That's right. It's me, Ji Soo.
Your wife.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were suffering so much.
It's okay now.
I'll stay by your side.
- Die!
-  Honey.
Do you think you can fool me? You can't trick me!
- Die!
-  Honey!
Die! Die!
- Honey...
-  Die!
Honey.
The result is out.
It's worse than we thought.
Congresswoman Hwang.
It's okay.
How bad is it?
He will have to get treatment for at least a year.
Will he get better if he's treated?
Gi Tan, the result is out.
Il Jae has gone crazy for sure. It's serious.
The chairman plans on bringing you back to the office.
I won't be going back.
Do you still think...
you have more left to fight with Il Jae?
He's gone insane.
I don't know what it is, but...
No one knows when he'll be back to normal.
Jae Man...
is also looking for a way to get back, too.
When should the chairman expect you back?
Once this is all over,
I want to live an ordinary life.
- Ordinary?
-  Yes.
I want to get married and have kids like everyone else.
I want to live my life...
appreciating the smallest things.
What do you think about Shin Young?
I think the chairman has you in mind for her.
I have someone I love.
Of course.
Getting married to a rich girl...
is far from being ordinary.
Perfect timing. Get on.
I told you not to come.
What's the big deal? I was passing anyway.
- What is it?
-  I think I saw Choong Dong.
He's in the United States.
Are you sure about that?
Cha Woo found his name on a flight to Los Angeles.
I'm sure it was him.
You're just tired. Go home and get some rest.
Why is he telling me to come over so early in the morning?
Wait a minute. He can't be...
Are you here?
What if he's trying to come onto me?
No way.
Why would Gun Woo do that to me?
No, you never know with men.
What should I do?
What are you doing in front of the door?
I won't go in.
Why not?
How can I go into a bachelor's place?
You're here already?
Did you sleep over last night?
Sleep? We worked all night.
I bought some burgers. Would you like one?
This is your schedule for the day.
My schedule?
You have back-to-back interviews with the media this afternoon.
Do you expect me to interview?
You had many interview requests.
We'll deal with the media aggressively now.
Hae Il wrote the manuscript last night,
so memorise it.
Hae Il, go to the office...
and gather up the new SPDs by 9am.
Yes, Sir.
Is it because you went to the United States? You're so pretty.
Thank you.
By the way, why is the vice chairman gathering us?
Why did he call for us?
Starting today,
you will be in charge of a special project.
We only have six months to bring our sales back to normal.
So get ready to work overtime.
The Secretary's Office...
will be in charge of reviewing all...
the affiliated companies.
You should focus on...
finding out the truth behind corruptions of suspected companies.
The Business Department...
Why is he acting like he works hard?
Why do you think? He's trying to get...
brownie points from the chairman.
Is he attempting to swallow the company whole?
Does he really want to fight?
Vice Chairman.
I need to talk to you.
I'm in a meeting. Why don't you come down?
Did he just give an order in front of the employees?
Just go shoot that commercial with Soo Yeon. What's with the act?
You're making a ruckus.
Tomorrow at this time, I'll expect you to report me the updates.
You're dismissed.
Don't move.
Let me say this as your supervising director.
I said, you're dismissed.
If any one of you move, you'll regret it.
Hey, you! Hey!
Those rats.
The chairman assigned me to be in charge of this project.
I won't ask for your help, so don't get in the way.
How dare they ignore me?
I'll kill them all.
You must have been heartbroken after getting fired.
Can you share how you felt?
Firstly, I would like to thank the chairman and my family...
at Dodo Group for reaching out to me first.
I heard you are in charge of product quality control, too.
Yes, I am taking part in product safety test.
I am watching them very closely,
so you may trust our product once again.
Does that mean recent products made by Dodo Group...
are safe to use?
Of course, you can trust them.
You're a good talker.
Your script was excellent.
- Are those your only clothes?
-  Pardon?
You're wearing the same clothes for every interview.
Can't you think?
What can I do about my lack of clothes?
What time is our ad shooting at?
We have less than two hours left.
Only Soo Yeon will follow me.
I'll take everything on this rack in her size.
Are you getting all of these?
Pack up everything on this shelf in her size.
Gosh. Why did we get so many when we just need one?
Be quiet. I'm doing this for the company, not you.
- I'll return these later.
-  Who'll take used clothes?
May I sell these, then?
Don't you dare sell them. I will find you.
That little...
People are our hope.
Us here at Dodo Group would like to open the door to the future...
with you all.
I love you.
Cut, that was good.
We'll keep that one and try once more.
Okay.
Wow, Soo Yeon looks so pretty.
She does.
Sung Ae, you're prettier.
You're embarrassing. Stop it.
Okay.
Hey, look at him.
Ready, action.
People are our hope.
Us here at Dodo Group would like to open the door to the future...
with you all.
I love you.
How is Gun Woo doing?
He's working overtime every day.
There are rumours in the company...
after he was exposed to the media.
What is it?
People say that he will become your successor...
if he successfully carries out this project.
You can take care...
of odd rumours like that.
Yes, Sir.
You may leave.
Is there a chance that he'll consider...
Gun Woo as his successor?
He likes competent people,
so there may be a chance.
That will have a huge impact.
The shareholders will take anyone who makes more profit,
but Ms Hwang is the problem.
How dare he try to put Gun Woo as his successor?
I hope...
you don't make a mistake.
I don't know how I would react.
Number 9077, you have a visitor.
Father.
What brings you here?
Why else would I be here...
if it wasn't for you?
I can't face you right now.
Please leave.
Do you blame me?
You reaped what you've sown.
You don't have the rights to blame anyone.
Why do you think I made that slush fund?
Do you think I made it only for my own sake?
Then what?
What were you going to do?
I was going to make...
connections with people in business and politics.
And I wanted to enlarge our business.
I was sick of hearing...
that I am incompetent...
from you.
That's exactly where you went wrong.
You don't know your place.
Whom do I take after?
I am your son.
I was born like this. What can I do?
You keep saying that I am incompetent, but that's me.
What can I do?
I did not...
wish for much.
I just wanted you...
to tell me that I did a good job.
Had you only said...
that you trusted me,
I wouldn't have turned out like this.
You are the one...
who made me into a criminal.
I...
respected you a lot.
Even when you were hard on me,
I believed you were a great man.
But...
I won't...
do that any more.
I will spend my years in here.
You can take Gun Woo...
and have your happy life.
You are my eldest son.
When something happens to the both of you,
I'll be hurt deeper with you.
That's because you are my first son...
and the eldest.
I don't care if you blame me or if you're angry at me.
When you come out,
I hope...
you will understand...
at least a little bit of my heart.
Don't turn on the lights, Guk Cheol.
I...
don't want to see my nephew's face.
You should have...
never returned,
Guk Cheol!
Il Jae,
you should just live the rest of your life as a lunatic.
Even if you wake up,
Jae Man won't be there to help you fulfil your ambition.
I will...
destroy everything.
Congressman Hwang must leave his post...
for deceiving people!
- Leave your post!
-  Leave your post!
Congressman Hwang must leave post due to his corruptions!
- Leave your post!
-  Leave your post!
- Hwang Jae Man must leave his post!
-  Hwang Jae Man must leave his post!
A protest was held to demand Congressman Hwang Jae Man...
to leave his office after his corruption was exposed.
The special investigation bureau is determined to demolish...
all deep-set corruptions among the defence industry,
the army and the politicians.
Even under these accusations,
Congressman Hwang has not made a public appearance...
and is keeping silent.
(Kim Dae Woo)
- Yes.
-  Where are you? Let's meet.
I'm a bit drunk.
I'll send you a car. Come over.
Also, be careful about being tailed.
Okay, what's your plan?
You know what I'm like.
Nothing can...
stop me from going my way.
That's what I wanted to say.
We've been through so much just trying...
to put you in the Blue House.
We went through thick and thin.
We've seen and done everything to get all the way here.
It'd be a waste to give up now.
I hear you're under investigation.
Make sure to hide a tail behind you.
Someone has to take the blame for you.
I'm saying, be prepared...
to give away that tail when they get to you.
Were you ready to give away your tail?
All of my underlings are from the military.
No one will hesitate...
to go if I give them the order.
Which one are you planning...
to give up as your scapegoat?
Il Jae.
Byun Il Jae?
You're going to make your son-in-law take the bullet?
I never got any money from you.
My son-in-law received it as an investment for his business.
I never gave you any money either.
My underling handed it over.
It seems like...
we can close things off here.
They won't be able to interrogate a madman.
You're extraordinary.
The problem is...
the impact I'll get as a politician.
People started to question my morals.
Don't mind them.
Don't you know?
People don't vote for candidates that are innocent.
The ones that are innocent are incompetent.
During war, a scar on your face...
shows your competence.
How will the citizens know what you're thinking?
They can only vote based on people's looks.
(Prosecution Services)
I'm Special Prosecutor Jung Han Soo.
All right. Let's get this over with.
Follow me.
I'm not sure if the prosecutors will be able to handle him.
That prosecutor is a friend of mine.
He's a man of integrity. It'll be fine.
There are a lot of politicians trying to protect...
Jae Man.
Is it possible to get up-to-date progress on the investigation?
I'll talk to my friend and find out.
- Is he still keeping quiet?
-  He finally opened his mouth,
but he says his son-in-law took it all as investment for his business.
His son-in-law is in a mental institute right now.
I know. That's why this is getting complicated.
The investigation won't end here, will it?
The chief prosecutor intends on interrogating himself, so we'll see.
You haven't been coming out to the reunions.
I finally get to see you here.
This is confidential. Turn the switch off.
How was dinner?
I had a few spoonful's of soup...
and now, I don't feel so good.
If you don't cooperate,
you'll feel worse.
Didn't the attorney general...
say anything to you?
He told me, "Good luck".
The investigation...
on the defence industry is finished.
The truth is out,
so what else do you need?
What we want...
isn't the tip of the iceberg.
We must know who received how much money as a bribe.
If you cooperate, I'll make sure...
you get the minimum number of years.
All right.
Write down what I tell you.
Park Gwang Soo, the attorney general.
Prime Minister Go Joon Tae.
Chief Secretary Lee Seok Goo.
Jang Min Gook, the minister of national defence.
What's wrong?
Is that pen out of ink?
I have about 30 more on my list.
Listen.
Do you know how far the roots...
of a 1000-year-old gingko tree can reach?
Its roots get tangled up with roots of other trees.
You'd have to cut down the oak, zelkova,
pine and the empress.
That's the only way you can pull out the gingko tree.
If you don't have the courage to dig up the mountain,
don't even dare think about holding onto an axe.
You should...
add your name on that list.
I've been paying for your alumni membership.
- Are you all right?
-  I'm just tired.
- How is Il Jae?
-  He's still looking bad.
I need to take a rest.
The congressmen...
have requested for your termination.
According to Congresswoman Hwang,
the party's leader told you to hang in there.
Schedule...
a press conference tomorrow.
Due to my son-in-law's...
disgraceful acts,
we have raised so much concern in everyone.
We deeply apologise from the bottom of our hearts.
(Hanguk Party)
I will be taking full responsibility...
for what happened...
and will voluntarily resign from my position.
The resignation of the previous representative...
of the Hanguk Party, Congressman Hwang Jae Man,
influenced the running candidates for presidential election.
The Hanguk Party is holding an emergency meeting...
to deal with...
Honey.
What should I do?
There's nothing I can do by myself.
Wake up!
Il Jae!
Please come back.
Please...
Il Jae is doomed.
Have someone keep an eye on him.
A care centre would work.
I'll find a place.
Your nose is bleeding. Tilt your head back.
It's dripping everywhere.
I'm not surprised. You barely sleep.
You stopped calling me "Sir".
Only because I was in shock.
Go home.
You can't...
Will you stay up, Sir?
Take a break.
You're acting like your life depends on this.
It does.
If I don't prove myself,
I lose a father, too.
I'm standing on a cliff's edge.
If I doze off, I fall and die.
Go home.
What?
Yes, Sir.
See you tomorrow.
- Hi, Gi Tan.
-  Are you still at work?
I was just leaving.
Didn't you get my text?
I said I'd be late.
- Shall I pick you up?
-  No thanks.
- Soo Yeon, I need to...
-  I'm sorry,
but can we meet up tomorrow?
I'm not done working.
I feel bad leaving Gun Woo alone.
- Soo Yeon.
-  Sorry, Gi Tan.
I need to earn my keep. I hope you understand.
I'll treat you to dinner tomorrow.
I'll call you.
I'm in the lobby. I'll wait until you're done.
I'll make the coffee.
Why are you back?
I want to claim overtime.
What coffee do you want?
The darker the better if you're going to stay up.
Don't you know what I like?
Do you not care about me?
I apologise.
Make a guess.
Not knowing your boss' taste means you're incompetent.
Concentrate on me.
Yes, Sir.
You should go home to change at least.
Gi Tan.
Why are you here?
Didn't you get my text?
Your text?
(I'm in the lobby. I'll wait until you're done.)
Were you here since then?
You should've called me.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Let's not do this any more.
I feel terrible.
The sun will rise soon.
You wasted your time.
Jeong Eun, this is the first time we held hands.
It's so nice and warm.
Il Jae.
This lady will look after you from now on.
How are you?
Can you go to his room and change the sheets, please?
Of course.
She has a lot of experience. He will be in good hands.
Thank you, Gi Tan,
for helping us out during the tough times.
You need to stay strong.
You just have to figure out...
if he's faking it.
Okay.
Thank you. See you tomorrow.
Yes, Ma'am.
Fire that woman.
Gi Tan did this to us.
Don't say things like that.
I'm not crazy, Ji Soo.
Honey.
I'm pretending to be crazy...
to find out who betrayed us.
I'm sorry.
But I need you to understand.
What happened?
I met Choong Dong.
I am Congresswoman Hwang Ji Soo.
Before we begin the hearing, Congressman Hwang Jae Man,
the head of the committee, will give a speech.
Do you know how much...
Byun Il Jae speaking.
It's me, Choong Dong.
The men who kidnapped me...
are at your hospital.
Kidnapped?
By whom?
I have no time to explain.
Kang Gi Tan.
Beware of him.
Are you saying...
Gi Tan was behind all this?
If it wasn't me or Gun Woo,
who else knew all about our plans?
I'll try to visit you...
when they let their guards down.
They spoke Mandarin?
That's how they communicated.
Does Gi Tan have any Chinese contacts?
Ok Chae Ryung is a Chinese expat.
She was Jung Man Ok's secretary at Sudo Hospital.
I overheard Gi Tan mention the name "Cha Jeong Eun".
I'm thinking he could be Guk Cheol.
That's impossible.
You saw him fall into the water.
But we never found his body.
Gi Tan and Guk Cheol are two different people.
(Not the same person.)
Guk Cheol's blood is kept at Sudo Hospital.
Check if that sample has MK2 antibodies.
That's why you deceived me and pretended to be crazy?
He's slowly...
strangling us.
If we don't find out the truth and stop him, we'll all die...
just like Guk Cheol's parents and Man Ok did.
Mr Oh.
I have the results of Guk Cheol's blood.
(Blood Serum Test)
His blood sample doesn't have MK2 antibodies.
That means...
someone swapped out...
Guk Cheol's blood sample.
Kang Gi Tan is...
Lee Guk Cheol.
Lee Guk Cheol...
is still alive.
What should we do?
Listen to me carefully.
I am still crazy.
That will put him at ease.
The hospital director's in on it,
so you have to keep up the act.
Okay.
I will get rid of Gi Tan.
No.
You can't kill him until I get the 50 million...
he took from me.
We know who he is.
Why don't you force him to...
You know what he's capable of!
He duped me completely...
and ruined my father-in-law.
He even has the backing of an unknown Chinese triad.
If we touch him,
it will only backfire.
What will you do then?
I will use Gun Woo.
He already betrayed you to gain Chairman Do's affection.
That's why I'll use him.
I'll get rid of Guk Cheol...
and win Gun Woo back.
Will he side with you again?
I know him very well.
He will choose to work with me.
You can't visit Mr Byun today.
Is something wrong?
His condition worsened, so we isolated him.
Here, take this!
Take your money back!
- What's wrong?
-  He is...
just too crazy.
I could do with the money,
but if I have to put up with him, forget it.
Hello, Gun Woo.
Drive to a quiet spot.
We need to talk.
So your attempt to buy the shares failed...
because of Gi Tan.
He has my money.
We need it...
if you're ever to take over Dodo Group.
Will you help?
What if I refuse?
Chairman Do is beginning to trust me.
I think I can take over the company without your help.
You can't do it without me for two reasons.
One, Gwang Woo will be released soon.
Once he gets out,
you won't have a free rein any more.
Because you were born from Do Choong's mistress.
You will feel the difference...
in how you're treated.
And the second reason?
Do you not regret killing your stepfather?
No, I don't.
Watch what you say.
Your life ends...
the second you're branded a killer.
I don't think what I did was murder.
He never was human to begin with.
In exchange for betraying me,
that recording will be sent to the press.
Chairman Do...
isn't merciful enough to accept a killer as his son.
Well?
That explains...
why you cannot do anything without my help.
Doesn't it?
It does.
When I saw you on TV, stabbing me in the back,
I prayed for you.
I prayed that you would gain Do Choong's utmost trust.
That way,
we can create the world we dream of.
I want you to deal with Gi Tan.
Get back...
the money he took from me.
What then?
That is all...
that you need to do.
I'm glad that...
Gi Tan's the target.
- Gi Tan's here.
-  Welcome.
How are you?
Not very well.
My family's a mess and my brother's in trouble.
You two should talk. I'll bring something to drink.
Have a seat.
I called you over today to ask...
a favour of you.
What is it?
Come back to work.
Gwang Woo's in prison and Il Jae was fired.
I can't stand the way things are going in Dodo Group.
I want you to go back...
and work for me.
- What must I do?
-  It's Gun Woo.
He's running wild.
I want you to stop him.
If we let him be,
he might take over the company.
I heard that...
you were the only trainee who was able to beat him.
I need someone to rein in and tame the mad colt.
He's now a vice chairman...
and your husband's son.
There's Shin Young.
Use her.
You should be able to keep him in check.
If you need anything else, I will help as best I can.
He's the reason...
our families are in shambles right now.
Please help us, Gi Tan.
For poor Il Jae's sake.
Please deal with...
Gun Woo for us.
Are you going to go back to Dodo Group?
- I might.
-  Gi Tan.
I need a reason to stay close to Il Jae.
I came this far.
I want to end it.
To catch a beast,
the hunter's eye must move even quicker.
If Gi Tan returns to the company,
it'll be much easier for you.
Okay. I understand.
Where were we?
Right, Gi Tan's Chinese backers.
They're firearms dealers called Huaping.
They're smugglers,
but they do legal trades and lobby, too.
Tell me more.
They're mainly Chinese expats from Southeast Asia.
Nothing much else is known.
Little is known about the boss, too.
Are you saying Gi Tan is one of them?
Ok Chae Ryung.
She's a lobbyist.
And I think she's helping him.
But they kidnapped you, which means...
he's involved with them.
I'll find out more about them.
No. You don't have to.
There's a way to see them work in person.
My eyes...
will be quicker than your feet, Gi Tan.
Kang Ga Din, why are you ignoring my calls?
I hired someone to help you out.
Kang Ga Din, if you come back, I'll pay you double.
Miss Do.
He's a very talented person.
He'll be a lot of help.
Shoot.
Don't bother.
How talented can someone be?
I have to go.
Kang Ga Din!
Welcome back to the company.
Is he the person you hired?
Thank you, Sir.
Do you like your new manager title?
I don't deserve it.
For now,
forget everything else and focus on her.
You bet he should.
I feel like I just found my long-lost puppy.
Try to make a human out of her.
Dad, it's not like I'm a ghost or something.
I'm giving you a special mission,
okay?
Do anything but hit her.
Other than that, do what it takes to get some sense into her.
Yes, Sir.
You can't give my secretary a special mission.
If, for some reason,
she doesn't obey you,
come and tell me right away.
I will ban her from entering from that day onward.
Is this why he's back?
Gosh. Why did you have to accept the offer?
Gi Tan.
Is something wrong?
You don't look pleased.
Someone's been following me.
Who's that?
I plan to find out today.
Sir.
Gi Tan's coming over.
Uncle.
It's me, Guk Cheol.
Lee Guk Cheol.
I almost...
fell for it.
Uncle.