Your future stands...
with Dodo Group.
(Dodo Group)
Who... Who are you?
Please don't let go.
You'll go six feet below, Byun Il Jae.
You are...
Sir.
Gi Tan's coming over.
Uncle.
It's me, Guk Cheol.
Lee Guk Cheol.
I almost...
fell for it.
Uncle.
I finished it.
Listen to me.
Nothing will change no matter if you're sane...
or insane.
From now on, where I stand...
will become your fire pits of torture.
No, it's all broken.
I won't let you have it!
I won't fall for this.
I will never fall for this!
Everything will be mine!
No, let go of me!
Hey, let go of me!
- No!
-  Calm him down.
No! It's mine!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yes.
Welcome back to the fire pits of torture,
Guk Cheol.
Since Guk Cheol showed his true identity,
There is no need for you to stay here any more.
He was just testing me.
He doesn't care if his identity is revealed.
There is no need to play his game.
Are you saying you'll stay here?
I left things in Gun Woo's hands. We'll see.
Choong Dong,
I want you to look for a girl named Cha Jeong Eun.
She has to be someone around Gi Tan.
If I remember correctly,
her younger brother was suffering from a rare disease.
What was it again?
Right. It's Lennox-Gastaut syndrome.
That would be the fastest way to find her.
I'll do that.
(This disease is an epileptic encephalopathy.)
What is he drawing?
It's the eyesight test chart.
He just had his eyes tested.
He remembered it just from seeing it once?
The doctor told me that...
he can remember anything he sees like a photograph in his brain.
I see. He has photographic memory?
(The ability to remember what one sees and hears like a photograph.)
He really is a genius.
I wish he could use his talent.
What is this?
It's a pigeon?
I have to go to Gi Tan's. Are you heading out, too?
Do you visit him at his place now?
I owe him for something so I offered to treat him.
Then he asked me to cook for him instead.
That's an old trick.
He just wants to be alone with you. Does he want ramyeon?
No, he wants home food.
He's sick of eating out.
Il Jae is acting his illness?
Aren't you being too sensitive?
Choong Dong has been tailing me.
We can't let our guards down.
We need to keep an eye on Il Jae.
I thought...
our business was over.
What do you mean?
- Cha Woo.
-  We succeeded...
in developing the MK2 vaccine.
Gi Tan, just ignore him.
If there is anything I can help with...
Good. I was getting sick of drawing blood.
I'll take care of Il Jae.
Thanks for all your help.
Gi Tan!
Chae Ryung, wake up.
- Let me go.
-  If we don't...
collect the MK2 vaccine from Na Do Gwang,
we'll both die in boss' hands.
We can't afford to help Gi Tan any more.
Are you sure the vaccine works on the mutant virus?
That could only explain...
why Do Gwang ran away with the vaccine's blueprints.
What is this about an MK2 vaccine?
Hi, Soo Yeon.
Where are you?
Sorry, I forgot.
I'm in front of your place. I already bought groceries.
I'll give you the password. You can go inside.
How long will you take?
Okay. That's enough time for me to cook and set up.
All right. See you soon.
Where was the kitchen again?
Why would you ring your own doorbell?
Where did you get that apron?
I got it while buying groceries.
Aren't you coming in?
What?
Right.
How did you make all this?
Have some before it's cold.
How is it?
It's so good.
I'm a pretty good cook.
I know it's good, but you should talk while you eat.
By the way, when was your first love?
What kind of question is that? You're so corny.
Don't tell me you never had a first love.
Come on, what do you take me for?
Then tell me. When was it?
It was during high school.
Okay. Then who was it?
He was a super rich boy.
His mother was the director of a hospital.
That must have been nice.
No way. He was really rude and temperamental.
But...
He was really handsome.
Although he was a boy, he had beautiful eyes.
Do you still...
miss him?
That's enough. Just eat.
Okay.
Don't eat so fast. You'll get sick.
It's delicious.
What?
Why is he calling me all the time?
Yes, Sir.
You have to work tonight. Come to the office.
What? But I am currently with a friend.
Don't you know you have a commercial tomorrow?
Enough whining and get over here.
If he wasn't my boss, I would've...
What is it? Is Gun Woo bothering you?
That little...
We're shooting a commercial tomorrow. I should go.
I'm sorry. I'll cook you something better next time.
I'm here.
Where is Hae Il?
He's not coming.
Sit down.
We decided to do a pictorial instead for the shoot tomorrow.
No.
Read it here.
I'll do it at my desk.
Do you feel uncomfortable with me?
No, it's not that...
I'm just a little awkward.
We used to be colleagues.
You used to joke and make fun of me.
I thought we'd get closer with your new job.
What's going on between you and Gi Tan?
What?
You can take those documents home.
May I go home?
Soo Yeon.
Don't be late tomorrow.
No.
Mum, are you going somewhere nice today?
Why are you dressing up?
Did you find out Soo Yeon's schedule?
Yes, she has an commercial shooting at a park in the morning.
Get a car ready in time.
Yes, Ma'am.
Are you going after her?
Gun Woo said that he'll save the company...
along with Soo Yeon in just six months.
Yes, they are both real eyesores.
I can't bear to see him succeed.
And he's with Soo Yeon.
- I'm coming, too.
-  You stay out of this.
I'd rather do this by myself.
Mum, you can do it.
Can you look over here? That's excellent.
All right, great.
Let's try the other hand.
Okay, great.
Can you turn a little? Good.
All right.
She's not so bad now.
Can you turn a little and face forward?
Okay, great job.
All right.
You're here, Ma'am.
What are you doing?
I'm shooting for the company...
Who said you could do such a thing?
- I'm sorry.
-  Don't be sorry.
What brings you here?
I heard you flirted with Gwang Woo, too.
I never did that.
Nonsense.
Did you move onto him because Gwang Woo wouldn't budge?
Was the love child easier to seduce?
Ma'am.
Stop this right now!
You can't let a humdrum like her become the face of the company.
Does Dodo Group look that stupid to you?
No...
Stop it!
Did you just shout at me?
- Sir.
-  It's not Soo Yeon's fault.
I chose her. I am the one responsible.
So what?
You can talk to me.
I know you're Chairman's wife,
but you can't treat an employee like...
My son is in prison because of this witch.
You got hit instead of her. That's what you get for covering.
- You can hit me again.
-  What?
You're going to pick on her again, right?
You can pay your dues right here.
What kind of a man are you?
I am Chairman's son! And he's your husband.
Are you insane?
Just hit me.
He did nothing wrong.
You two are unbelievable.
I will make sure I watch how far...
you lowly people make it.
Sir.
- What time is the meeting?
-  You can leave now.
Finish up the shooting before you return to the office.
(Dodo Group)
Who on earth...
invented the vaccine for the mutated influenza virus?
He's a biotech professor named Na Do Gwang.
Na Do Gwang?
Are you sure...
the vaccine works on the mutant virus?
That could only explain...
why Do Gwang ran away with the vaccine's blueprints.
Then what will happen with the vaccine we're creating?
Not only us, but everyone who's been developing...
vaccines for this virus will be affected greatly...
by his creation.
What on earth is this vaccine about?
It treats mutant influenza viruses.
We can...
expect to make around three billion dollars...
once it's developed.
Make sure you approach Na Do Gwang...
and make sure you buy off the vaccine from him.
Who can take this?
- I can.
-  I'll do it.
Gun Woo has a project,
so Shin Young can take it.
I'm only letting her do this...
because she's with you, Manager Kang.
Yes, Chairman.
Did you say it was Huaping?
Is that Ok Chae Ryung's association?
Their boss is a man named Jo Gi Ryang.
Jo Gi Ryang?
This is the information about him.
(French arms transferred to Pakistan under Jo Gi Ryang.)
He sells arms to troubled areas of this world.
He speaks fluent Korean and he's from Beijing.
Other than that, there is no more information about him.
Is Gi Tan a member of Huaping?
I don't think he's directly associated.
Speak.
Let's meet right now.
What is it?
I thought of a great way to get back at Gi Tan.
He has his eyes on you, so be careful on your way out.
Did the vaccine really get stolen?
That vaccine is...
actually the MK2 vaccine made with Gi Tan's blood.
That must be why Ok Chae Ryung has been helping him.
If we take the vaccine,
Jo Gi Ryang will get his revenge.
That revenge will be done on Gi Tan, not us.
I will make sure that happens.
You aren't so bad.
I may be able to kill two birds with just one stone.
Tell me about the specifics.
Na Do Gwang.
(Na Do Gwang, a biotechnology doctor)
He's a biotechnology doctor who once served as a professor.
He loved gambling too much...
that he almost went bankrupt after he was fired from the university.
(Na Do Gwang)
But he succeeded in creating a vaccine for the mutant virus.
Na Do Gwang is infamous for his odd personality.
But...
I beg to differ.
He's not so great as he seems.
It's a hot day.
Right, Miss Do.
Do you like flowers?
Why do I keep seeing him in slow motion?
- Are my eyes acting up?
-  He was treated as an outsider.
If you're sleepy, go wash your face.
I'm not sleepy.
So what? Where is this Na Do Gwang?
He returned to Korea a few days ago.
Everyone at Secretary's Office are looking for him in casinos,
so we'll find him soon.
These are the contracts we need to fill out with him.
This place is suffocating.
I'll check it at a cafe.
Bring me the contracts which Gi Tan wrote.
Gi Tan.
I have to be on my way.
You can take your time. I'll take care of Miss Do.
Look, I'm seeing him in slow motion again.
It's for you.
I don't like sweet drinks.
You need sugar when you're tired.
How is it? Doesn't it make you feel better?
No, it makes me more tired.
Why does he look so sparkly? It's so annoying.
Book me an appointment with an optometrist.
- Do your eyes hurt?
-  Yes.
They're in critical condition.
So find me a good doctor.
They look fine to me.
Let me see.
Stop!
- Don't come within a metre radius.
-  What?
I said, keep a distance from me.
Is that better?
Don't laugh.
You're making me feel bad. Don't laugh.
You're strange today.
I'm completely normal aside from my eyes.
Are you kidding me?
What kind of contract is this?
I'll explain, so listen carefully.
What are they doing?
They seem to be looking at work documents.
That's what I mean. Why would they do work there?
Don't mind them. Let's go.
I heard from the secretary's office...
that the chairman is considering Gi Tan as his son-in-law.
- Really?
-  Yes.
That's why he got that crazy promotion.
Good for him.
They look good together, right?
Yes, you're right.
We found Do Gwang.
Where is he?
Hwang Hae Hotel in Incheon.
Let's go.
Here is the contract Gi Tan prepared.
Na Do Gwang is at the Hwang Hae Hotel in Incheon.
Go there and take Gi Tan with you.
Yes, Sir.
Vice Chairman.
Hurry up, I'm busy.
Once this job is over...
- Didn't you tell him?
-  I did.
I want to hear it from you.
I'll rehire you under me with a 20 percent increase on your salary.
You'll become my family.
Thank you.
Do you think we can trust Soo Tak?
He had a difficult childhood, so he has strong desires for success.
We'll write ours with five percent less in royalties.
Are you letting him win on purpose?
We'll leave in two hours.
Don't let Soo Yeon find out.
Okay.
Gi Tan.
Let's end our match here.
(Advanced correction for the better of the future)
- Boss.
-  Boss.
I told you not to act like you know me.
How can we not?
You're as high as the skies to me.
The skies?
Why would you spit at the skies?
I need to speak to you about that.
Forget it.
Aren't you curious about who did this to you?
What do you mean?
You have a traitor amongst your closest people.
He's the reason why you're in here.
Well, who is it?
If you can get them to put me...
in your cell,
I'll tell you then.
You want to come to my cell?
I miss our old days.
Please give me another chance.
There's no reason for you to stay here overnight.
I thought you said it'd take days to convince Professor Na.
Soo Tak and I can do it.
Book the best room here.
Check her in. I'll find out where Professor Na is staying.
Okay.
Professor Na.
Chae Ryung. You're as talented as I thought.
You found me so fast.
I won't beat around the bush.
Just give us the MK2 vaccine.
I was on a roll. Don't jinx me.
What are you doing? Go ahead.
Do you want to die?
I know you people are scary.
But money scares me more.
Money isn't more precious than life.
You can't kill me.
I got rid of every documentation...
on the MK2 vaccine.
It's all gone.
There is no MK2 vaccine any more.
Where do you think it went then?
Right in here. It's in my head.
Do you want to kill me?
Are you willing to throw away billions of dollars...
for it?
Tell your boss this.
I'll return his advancement money with the penalty fee.
I had fun.
Are you Professor Na?
- And you?
-  I'm from Dodo Group.
(Kang Gi Tan)
Gi Tan.
What? The MK2 vaccine...
is the mutant virus' vaccine?
You have to help us.
If we don't get the blueprints back,
the organisation will terminate us.
Things really got tangled up.
Tell me all you know about Na Do Gwang.
Are you going to help us?
There's no reason for me to help Dodo Group.
You've helped me so far.
I should pay you back.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I thought I heard shutter sounds.
I didn't hear anything.
That man on the piano is Professor Na.
I wouldn't have expected it, but he's really good.
Most of the customers here...
are people from different pharmaceutical companies.
Professor Na's hobbies are gambling and piano.
- Anything else?
-  He dislikes women.
He was conned a few times.
Why waste time? Let's sign the contract.
You should stay out of it.
Why?
I got a tip that Do Gwang dislikes women.
It depends on the woman.
Watch me put on my charm.
That lady bought you a drink.
She just got rejected.
Gi Tan, look.
May I join you?
Of course.
C16H30O.
You wear a nice perfume.
I apologise for what I did earlier. I dislike cocktails.
I see.
Thank you for the lovely music.
I'd never heard that piece before.
You know your music.
I wrote it myself.
I'm glad you liked it.
Did you write it?
I thought you only did research, but you write music, too.
Who are you?
Sorry for the late introduction.
This is about business.
I don't read the contracts myself.
Hand yours to my assistant. Goodbye.
I don't do things myself.
My assistant does the work for me.
Let's let our assistants do all the work.
Would you like a drink with me?
How about a bottle of whiskey?
I was afraid she'd make a mess of it.
She's not bad with people.
You're right.
Where's Gi Tan?
He's in the lounge.
Cheers.
Excuse me. Are you Professor Na?
Why do you ask?
I'm Do Gun Woo, Vice Chairman of Dodo Group's SPD.
These are our conditions. I hope you review them.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't you see me?
You're from the same company. Aren't you a team?
We aren't. He's just a...
We're two separate teams.
Our conditions will be different.
My business card's inside. I hope to hear from you.
Competition within the company...
I'll call you when I'm ready.
Goodbye.
Are you leaving already? The bottle isn't empty yet.
Give me your contract.
Here it is, Sir.
Goodbye.
Thank you for taking me back.
I will serve you with my life.
Forget about all that.
Finish what you were saying earlier today.
Who betrayed me?
Byun Il Jae.
What? My brother-in-law?
Don't even call him that.
He colluded with the prosecutor to put you behind bars.
What for?
I don't know why.
He told me to cooperate in exchange for a shorter sentence.
That's why I wasn't able to tell you until now.
You mean...
I let Il Jae use me.
Like a fool.
You let people take advantage of you like some idiot...
I apologise.
I have to add...
one more name on my hit list.
Oh, and that other guy.
Kang Gi Tan.
He's one of them.
What? Gi Tan as well?
He's Il Jae's right-hand man.
Yes, Kang Gi Tan...
You wait and see.
The day I get out, all of you...
will be taught a lesson.
Are you sure you can beat me?
If I weren't sure,
I wouldn't have come to this dump.
Gi Tan has taught you a lot. You care about business now.
Where's Soo Yeon?
You kept her so close until now.
She's very busy trying to revive our company.
Have you heard the rumour?
They say you're her sponsor.
What? Is it wrong to look out for someone poor?
Watch what you say.
Why is she poor?
What did you just say?
Fire me if you want. I don't mind.
Do you think I can't?
If you dare touch him,
we'll see who gets fired first.
You two make a lovely couple.
So do you and Soo Yeon.
Good luck with her.
Thanks.
How long does he need to read our contracts?
You sound confident.
I'm just curious.
I wonder who Do Gwang will sign with.
(Do Gun Woo)
(Kang Gi Tan)
Kang Gi Tan speaking.
I'll come right up.
Was it him?
I guess he liked our offer.
I'll be right back.
Yes!
See? I said we'd win.
- Drink up. Bottom's up.
-  Yes, Ma'am.
Gi Tan.
I will make you shed tears of blood very soon.
Manager Kang. Have a seat.
Does this mean I decide what I want?
Yes.
What if I demand too much?
Whatever it is that you want, it can never be too much.
The bear who does the tricks should take most of the profit.
That is only fair.
As the developer of the vaccine, that's a very important issue to me.
You seem to understand.
I respect and honour your demands.
Use that pen to write whatever it is you want.
I have some beer in the fridge. Do you want some?
- Yes, thank you.
-  Just a moment.
Isn't that what you played?
I've never seen a music sheet like that.
Did you compose that piece?
I really dislike it when...
others touch my belongings.
I apologise.
Can I have the beer?
There's no need to apologise. I'm sorry.
I'm tired, so I overreacted.
I heard you like to play games.
Would you like to play baccarat tomorrow?
I never say no to gambling.
Here you go.
Just a moment.
Can I use your bathroom?
Sure. It's down that way.
I'm Do Gun Woo, Vice Chairman of Dodo Group.
- I'm listening.
-  Did you see the photo?
Kang Gi Tan is a member of Huaping, a group Ok Chae Ryung belongs to.
He approached you to get the vaccine.
I'm at the bar in the basement.
I'll see you here in an hour.
Shall I get more beer?
No. Actually...
I'm very tired.
Could we meet again tomorrow?
Of course.
The music sheet is the vaccine blueprint?
He got very upset when I touched it.
I think I'm right.
How can musical notes represent a chemical formula?
I thought about it.
There are a little over 100 chemical elements.
There are 88 keys on a piano.
The sheet music...
included notes that aren't on a standard piano.
Cha Woo and I will try to get our hands on it.
You can stop now.
He's closely watched.
The professor trusts me, so I should wrap up...
What is it?
I heard someone.
Thanks for helping out today.
I was glad when you agreed to help so willingly.
Shouldn't you leave Huaping?
It's my destiny.
I can't leave until I die.
If this works out, try talking to your boss.
The work is taking its toll on you.
Now that we don't need your blood, you won't want to see me.
I want to live a normal life.
You should go home.
I know where the vaccine's blueprint is.
The music sheet Do Gwang has...
That's it.
Good job.
It just got much easier.
Tell Soo Tak to get ready.
Yes, Sir.
Make Gi Tan drink this.
It's spiked with a sedative.
- A sedative?
-  Our vice chairman...
will finalise the deal tonight.
We can't let Gi Tan interrupt,
so we'll put him to sleep.
I don't believe this.
He can't be a spy.
All you have to do is drink and have a good night's sleep.
Then you'll get to take the credit for the whole thing.
What's this?
I brought a bottle from home to share with you.
I had a lot of beer. I don't want any more.
Come on, don't say that.
I brought this for you.
Okay, then. Let's just have a little.
A toast to a successful deal.
Cheers.
Soo Tak.
Are you drunk already?
(Kim Hae Il)
I got Gi Tan's fingerprint.
Give it to Oh Choong Dong.
- I apologise.
-  It's fine.
If it hadn't been for you,
I could've gotten into trouble.
Get rid of Do Gwang.
Sorry?
The MK2 vaccine...
will earn us more money than you can ever imagine.
The 50 million that Gi Tan took is nothing compared to that.
If we're to make a profit,
we have to kill Professor Na...
and pin it on Gi Tan.
Gun Woo plans to make Gi Tan look like an industrial spy.
If he finds out we killed him, he could retaliate...
He can't do anything about spilt milk.
He won't be able to think of a way to turn things around.
I'm ready.
Let's sign the contract.
But...
you offered 20 percent of the total profit,
and that's not quite enough.
I will offer you the blank cheque deal...
that Gi Tan did.
Do you mean that?
My father is Chairman Do Choong.
Does that help?
It does.
In exchange,
promise me that...
you won't consider any other contract.
Cheers.
Goodnight, Sir.
Mr Choi, you all had a long day. You can retire for the night.
Wake me up at 7am tomorrow.
That's it for the day. Get some rest.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
How did it go?
It's a success.
Well done.
I brought dumplings, your favourite.
Where is Guk Cheol?
I miss Guk Cheol.
Guk Cheol isn't with us any more.
What?
No.
Stop it, Dong Soo. What's wrong?
Why don't you be honest? You don't want...
Soo Yeon to find out that Gi Tan is Guk Cheol.
What are you talking about?
Is Gi Tan...
Guk Cheol?
Yes.
Tell me.
Is Gi Tan...
really Guk Cheol?
Yes. Guk Cheol.
He cried.
Did Gi Tan...
cry in front of you?
He cried.
Guk Cheol cried.
I miss Guk Cheol.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
Guk Cheol, I'm Jeong Eun.
Please pick up.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
You mean Gi Tan...
is your friend from a long time ago?
Yes.
No wonder.
I could tell that he liked you a lot.
That explains a lot.
But why didn't he tell you?
Whatever the reason, he tried very hard to help you.
He's the one who settled Dong Soo's hospital bills.
The Hwang Hae Hotel in Incheon?
He said he'd be there on business.
Why aren't you picking up?
Professor Na.
Professor.
Are you awake?
Professor!
Is something wrong?
Open the door!
He's still alive.
Call 911!
Get him first.
Professor.
Professor. Who hurt you?
Tell us!
Who did this?
Professor!
(Monster)
Go and tell Il Jae that...
he picked on the wrong guy.
You shouldn't have gotten involved, Gun Woo.
The chairman wants to help Gi Tan.
I need your help, Mr Hwang.
To catch a big fish,
you need to learn to let go of the little ones.
Will that make you the next chairman of Dodo Group?
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out of here this instant!