(Episode 22)
The Hwang Hae Hotel in Incheon?
He said he'd be there on business.
Why aren't you picking up?
Professor Na.
He's still alive.
Call 911!
Get him first.
Professor.
Professor. Who hurt you?
Tell us! Who did this?
Professor.
He's dead.
That's the end of Gi Tan.
He wanted to kill...
He has good ears.
Oh Choong Dong.
Was it Il Jae...
who framed me?
Murder wasn't a part of my plan.
It wasn't a part of ours either.
He just killed him.
Gi Tan.
What happened? What did you do wrong?
Don't worry, Soo Yeon. It's all a misunderstanding.
Gi Tan killed a man.
Don't trust him. Just trust me...
and don't worry.
Don't worry, Soo Yeon!
I trust you, Gi Tan.
I know something is wrong.
So don't ever give up,
okay?
You'll be fine. I'll help you.
Gi Tan!
Jeong Eun.
Guk Cheol.
I will save you this time.
So please hold out.
Why are you here?
Are you crying?
I know Gi Tan well.
He's been framed.
What do you know...
about him?
Gi Tan and I are...
I tell you.
He would never kill a person.
Let me ask you a question.
- Did...
-  Get out.
You can't stay here. Go on.
Excuse me.
May I check yesterday's CCTV footages?
A police officer was just here.
Are you a reporter?
No, I have to look for something.
They've all been deleted.
You can't prove his innocence.
No, I will make sure I prove that he's not guilty.
- There he is.
-  He's here.
Kang was arrested for the murder of Professor Na,
who recently created a vaccine for a mutant virus.
His case was sent to the prosecutor's office today.
Prosecution believes he pocketed the blueprint of the vaccine.
They are making every effort to find the missing blueprint.
Do you want to know who really killed Do Gwang?
It's Gi Tan.
Show me the blueprint of the vaccine.
The chemical formula must be hidden in here.
It'll take a while for us to decode.
I'll take it with me.
Are you saying you'll decode it?
What is it? Don't you trust me?
Then you should have kept me out of your plans from the beginning.
I never planned to kill Professor Na.
Unfortunately, I found out too much.
Gun Woo.
Sure, you can take it.
Director Byun.
If you decode it, we would reach our goal.
People with the same dream should stick together.
I'll call you.
Are you sure we can trust him?
I have control over him. He won't act rashly.
Find out where my father-in-law is.
Dad, Il Jae is here.
Did you get discharged?
I apologise.
You lost your seat because of my incompetency...
I don't care for a seat at the National Assembly.
In order to catch the big fish,
you must learn how to free the small fish.
However...
Since I broke my usual rod,
It's difficult to go out to the big waters.
Il Jae has the blueprint...
for the mutant virus vaccine.
I plan on founding an international business company.
Once the new vaccine gets patented,
there won't be a problem moving forth with our plan.
When I heard that Gi Tan was involved,
I had my doubts.
You finally have the sword in your hands.
While I was in a state of dejection,
you were the one who helped me back on my feet.
A pond like this...
doesn't suit you.
Your aunt...
promised to give me...
all of her shares at Dodo Group.
- Dad.
-  Really?
In return, I promised to help her...
by getting Gwang Woo out on special pardon.
Now that you have the sword in your hands,
the day we take over Dodo Group will come faster than we expected.
I'll show you, Sir.
You'll soon catch the biggest fish on Earth.
When I take...
a big stretch tomorrow morning,
the world will be a different place.
It wasn't me! It wasn't me!
Someone has been tailing me.
I'm Do Gun Woo, the vice chairman of Dodo Group's SPD.
This contract is our offer. I hope you'll consider it.
I guess that's the end for Gi Tan.
Il Jae.
Gun Woo.
Choong Dong.
(Prosecution Service)
You will be questioned as a testifier.
What was Gi Tan like?
I heard the blueprint for the mutant virus disappeared.
Does it have anything to do with Dodo Group?
Who are you poking?
This case and Dodo Group has nothing in relation.
If we find any false reports,
we'll be taking legal measures.
Kang Ga Din.
- Ma'am.
-  What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
What is it? What happened?
I don't know.
I feel like my heart will burst.
I don't think I can testify.
Take me to a hospital.
Hae Il, take her.
We found your fingerprints on the tools.
On top of that, you were at the scene of the crime.
Where did you sneak away the vaccine's blueprint?
I told you, I didn't kill him.
You should check the security footages at the hotel.
You're the one who deleted all the footages!
- They're gone?
-  Listen, Mr Kang.
If you keep this up, your sentence will just get longer.
Then please check the alcohol I was drinking.
I lost consciousness after drinking it.
We already checked its components and it's completely fine.
Then ask the friend who was drinking with me.
He'll be my alibi.
It's true that we drank together.
But I became unconscious before him, so I'm not sure.
Gi Tan said that someone...
might have put drugs in the alcohol.
I brought that drink.
It's just really strong. I didn't put in any drugs.
No way.
After getting the call, Gi Tan headed for Professor Na's room.
Maybe it was an hour later.
When I called him, Professor Na wanted to see me.
Did you end up seeing him?
Yes. We talked about our contract.
The murder happened afterwards.
Did Professor Na say anything about Gi Tan?
He said that he felt pressured.
Gi Tan tends to be persistent.
- Did you do as I told you to?
-  Yes.
But Gi Tan lost his consciousness after drinking. How did...
Watch your mouth.
The police will find out the truth. Don't let anyone know what you did.
Do it for the company.
All right.
You've tainted our company's name.
You know more than anyone else...
that I'm innocent.
Are you saying I framed you?
No.
You don't have the power to do that.
But Il Jae does.
We'll see if you can say that in court.
Tell Director Byun this.
He picked the wrong person.
- Gi Tan.
-  Also,
you'll regret getting involved in this.
I won't...
forgive you.
What does he mean?
What does this have to do with Director Byun?
He's talking nonsense since he's cornered. Ignore him.
Dad, you know Gi Tan isn't like that.
He was working so hard to get Professor Na's signature.
How does the investigation look?
There's evidence and his motives are clear.
Even if we hire a talented attorney,
it'll be hard to get him acquitted.
What about probation?
Or maybe it could be seen as accidental homicide.
We should hire famous lawyers to...
I disagree.
There are suspicions that our company is involved in the murder.
If we help Gi Tan,
it'll only make those suspicions stronger.
According to the prosecutors,
Gi Tan claimed that he was framed by someone.
Framed?
Who would do that?
Gi Tan...
apparently mentioned Byun Il Jae.
Byun Il Jae?
Gi Tan is not the type to talk nonsense.
Then Director Byun must be the suspect.
As for the prosecutors, they believe...
Gi Tan's testimony is absolutely not trustworthy.
Form a defence counsel.
I don't care if he is the murderer or not.
This happened while he was working.
It's what we should do.
I will see to it.
You're the best, Dad.
(Do Gun Woo)
Speak.
From Dodo Group?
Okay.
What is it?
It looks like Chairman will save Gi Tan.
Do Choong?
If he is found not guilty, things will get complicated.
I think it's your turn to step up, Sir.
Chairman is waiting for you.
It's been a while, Chief Secretary Moon.
I was too busy to visit you.
I'm glad you didn't come.
I heard I looked ridiculous.
Isn't it weird?
I don't know why Gi Tan said...
you were the real murderer.
Weren't you at a mental institution?
According to Gi Tan, that means you carved up a plan...
while pretending to have a mental disease.
Is this why you formed a defence counsel?
You're not the only one with connections to the prosecution.
I have ears, too.
Chairman is very curious about the whole story.
We'll find out the truth once Gi Tan is out.
Chairman...
won't be able to form a defence counsel.
I will give you my word.
Anyways,
aren't you discharged a bit too early?
Schizophrenia isn't so easily...
There are...
exceptions to everything.
Right, exceptions.
Sure.
Are you asking me...
to stop helping Gi Tan?
He's someone who betrayed me...
after he pretended to help me.
Thanks to him,
I've been ruled out of everything.
I cannot forgive him.
I'm sure you didn't think I would accept your terms.
So what is this...
that makes you so confident?
You are very quick-witted.
However,
I do not have anything with me.
Are you asking me to do something...
without any condition?
Instead,
I have buried a bomb inside of my heart.
A bomb?
It's a bomb...
that will kill both of us once it's blown up.
What...
are you talking about?
It's everything...
I learned about you while I helped you.
It's about everything that's illegal.
Tax evasion, bribe, lobbying...
and even women problems.
I will expose them to the entire world.
Are you saying...
that you'll go down with me?
You're the one who emptied me out...
with Gi Tan's help.
I have nothing to lose.
So what can't I do at this point?
Don't you agree, Choong?
What happened with the defence counsel?
I've contacted Oh Gwang...
and asked for their best...
- Cancel it.
-  What?
Take your hands off...
of Gi Tan's case.
Yes.
Please, Attorney.
No one is helping Gi Tan.
You have to help him.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
Okay, sure.
I got it, so stop crying.
Why are you crying so easily these days?
Can you go and meet with Gi Tan?
I'll be there right after work.
Okay.
I'll see you at the prosecutor's office.
Didn't that make you feel sad, too?
Why did you want to hear her voice anyways?
Soo Yeon...
isn't sick, is she?
My gosh, she's a mess.
She's been looking...
for evidence everywhere to prove your innocence.
Even if she's ill, she's probably holding back.
To be honest, Soo Yeon is...
Don't tell him that we're childhood friends.
Why not? I thought you missed him.
There must be a reason why...
he didn't say anything to me.
He may not want to get recognised...
because he's not doing so well.
Will you keep it a secret forever?
I will wait until he is ready.
Sure.
It'll be better if you talk to him about that.
What about her?
No, it's nothing.
Now, where were we?
Right.
Did you say people who framed you are...
Byun Il Jae, Do Gun Woo and Oh Choong Dong?
I believe my speculation is right.
According to the prosecutor, they all have alibis.
Did you look for Oh Choong Dong's alibi?
Yes, he was in Seoul that night.
No way.
It's not so promising.
I didn't kill him!
I know, I know.
But what can I do?
There isn't a way to prove your innocence.
Please keep this...
a secret from Soo Yeon.
She'll be very curious.
The more she tries to help me,
the more in danger she'll be in.
Is it because of Il Jae?
Lawyer Min?
Did that public defender take his case?
The prosecutor said that he's rather good.
I really don't like him.
If he brings out the fact...
that he's a first-time offender and that he was drunk,
he may receive much less of a sentence than I expected.
9077, you have a visitor.
Look who this is.
I thought you were insane but you look fine.
It's been a while, Gwang Woo.
Hey, Mr Byun.
You've become quite bold.
How dare you come visit me...
after putting me in here?
The one who put you in here isn't me, but Gi Tan.
He's on your side!
Did you think I didn't know that?
I've been fooled by him, too.
Stop your nonsense and be prepared to go down...
once I'm out of here.
Gi Tan is...
Lee Guk Cheol.
What are you talking about?
He's the son of Sudo Hospital, who died because of you.
He died.
He didn't.
That's why all of this happened.
What about his eyes?
How can he see?
They were curable with surgery.
He approached us on purpose.
We were both fooled by him.
Wait.
His parents didn't die because of me.
You killed them!
You ordered me to kill them by threatening me!
His trial will be soon.
Once he's found guilty and ends up coming here,
I intend to put him in your cell.
Are you telling me to get rid of him?
Kill him or not,
it's up to you.
It'll be best to have him within your eyesight.
Boss, why are you still up?
Is something worrying you?
Kang Gi Tan...
might come here.
That's good news.
Just give me the order...
and I'll have my boys get him.
You fool.
What do you mean?
Don't you watch the news?
He might have the blueprint for the vaccine.
Right.
I hear it's worth a lot of money.
If we can get that blueprint from Gi Tan,
my life will turn around overnight.
Does that mean you'll become the chairman of Dodo Group?
Yes.
Do you know how much that vaccine would sell for?
Please let me help you.
Blueprints and anything else.
I'll steal it from him and then get rid of him.
That's why I'm still up.
How should I cook him up...
to make it delicious?
Under Article 250 of the Criminal Law,
Kang Gi Tan is sentenced to five years in prison.
You asked me not to bring Soo Yeon to the court...
since she might run into Il Jae.
Make sure you stop her from visiting me in prison.
How can I stop her?
I'll decline if she comes.
That is...
the only thing I can do...
for her right now.
Gosh. It's breaking my heart.
Guk Cheol...
Guk Cheol.
Guk Cheol!
It is...
my second time in prison.
During the first time,
I was afraid because I couldn't see.
Byun Il Jae.
He turned me into a murderer twice.
What's different now...
is that instead of fear,
I'm full of rage.
(Advanced correction for the better of the future)
You have a new cellmate.
Don't fight and get along.
Hey, Gi Tan.
Fancy seeing you here.
Who is this?
It's so nice to see you.
What a coincidence, right?
I heard your news.
You know, bad things happen...
and you fall time to time throughout life.
Anyway, I'm glad we're in the same cell.
Don't put up an act.
I'm sure your subordinate already told you.
You jerk. We were being nice.
What are you doing?
Sorry, Boss.
Yes.
I know you and Il Jae are the ones that put me here.
But to be honest,
you're innocent.
You only did what he told you to. Aren't I right?
The one I want to pay back is Il Jae,
not you.
While you're here,
let's try and get along.
Gi Tan didn't take...
the MK2 vaccine's blueprint.
Someone else is behind this.
I'll catch the suspect...
and bring you the blueprint, Boss.
You two...
are no longer in charge of this.
- I'll get to it myself.
-  Boss.
Even if it means killing Gi Tan,
that blueprint must come into my hands.
Gi Tan, it's me, Chae Ryung.
Cha Woo and I are under close surveillance by the boss.
The boss thinks that you have the vaccine's blueprint.
Be careful.
There are Huaping people in the penitentiary.
I don't know if they're trying to kill you or to steal the blueprint.
I can't be sure.
What I'm sure of is that you're in danger.
I'm sorry I can't be of any help.
What are you up to?
Don't walk around alone here.
There are a lot of insane people here.
If you're unlucky, you might never open your eyes again.
I have this place under control.
If you stick with me, you won't have any problems.
Gwang Woo is the king here.
Just trust him.
Are you going to stay there?
I need time to think alone.
Hey, take the boys over there.
Yes, Boss.
Come on.
Gi Tan.
There is something...
I want to talk to you about businesswise.
Don't take this the wrong way.
- Do you happen to...
-  Vaccine's blueprint?
Yes, the blueprint.
Do you want to split it in half with me?
Don't you know what I mean? Hand it over to me...
and I'll give you 50 percent in royalties.
I'll be discharged with a special pardon soon.
I promise to get you out on parole.
- Tell me where the blueprint...
-  I don't have it.
Come on, you can trust me this once.
You're barking up the wrong tree.
Is this...
how you're going to play it?
Shall I lie and say I have it?
Will you believe me then?
Do you really not have it?
I really don't.
Too bad, then.
From now on,
treat me with respect.
I don't like your tone.
I'll be careful, Sir.
Did you think I'd say that?
There's nothing but fury left inside of me.
I'm here because I was framed for murder,
but if you provoke me, I might actually kill you.
Watch out.
Boss.
What did he say?
We should...
host a welcoming event for him tonight.
Got it, Boss.
Boss.
Who's going to solitary?
Me, Boss.
Cover him up.
Yes, Boss.
You don't take me seriously, do you?
This is your lesson.
You arrogant piece of scum. Die!
Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die!
Die!
How dare you...
turn your back on our boss.
You need to be taught a lesson.
This isn't working.
Hold him up.
I'll beat him up myself.
Who did it?
Who beat him up?
He taunted us, so I taught him a lesson.
You're going to solitary.
Take him.
Let's get ready for bed.
What sleep?
You won't be getting any sleep!
Let's see how long you will hold up!
We'll do this every day!
Gi Tan.
I'm being nice here.
Tell me where the blueprint is.
Are you feeling unwell?
Why can't you eat?
Don't talk to me.
I have no appetite,
no will to live and I feel depressed.
We have doctors for a reason.
Go and see Doctor Hwang.
Is it depression?
I doubt that.
Is it...
about Gi Tan?
Why would I lose my appetite over him?
It's because I didn't get the vaccine deal.
Come by for breakfast more often.
Yes, Father.
Sir.
An extraordinary general meeting was called.
An EGM was called?
By whom?
Your wife, Sir.
What's the agenda?
The dismissal of Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo.
Where are your manners?
That's what I should ask.
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
I'm here skipping breakfast because I can't stand Gun Woo.
The EGM.
Cancel it immediately!
Is that what this is about?
I thought it was something serious.
Call it off right now!
Do you know what Gun Woo did to me?
He stood up to me in public.
He challenged me.
Hey.
Gwi Ja.
Promote him further.
Make him CEO if you will.
I will still push him off the cliff.
Gwi Ja.
Don't call me that. It makes my skin crawl.
If you keep doing this,
I might actually make a very critical decision.
What critical decision?
You're not going to make Gun Woo...
Yes.
That's what you fear the most.
Choong!
Call off the extraordinary general meeting right now.
If you don't,
at that very meeting,
Gun Woo will be welcomed with a round of applause.
So...
you want me to cross the line.
Be careful, Gi Tan.
There are Huaping people in that prison.
8253.
You have a visitor.
Is it Oh Soo Yeon?
I don't know. Go and find out.
You look terrible.
Come and sit.
This is all I can do for my own nephew.
I didn't think...
you would kill someone, Guk Cheol.
Why don't you...
hand over the blueprint?
Stop being so creepy.
I know you took it.
You should have...
died that day.
Or never reappeared.
This is where the real torture begins.
Do you remember what I said?
I said that if I survived,
I would get my revenge.
Yes, Guk Cheol. Get your revenge.
But...
someone else told me to kill your parents.
Do Gwang Woo.
I have nothing to give you,
but I thought you'd want to know why your parents died.
Consider it a gift.
I heard that inmates here die of various causes.
Do Gwang Woo.
Lee Guk Cheol.
I wonder who will die first.
Whoever it may be, I will attend the funeral.
Thank you, Uncle.
I'll eat well...
and get out alive.
Sorry. You can't see him.
Can't you let me in?
But he told us first...
that he won't see you.
(Visiting Room)
(Visitor Registration)
About Do Gwang Woo's involvement...
Did you tell him on purpose?
Now that Guk Cheol knows, things will get interesting.
He knows who Gi Tan is.
He knows we have it.
Shouldn't you worry about his lawyer, Min Byung Ho?
They have no evidence.
Don't worry.
What was that about?
What do you want to hear from me?
How is Il Jae involved in this case?
I really don't know.
Then why is Gi Tan refusing to see me?
How would I know? Only he knows why.
Mr Min, will you please stop it?
Soo Yeon.
This is for your own good.
That's all you need to know.
What do you mean?
Nothing. Forget about it. I have a headache.
How is this for my own good?
Oh, right, I'm in trouble.
I should be in court.
I have to go.
See you.
I can't stay for long.
Tell me how Il Jae is involved...
in this incident.
He's behind everything that happened.
Do Gun Woo and Oh Choong Dong were accomplices.
Gun Woo?
Yes, him.
They framed Gi Tan for murder.
But...
didn't he ask for your help?
I think he didn't to keep me out of danger.
Is there no way to clear his name?
I can do anything to help him.
It's not something you can do.
You have to risk your life.
I fear...
losing Guk Cheol again more than death itself.
"Guk Cheol"?
Tell me what I have to do.
It's the blueprint of the mutant virus vaccine.
That's all we need to set Gi Tan free.
Where is it?
It's either with Il Jae or Gun Woo.
Can you find it?
I will find it.
I will find it...
and free Guk Cheol.
(Dodo Group)
Someone else told me to kill your parents.
Do Gwang Woo.
Hey, guys.
What is it?
Stop it.
Get him off!
Stop him.
Guard! Guard!
Guard! Here!
- Let go!
-  Guard!
- Let me go!
-  Come along!
Let me go!
Let go of me! Let go!
- Open the gate.
-  Let me go!
Let go!
Let me go!
Get in there.
Let me out! Open this door!
I said, open this door!
It still aches.
When did you get out?
Stop it!
Stop it now!
8253, come on out.
Did you have a bad dream?
You screamed in your sleep.
It's Gi Tan.
He appeared in my dream.
He's the worst I've ever seen.
Beating him doesn't work. Neither does solitary confinement.
I asked the director to send him to another cell.
We won't see him again.
That's a relief. I'm sick of him.
It's him!
Guard! Come back!
Why is he back here?
Put me in another cell!
Guard! Guard!
What happened? Why is he back here?
No.
What's this?
Gi Tan.
What's wrong with you?
Are you trying to get us both killed?
You met Il Jae.
- What?
-  I'm not here by coincidence.
You were his right-hand man.
He's the reason I'm here. Why would I care?
I am...
Lee Guk Cheol.
I'm the son of the director...
of Sudo Hospital that you had killed.
Did Il Jae tell you that?
That I had them killed?
Gwang Woo.
Do you know why I got my sight back?
Because I wanted to see who had killed my parents.
I'm so grateful that we sleep in the same room.
I can kill you whenever I want.
Wait, Gi Tan.
Your life ends the day you kill me.
You still have years to live.
Wouldn't it be a waste to throw it all away?
It would be.
Because I have the blueprint.
But I have to rot in here for five years.
By then, another company will have developed the vaccine.
I'd rather kill you and avenge my parents!
The blueprint.
Do you have it?
Of course, I do. Do you think I killed a man for fun?
Gi Tan.
I get out soon because of a special pardon.
Once I'm out,
I'll do whatever I can to get you out on parole.
So give me the blueprint.
When you get pardoned,
take me with you.
That's...
practically impossible.
I'll ask for a retrial. Help me get acquitted.
Until I get out,
I will never give you the blueprint.
Okay, then.
But in return,
you'd better keep your side of the bargain.
We know what Gi Tan is.
He's an industrial spy.
He was caught for murder while trying...
to steal the blueprint to the mutant virus vaccine to sell to China.
Are you sure he killed the professor?
The court found him guilty. Why would you ask that?
I understand the spy part,
- but murder...
-  Hey.
You aren't a fortune teller.
You have a mission to stick to.
Yes, Sir.
We have orders to get Gi Tan out of prison.
Help him break out...
and get the blueprint.
What do you mean?
If that blueprint ends up in foreign hands,
it will cause us a huge loss.
We have to prevent that.
Jailbreak is illegal. However important our mission is...
As soon as we get the blueprint,
he will go straight back to prison.
Do you get it?
Yes, Sir.
Yes. I'll be right there.
Sure.
It's been a while.
We last met in Hong Kong three years ago.
I would say so.
Sorry for calling you...
whenever I'm in a bind.
This is just enough.
Any more calls would get me into trouble.
How are things?
I know an agent who knows Gi Tan very well.
I'll send that agent in.
We will get Gi Tan out of prison.
You take care of the rest.
How do you plan to get him out?
That part is very simple.
What happens next is the problem.
That's why I asked for your help.
Food.
We aren't a bunch of goats. Is this all we get to eat?
Don't we get any meat?
Shut up and eat.
8253.
This is for you.
- Here.
-  What soup is it?
(The Bible)
Genesis 9:20, James 1:20,
Jeremiah 50:36.
Are you religious?
Who would send you a Bible?
Are you okay?
Sorry about that.