(Episode 23)
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Sir.
Tell your boss this.
The one who has the blueprint to MK2 vaccine is...
not me,
but a man named Byun Il Jae.
Hey, how does this feel?
That hurts.
That hurt.
You punks.
Try doing that on my legs. I think that'll feel better.
That hurts.
Genesis 9:20.
James 1:20.
Jeremiah 50:36.
"Old man"...
and "knife"?
Did you say you failed?
Yes, Boss.
Why did you fail?
I think he knew about our plan.
From what we've learned,
Gi Tan's abilities are much better than most secret agents.
Ok Chae Ryung.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry.
It's as if we used a rabbit trap...
to catch a leopard.
Gi Tan continuously claims that Byun Il Jae...
has the blueprint to the vaccine.
From what I've found,
it's definitely not him.
You should look more into it, Boss.
- Byun Il Jae may...
- Don't you trust our source?
What will you do now?
I found out about Gi Tan's abilities.
So I'll make a different approach.
Chae Ryung.
It's you.
You told Gi Tan, right?
Don't say that without any evidence.
I won't let you...
keep betraying our organisation.
Keep that in mind.
Call all of the shareholders and cancel it.
If you don't,
that meeting will become a place where Gun Woo is praised upon.
Where's the bottle?
Here it is.
It looks exactly like the pills which Chairman takes.
However, the ingredients are completely different.
You've been through so much with Gwang Woo, right?
Once Gwang Woo becomes the chairman,
you'll be paid for all of your work.
I am waiting for the day he'll return.
Remember to keep your mouth shut.
I won't ever say a word.
It's a secret from Gwang Woo, too.
Yes, Ma'am.
Go and stand guard.
Throw these away, Mr Han.
Yes, Ma'am.
You brought this upon yourself.
It's not my fault.
Where are you going?
I'm going to eat out with Shin Young.
I wanted to eat steak at Dodo Hotel with Mum.
Don't be late. Come back early.
Are you worried about me?
I was talking to Shin Young.
I don't care if you walk in late or stay out all night.
Chairman.
Here are your pills.
What happened to cancelling that shareholders' meeting?
Oh, I forgot...
to cancel it.
Didn't I order you to do so?
Don't be mad.
Your doctor always told you to watch out for your blood pressure.
I warned you.
If you hold that meeting,
something that you fear the most will happen there.
What I fear the most?
I fear you the most.
You've been very angry recently.
What if you collapse?
Take care of your health.
Let's go, Shin Young.
Bye, Dad.
I think...
you should cancel the meeting yourself.
I'm waiting around until she cancels it...
on purpose.
Then are you really going to announce...
Gun Woo as your successor at the shareholders' meeting?
Go and find...
where Gun Woo is.
Yes, Chairman.
Why aren't you eating?
I didn't know you'd come to a place like this.
I used to come here often...
with your mum.
She loved...
this place's rice soup and steamed meat.
I know that people are...
gossiping very much about you.
If you're fine, I couldn't care less.
Humans are...
very cunning.
If someone is about 3 to 4 times better than them, they bash him.
If someone is 10 times better, they start to fear him.
If someone is 100 times better, they respect him.
If someone is 1,000 times better,
they get on their knees...
and want to be your slave.
That is how cunning people are.
I know people are insulting you and are jealous,
but there is one thing they don't know.
They don't know how proud I am about you.
Just wait around a little more.
I will make you...
1000 times better than now.
No one...
will be able to disregard my son.
Welcome.
Where are the shareholders?
They're waiting for you.
Stay seated.
Serve us the VIP course...
along with the best of their wines.
Yes, Ma'am.
I only invited...
the people I value and think dearly of.
Did you all get the notice of the extraordinary general meeting?
Yes,
but would your husband let this happen?
My husband's health has been deteriorating.
Mum, he eats like a horse.
I'm trying to speak.
I'll keep it short.
At the EGM,
vote to dismiss Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo.
(Dodo Group)
What do you want to say?
Doesn't it bother you that Gi Tan was framed for murder?
What's there to be bothered about?
The whole world knows he did it.
Soo Tak.
Do you think I don't know you work for Gun Woo?
What did he offer?
A promotion and a raise?
Did you betray an innocent friend for that?
What are you talking about?
Tell me where Gun Woo put the vaccine's blueprint.
I don't even know what it looks like.
It's a coded music sheet.
What kind of music sheet...
I don't know anything.
Will you stop lying?
Soo Yeon.
You shouldn't doubt your boss. Not after all he did for you.
You should be grateful.
What a jerk.
The blueprint of the mutant virus vaccine.
That's all we need to set Gi Tan free.
I have something to say. Are you free this evening?
- Should we have dinner?
- No.
Buy me a drink.
If you are busy, it doesn't have to be today.
It's fine. Let's leave together.
Thank you.
What do you have to say?
It was just an excuse to have a drink.
Just don't go overboard.
Shall we have a bet?
Whoever gets drunk first grants the other a wish.
You know I'm a lightweight.
I wouldn't suggest a bet I know I'd lose.
What if I win and demand something extravagant?
What do you...
consider extravagant?
It's something you can't handle.
Then...
is the game on?
The blueprint is a music sheet.
What are you doing?
I was going to help you take off your jacket.
Did you bring me here alone?
Thank you.
I should go.
I have to grant you a wish.
I lost. Tell me what you want.
I'll tell you later.
Goodnight.
Soo Yeon.
How many more times do I have to forgive you?
Guk Cheol.
I trust you, Gi Tan.
I know something is wrong.
So don't ever give up, okay?
Kang Gi Tan.
We're getting him out tomorrow.
How will you do that?
Gosh. The dratted cucumbers made the rest soggy.
First, they'll have a stomach ache.
Dong Yi, call the guard.
- I think I'm going to die.
- My stomach hurts bad.
Guard!
I think we all have food poisoning!
I think I'll need one more.
What medicine will they give him?
It's a toxin that slows the pulse...
and causes a shock.
He'll react to it within 24 hours.
As soon as he's out,
inject him with the antidote.
If you don't, his heart might really stop.
Tell me in detail what I must do.
We will set everything up well in advance.
Take Gi Tan to a safe house...
and steal the blueprint.
That is your duty.
If you fail while helping him escape,
you'll become a criminal.
Don't make any mistakes.
Understood.
Then,
are you saying Gun Woo will be kicked off from his position...
at the next EGM?
That's what I mean.
You won't have to wait too long. Just take it easy.
Mum.
Gi Tan is in my cell.
Kang Ga Din is?
How is he? Is he sick?
Gosh, why are you worried about him and not your brother?
I am.
I was very worried about you, too.
Anyway, can you pull some strings...
to get him out with me?
What are you talking about?
That vaccine blueprint that went missing...
is with him.
Then is he really the killer?
What are you talking about? It's definitely not him.
Mind your own business!
Anyway, once I get my hands on the blueprint,
it doesn't matter if I'm not the heir to the company.
So I really need you to help me.
It won't be easy, but I'll try.
No matter how much it costs,
we have to do it.
Boss.
How was the visit?
You'll be released on special parole with me.
Don't worry.
Good work.
It's okay, you should rest.
Hey... Hey!
Hey!
Gi Tan!
- What's wrong with you?
- Hey!
Hey!
Gi Tan! Guards!
Guards! Someone's dying!
Gi Tan, you can't die like this.
Where is the vaccine's blueprint?
Gi Tan!
No, please...
Go.
That's not the way to the hospital.
Tail it.
- What was that?
- Something is suspicious.
Call for backup.
We think the ambulance is trying to escape.
Stop the car!
Excuse me! Stop!
Once you get a hold of Gi Tan,
inject him with this antidote.
Otherwise, his heart might really stop.
Kang Gi Tan, who was sentenced to serve time for murdering...
Na Do Gwang, escaped from prison this afternoon.
Dong Soo, it's time for your medication.
- The police is investigating...
- It's Guk Cheol!
his whereabouts while collecting witness comments...
and security footages.
They're looking into who the accomplices are.
This just came in.
The accomplice who helped Kang Gi Tan's escape...
was caught on the security camera in the ambulance.
(Accomplice caught on camera)
Isn't that Yoo Sung Ae from the secretary's office?
It is.
What's going to happen to them?
Now that her face is revealed, they'll be caught soon.
What about Gi Tan?
If he gets additional punishment, his sentence will get longer.
What a fool.
Why did he escape?
Gosh.
Yes, Vice Chairman.
I'm on my way from meeting with a cipher officer.
The person is talented, but I'm not sure about their background.
Okay, Sir.
A cipher officer?
There are secret codes on the music sheet.
Soo Yeon...
was telling me the truth.
What on earth did you do?
Because of you,
the NIS is in trouble.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
What about Gi Tan?
He'll wake up soon.
Do everything in your means...
to get that blueprint from Gi Tan.
What will happen to me?
A secret agent's face...
was on national television.
What do you think?
Once this job is done,
you'll be sent abroad.
Got that?
There's a limit to how much we can stop the police.
Don't take too long.
Wasn't this mission...
a deal made with the police?
I told you it was a secret mission. A secret mission!
That's why it's such a headache.
Anyway,
just do as I tell you.
I'll figure out the rest.
Yes, Sir.
Right.
Gi Tan...
will claim that Byun Il Jae is the suspect.
Don't trust him.
Sung Ae?
Are you awake?
Are you also with Huaping?
Are you dreaming? Huaping?
How did you get me out?
I sacrificed my life for it. It wasn't easy.
- Happy?
- Sung Ae...
There's police everywhere.
You'll be caught as soon as you set foot outside.
Stay here for a while until things quiet down.
I'll look for routes for you to escape after that.
People around you are being watched upon.
Do not think about contacting them.
I don't care who you are.
I don't have the blueprint.
You're doing this in vain.
I will return to the prison.
All right?
Who are you?
Let's not make this hard on us.
If you're not with Huaping, who are you?
I'm with the National Intelligence Service.
The National Intelligence Service?
Where is the blueprint?
The police, Huaping and now, it's the NIS.
I'm a big boy, am I not?
Tell me.
Where is it?
Why did you give the MK2 vaccine to that woman?
Even when things go wrong,
we can't come out to the open.
Gi Tan may run.
The moment he runs,
I'll get him with my own hands.
I feel so nervous.
Gi Tan will...
try to get back at us.
He can't come out to the open because he's on the run.
He's a dangerous man.
If the police couldn't get him,
you should get him, Il Jae.
That's what I was going to do.
What happened to finding Cha Jeong Eun?
There is a patient I'm suspicious about.
Her brother has a very unique disease.
Everything else is the same, but his name is Oh Jin Cheol.
Go and find out.
Guk Cheol broke out from prison.
I'm sure he'll go find Jeong Eun.
Yes, Sir.
Wait.
I have something to give to you.
What is this?
When someone's shot with that,
their heart will slowly stop.
Should I inject this...
He'll be a problem to us as long as he's alive.
It's better to kill him.
(Oh Jin Cheol)
Kang Gi Tan and Yoo Sung Ae are yet to be found.
The police believe that they are still near Seoul.
They have increased security...
- among all streets.
- Guk Cheol is here again.
It's Guk Cheol.
Does Gi Tan really have a woman?
I'm not sure,
but I think they were childhood sweethearts.
(Oh Choong Dong)
What happened?
I found Jeong Eun's brother.
We'll be there. Send me the address.
You're here.
Do you want a drink?
I don't have time to drink with you.
What is it?
My father...
recently passed away.
The hospital said...
that he'd live for another five months,
but he suddenly passed away.
He lived his whole life...
as a guard in an apartment.
He was really glad to hear that I started working...
for a big name company.
My father...
passed away because of me.
I did too many...
bad things to Gi Tan.
It feels like my father was...
punished for everything that I've done.
I'm sorry, Soo Yeon.
I apologise.
I have nothing I can do for Gi Tan.
You can retrieve the blueprint from Gun Woo.
Gi Tan can't be proven innocent with that.
It can. I will take care of the rest.
Just make sure you get the blueprint.
If it goes wrong, you can just quit work.
But for Gi Tan, this is a matter of life and death.
Okay, I'll try.
I will...
get that blueprint.
Thank you.
Is that Jeong Eun's brother?
I heard him say Guk Cheol's name.
I guess Jeong Eun will be here any second.
I'll call you as soon as I see her.
Okay. Thank you, Choong Dong.
Wait one second.
It's Oh Soo Yeon.
I'm here, Dong Soo.
You're here!
(Oh Jin Cheol)
I brought some fried food.
I love fried food. I want it.
I knew she'd be someone near Gi Tan.
But I can't believe Oh Soo Yeon was Cha Jeong Eun.
- Keep your eyes on her.
- Yes, Sir.
Is it really that good?
Did Soo Yeon ever act suspiciously?
- Was she interested in the vaccine?
- Not... Not at all.
If it seems like...
she knows something about our secret,
you must do something.
We're working on something big here.
We can't let this go down with a small glitch like her.
Don't worry. Nothing like that will happen.
What about the person who can decode the blueprint?
I'm looking for one.
Many people are after this. Keep it low.
You got through this very well.
If I say that it hurts,
it'll only make you feel bad.
We found out who Gi Tan is.
He is an industrial spy.
He wanted to take the blueprint...
and sell it to the Chinese market,
but he killed someone on the way.
Get a grip, Sung Ae.
Gi Tan is a murderer.
Don't feel sorry for him.
It's all useless.
Where is the blueprint?
Water...
Give me some water.
I told you, Il Jae has it.
Where is...
the blueprint?
Please...
Please, just let me sleep.
If you give me the blueprint,
I'll help you out of the country.
That's the only way you can live.
Il Jae...
Gun Woo...
I already told you that they have it.
I despise...
people like you.
You only care about yourself.
How can you think about selling such a thing to another country?
Sung Ae...
Let me ask you again.
Where is...
the blueprint?
I told you that Il Jae has it!
Speak.
Are you sure...
Gi Tan has it?
I'm sure.
It's impossible to get him to confess.
We need a new strategy or...
Or what?
Never mind.
Stop the interrogation until I give you the next order.
The truth serum didn't work,
and he withstood all the torture.
I think he's had special training.
Did you train him?
Yes.
You sure spent...
a lot of time on him.
What he claims might be true.
I'm telling you that it's not Il Jae.
There's nothing to lose.
We should check, Boss.
Contact Kim Dae Ho...
- to set the time.
- Yes, Sir.
Isn't he the president of a company in the defence industry?
You're right.
We're in the same industry, so we know each other.
I see.
That makes sense.
Is he that big of a deal?
If I'm a pebble in the defence industry,
he's a star in the sky.
I heard he has a strong network in China as well.
It's not just China.
He knows people in the Middle East and Europe, too.
You should get to meet him while he's in the country.
He'll be a big help to you.
I heard you're from Hong Kong.
Your Korean is excellent.
I had a lot of businesses with Korea.
What brings you to Korea?
I heard there is a professor who found a vaccine for MK2.
I came to make a deal with him.
I believe that professor was murdered a few months ago.
I'm not talking about Na Do Gwang.
There is another professor that was studying the virus with him.
That's a relief.
I heard there are a lot of people dying from the mutant virus in Asia.
Please let me know if you need anything during your stay.
I'll do my best to give you good hospitality.
I'll be asking for your help if I need it.
It's not him.
How do you know?
His eyes didn't shake once.
Kang Gi Tan.
He lied to us.
We almost...
fell for Jo Gi Ryang's tricks.
How did you know that he was Gi Ryang?
I have an informant.
An informant?
Mr Yeon, come on in.
Long time no see, Sir.
Come.
Gi Tan...
is currently kidnapped by Gi Ryang?
Yes, Sir.
Then...
is it Gi Ryang's men who helped him escape from prison?
Yes, that's right.
Since he doesn't have the blueprint, he'll die soon.
That's good news.
Thanks to Mr Yeon, we were able to avoid a big trap.
I'm sick of working in the shades.
When do you plan on bringing me back?
Once this job is over,
you'll get what you want.
Thank you, Sir.
Go to the United States for two months of training.
What's this all of a sudden?
Once you land, someone from our office there will greet you.
I can't go.
Soo Yeon.
It's my resignation letter.
I won't work under you any more.
If you leave like this,
I won't ever ask you to stay.
That's just what I wanted.
I thought you wouldn't ask me to stay.
What are you doing? Let me go!
What's wrong with you?
I don't know! I really don't.
But I just think I should do this.
If I let you go like this,
I might lose you forever...
like I did with my mum.
I might go crazy.
Whether I die or not,
it's none of your business.
Whether you go crazy or not,
it's none of my business.
Do you get it now?
I don't like you.
Let's never see each other again.
I don't have the blueprint. You're wasting your time.
Gi Tan.
I'll take the car.
Don't move.
You're a fugitive.
I have no problem...
shooting you.
Then shoot me.
Do you think I won't?
Shoot.
I don't fear death.
Stop right there.
Who are you?
He tried to escape.
Where should I take him?
I want you...
to get him to confess.
Are you not confident?
- No, Sir.
- I sincerely hope...
you won't let me down.
He's testing me.
What should I do?
(Prison)
Welcome back.
- Thanks.
- Have some tofu.
Gi Tan.
Where is he now?
He's still on the run. No one knows where he is.
Chief Secretary, use all your resources...
and find him immediately.
What for? The police are looking.
Just do as I say.
I have my reasons and they are good reasons.
Yes, Sir. Your father is waiting for you at home.
Before I go home,
I'll drop by the office.
The office, Sir?
Very well, then. I'll drive you.
Good morning, Sir.
I have a list of secretary candidates.
Once you accept Soo Yeon's resignation...
She took time off.
- Pardon?
- Say it's paid leave.
She'll get paid for taking a break.
Leave her seat vacant for now.
Yes, Sir.
(Dodo Group)
Why do you look so surprised?
Aren't you happy to see me?
Move your feet.
What?
I work for the company.
Insulting my seat means you're insulting the company.
You got better at talking back.
You rode my father's coattails all the way to the top.
Do you actually think you're a vice chairman?
While you did time for ruining our reputation,
I worked very hard for the company.
You have no right to mock me, Brother.
"Brother"?
Who's your brother?
I see you're trying to squeeze into our little family.
I'm in no mood to put up with your antics.
So get out of my room in silence.
Are you high? Or insane?
Please, just go!
Don't bug me.
I don't know what I might do.
How dare you?
- You...
- I warned you.
Don't touch me!
How dare the son of a mistress even touch me?
Yes, my mother was the other woman.
So what?
You jerk.
What are you doing?
Did you see that?
He tried to kill me. He beat me up!
Shall I tell your father that your little brother hit you?
What?
If you don't apologise right now,
I will report this!
I don't want an apology.
I will remember this for the rest of my life.
I hope you do the same as well.
Whatever I do to you down the line...
won't make you feel so bad.
Gi Tan.
Wake up.
Who are they?
Are they Huaping?
I think so.
What are they?
It's your last chance.
Where is...
the blueprint.
It's not...
with me.
I have...
a special skill...
that makes people talk.
What are you doing?
Untie me! Stop!
Let me go!
How many pain spots...
do you think are on a human body?
There are more than you think.
And the pain...
is beyond belief.
People fear extreme pain...
more than death itself.
And that fear...
makes them tell the truth.
It will be beyond anything you can bear.
Gi Tan!
One more.
Drag it on for too long...
and you could die.
Tell me.
Continue.
It's too dangerous.
He could die.
Do it!
You can't...
use pain to change the truth.
Do it!
(Monster)
Is your name Dong Soo?
Did you draw this?
I told you to leave Soo Yeon alone.
Gi Tan will show up.
If Sung Ae comes back to work,
it will cause problems for me.
Il Jae is here.
Don't you regret it?
I bought you.
Get me to the States.
Jeong Eun, I'm Guk Cheol.
I'm Gul Cheol, Jeong Eun.