(Episode 24)
People fear extreme pain...
more than death itself.
And that fear makes them tell the truth.
You can't...
use pain to change the truth.
Gi Tan!
Gi Tan.
What a tenacious one.
He never once begged for his life.
Let me know when you have a lead on Gi Tan's whereabouts.
Okay, thanks, Detective Kim.
Even the police don't know where Gi Tan is.
Yes, Chae Ryung.
We need to meet now.
- No one followed you, right?
- Yes.
I was worried because I couldn't reach you.
What happened to the blueprint?
We're looking for it.
Do you know where Gi Tan is?
He doesn't have anywhere to hide.
I hope nothing bad happened to him.
Gi Tan's life is in danger.
What do you mean?
You can save his life only with that blueprint.
Can you explain a little more? What happened to him?
We haven't much time. Remember what I just told you.
Chae Ryung.
Chae Ryung!
Is Gi Tan dying?
He's captured by Jo Gi Ryang.
If they don't find the blueprint,
it's obvious that he'll die.
In that case, we needn't keep our eyes on Soo Yeon.
Gi Tan is the problem to everything.
There won't be any more problems after he's gone.
(Kim Hae Il)
Yes, speak.
I found someone to decode the blueprint.
Is he trustworthy?
- Thomas?
- Yes.
He is waiting for you in the room. Follow me.
It's this American named Thomas.
He's a ciphering specialist.
He worked with the CIA, too.
Nice to meet you. Please call me Steve.
Nice meeting you.
So,
how long will it take you to decipher the job?
It's very complex.
Probably over a month.
Okay.
You have this room to yourself.
You are to stay in here and not leave until you're finished.
My men will take shifts to keep an eye on you.
The pay is a million dollars for the job...
and an extra million if you succeed.
What do you say?
When do I start?
Don't take your eyes off from Thomas, not even for a second.
Soo Tak and I will take turns watching him overnight.
Okay.
Hey, is it all right to just leave the blueprint with that foreigner?
How will he decode it otherwise?
He could copy it.
He might even take a photo to send it to someone.
Won't it be dangerous?
The music sheet...
has a special coating on it.
A special coating?
It won't show up even if you try to photocopy it or take pictures.
That's how Professor Na made it in the first place.
As long as we watch Thomas, there's no chance it'll leak.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried.
The vice chairman is so smart. I'm sure he thought it out.
I'll go in now. Come and change shifts with me at night.
Okay, have fun.
Soo Yeon, it's me.
We have to meet right now. Where should I go?
What is that?
You can't photocopy it nor take a picture?
Your only chance is to run with it.
Who will do that for us?
Who do you think?
There's only one person who can do it.
Soo Tak?
No, it'll put him in danger.
I wish I could help,
but I'm looking after my mum. I have nephews to look after, too.
Then...
Can you somehow copy it by drawing it out?
It's like a piano score. It's very complicated.
If I get the components slightly wrong while copying it in a rush,
all our efforts will become useless.
Gosh. It's a pie in the sky.
It's right in front of us, but we have no way of getting it.
We'll find a way somehow.
It's time for my shift.
I should go.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
What should we do? We don't have much time.
Gosh, I wish we could just memorise it by looking...
He can remember what he sees like a picture in his brain.
Photographic memory...
Jin Cheol, Jin Cheol. Stop sleeping and get up.
I'll buy you cookies.
Search online for any music sheet.
Okay.
Here. There you go.
I'll show you a music sheet. Take a look.
Take a look at it then draw it out. Okay?
I'm sleepy. I want to sleep.
Come on, help us out, you punk.
Get up, get up.
If you don't draw it, I won't let you sleep until you're 60.
This is it.
Jin Cheol can draw it.
We'll save Guk Cheol, okay?
Guk Cheol. I miss him.
The chairman's health is deteriorating. I'm worried.
He's having a hard time at work as well.
Take this and remind him to take it regularly at the office.
I will.
But do you know why his blood pressure suddenly got bad?
Ever since Gwang Woo got out,
he's been extremely stressed.
The chairman wants you to join us for the meal.
Yes, Ma'am.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
How many of these will he have to take...
for his blood pressure to calm down?
Why is that punk... What is this?
It's awkward seeing him across the table, right?
I still have a hard time swallowing.
Father, I don't think this is right.
Why are we eating at the same table with him?
Tae Gwang.
Look into a place abroad for Gwang Woo to stay for a few years.
I don't care if it's Africa, the Middle East or Eastern Europe.
I prefer him to be as far as he can be.
Are you going back home?
You had four years left of your sentence, right?
Go live abroad...
for those four years.
Gun Woo, get out right now.
Get out of this house.
What do you think you're doing?
Dad. It's because of him, isn't it?
Are you kicking me out so that you can support him?
Gun Woo saved our company...
after you almost ruined it.
You don't deserve to say a thing.
How dare you raise your voice?
Are you taking his side in front of me?
Tae Gwang.
Kick him out of the country within this week.
Yes, Sir.
You can't kick him out!
He has the right to be a shareholder.
Gwang Woo, I'll find your place for you. Don't you worry.
Hey.
You must think that the EGM has your back.
I can't go.
I won't.
Why do I have to be kicked out because of him?
You little...
Just tell me to go and kill myself instead.
I'll disappear from your sight.
You little...
- Sir!
- Chairman!
- Father!
- Dad!
Call 911 right now! Hurry!
Dad!
Sir!
Chairman!
That's weird. This pill should do it.
What do you think about switching it to something else?
This is the best there is in Korea.
I think it'll depend on the type of person...
What do you know?
Doctor Hwang would know what's best for him.
Make sure he doesn't get any stress for a while.
I will.
This is all because of you.
Don't ever come back to this house.
I think Dad's in trouble.
How is Chairman doing?
He'll be fine soon.
Hey.
Stop pretending like you're concerned about him.
Of course.
Without Dad, he's nothing.
- I'll go back to work.
- Okay, Sir.
Chief Secretary Moon.
Did you find anything about Gi Tan?
We're using all of our men to find something,
but we can't find anything.
I can only get rid of Gun Woo and the others...
if I get my hands on that blueprint.
Are you okay?
You've been sleeping.
I thought you were dead.
They will kill us.
They won't let us live.
Darn it.
Why do I have to spend my final moments...
with you?
I thought I would die...
a bit more glamorously than this.
Come near.
Can you do it?
We need to try.
We can't sit around to die here.
- Come nearer.
- Okay.
What will you do with Gi Tan?
He passed through the needles, so we can't get him to speak.
You should just kill him.
What a strange man.
It's not just the way he endured pain.
But I can't forget about those piercing looks...
which he gave me.
Are you fond of him?
I know him very well.
- If you let him live, he'll...
- Will you take...
the responsibility...
if he becomes trouble?
What will happen to my junior?
What do you want me to do?
I'll get in trouble...
if she returns safely.
You're asking me to kill her.
To be honest,
that'll be a relief for me.
Cha Woo.
Go and bring those two here.
I must decide...
whether to kill them or to let them live.
Yes, Boss.
We're almost there. Just a little more.
Don't untie everything yet.
They'll be here soon.
(Give them some water.)
Water.
Give me some water.
How many of them are there?
From what I hear,
there are at least 10 of them.
We grew too tired.
We can't fight all of them.
Whom are you calling?
Hello? Is this the police?
A group of Chinese is smuggling something.
You can track this phone to find their location.
How long will it take?
Okay, you should hurry.
Police officers will be here in about 10 minutes.
You're smart.
Are you ready?
Yes.
(What's taking him so long?)
(Go and check.)
- Are you okay?
- I think I broke my leg.
- They'll kill us.
- I can't make it.
Go without me.
Shoot.
You lost them?
I'm sorry, Boss.
It must've been difficult to escape.
The police stepped in at the worst timing.
Gi Tan must have done something.
I told you, he's a professional.
He's the one who took down Michael Chang...
in Hainan.
Is that true?
Yes, Gi Tan destroyed...
Michael's foothold in Hainan.
What a man.
He's dangerous.
Do not let him live.
Chae Ryung.
Find Gi Tan yourself.
- Pardon?
- You probably know...
where he'll go to.
You must bring him to me.
Yes, Boss.
Move your ankle.
Thankfully, it doesn't seem broken.
If you can walk on your own,
we should part ways here.
Why did you save me?
You could've gotten caught because of me.
I even tortured you.
So why did you...
You were only doing your job.
It was for the better of the country.
I have nothing against you.
Where will you go now?
I'm going to find the blueprint...
and prove my innocence.
- What about you?
- I'll go see my direct supervisor.
Is he the one who organised this mission?
Yes.
He's the one who gives me all the orders.
Don't you find it weird?
He left you alone with the police.
Also, Jo Gi Ryang's gang was waiting outside the safe house.
He worked over 20 years with the NIS.
- I doubt...
- I'd be suspicious if I were you.
There's no harm in being careful.
You should check on it first.
Gi Tan escaped from Gi Ryang's men?
They're not the type to make such a mistake.
He tends to be swift on his feet.
He's cornered right now.
If we act aggressively,
he'll have a tough time.
There's a limit to where he can go.
We'll be able to catch him if we stake out in those spots.
Goodness.
- Yes.
- It's Yoo Sung Ae.
What happened?
I was held captive by the Chinese organisation. I barely got out.
Where is Gi Tan? Is he with you?
Yes, he's with me.
Where are you right now? I'll come to you.
I'll be there within an hour.
Don't go anywhere.
What is it about Gi Tan?
They're at a reconstruction site in Jungnam-gu.
Is that so?
Hurry and inform Jo Gi Ryang's gang.
No.
Il Jae, you should go there yourself...
- and finish off the job.
- Dad!
He already escaped from Gi Ryang.
We can only rest easy if we witness his end.
I understand.
Get me some trustworthy men.
I have to get rid of my subordinate as well.
I'll gather my men instead.
That's a good idea.
You should keep an eye on Soo Yeon instead.
Yes, Sir.
I'll be back, Sir.
All right.
Dad.
There's no need to get blood on our hands.
He's responsible for ruining my 30-year-long political career.
Getting blood on my hands is not a big deal any more.
How dare he?
It's already been over an hour since we were supposed to meet.
She promised to meet me here.
Hey, Mr Yeom!
Be quiet, will you?
What?
Hey.
Look everywhere in this area.
- Yes, Sir.
Your work process is pathetic.
What did you say?
How will you serve my father-in-law like this?
What about you? Weren't you the one who ruined him like that?
What?
Let's stop it here. Okay?
You...
That...
You were caught in Il Jae's trap.
How can this be?
Ever since I joined the NIS,
I worked under Mr Yeom.
His orders...
were orders from the state for me.
I'm a fool...
I'm so foolish.
What have I been doing with my life?
I know how it feels...
to be betrayed by someone you used to trust.
Byun Il Jae...
was my uncle.
I used to follow him around so much when I was young.
But he killed my parents and my aunt.
What's important is now.
The things that happen after you find out the truth.
What are you going to do?
A secret agent like me...
can only receive orders from one person.
I don't know anyone at headquarters.
So it won't be easy.
Meet me here in two days.
(Oh Jin Cheol)
Yes, Sir.
She's currently in her brother's room.
No. Gi Tan is nowhere to be seen.
He'll definitely show up.
Keep an eye out.
I will.
Okay, Soo Tak. Good luck.
What did he say?
We'll meet him at the hotel tomorrow at dawn.
Tomorrow at dawn?
Shouldn't we let Jin Cheol sleep in advance?
Go to sleep.
- Okay.
- Let's sleep.
Good boy.
There. Let's go to bed.
I hope he'll be able to help.
What is it this time? Gosh.
I don't need any loans.
It's me, Gi Tan.
Gi Tan! Where are you?
Is Soo Yeon doing all right?
Of course.
Gi Tan, it's me.
Where are you? Let's meet. I'll come to you.
Not yet.
I'll call you back later.
Don't hang up.
If you hang up right now, I won't ever see you again.
How are you? Are you hurt?
Where are you sleeping?
Let me talk to Lawyer Min.
Me?
Yes, Gi Tan. Go ahead.
I'm sure Soo Yeon is being watched by Il Jae.
You have to be careful.
All right. Where should I meet you?
Okay. Okay, don't worry.
What did he say?
He'll come see you now.
Let's go.
My car is parked on the first spot in the parking lot.
I'll take care of the guy following you.
Go and see him.
Gosh, that's hot!
You should look where you're going.
You can't go. You hurt my hand.
Hit-and-run isn't just a thing for cars.
Pay for my treatment.
Get out of my way.
Call the cops!
He just hit me!
Help me! Help me! Please help.
Get him!
My hand! It's burning!
- Come along.
- No!
Soo Yeon.
You look terrible.
It's just my face that's a mess.
I missed you a lot.
This is from Mr Min.
Use this to call me.
We'll have the blueprint very soon.
Do you know how dangerous this is?
I won't let you go down like this.
This time,
I will protect you.
I'll send you the blueprint once we get it.
Spend this.
I have to go.
Look after yourself.
Jeong Eun.
Cha Jeong Eun.
I'm Guk Cheol.
I'm Guk Cheol, Jeong Eun.
Why are you telling me now?
I missed you so much.
You silly.
- Did she get away?
- I apologise.
She knew I was onto her.
Pull back for now.
Yes, Sir.
I don't like how things are going.
When do you think the expert...
will decode the blueprint?
He needs at least a month.
That is what...
Gi Tan is after.
Gun Woo is a smart man.
You won't have to worry about that.
He keeps slipping out of our grasp.
I don't like that.
Soo Yeon.
Have you heard from Soo Tak?
He just sent a text telling us to wait.
I'm going to have a shower and then take a nap.
Could you please wake me up after three hours?
Oh, sure.
It's me. Come up.
- Concentrate.
- It hurts.
There's no time.
Look carefully and remember it.
Don't yawn. Look at it carefully.
I'm done.
Put it back.
Was that it?
He took his time because he's tired.
Thank you, Soo Tak.
I really hope it helps clear Gi Tan's name.
It will. Go back inside.
Well done.
That's Soo Yeon.
What is she doing here?
What are you doing here, Sir?
Did you just see Soo Yeon?
Soo Yeon? No.
Why are you here?
He was passing by and dropped in.
How far has he gotten?
I don't know much, but I think he's halfway there.
Excuse me.
Where's the patient gone?
He left last night and hasn't come back yet.
I'm hungry.
I'll buy you some tasty jajangmyeon when you're done.
I'm finished.
He's a genius.
- Give me jajangmyeon.
- I ordered it. It'll be here soon.
Take a photo and send it to Gi Tan.
Okay.
I just got it.
The music sheet is the blueprint.
Okay.
Thanks, Soo Yeon. When it's all over,
I'll come and get you.
Look after yourself.
Don't worry.
- Soo Yeon.
- Yes, Gi Tan.
When this is over...
Yes?
You, Dong Soo and I...
The three of us should move abroad.
Let's go to a place where no one knows of us...
and live happily.
Then were you going to leave alone?
I won't let you disappear again.
Dong Soo and I...
will follow you to the end.
I'll call you.
Be careful.
I'm here. Where are you?
Are you alone?
Don't you trust me?
Walk towards me.
Do you have the blueprint?
- Yes.
- Where is it?
Send it to me.
- When our boss sees it...
- Don't bother.
Tell your boss this.
If he wants the blueprint,
he should clear my name.
Gi Tan.
Your group has that much influence.
But before that,
send me to the States.
Gi Tan.
How about this?
We can take the blueprint and leave Korea together.
We can...
apply for a patent in America.
We just have to give the licence for China to Huaping.
I give you my word.
I'll leave with Jeong Eun.
Let's do the rest as you say.
If he gets us to America,
we'll give him China's licence.
I'll wait for an answer.
You'll leave me...
to go back to Jeong Eun, will you?
Did you ask for me?
Oh Soo Yeon.
- Find her.
- Pardon?
I heard that she and Gun Woo can't live without each other.
There were such rumours, but...
The two ruined my life.
I will make them pay.
If I don't, it'll kill me.
I have something very nice you can use against her.
What's that?
She took out a loan.
Quite a bit of loan, in fact.
So what?
Yes?
I wired this month's interest.
You're mean, even for a loan shark.
Yes.
Okay. I'll be there.
Dong Soo, I have to go. Don't go anywhere, okay?
Okay.
(Joongwon Capital)
Oh, wow, look at you.
You've gotten prettier since we last met.
Don't be so scared.
I don't bite.
What are you doing?
Don't you regret it?
"Why on earth did I say that in court?"
No.
Aren't you afraid of me?
Hit me. What else can you do?
Hey, hey. I would never hit a woman.
I hate that kind of thing.
Then what will you do?
You owe a lot of money.
So what?
I bought you.
You even signed away your organs.
Were you in need?
That's one contract you should never sign.
I pay the interest every month.
You should have paid back the principal long ago.
So what?
Do as I say.
Or serve time like I did.
Hey.
How did you find me here?
I told you to leave her alone.
Get him.
My secretary's outside.
If I don't show up, he'll call the police.
Let's go.
That little punk...
I told you to stay away.
I don't want to be involved with you.
Then stop getting into trouble!
- What?
- If you're okay,
then I'll stop caring.
You must think I'm struggling.
But I'd be just fine without you people.
So please...
get out of my life.
Did he just get turned down?
I believe so.
Oh Soo Yeon...
She's so charming.
It's like...
Anyway,
she's not like...
other girls.
What are you doing?
Are you studying?
You can stop drawing that. It's over now.
You don't have to draw this any more, so stop it.
Okay. Go on, then.
Keep drawing it if you want to.
Once he starts, he never stops.
Where's your sister?
I don't know. She's angry. She left.
Why isn't she answering her phone?
I'll be right back.
Bye.
He wasn't here last night?
The nurse said he returned in the morning.
I think you need help monitoring them.
Find a nurse or member of staff who will help you.
Yes, Sir.
- It's a plane.
- That's Soo Yeon's brother.
Sir, this is...
I'm sure of it.
It's the blueprint.
It's my plane.
You did a great job drawing this.
Did you do it?
I drew it. Dong Soo... No.
Oh Jin Cheol did it.
Yes, Jin Cheol. Where did you see this?
My sister showed it to me.
Did you really draw this?
I'm a genius.
Photographic memory. Genius.
"Photographic memory"?
Give me that. It's mine.
Right. Of course.
Jin Cheol, it's time for your drip.
Bye.
The blueprint...
is inside his head.
Yes, Sir.
Do you still have...
the syringe I gave you?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're such a good boy, Jin Cheol.
You don't mind injections.
When will Soo Yeon come back?
Very soon.
I should go.
Okay.
Bye.
What are you doing?
Dong Soo.
Isn't that your name?
Yes. No. My name is Oh Jin Cheol.
Is it?
You will feel very sleepy.
Have a good, long rest, Jin Cheol.
I brought tempura. It'll go all cold.
You're fast asleep.
Hello?
Soo Yeon.
Gi Tan.
Dong Soo! Dong Soo, what's wrong?
What is it? Dong Soo!
Help!
Wake up!
Dong Soo! What's wrong?
Help!
Dong Soo! Dong Soo!
Dong Soo! Is anyone there?
Dong Soo!
- Soo Yeon. What's wrong?
- Help!
What's going on?
Something happened to Soo Yeon.
I have to go.
To do what?
Dong Soo. No, you have to wake up.
Dong Soo...
Dong Soo. Dong Soo.
What happened?
Why is he...
like this?
Why is he in this bed?
My brother's dead.
Poor Dong Soo.
Dong Soo...
Dong Soo is dead.
Don't.
Let go.
Il Jae's here.
Guk Cheol.
I will destroy everything you cherish.
So you better come out into the open.
Byun Il Jae...
Il Jae...