Sir, this is...
I'm sure of it. It's the blueprint.
This is mine. It's a plane.
Did you really draw this?
I drew it. I'm a genius.
Photographic memory.
The blueprint is inside his head.
What are you doing?
You will feel very sleepy.
Have a good, long rest.
Dong Soo. No, you have to wake up.
Dong Soo...
Dong Soo. Dong Soo.
Dong Soo.
Wake up.
(Episode 25)
I think that car is with Il Jae, too.
Where is he going this late?
(Funeral hall)
Gi Tan will be here.
Find him.
- Yes, Sir.
Isn't this Soo Yeon's brother's funeral hall?
It is.
Then he's here to get you.
Thank you for coming.
If you haven't eaten, go and have some soup.
This way, Vice Chairman.
I saw you at the hospital...
on the day Dong Soo died.
Didn't he have a heart attack?
That's what I heard.
His heart was completely fine.
He couldn't have died like that!
But why are you telling me this?
I signed up for his autopsy.
I will do everything I can...
to make the criminal pay...
for murdering my brother.
Are you Lee Soo Tak?
Yes, I am.
You are under arrest...
for violating the law on industrial technology protection.
You have the right to consult an attorney...
and the right to remain silent.
You can refuse to testify against you.
What?
What are you doing? I haven't done anything.
Take him.
- Come with us.
- Wait a second.
Wait.
Hey.
Are you Oh Soo Yeon?
You must come, too.
I'm a lawyer.
What do you think you're doing at a funeral?
Are you Lawyer Min Byung Ho?
You have to come with us, too.
How dare you?
Detective Kim.
Their family member died. Leave them.
Just check their phones.
It would be cruel of us to take them to the station.
Let me see your phones.
It's Soo Tak.
They don't have the blueprint in their phones.
Good job.
You should have been more careful with the blueprint.
We could've been in trouble.
Is that why you killed my brother?
We received the blueprint...
through an official contract with Professor Na before he died.
You were the ones who stole that blueprint...
in order to prove Gi Tan's innocence.
You're going to ask for an autopsy?
Be my guest.
The criminal is you,
not us.
Soo Tak was accused of being an industrial spy?
Il Jae, that snake.
He struck first before we could report it.
How is Soo Yeon?
What do you think?
She's out of it.
Please take good care of her.
Gosh, don't worry about that. You should be careful.
What happened with Ok Chae Ryung?
No updates yet.
I should go. Soo Yeon is alone.
Please tell your brother...
"thank you" for lending the taxi.
His license got suspended, so he can't drive anyway.
Call me if you need me.
Let's run away abroad with the blueprint.
I'll leave with Jeong Eun.
It'll be better to tell them this.
If they let us go to the States,
we'll give them the Chinese license.
Boss is looking for you.
You still haven't seen Gi Tan?
Cha Woo.
How long do you plan to be with this organisation?
What do you mean?
Don't you know we can't leave until we die?
I'm going to leave.
Are you crazy?
Come with me.
Chae Ryung.
I know you're sick of this life, too.
You don't want to live like a puppet for the rest of your life, do you?
We have no other choice.
All we need is the blueprint.
If we have that,
we can live anywhere and do well.
Betrayal means death.
I just told you that I have a plan.
I'll ignore what you just told me.
Cha Woo.
Don't ever mention it to me again.
It's me, Mr Yeom.
Let me ask you something.
Chae Ryung is the contact for Gi Tan,
but I don't think she's in touch with him yet.
Are there any other ways...
he can get in touch with Gi Ryang?
No.
All right. Keep it up.
Do you plan on bringing Chae Ryung to our side?
That might be...
the fastest way...
to get rid of Gi Tan.
Welcome.
Luckily,
Gi Ryang doesn't have the blueprint yet.
Is it true what Soo Yeon said?
Did you kill her brother?
Do you know what this situation is like?
It's like a thief claiming his innocence.
Soo Yeon stole the blueprint, but she's blaming me.
Trust me.
I would never lie to you.
Don't ever touch Soo Yeon.
Even if Gi Tan has it,
it'll take a while to decode.
We can decode it and apply for the patent.
If you...
have feelings for Soo Yeon, you need to get over it.
It's no time for you to be falling in love.
On top of that,
you have a big project in front of you.
Do I have to get your permission to like someone?
Gun Woo.
Don't get involved in my life.
We're nothing more than business partners.
Business partners?
The vaccine will be decoded by the promised date.
Everything will go according to plan.
But if something happens to Soo Yeon by any chance,
our plan will be ruined. Mark my words.
All right.
If that's how you feel,
I'll respect you.
There's an empty office...
inside that building.
Is Gi Tan up there?
Yes. He's waiting for you.
All right. Thank you.
Gi Tan.
- What did the autopsy say?
- It's a heart attack.
But...
what the doctor says throws me off.
It's true that he had a huge shock to his heart,
but there are no marks proving that he was drugged.
It was definitely a murder.
We're sure that it was, but we have no evidence.
That's why it's driving us crazy.
What does Soo Yeon think?
She also thinks that someone killed him.
If there is no evidence,
we'll make it up to find out the truth.
I'm going to prove...
that Il Jae killed Dong Soo.
Listen, you're on the run.
You have to be careful.
Dong Soo died because of me.
He was trying to prove my innocence.
Soo Yeon lost her brother for it.
When she was young,
she lost her dad because of me, too.
I heard what happened,
but she doesn't think like that at all.
I can't bear to watch her...
become unhappy because of me.
I'll make sure...
I solve this.
Mr Moon, is the chairman going to work today?
Yes, Ma'am.
Don't forget to give him his pills.
He just had them now. Don't worry.
How can I not?
His condition keeps getting worse.
Honey,
are you sure you can go to work?
Even if I have to get an IV,
I'll get it at work.
Gwang Woo.
What have you been up to?
I've been attending the junior CEO association meetings,
and I attended a seminar on free economy yesterday.
Who holds a seminar in the middle of the night?
You slept all day long...
and went out at night.
What time did you come home?
You know nothing about seminars on economy.
Sure.
Gwang Woo.
Come to work starting today.
What?
Don't sit around at home.
Come to work.
Father.
His health is faltering,
so you should help him.
Father, I will do my best.
I can give my life to this company.
No one wants your life.
Chief Secretary Moon, you will be assisting...
Gwang Woo.
Yes, Chairman.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Hey, ride your own car.
Dad wants me to get in.
You little...
I wanted to make a sweet return with Chairman, but she ruined it.
Mr Do, you can come with me.
Here.
What did you say?
Mr Do?
Is he one of the rank and file?
I'm sorry.
Chairman sent him to the management department.
Is he insane?
Mum, is this how I should be treated?
Don't go. You'll damage my honour, too.
Chairman is putting Mr Do through a test.
A test?
If he doesn't pass,
he'll never let him come back.
Fine, I'll go to work.
Let's see how far...
he goes.
Hold out until the general meeting.
I will make you the best after that meeting.
- Let's go, Mr Do.
- Come on.
Stop calling me that.
I can't call you CEO Do any more.
Where's your car?
Over there.
Do people know...
that I'm demoted?
The announcement is out.
What does a management department do?
You were once a CEO. How can you not know?
How could I know?
Go to the storage.
The storage?
It's a place to manage supplies.
You have to fill out a lot of papers.
It's harder than you think.
You know what? No one asked you.
Vice Chairman of SPD does not teach a mere employee...
about managing supplies.
So what? Do you want me to consider this as an honour?
Chief Secretary Moon.
Yes, Vice Chairman.
Who's in charge of supply management?
It's Chief Go Geum Sang.
Tell him to come to my office.
What is he trying to do?
This is work and he's Vice Chairman.
- So what?
- If you'll work, work.
If not, go home right now.
Where is the storage?
First basement.
Gosh, darn it.
(Dodo Group)
Yes?
It's me, Gi Tan.
Gi Tan!
Hey, where are you?
Is the blueprint safe with you?
Come out and meet me right now.
If you do anything rash,
you won't lay your hands on the blueprint.
Okay, fine. I'll be there.
Just tell me where.
Okay, send me the address.
Okay, Gi Tan. I'll see you there. Bye.
Finally.
This is the luck of my life.
Did I surprise you?
My gosh!
Why does he want to meet here?
Gwang Woo is headed over.
No, he's alone.
- Gi Tan.
- Silence. Follow me.
Gi Tan, what happened?
I was really worried about you.
Don't be so friendly. I'm not glad to see you.
Yes, you are.
You didn't call me for nothing.
Okay. Where is the blueprint?
Show me the blueprint first.
Then, I'll give you anything you want.
What... What is this?
It's just a music sheet.
This is the blueprint.
The deceased Professor Na wrote it as a code.
Are you trying to fool me?
You can check with Il Jae if you like.
What are you talking about?
The original is...
in his hands.
What?
Gun Woo is probably...
decoding it right now.
Did you just say, Gun Woo?
Il Jae and Gun Woo were...
on the same side all along.
Why would my brother-in-law do that?
Don't you get it?
Do I have to explain everything for you?
Wait, that means...
Il Jae wants to make Gun Woo the successor.
Later, he'll try to take it for himself.
It's pretty easy.
Gi Tan, wait. I'm dizzy.
Give me some time to think.
I have no time to wait for you.
So listen to me and do as I say.
Soo Yeon's brother is dead.
Il Jae killed him because of this blueprint.
You have to find the evidence of his murder.
You can't beat Gun Woo...
with Il Jae around.
You'll be completely destroyed...
once he decodes the blueprint.
I'll call you later.
It was Il Jae...
who brought Gun Woo.
Who do they think they are?
You can wait here.
Will Director Byun say that he murdered someone?
I have to try.
Don't get caught, Sir.
Don't worry. I'm not a kid.
Welcome.
Whatever.
Congratulations on your discharge.
How's Chairman doing?
Let's cut to the chase.
I heard you are with Gun Woo.
You met Gi Tan.
Why?
Are you afraid people will know that you murdered Soo Yeon's brother?
Gi Tan...
showed me the blueprint.
I wanted it at first,
but then I thought about why he would show that to me.
He just wants to come between us.
Il Jae.
You can tell me.
Was it you?
Did you kill Soo Yeon's brother?
You don't need to keep it a secret from me.
Hey! What are you doing?
Let go! Get away from me!
Did Gi Tan put you up to this? To get my confession?
Don't get involved with him!
He's the son of Director Jung whom you killed. He's Guk Cheol!
Give me the vaccine's blueprint.
Are you trying to get rid of me by using Gun Woo?
You're worse than Gi Tan!
Get him.
What? Hey, let go.
Hey. Do you want to die?
Did you just hit me?
How dare you?
You punk.
You're rude, incompetent and evil.
So why wouldn't I hit you?
Let him go.
Fine. You just watch.
That blueprint will end up in my hands.
Bark all you want.
Your father-in-law whom you respect so much...
is my uncle.
He's my mum's brother.
Whom do you think he'll take sides with...
between me and Gun Woo?
Do you think you can make our family fall...
by bringing in Gun Woo?
That blueprint...
will end up being mine.
I'll make it that way, Director Byun.
What a headache.
- Yes.
- What happened?
I got it, Gi Tan.
You got the evidence?
Yes. Il Jae said so himself...
that he killed Soo Yeon's brother.
What about the recording?
It's crystal clear.
So send me the blueprint first.
Then I'll send you the recording.
No, you send it first.
I'll check it first before sending it to you.
Let's meet then.
How about we exchange them on the spot?
Hello? Gi Tan?
Are you listening?
Don't try to trick me.
I'm not.
I just told you. I have the recording.
An idiot like you...
could never fool Il Jae.
What?
Just like how you were used until now,
you'll continue to be used by him...
until he throws you out like trash.
How dare you?
Find the evidence first.
That's the only way to get rid of Gun Woo and to save yourself.
I'm only telling you this because I feel sorry for you, you pushover.
Hey, Gi Tan!
What?
"Pushover"?
What do all these garbage take me for?
I knew he couldn't get it.
But he's tenacious.
He won't give up easily.
(Unidentified number)
Yes?
Did you have a nice chat with Gwang Woo?
Guk Cheol, where are you?
I was always near you.
You just didn't notice me.
Let's meet.
Sir.
Look over there.
I'll give it to you.
You know how to strangle me without moving a finger.
It's what you taught me when I was in prison.
Don't you remember?
People are dying out...
from prison as if to keep you entertained.
Do Gwang Woo or Lee Guk Cheol?
Who will die first?
Whoever it is, I hope he rests in peace.
"Do Gwang Woo or Byun Il Jae?"
"Who will die first?"
"Whoever it is,"
"I hope he rests in peace."
Before that happens,
Gi Ryang will kill you. You can take my word for it.
Should I give you a tip as well?
Before I see your end,
I will never die, Il Jae.
He disappeared.
I've informed the police, so let's wait and see.
It's an inspection.
Sir, could you lift up your head?
Don't throw up in the car.
Do it in this bag.
Hurry up and go.
Thank you.
We should be careful for a while.
Why hasn't Chae Ryung called?
I'm not sure. She must have her reasons.
Is she trustworthy?
We'll both be in danger if she changes her mind.
She'd never betray me.
Don't worry.
What happened with Gi Tan?
I haven't found him yet.
I can't wait much longer.
I'm sorry, Boss.
I'll take care of it soon.
When he got his vision back,
that's when...
you suggested that we recruit him to our organisation.
I regret...
not listening to you then.
If someone like him was under me,
I wouldn't worry about my successor.
Chae Ryung.
Yes.
The only way for him to live...
is to come work for me.
Do you mean that you will accept him?
Boss.
He doesn't suit our organisation.
He's the one...
that we really need.
He stole the blueprint.
We should follow our rules and terminate him.
Gi Tan...
is a weapon I really want to have.
A dealer like myself...
shouldn't miss such an opportunity.
You asked me to leave with you.
Does the offer still stand?
I think our boss wants Gi Tan as his heir.
I can't stand that.
After all I did...
to serve him...
Are you sure about this?
If you can keep me safe.
Let's talk about it again.
This is Ok Chae Ryung.
You're a hard person to reach.
What do you want?
Let's meet up.
I have no reason to meet you.
Why won't you tell your boss...
that you met Gi Tan?
You aren't the only one with ears.
I have spies everywhere as well.
Come to the gallery.
Do you think she'll accept our demand?
A broken reed...
will keep on swaying.
She's broken.
Tell me what you want.
I want you to stop Gi Tan...
from giving your boss the blueprint.
Are you asking me to betray my organisation?
Once we get the patent,
I'll give you 15 percent of the royalties.
Do you need time to think?
I refuse.
- Why?
- I don't like you.
I don't think...
you'd waste the rest of your life serving Jo Gi Ryang.
You and I are both cornered.
We can help...
and benefit each other, too.
Do you still not like me?
I want 30 percent of the royalties.
You want too much.
I think it's scrap value for having to risk my life.
It's a deal.
I want a legally binding contract.
I'll hire the lawyer.
Bring the contract tomorrow.
I like how you do business.
You're a true lobbyist.
Dong Soo, don't go.
Don't leave me.
Dong Soo...
Dong Soo!
Come back, Dong Soo...
Dong Soo...
He won't be in pain any more.
He went to a good place.
He left just like that, so you wouldn't need to nurse him any more.
Try to cheer up now.
Come in.
Welcome.
Did you ask around?
Yes. I had someone look into it for me.
- Thanks.
- Here.
Is this it?
Hang on.
Isn't this the doctor who performed Dong Soo's autopsy?
Why is he with Il Jae?
The autopsy result...
was fabricated.
I couldn't sleep a wink last night.
How could Il Jae do this to us?
- Auntie.
- He raised a tiger.
That means he wants to fight us.
That's not why Il Jae helped Gun Woo!
Ji Soo, don't try to defend him.
He showed me his true colours.
What will you do about this?
If he wanted to help Gun Woo,
he wouldn't have let Gwang Woo out of prison.
That's what you think.
Il Jae has the blueprint...
and he's helping Gun Woo.
The vaccine's blueprint.
I'll make him give it to you, Gwang Woo.
- Father.
- If you'll do that,
I can forgive and forget everything that happened.
Il Jae found it.
- You can't give it...
- He favours Gun Woo!
I never liked that!
Right?
This is why blood's thicker than water.
A son-in-law can never be true family.
We're done.
You can all go.
I trust that you will help me out.
Thank you, Brother.
Let's go.
You approved of Il Jae's plan at first.
What's done is done.
Losing those two over Gun Woo...
would be just foolish.
Mr Hwang.
What do you mean?
Why should I give Gwang Woo the blueprint?
I explained over the phone.
Just do it.
I won't.
We have the blueprint,
and Gun Woo has the chairman's trust and approval.
Why should I help a man Choong likes?
We want the same thing. We're just using different tactics.
What do you think...
Gun Woo will do for you?
Mr Hwang.
He will abandon you.
He has his father.
But still,
I won't do as you say.
What?
Honey.
I will not give Gwang Woo the blueprint.
I have made up my mind.
Think about it very carefully.
Father.
Where are you, Gun Woo?
I'd like to have a drink.
My joints ache.
I know how you feel about it,
but how long must we wait to see Il Jae?
I can't even talk to you.
I really need to pee.
He's here. He just left home.
Hide.
Why are you here?
I'm here to tell you something.
Are you going to go on about your brother again?
What?
Maybe you're sick of it,
but it breaks my heart.
They performed an autopsy.
Can't you get over it?
Explain that.
What were you doing...
with the doctor who did my brother's autopsy?
If you think...
you can use this to frame me for murder,
do it.
Don't worry.
You killed my brother.
And I will prove it.
How dare you come to the wake?
Whom were you there for?
You're not even human.
Don't let it get to you.
You shouldn't have...
harmed her brother.
What?
I will not...
forgive you for it.
Are you going to betray me for Soo Yeon?
Why can't I?
Watch your mouth.
You are...
very mistaken.
I can do without you,
but without me,
your life is over.
The second you touch me,
the truth about everything you did...
will hit the press.
You have no proof.
What will you reveal?
Do you think I won't?
I think...
he's a ticking time bomb.
He's a fool.
He wants...
to become my enemy.
I will make you...
and Il Jae pay for everything.
I didn't know about...
your brother's death.
I don't believe you.
Can't you...
believe me just once?
You want revenge.
But how?
Why don't you just use me?
- What?
- You can use me...
to get your revenge.
I'll let you.
You're crazy.
Stop ignoring my advances.
If you want,
I can crush Il Jae.
I can do it!
Has he not given an answer yet?
I'm off to see him now.
Tell him your demands in person.
Didn't you tell him?
Things have changed.
If you talk to him now, he might accept them.
Pick a location.
You have to be alone.
I agree.
Gi Tan.
I'll ask you one last time.
Must you meet my boss?
I can help you go abroad.
With that blueprint...
I want to clear my name and be free.
Gi Tan.
It was your call.
Don't blame me.
That's what I want for giving him the blueprint.
He should be available within the hour.
I'll call you.
(Select workout)
Are you exercising again?
(15 crunches)
Staying fit is part of our job description.
Why did you join the NIS?
To serve my country.
How did the meeting go?
I'll hear from her boss today.
Ok Chae Ryung.
Can she be trusted?
Why do you keep asking that?
Is there a reason?
You trust her too much.
Because I can.
Don't worry.
(Select workout)
I got a call from Gi Tan.
And the blueprint?
He has it.
Get him on the phone.
I'm Jo Gi Ryang.
Hello.
I'll send Chae Ryung.
Bring me the blueprint.
I will decide when and where we meet.
How dare you demand I come and meet you?
I have the blueprint and the upper hand.
It's my call.
What must I do?
You can bring only one man.
Refuse that and the deal's off.
You know how to exercise your advantage.
Very well.
I will give you...
anything you want.
And you can't tell...
Yeom Hyeong Gu that we're meeting.
- Yeom Hyeong Gu?
- I will tell you...
about him in person.
(Cha Joong Tak)
(Cha Dong Soo)
It's me, Jeong Eun.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
No.
It's not your fault.
With a flick of this trigger,
Gi Tan's dead.
We have a new target.
It's our boss, not Gi Tan.
Are you crazy?
My goal was to leave the organisation,
not to kill Gi Tan.
What about the deal with Il Jae?
His conditions were that...
I stop our boss from getting the blueprint.
But he's our boss.
His death will end it all.
For you, me and Gi Tan.
We'll all be free.
And very rich, at that.
Are you sure you won't need me?
I'll be fine.
Let's go.
He just left.
Don't worry.
He only took one man.
We should go.
You kept your word.
A man's word is equal to his pride.
I can't be the one...
to bow to you over a deal like this.
It's the blueprint saved on my phone.
Byun Il Jae has the original document.
I got a copy of it.
Do you mean that...
everything you said is true?
I told you.
Il Jae killed Professor Na.
Do you expect me to believe you over one photo?
Did Yeom Hyeong Gu...
frame Gi Tan?
He was...
in it with Il Jae.
If you don't believe us,
hear him say so himself.
Hello?
It's me.
Hyeong Gu told us everything.
Huaping will come after you now.
I met him yesterday. You're bluffing.
You just wait.
I'll make you pay...
for killing Professor Na.
You might have to watch your back.
Now, do you believe me?
How dare the likes of him...
covet what is mine?
He's calling you so brazenly.
This will be the last time.
What do you mean?
Today,
Gi Tan will die.
You want me to clear you of murder...
and share the profits of the vaccine.
Yes.
I have one condition.
I'm listening.
I want you to work for me.
Do you want me...
to become a member of Huaping?
Not a member.
Be my right-hand man.
The second-in-command.
(Monster)
Don't go, Gi Tan!
Please stay.
Now, I won't have any more nightmares of Guk Cheol.
Gi Tan, are you okay?
Neither of us can leave.
We'll both starve.
Did you forget that I have the advantage?
I'm sorry, Father. I'm so sorry.
It won't be a royal road.
It'll be a road of suffering.