(Episode 26)
Do you want me to drop your murder charges...
and give you some share of the blueprint?
- Yes.
- I have a condition, too.
What is it?
Why don't you come work for me?
Are you asking me...
to become a member of Huaping?
Not just a member.
I'm asking you to be my right-hand man.
You'll be the second-in-command.
That was...
not part of my plan.
It wasn't in mine either.
I would never make this offer to anyone else from now on.
Answer me, Gi Tan.
Will you take my offer?
- Gi Tan!
Gi Tan!
- You have to go, Boss.
- Hurry up.
- Don't shoot.
- Move.
Don't shoot. You shot Gi Tan.
Move away!
Gi Tan.
Where did it come from?
Across the river, Boss.
Start the car.
Hold on, Gi Tan.
Get him in the car.
Stop it, Cha Woo. We failed.
No, it's not over yet.
- What is that?
- I installed a bomb...
just in case we fail.
Our plan will end perfectly...
if those four people die.
No, Cha Woo.
Don't press it.
Why? Are you sad to see Gi Tan die?
Don't do it!
Watch me.
This bomb will be the firework that blesses...
our brand new beginning.
No!
Don't get in the way.
This is for the both of us.
Hurry up.
Yes, what?
Please get out. There's a bomb in there.
What?
Cha Woo has...
Drop it.
You started this.
Are you trying to back out...
because of Gi Tan?
Drop it, Cha Woo.
Shoot me if you can.
I know that you can't.
Please.
Our lives will change...
with this button.
I killed...
Cha Woo.
Cha Woo...
It's me, Mr Jang.
There's someone you need to save right now.
It's a gunshot wound, so he can't go to the hospital.
There's an operating room near Cheongpyeong. Meet us there now.
- Leo.
- Yes, Boss.
Call the boys to clean up the area.
Gi Tan and Sung Ae...
both died today from the explosion.
Hyeong Gu and Il Jae are on the same side.
So if we want to fake our deaths,
we have to fool Hyeong Gu first.
I'll get rid of him.
He's an executive of the NIS.
We don't want to get in trouble. Leak fake rumours instead.
Yes, Boss.
Gi Tan!
Wake up!
Gi Tan, wake up!
- Gi Tan. Wake up...
- Wake up!
Please. You can't die.
You promised you'd come back.
Jeong Eun. Jeong Eun.
Please, Guk Cheol.
Gi Tan. Gi Tan.
Don't go. Don't.
I'm sorry, Soo Yeon. I have to go.
You can't. Don't go!
Don't go, Gi Tan. Please don't leave me...
Please...
Don't go, Gi Tan.
Gi Tan.
Is everything all right?
- Cha Woo betrayed me?
- Yes.
I saw him take a sniper rifle, so I tailed him.
Why did he betray me?
I think he was eyeing the blueprint Gi Tan has.
Where's Gi Tan?
How did it go?
I did all I could with the emergency treatment,
but I'm concerned about the bullet in his head.
What will happen to him?
It's a miracle he's still alive.
It's stuck in a difficult area. If we end up making a mistake...
- during surgery...
- So?
What will happen to him.
It's hard to say that...
he'll make it out alive at this stage.
He took the hit for me.
His life is the same as mine.
You have to save him no matter what. No matter what!
I did my best. Let's wait and see.
You love kimchijjigae.
Here.
You should eat more.
It'll give you more energy.
Okay.
Yesterday, near Yangju Bridge,
a car exploded and fell into the river.
The police are investigating nearby security cameras and witnesses,
and they believe that the people inside the car were...
the escaped prisoner Kang and his accomplice Yoo.
- Isn't that Gi Tan?
- In the damaged car,
police found their personal belongings.
The police are assuming that it was a suicide...
and have started a search to find the bodies.
Are you sure Gi Tan's dead?
Yes, I'm sure.
You shouldn't believe anything until they find his body.
Huaping is good at cleaning up after themselves.
It'll be impossible to find their bodies.
Coma? Gi Tan is in a coma?
His brain is alive,
but he's unconscious.
When will he wake up?
It could be a month or a year.
He may never wake up at all.
I'll call you back later.
Did Gi Tan really die?
I saw the corpse myself.
I have to see it myself to believe it.
If you want everyone to know that you're behind this, go ahead.
I'll call back.
I won't be having nightmares about Guk Cheol any more.
I'm sorry, Gi Tan.
My greed...
did this to you.
Forgive me.
She's up to something for sure.
Is Soo Yeon still looking for Gi Tan?
Please look out for him.
Hello.
She's going around police stations and hospitals.
Why hospitals?
She's trying to see if any of the unidentified patients...
might be him.
(Hangang Hospital)
Why do you look so shabby? Did you even eat?
I told you to leave me alone.
How long are you going to be like this?
I don't have the energy to talk to you.
Gi Tan is dead!
He's not dead.
Wake up, Soo Yeon!
Let me go. Let me go!
A dead man won't come back even if you do this.
He's alive.
He's alive. I'm sure of it. He has to be alive!
Just accept it.
You already know that he's dead.
Find out what Gwang Woo is up to these days.
Sorry?
Yes, Sir.
Are you looking down at me because I'm a regular worker?
- No, Sir!
Chief Oh, stand up.
Chief Oh.
Do you think...
I'm a joke?
Not at all.
Then why are you telling me to work?
How dare you order me around?
I'm sorry.
Head down.
Hey, hey, hey! Raise your hands up higher!
How's Gwang Woo doing?
Nothing has changed.
Can you...
make him into a worthy man?
How could I do something even you couldn't do?
Could you do it...
if I gave you all of my authorities?
Authorities?
All authorities to him...
as his father and Chairman.
Even kings can't change their children.
If you give up on him,
I'll have to give up on him, too.
I hope you can...
accept this offer...
for his sake.
Please make sure...
nothing will happen to me, Chairman.
Nothing will happen to you even if that means...
I have to let Gwang Woo go.
I understand,
Chairman.
Hey, Chief Secretary Moon.
Did Father say anything about me?
Did he say anything about how long I have to be at the storage?
Follow me if you want to know.
What? Make me into a man?
He asked you to make me into a man, right?
Exactly.
What if I am made into a man?
I'll get complimented...
and you'll be appointed into an important position.
This sounds great. You and I can come up with a story.
Go and tell him that I have become a new man.
I'll behave when I'm around him.
I respect Chairman's will.
That's why I'm asking you to put on a show with me.
I really am going to make you into a new man.
- What?
- First, clean up this storage.
I don't want to see a speck of dust on my hand.
Chief Secretary Moon.
Next, fill out the supplies management book.
If anything is missing, you'll do it again.
Do you think you're somebody because Dad's behind you?
I'll give you three hours. Begin.
You're crazy. You've gone insane.
Begin.
Aren't you afraid of my backlash?
Just do it, you idiot!
- "Idiot"?
- Chief!
Yes, Sir.
Lock the door from the outside.
- What?
- It's Chairman's orders.
Lock the door and open it only on my words.
Yes, Sir.
We're not leaving until this place is clean.
Or we can starve to death.
Did you decode everything?
Yes. Vice Chairman is waiting for you.
Is that it?
What about the company?
It's already registered.
We can register the vaccine under that company's name.
When will you sign the contract with me?
I heard your dismissal is...
one of the topics for this general meeting.
Why don't we sign it at that time?
Sure.
Good job.
Your future is looking bright.
You did a good job as well.
I'll keep in touch.
Your future isn't bright.
It's your way to the rock bottom, Gun Woo.
When will you contact Gwang Woo?
Are you asleep?
Are you sleeping?
I won't forget...
this humiliation, Moon Tae Gwang.
What humiliation?
Are you finished?
I'm finished. Open the door.
All right.
Clean this shelf again.
Mr Do, are you deaf?
My gosh.
"Are you deaf?"
What if I am?
This one, too.
Great job today.
Goodness.
I will report everything you've done today to Chairman.
- What?
- From now on,
our work days will be like this.
You should be prepared.
What are you trying to do?
I'm trying to fix you...
because you're ill.
Gosh.
(Byun Il Jae)
Hello, Il Jae.
What's up?
Are you busy?
I just have to sign papers.
I'm not so busy.
I have to talk to you. Let's meet right now.
Where are we meeting?
Wow, look at this.
This is the famous blueprint we've been looking for.
Take a look at the contract.
Contracts are always the same.
You should take a look.
If I can't trust my family, whom can I trust?
Isn't that right?
Let's sign this...
in front of the shareholders...
at the extraordinary general meeting.
What did I tell you?
I told you that I'll find it.
I'm not signing this with you because I like you.
Gosh. Then you can take it back.
Sir.
You can't.
You're scared of your father-in-law.
Did you forget...
that I have the upper hand?
You have the upper hand, but you can't act like one...
because of your father-in-law.
You will see me...
acting like one very soon.
Get the papers.
Just go.
Congratulations, Sir.
I finally got it. Everything's over.
Mum, it's me.
Everything is taken care of.
Yes, I look forward to the extraordinary general meeting.
Keep your mouth shut until then.
It looks like Il Jae can't go against you.
It's not that he can't.
He won't because he loves him.
Let me announce...
the power of attorney at the EGM.
Do you want to give Gun Woo the blow?
I wanted to do it.
Is it because of Uncle?
Chairman Do?
Fine then.
Feel free to go ahead and give him a taste.
It's not a bad idea to begin...
my political career again at Dodo Group's EGM.
Send this...
to China to decode it.
Yes, Boss.
I'm sure Il Jae's side has it decoded already.
The new vaccine won't be able to enter China.
All we need is control over the mainland.
What will you do with Gi Tan?
- Leo.
- Yes, Boss.
Look for the right time...
to turn Cha Woo into...
the murderer of Professor Na.
He might never wake up.
I'll take him to mainland with me.
Are you saying you'll move him to China?
His brain is still alive.
I'll get all the help I can there...
to make him wake up again.
Look into a boat to get us out.
- Yes, Boss.
What do you...
plan on doing?
I need more time to think.
What a beautiful house.
Whose house is it anyway?
It's Cha Jeong Eun's house.
And if you permit,
it'd be our house.
Guk Cheol...
Will you...
marry me?
Jeong Eun.
Dong Soo.
The three of us can live happily together forever.
Let's never leave each other's sides.
Thank you, Guk Cheol.
Gwang Woo, you secured a deal for the new vaccine?
Be quiet. Your father will hear you.
He already left for work.
I thought he wasn't well. He was really sick last night.
Mr Gong took him himself.
Why is he trying to protect his son outside of marriage?
I can't bear to see him work.
Don't get upset.
Once we have the extraordinary general meeting today,
everything will be cleared.
But how did you manage to secure the deal?
Don't be so rude. You'll ruin my day.
If Gi Tan was here, he would've helped me...
secure a deal.
Why are you talking about the dead? Don't jinx us.
Mum. Once I become the CEO,
there's someone I want to fire right away.
Who is that?
Moon Tae Gwang.
Why him? Did he look down on you?
I couldn't mention it because it was embarrassing, but...
Just know that I'll fire him.
It won't stop with him. Once your dad collapses...
Mum.
Why would Dad collapse?
He's unwell these days. Eat your breakfast and go to work.
What's the matter?
It's nothing. I feel dizzy, that's all.
Do you want your pills?
I already took my pills, it's okay.
Hi. I'll try to stop the meeting today...
about your Vice Chairman position.
We'll sign the contract for the mutant virus vaccine at the EGM.
Is the vaccine...
ready?
A new company named B World registered for the patent,
and I was able to sign with them.
You're such an asset to the company.
The CEO of that company...
is Director Byun.
Byun Il Jae?
Does this mean that he's the one who stole the blueprint?
I don't know the details.
What's important to me is who gets to sign the contract.
Father, we can't pick and choose whom to work with.
Our company's benefit is our priority.
As long as we can secure the deal,
I don't care about anything else.
Please watch me. I won't disappoint you.
He takes after you on how he does business.
Gwang Woo changed a lot these days, too.
Did he?
How?
Didn't I report it to you already?
When?
You asked me to make a human out of him.
When did I say that?
Sir. Did you forget about the order you gave me?
Hold on.
I have a headache.
Right.
I remember it now.
I told you...
to teach him a lesson.
It's time for the EGM.
Let's go.
Is he all right?
It's normal for a human to be forgetful sometimes.
I've reported three times already, but he looked so clueless.
I have to escort him for now.
We'll talk later.
How can he forget that...
after making me the bad guy?
(Dodo Group Extraordinary General Meeting)
It's been a while, Chairman Do.
Why are you here?
An extraordinary general meeting isn't a party.
Obviously, I'm not here for the food.
That's why I'm asking.
He came as a shareholder.
I gave all my shares to him.
Are you teaming up...
to kick Gun Woo out?
There are a lot of eyes on you.
Don't you consider saving face more important than your wife?
It won't...
ever go as you planned.
You'll see.
When is Director Byun coming?
He won't be late, don't worry.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
Il Jae's father-in-law is here.
Are you sure he'll make the deal with you?
According to my intelligence, the two of them...
have gone their separate ways.
Before we get into the issue of the Vice Chairman's position,
the chairman will say a few words.
- Let me.
- I'm fine. It's okay.
I'll keep it short.
Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo...
has all but signed the contract...
to produce...
the vaccine to the mutant virus.
What's going on?
Is this true?
You must know...
better than anyone what that means for...
the future of our company.
Of course, we do.
If we sign the contract,
then you must promote Vice Chairman Do.
When will the contract be signed?
The CEO of the company that developed it is here.
It's good to see you again.
Our shareholders would like to know...
whom you decided to sign with.
May I tell them myself?
You may.
I'm Byun Il Jae, the CEO of B World.
I decided to enter into a technical partnership...
with Dodo Group because...
I was greatly moved...
by one person's passion.
Executive Director Do Gwang Woo.
Come and join me.
Put the vice chairman's dismissal to a vote.
Shouldn't we reinstate Do Gwang Woo as the CEO of Dodo Pharmaceutical?
Let's lay an urgent bill and vote right now.
Let's just vote.
Let's vote.
- Father.
- Dad!
- Sir.
- Father!
- Chairman!
- Sir.
Take him out.
Gently.
Mr Do just went into surgery.
- Surgery?
- We'll have to wait and see,
but the worst is over.
Get the car ready.
Yes, Ma'am.
I know quite a few people...
who would be devastated if my father collapsed.
What are you implying?
Hey.
Don't put on a show.
You aren't worried for him.
You're worried for your future.
Your father's in surgery.
Please stop.
What did you say in your job interview?
You said you wanted to succeed and make your father pay.
You got your way. You must be pleased.
Did he really say that?
Will you please stop?
Why are you here?
Send him away.
Can I stay until he wakes up?
Get him out of here.
Ma'am, you can't do this.
Why not?
Do you want to join him?
He is Chairman's son.
- He should get to see...
- Chief Secretary Moon.
Shut your mouth.
Get him out of here.
Until my husband is fully able,
I will make all the important decisions.
Do you both understand?
There's one thing that those who dislike...
and envy you don't know.
They don't know how incredibly proud I am of you.
Bear with me and hang in there.
I will make you...
a thousand times greater than you are now.
No one...
will be able to mock my son.
I'm sorry, Father.
I'm so sorry.
I don't...
pity you at all.
Why should I?
You had everything.
You tortured everybody.
Don't get it wrong.
These tears...
are for poor, little me.
You hated me all your life,
and now, I can hate you back.
I'm crying over the past that I lost.
Lie here in comfort...
and watch what I do next.
You used me...
to create this world.
Now, I'm in control.
(Hwang Gwi Ja, Dodo's Interim Chairperson)
Chairwoman is here.
Take this opportunity...
to get rid of all your father's allies.
He'll come back to Korea once he recovers.
What if he gets furious?
He might not come back to work.
He's making progress.
That's why we have to work fast.
So he can't do anything on his return.
What about Gun Woo?
He lost his title.
Deal with him later to avoid scrutiny.
Look at all these names.
I wonder whom I should start with first.
It's so much work.
Starting today,
we will shuffle personnel and restructure the organisation.
CEO Do Gwang Woo...
will be in charge.
Yes, Chairwoman.
Before we begin...
Chief Secretary Moon.
Yes, Sir.
I looked into the people in the Secretary's Office.
I can charge you for embezzlement.
Embezzlement?
That never happened.
That's the company's credit card statement...
and records of your operating expenses.
Explain those to me.
These were fabricated.
I swear that...
these purchases were never made.
Do Gwang Woo.
I worked here my whole life.
Now, I'll spend...
the rest of my life working towards tearing you down.
Gi Tan.
When will you wake up?
I can't leave until you do.
Because of you,
my life changed in many...
Can you hear me?
Do it again.
Move your fingers.
He moved.
I saw his fingers twitch.
Were you mistaken?
I'm positive.
I haven't seen you glare like that in a while.
This is what I wanted from you.
Lonely, angry and determined to win.
But then,
I noticed your eyes...
begin to glaze over.
You forgot who you are and why you're here.
Then again,
you were blinded by love.
No wonder you lost touch.
Is that why you sided with Gwang Woo?
It's business.
Nothing more, nothing less. You said so yourself.
Without what little expectations, pity...
and interest I had for you,
Gwang Woo was more useful.
Do you hate me for choosing him?
No.
I hate you...
for bringing me into this disaster.
The deal with Gwang Woo...
is for one year.
One year from now,
I'll sign a new one.
It could be with him or with you.
Get rid of your excess baggage.
Your father, women, friends.
Start again.
Kneel in front of me, hold my hand and thank me.
That's how...
you can start again.
You have until next week.
Come to me or not.
It's up to you.
Don't wait.
I won't...
go back.
I'm looking for someone.
I'm looking for someone. Please take a look.
Call me if you see someone similar.
I'm looking for someone.
Hello, please take a look.
(Missing Person)
I'm looking for someone.
- Soo Yeon.
- Don't get in my way.
I'm looking for someone.
I won't...
bother you again.
This is it.
I can't hold out any longer.
I'm looking for someone.
Please take a look.
Are you waiting for Gun Woo to call?
I sided with Gwang Woo because of Mr Hwang,
but he's poisonous.
I don't see why...
you can't give up on Gun Woo.
Mr Hwang is my biggest obstacle.
When the time comes,
I'll need Gun Woo, not Gwang Woo.
(Do Gun Woo)
Have you made a decision?
Let's meet.
I'm just an employee now.
I know that.
Your contract with Gwang Woo was for a year.
How long will ours be?
Three years.
That should be enough time to make you Vice Chairman again.
Make it 10.
I won't stop at being Vice Chairman.
Do you want me...
to trust you for 10 years?
I bought a plane ticket to the States.
If this deal falls through, I leave tonight.
There's something...
I wanted to ask you.
The mutant virus leak.
Do you know the truth?
- Soo Yeon.
- Tell me.
My father died in that accident.
Gi Tan.
Il Jae did it.
I'm meeting Jo Gi Ryang today.
Jo Gi Ryang?
From that weird Chinese organisation?
If all goes as planned,
I'll be in the clear tomorrow.
If something happens to you,
I don't think...
I'll be able to survive alone.
Until now, I couldn't die because of Il Jae.
I needed revenge.
Now,
you're the reason I can't die.
I won't ever...
leave you again.
Here.
Take those, too.
They'll help you a lot for the bar exam.
Thank you.
You should've done this sooner.
You graduated from law school only to join Dodo Group.
I wouldn't have met Gi Tan if I didn't.
But why the bar exam all of a sudden?
Are you going to become a lawyer to punish Il Jae?
No, right?
Good for you.
You need a new start anyway.
I won't call you.
I don't expect you to.
(B World Holds Partnership with Dodo Pharmaceutical)
Is Gi Tan...
making progress?
He twitches sometimes.
But I'm not sure.
If he wakes up,
will you take him in?
You said...
you'd make him your second-in-command.
I changed my mind.
- What?
- I won't live for much longer.
When he wakes up,
I will give him the whole organisation.
(1 year later)
It's time to go, CEO Do.
(Inauguration of CEO Do Gun Woo)
Dear fellow employees.
Starting today,
Dodo Group...
will enter a new phase of innovation and change.
Your great desire for something new...
put me where I am right now.
Mister, can you put it a little lower and to the left?
- No...
- It's a bit wonky.
The right side should go up a bit.
Oh, come on, you people.
Now, the right side is too low.
Is this your first job?
Lawyer Oh, do you like the office?
The thought of paying the rent keeps me up.
Don't you worry.
We'll take cases that only make money.
Yes.
This is great.
Gi Tan, watch me.
It's my new beginning.
It's been a year already.
Will you please wake up?
Close the curtains.
The sun's blinding me.
Gi...
Gi Tan...