(Episode 27)
(1 year later)
(Jo Gi Ryang's hideout, China)
It's been a year already.
Will you please wake up?
Close the curtains.
The sun's blinding me.
Gi...
Gi Tan.
Are you okay?
Do you know who I am?
It's me, Yoo Sung Ae.
Say anything. Anything at all.
Gi Tan, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Gi Tan!
The doctor said...
that the bullet left in his frontal lobe caused a problem.
Did he lose his memories?
He didn't lose them, per Se.
But his memories are all mixed up in his mind.
What will happen to him?
His memories will come back in time.
The problem is...
that he suffers from great pain because of that bullet.
How bad is his pain?
It may be difficult for him to lead an everyday life.
There is one way to remove the pain.
What is it?
Hypnotherapy.
Hypnotherapy?
We can put Gi Tan's memories back in order...
and remove his pain with hypnosis.
Is there anyone who can do that?
The professor of Jilin University can do it.
Bring her in immediately.
Yes.
(Urgent Press Conference for Former Congressman Hwang Jae Man)
Hello, everyone.
I am about to make...
a huge decision for every single person...
who was hurt in the army accidents...
because of the corrupt defence industry.
I, Hwang Jae Man, will...
donate every single property under my name...
for the treatment and welfare...
of those who were affected.
Former congressman Hwang Jae Man's decision is...
a hot potato in every aspect of the society.
On the same day, Mr Hwang's son-in-law,
Byun Il Jae, declared that he's running for Seoul Mayor.
Therefore, many believe that this is...
a new beginning of former congressman Hwang's return.
The political arena believes there will be...
a shift in power of this ruling party.
Soo Yeon.
Are you ready?
I'm almost done.
Good. It's your first time on television,
so make sure you look great.
I don't want to be known for my looks.
It should be for my ability.
Look at you. You're so proud again.
Don't do that on TV.
People will write bad comments about you.
People are getting nervous...
about your return.
I haven't any power or money.
They have nothing to be nervous about.
We don't do politics with power and money nowadays.
Also, your son-in-law is rich.
You've got nothing to worry about.
Come on, Congressman Kim.
Listen to you.
Hello.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
The real powerful man is here.
It's good to see you on TV.
My wife is a fan of yours, too.
Today's his last episode because he just registered as a candidate.
Mr Byun, are you confident about this election?
I've been considering this for the last year.
If all of you can help me, I can definitely win.
If you made up your mind earlier,
you could've been a candidate for our party.
He has this image he built up on television,
so running independently isn't a bad idea.
The candidate for the ruling party...
isn't one of us, either.
You should all come together...
to support my son-in-law.
Of course. We're on your side.
All right, lift up your glasses.
Okay. He just started his journey.
Thank you.
Who will be the mayor of Seoul?
- Byun Il Jae!
-  Byun Il Jae!
Who will be on the show after you?
She's this female lawyer from a new law firm...
called Min and Oh Law Firm.
Whoever it is, she should be thanking you...
for her chance on TV.
Go to the other side.
Soo Yeon.
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
Yes. What brings you to a TV station?
Oh, haven't you heard?
Lawyer Oh is your next host...
for your show "Legal Consultation".
Lawyer?
Did you become a lawyer?
Soo Yeon went to law school.
It was hard for her...
to work by the day and study by the night.
It's the fruit of her diligent study.
There were so many unfair things in life,
so I wanted to take care of them by the law.
Congratulations.
Hosting that show will really help your career as a lawyer.
I'll see you on the show.
Sure.
Let's go.
Why do you look so down?
Oh Soo Yeon is...
Cha Jeong Eun, the girl Guk Cheol liked.
What?
Are you saying that she knows...
about Gi Tan?
Probably.
Don't worry about it.
Let us begin.
Hello, everyone. Welcome to "Legal Consultation".
We have two special panellists today.
It's your last show. How do you feel?
While giving advice to those in need,
I learned so much.
Law and justice are close to you.
I hope all of you remember that.
I have a beautiful lady beside me.
Could you introduce yourself?
Hello, I'm Lawyer Oh Soo Yeon of Min and Oh Law Firm.
Hey.
When did Soo Yeon become a lawyer?
- I'll be seeing you every week now.
-  I never heard about it either.
I look forward to it.
She's become...
even cuter since I last saw her.
It's your first show today. Which case did you bring with you?
Some of you may remember this case. Director Jung Man Ok...
of Sudo Hospital was murdered 12 years ago.
Yes, there was a lot of commotion around that case.
At that time, Director Jung...
had a young nephew named Lee Guk Cheol.
The police concluded that the nephew was the murderer...
of Director Jung due to dispute over assets.
Hey.
What is she talking about in front of Il Jae?
- Il Jae looks really bitter.
-  After that, Lee ran away from...
the hospital, and he jumped into Han River.
Lawyer Oh.
I don't think that case is suitable for this television programme.
I plan on going over basic laws about inheritance...
and succession of property.
Please continue.
You already have over 10,000 comments on our website.
Lee Guk Cheol was 19 years old then.
He was blind.
The police said that it was a dispute over assets,
but he was already the heir to Sudo Hospital...
once he came of age.
Are you saying that there was no reason...
for his murdering his aunt?
One funny thing is that...
there is someone else who benefited from all this.
Who would that be?
It was Director Jung's husband...
who has no blood relations to Lee Guk Cheol.
That crazy...
Me?
No, I wasn't talking about you.
Did you eat something rotten for lunch?
You have a foul mouth for someone in politics.
A lot of people are curious about what the uncle is doing now.
Unfortunately, we can't share that with you.
Mr Byun.
It's your last show and all.
Why don't you tell our audience the truth?
Is it someone you know as well?
He knows him very well.
Could I tell them?
It's a hurtful memory,
so I've managed to forget about it.
I'm Lee Guk Cheol's uncle.
I see.
Soo Yeon is...
really putting Il Jae on the spot.
We just received a question.
"What if the inheritance has been processed, but the deceased...
ends up coming back? What happens then?"
Who will answer this question?
Since it's your last show,
you should go ahead.
- Good work.
-  Thank you.
- Be careful.
-  Are you all right?
Yes.
Gosh.
Are you going to get fired after one show?
The station is going crazy saying that it's an invasion of privacy.
If they don't like it,
I'll just quit.
Okay, fine. I felt good watching you talk like that,
but it's too reckless.
Even if I'm reckless,
I'm not as bad as someone else.
I know, but...
I give up. It'll work out.
You did well. You did great.
Lawyer Oh.
Can we...
talk in private?
You surprised me twice today.
Once by showing up as a lawyer...
and then once again when you spoke so boldly on television.
If you were surprised by just that,
you better brace yourself for the future.
If you brought up Guk Cheol's case...
to give me a hard time, you should give up now.
No matter how hard you try,
you won't find anything. It's clean.
It may be clean on paper, but what about morally?
I think...
the good image you've built up on the show...
will shatter into pieces.
Lawyer Oh.
Talking a lot and talking well are two different things.
Troubles...
will always start from one's mouth.
I'm a lawyer.
I make money with words. What else can I do?
Do you still think...
that I killed Dong Soo?
Thank you...
for still remembering...
my brother's name.
I don't have time to meddle with people like you.
You better not get in my way.
If something happens to me,
you will be the number one suspect.
I've already set up everything...
with the police, prosecutors and the television show.
Not bad.
I learned it from you.
You taught me how to ruin someone...
and not get a peep out of them.
And also where to stab to make them bleed the most.
And how pathetic and upsetting it is to be unable...
to stand up for yourself.
I learned it all from you.
The world is...
more complicated and scary than you think.
By the time you realise that,
you would have...
already ruined your life.
I hear you're going to try for the mayor of Seoul.
I hope...
you manage to go up as high as possible.
Because I'll make sure you fall down hard.
Hang in there.
Someone will be here soon to help you.
Professor.
I have a favour to ask before you treat the patient.
Go ahead.
Please erase his memories of "Oh Soo Yeon".
Her name used to be "Cha Jeong Eun".
Erase any memories of her...
along with any feelings associated with her.
What's the reason?
He's suffering because of her.
If he forgets about her,
it'll be easier for him to get better.
I'll try.
Kang Gi Tan.
Who are you?
I'm here to heal you.
First, put your mind at ease.
Look carefully at this watch.
Can you see the time?
Yes.
When this watch stops, your time will go backwards.
Time...
is moving backwards.
Now, close your eyes.
You're going back into your past.
What do you see?
I am eating a meal with my family.
Were you happy?
Yes.
Why did that happiness disappear?
Dad!
What's with you? Are you insane?
Why are you doing this?
My uncle...
killed...
my parents.
What happened to you afterwards?
Byun Il Jae tried to kill me.
I was reborn...
as Kang Gi Tan to get my revenge.
It will hurt you a lot...
to get revenge on someone.
Dad!
Are there any good memories?
Why are you suddenly crying?
There is someone I love.
It lasted very shortly,
but that was the happiest moment of my life.
Now,
your memories are...
perfectly in order.
Do you see that bullet stuck in your head?
Yes.
That bullet...
erased...
the name Oh Soo Yeon from your memory.
You do not have...
any memories...
regarding Cha Jeong Eun...
or Oh Soo Yeon in your head.
Also,
your headache will disappear, too.
You will go into...
a deep sleep.
Yes, sure.
- Sure.
-  I'm back.
You should work harder if we're paying you so much.
Where have you been?
- I wasn't slacking off.
-  Are you talking back to me?
Did you find anything?
I asked this directly to the legal team of Dodo Group.
The contract with their current lawyer is definitely over.
Why did you find that out?
Tell me more about their situation.
Didn't you get the order to change the company's lawyer?
He's been doing well so far. Why is that necessary?
It's my order!
Do you need another reason?
I also have the right to decide.
You should respect my opinion, too.
Hey, Gun Woo.
You must trust your board very much,
but I am the chairwoman.
Do you think you can outdo me?
You forgot the word "temporary". You're a temporary chairman.
What?
Once Father comes back, you'll have to leave.
It's been a year since he left.
That may as well become 10 years.
It's as if...
you wish that he would never return.
I have no time to fight with you.
Follow my orders.
Yes, I will recruit someone openly.
But do remember that I prefer to renew the current contract.
There's a war between Chairwoman and Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo.
That means, Vice Chairman Do's power has grown.
What do we have in common with Dodo Group's...
corporate lawyer position?
Which side is CEO Do Gwang Woo for?
Yes, don't worry, Lawyer Choi.
You will definitely become the corporate lawyer.
I'll call you back.
Are you referring to...
Lawyer Choi Guk Jo of Cheonmyeong Law Firm?
You're very quick to catch onto things.
You're really fast.
They were recently involved in a rebate scandal.
Who cares?
If we like him, we can work with him.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you think?
I want to cut off your arms and legs,
and place people from my side there.
You know this already.
Arms, legs, arms and legs.
We will also apply for the position.
Fill out the necessary papers and apply.
Okay, Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon.
A lot of high-profile lawyers will apply for the position.
Do you think we'll make it?
You have to try to see what happens.
You don't need to try anything this obvious.
If we do get the position, this will be a huge success for us.
I know that, too.
Be honest.
You're doing this because Il Jae is on their board.
Is that wrong?
I'm not saying that it's wrong.
I'm worried you'll get embarrassed for trying something impossible...
because of your hard feelings.
I wouldn't give it a shot unless I saw a possibility.
I have everything planned out.
Just stick with me.
My gosh, I chose the wrong partner.
She's practically my boss.
Did you sleep well?
Good morning.
Is Gi Tan still asleep?
It's been three days already. I'm worried.
- Gi Tan.
-  Are you awake?
Where am I?
You're in China.
China?
Don't strain yourself.
You were lying in bed for a year.
A year?
Has it been a year already?
Drink this.
It will clear up your mind.
Do you understand what happened in that year?
I heard it from Sung Ae.
Thank you for saving my life.
You must be very weak because you were bedridden for a year.
You should focus on getting your body back in shape.
Of course.
I have to talk to you in private.
Why did you...
step in to take the bullet instead of me?
I once tried to kill you.
So why did you save me...
while risking your own life?
Just because.
"Just because"?
Yes.
I just did as my heart told me.
Hearts never move without a reason.
Your heart will only move if you and I have...
a special relationship in this life...
or in our lives before.
What will you do after you get well?
I'll go back to Korea...
to finish my revenge on Il Jae.
Just like you,
I also lost my family.
We were on a vacation to Turkey about 20 years ago.
The moment I got out of my car to get my passport which I forgot,
the car blew up.
My old mother,
children and wife were...
sitting in that car.
I sold their government some missiles,
so the rebel army got their revenge on me.
Since then,
I have never had a family.
Just like you, Gi Tan.
I think...
I can understand how you feel.
I don't have...
much to live.
I also have fragments of a bomb...
stuck near my heart.
Come to think of it,
you and I have a lot in common.
Gi Tan.
Yes.
What do you think...
about becoming my son?
You'd get a father, and I'd get a son.
I want to have a family before I die...
so that someone would at least come to my grave.
I'm not trying to pressure you.
I'm only saying it...
because my heart's telling me to.
If you decline,
that's where our fate ends. It can't be helped.
(Father.)
Father.
I...
like it.
(Dodo Group)
It's already past the starting time. What's the delay?
Min and Oh Law Firm is supposed to go first,
but they're not here yet.
Min and Oh Law Firm?
That sounds familiar.
- We'll start without them.
-  Okay.
We'll now start the presentations to choose the next law firm...
for Dodo Group.
If I call your name, please come up.
Hold on!
Sorry we're late.
We're from the Min and Oh Law Firm.
Right, Min and Oh Law Firm. I saw you on television.
Since they just got here, let's change their order to the back.
It's their fault for being late. We'll just go as is.
You may start the presentation.
(Min and Oh Law Firm)
Please refer to the presentation documents we've handed out.
Min and Oh Law Firm...
was founded earlier this year...
You don't have any experience in working with a big company.
No, we don't.
There's no need to hear any more from you. Next.
Vice Chairman Do...
I want to hear more.
Lawyer Oh, please continue. Min and Oh Law Firm.
We're new and might not have as much experience,
but our success rate is over 90 percent.
It looks like...
all of the cases you've won are worth under 10,000 dollars.
Even so, a success rate of 90 percent is quite extraordinary.
I think you guys are competent enough.
Legal disputes between companies...
can range from millions to billions of dollars.
Just because you owned a small shop...
doesn't mean we can let you manage a department store.
Are you saying that we're not competent enough?
We're short on time. Next.
Vice Chairman Do.
Please step down.
Thank you.
That concludes today's presentations.
Once we come to a decision, we'll contact each firm.
Thank you.
Wait for me outside.
I'll be in the parking lot.
Can we talk?
When's my next meeting?
It's after lunch at 3pm.
I agree that we don't have enough experience.
However, I cannot agree that we're not competent enough.
That's for me to decide, not you.
Then you should look into everything before making a decision.
I've already made my decision. You didn't make it.
Gun Woo's not the type...
to be generous.
Do you want to have lunch with me?
Who knows?
If you're good to me,
maybe I'll help you become our lawyer.
I'll pay you the debt and interest on time this month.
Right, right. I forgot about that.
I'm not so good with small numbers.
So what do you like to eat?
We can drive out to Yangpyeong...
Or maybe somewhere closer? Hello?
Soo Yeon...
I wish I could make her come to my side.
You don't plan on recommending her...
for our legal advisor, do you?
Are you crazy?
I'm not a pushover.
I saw her ripping Il Jae apart on television last time.
It made me become interested in her.
Whenever I think about that contract I have with Il Jae,
it makes me angry down to my bones.
That's why I told you to read the contract carefully.
Why are you bringing that up?
Anyway...
If Soo Yeon...
joins Dodo Group,
it'll be a war between her and Il Jae.
May I sit for a minute?
I don't want to be disturbed.
I came up with a strategy for you to win with the appeal.
Give me a chance to show you what I can do.
If we lose any of the trials,
I won't ask you to sign with us.
There's no point in doing this. You should give up.
Sir!
Even if it's just once,
please look at these documents before making up your mind.
I will not give up.
Have a good night, Sir.
Soo Yeon, you...
Just read it.
See what strategy my law firm came up with.
Why do want to be our legal counsel?
You acted like you never wanted to see me again.
What is this about?
I want to make Il Jae pay.
I will destroy everything he has.
So that's it.
So...
are you going to use me to avenge your brother's death?
It was your idea.
You told me to use you. You said I could.
You turned me down and made me feel miserable in the process!
I was powerless then.
There was nothing I could do.
But not any more.
With someone's help,
I can do it.
Because I am...
not who I used to be.
Is that so?
Then you must act differently, too.
You aren't the only one who has changed.
I don't care about you any more.
So get out of my life.
Stop bothering me.
I wouldn't have started this...
if I were to give up so easily.
I will keep going.
Even if I end up in a fire pit.
(Dodo Group)
Shin Young, are you trying to bankrupt our hotel?
What's the problem now?
I gave you a company against the board's advice.
Don't make a mess of it.
Sales of the first half of the year hit rock bottom.
It's not just rock bottom, Mum. She's practically underground.
Is it my fault that no one wants to stay?
That's the last thing you should say.
Look at Gwang Woo.
Dodo Pharmaceutical's the most profitable in its industry.
How is that down to him?
It's because Gun Woo signed the deal for the new drug.
If you want to keep your title,
do something before the next general meeting.
I have some bad news.
What could happen so early in the morning?
I just got a call.
Chairman Do just boarded his private jet to Korea.
What?
He's coming back?
That's great. I missed him so much lately.
It's not great at all. This could be a disaster.
What should we do?
It's not like we did anything wrong.
You and Gwang Woo...
fired all of Dad's remaining allies.
What if he collapses with shock again?
The company's just fine, isn't it?
Keep your chin up.
We saved the company.
Who sent him the private jet?
I wonder.
The doctor said...
he hadn't recovered yet.
Seeing how he cancelled all his morning appointments,
I think it's Vice Chairman Do.
What?
How dare he?
He's always the one to stir up trouble.
Nothing works out when he's around.
Father.
Hi, Gun Woo.
How do you feel?
My legs are still weak,
but otherwise, I'm fine.
I've missed you.
I heard about...
how things are.
The shareholders...
seem to trust you immensely.
He must be tired. Take him home.
Let's go to the company.
Sir.
Your doctor told you not to tire yourself out.
Don't worry.
Take me to Dodo.
Did you tell them?
No, I didn't.
Dad.
Do you know how much I've missed you?
You've aged so much more since I last saw you.
I'm not old.
And I'm very healthy.
Welcome back.
I couldn't sleep a wink since I heard you'd be back.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to visit you, Father.
Gwi Ja.
We need to talk.
Can't we talk at home? I have work to do.
- Take me to my office.
-  Yes, Sir.
(Chairwoman Hwang Gwi Ja)
You went from working at a sewing machine...
to being called chairwoman of a huge company.
What an improvement that is.
Do you have to be so spiteful?
I worked hard night and day to keep the company afloat.
You had to fire all my allies and those loyal to me.
I bet that kept you busy.
Honey,
I didn't make that decision alone.
The executive board...
Your followers supported you!
Do you think I don't know?
Don't be so angry.
You have high blood pressure.
The people you fired.
Do you know who they are?
They are the pioneers...
who made Dodo Group the great company it is now!
The trust...
I'd worked all my life to build up and maintain...
was crushed in a second by you!
This is your problem.
Look towards the future, not back at the past.
Pioneers?
So what?
This is why the executive board wants me to run the company.
What?
You stay at home and rest.
I am in charge now.
Resign right now...
and go back to being the housewife you always were!
I will start work tomorrow, okay?
I won't let you.
What do you think you can do now?
What? Gwi Ja.
There are processes to follow.
Too bad for you that I set them up.
Are you...
trying to start a bloody war?
There's nothing to fight about!
Shall I show you how useless you are?
Is anyone out there?
Mr Do is tired. Take him home.
I'm not done talking.
You heard me. Take him home!
Take him home.
Hey! Get your hands off me!
Get him out!
Don't you know who I am?
I am Dodo Group's Chairman!
Don't just stand there! Move it!
- Chairman!
-  You fools!
Chairman!
Chairman.
"Chairman"?
There can be only one sun in the sky!
I am the Chairwoman of Dodo Group!
Do Choong is no longer in charge!
I think you made a full physical recovery.
Were you always this good at kendo?
I'm an expert.
Let me ask you something.
Did I ever...
like you at one point?
Do you still have memory issues?
No.
I remember everything clearly.
How should I explain it?
It's like...
I think I liked someone very much.
And was that me?
Yes.
What if it was?
Can you like me?
No. I'm sure it wasn't you.
Then why ask? You ruined my mood.
Your father calls, Sir.
Can you stop being so polite?
It's so awkward.
You're my boss' son and second-in-command.
Deal with it.
See how things are in Seoul.
I want to know everything about Il Jae.
Yes, Sir.
Do you want to return to Korea?
Yes.
We were commissioned...
to procure a large ship.
Why don't you work on that while you're in Korea?
Until I sort out my personal life,
I don't think I can help you.
Dodo Group applied...
for the right to build the ship.
Isn't Il Jae deeply involved with Dodo Group?
Are you saying I can run a business and get my revenge?
Il Jae...
ruined my plans for the vaccine.
Your revenge is now mine as well.
I will do as you say, Father.
Wait, stop, please.
I only barely got this job.
Please leave me alone.
Then pay us what you owe.
Do we look like pushovers to you?
Wait, isn't that Tae Gwang?
I'll sell my heart if I must to get you your money.
So please.
Please don't touch my family. Please...
Oh dear.
You have a week to pay the interest.
- Okay.
-  If not,
say goodbye...
to your family in the Philippines.
- Start paying me back.
-  I will.
Goodness.
Let's go.
What a mess.
Why are you here?
Didn't you want to get back at me?
All my life,
I begged and grovelled to please you.
So why should I suffer like this?
You don't know what you did wrong.
You took the wrong side.
You should have begged me.
Do you know what a crucial mistake it is to take the wrong side?
For as long as I live,
I will bring you down with my own hands.
Do Gwang Woo...
Give up.
I don't like seeing you get beaten up.
You used to be Chief Secretary.
It's such an embarrassment.
I won't die.
I can't die...
before I make you suffer as much as I did.
Do Gwang Woo.
Gwang Woo kicked Tae Gwang out.
He started selling fried chicken but went bankrupt.
His wife divorced him over his debt,
and now, he's a delinquent borrower.
What about Lee Soo Tak?
Welcome.
Why are you back again? Business is already slow.
Give me some soju.
Just one bottle.
Let's start a business.
Do you have the money?
You're a delinquent borrower.
I can still help bring in customers.
The local gang trashed my place earlier today.
I'll end up like you if I lose this.
I don't know how we ended up like this.
Do you want some chicken feet?
Don't mention chicken. I lost everything frying chicken.
You aren't hungry, then.
Here.
Soo Tak served six months for industrial espionage.
He owns and runs a tent bar.
Why did you locate them?
We need people to help us.
Will you scout them?
Mr Moon...
is very skilled.
Soo Tak is a friend I need to help out.
- I agree.
-  Once we land,
find those two first.
Yes, Sir.
(Dodo Hotel)
A Chinese businessman wishes to stay long-term?
Yes, Miss.
But there's a problem.
What is it?
He wants to stay in the suite you're in.
My suite?
- Tell him to go somewhere else.
-  But in return,
he'll rent all the rooms in the floor directly below.
- All of them?
-  Yes.
Is he bringing a group of old people on a tour?
I don't think so.
VIPs tend to reserve the whole floor...
for security reasons.
We must be expecting someone great.
If he does show up, I suggest you thank him in person.
Must I?
Someone like him will be very connected.
Make his acquaintance.
He must be a fat, old man with white hair.
I hate that.
You do it.
Miss.
Sales have been dropping and we've been in the red for...
I said no.
Everything's in the red.
More, please.
Chae Ryung.
Why are you here?
My chairman would like to meet you.
Who's your chairman?
Here's his business card.
"K"?
Is that his name?
Yes.
Why does he want to see me?
At 6pm tomorrow,
come to Dodo Hotel's suite.
Hey, Soo Tak.
Welcome...
How are you?
Wake up, Soo Tak.
You are awake.
Then...
am I possessed? I'm seeing ghosts.
Someone wants to see you.
It's okay, Miss. I still have more years to live.
Come to Dodo Hotel's suite by 6pm tomorrow.
She just hit me.
Was that her?
Yoo Sung Ae!
Where is Il Jae?
Campaigning in town.
Will you see him?
I saw his face even when I was in a coma.
I'd love to see him.
What's this businessman's name?
Everyone calls him "K".
"K"?
Is he in?
I just called to confirm.
Do you want me to invite him to dinner?
Yes, Miss.
Dear fellow citizens of Seoul.
I am...
a citizen of Seoul...
and the breadwinner of a family.
I've lived in Seoul for 50 years.
As a young boy, I grew up on the banks of Cheonggyecheon.
I spent my 20s in Mapo looking at the Han River.
Now, I work on Namsan and look down at Seoul's city centre.
I work for you.
I thought and dreamed of a Seoul...
that works for the weak.
Only I, Candidate number three, Byun Il Jae...
can work for the weak and the underprivileged.
The real people of Seoul.
I will create a city that serves everyone!
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
How can someone manage to tell a lie each time he speaks?
If we're to stop him from becoming the mayor,
we have to become Dodo Group's legal counsel.
How will you stop him?
Where do you think all his funds come from?
I'm sure he's stealing it from Dodo.
We need to find evidence of it.
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
It's time to meet Gun Woo.
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
-  What's wrong?
You need to smile.
Show the people how trustworthy...
It's Gi Tan.
(Monster)
How have you been?
The chairman called "K" was...
It's me. I'll take you all the way with me.
I know more of Il Jae's weaknesses than anyone else.
Come to the bar in the basement of Hangang Hotel by 9pm.
Miss this opportunity and you'll never get back at Il Jae.
Can I trust Soo Yeon?
The boss gave his order. It must be done.