(Episode 28)
Hello.
This is our CEO.
I'd like to meet with the guest.
Did you set an appointment?
No, she came to greet...
He's not in. Please leave.
He's not in?
Then why are you guarding an empty room?
Ma'am...
We'll come back another time.
Let's go.
They're making a fool out of me, right?
Not necessarily. You didn't have an appointment.
I wasted my time. They're totally making fun of me.
Who is this K or whatever? What's so special about him...
that even his guards are so rude?
They'll hear you. Please lower your voice.
I'm not in the mood. Cancel it.
I'll set a time with him.
Just show up to eat.
We're in the negative again this month.
I know. Stop with the money talk.
I'm sick of it.
I'm sorry.
I should just sell the hotel.
Gosh.
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
If we're to stop him from becoming the mayor,
we have to become Dodo Group's legal counsel.
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
It's time to meet Gun Woo.
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
That's...
It's Gi Tan.
Darn it.
Hi.
What happened?
Professor Na's murder case has been terminated already.
Gi Tan is still alive.
The murderer is still out and about.
The real murderer for that case is known as...
someone named Cha Woo.
What are you talking about? Who's Cha Woo?
He's Jo Gi Ryang's man.
He killed himself and left a note saying that he's the murderer.
Did the police buy that?
There is a witness...
who saw him murder Professor Na on that day.
That witness must be another one of Jo Gi Ryang's man.
Yes, you're right.
In other words, Gi Ryang framed...
the deceased Cha Woo with that murder...
and saved Gi Tan.
Why didn't he hide himself?
Why did he show himself to us?
It's a declaration of war.
His tactics did not work thus far,
so he's going into a full-scale war.
What should we do? Now that he's free,
he'll become more evil.
Even sharks are...
merely fish once they're on land.
I don't care if he has Gi Ryang on his side.
This is Korea.
He is completely misled into thinking...
that he can win a full-scale war in Korea.
My thoughts are just like yours, Father.
But the fact that he appeared right before the elections...
concerns me.
He probably...
can't do much.
Be thoroughly prepared.
Okay.
(Ok Chae Ryung)
The number you have called is no longer in service.
Ok Chae Ryung?
I've been watching her closely for the last year.
She seems very suspicious.
Hey, Sung Ae.
She can never betray...
This is a copy of her mobile.
If she has betrayed you, she'll get a call from Il Jae.
Is it because he knows about me now?
When did you do that?
Did you forget? I'm with the government.
Her number has changed, so he may not know about it yet.
I will make sure he gets her number.
What? Did that K guy decline my invitation?
Not only that. He wants to call his own chef...
instead of eating the hotel's food.
He's treating us as if we are a cheap motel.
Did you tell him about me?
He's a businessman. Of course he'd know about you.
Are you saying that he did this knowing who I was?
What does he look like?
He's very tall and handsome.
- Isn't he an old man?
-  He was young.
My goodness. That's worse.
He's just showing off.
I'm not surprised. He definitely can show off.
Okay, then.
Make sure he dines with me tomorrow night.
- Are you serious?
-  Our hotel is in a loss.
Okay.
He's really getting on my nerves.
(Dodo Hotel)
Wait a second.
Wait.
Why are you here?
I'm visiting the suite. Why?
Wait a second. Let me check.
He's our guest.
Welcome.
I'm sorry.
- Let's go.
-  Sure.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, are these the company's employees?
Chief Secretary Moon.
Soo Tak, why are you here?
Both of you were invited.
Chairman will be here soon.
You can eat first.
Okay.
Hey.
Do you know who the chairman is?
I only got his business card.
Something is weird.
Those people outside are weird, too.
Do you think...
they're trying to kidnap us for organ trafficking?
Organ traffickers wouldn't give us a huge feast.
That's true. I'm here because Sung Ae called me.
- Sung Ae from Secretary's Office?
-  Yes.
I thought she was dead.
I thought I was seeing a ghost, too.
Things are getting weirder and weirder.
Gosh!
Hey, you can't eat that.
I only had instant noodles today.
But still.
How have you been?
Gi Tan.
That means K was...
A lot happened within the last year.
Gi Tan became a chairman,
but I became a loser.
Anyways, I'm glad to see that you're doing well.
You should have called Soo Yeon here, too.
Soo Yeon?
Come on. Soo Yeon. Oh Soo Yeon.
You should talk about your business, Sir.
Soo Tak, will you come with me?
Oh, okay.
I heard about you.
You were fired by Gwang Woo and got a divorce, too.
I'm the bad guy.
I always made excuses that I was busy working.
And now,
I can't even be a father.
Can you help out with my business?
What is it?
Legally speaking, it's about making investments...
and signing contracts with ships from China.
What's the illegal part?
Getting my revenge...
at Il Jae and Gwang Woo.
(Account Book)
This is your front money.
Three million dollars?
You can clear your debt...
and take care of your family.
Why did you...
choose me?
You are...
the best in Korea.
You can get your revenge on Gwang Woo.
You're the best partner for me.
I don't fire people like Dodo Group does.
You'll stay with me to the end.
Thank you, Gi Tan.
You have saved my family.
I owe my life to you.
Do we have a deal?
I will do my best.
I will be loyal.
From now on, I will call you Chairman.
Thank you, Gi Tan. Thank you.
Does that mean he doesn't remember Soo Yeon?
He has a bullet in his head.
If you force him to remember, it may endanger his life.
So don't ever mention Soo Yeon's name.
Also, don't tell her about him either.
Poor Soo Yeon.
She's working so hard to take revenge for him.
Please review it just once.
That's not too much to ask.
You're so persistent.
Get out.
Leave it.
You want me to review it?
Here. I reviewed it.
Happy?
You're not the only stubborn one.
You should give up.
Gosh. Why are you eating this...
alone?
I'm stressed.
If you're not here to eat, can you leave me alone?
How is that? Is it tasty?
Why would I pay for something that tastes bad?
Gun Woo trampled over you,
but you seem to be doing fine.
Hey.
You have a beautiful neck.
It's so slender.
Do you want to be sued for sexual harassment?
You're so charming.
I love girls who play hard to get.
Other girls can't act like you in front of me.
Ta-da.
How can a girl not have a single necklace?
Bring me that long and beautiful neck close.
I hate people like you.
Gosh.
No woman has ever rejected me.
Are you trying to make me antsy?
You disgust me.
You're such a player.
You know how to play with people's hearts.
Hey.
I hear you're enemies with Il Jae.
What do you think about holding hands?
I want to kill him, too.
He scammed me for the year long contract.
He made a fool out of me.
Il Jae and Gun Woo are on the same side.
- I know.
-  How can you act like that...
if you already know?
You and I should partner up if you want to pay Il Jae back.
I pick and choose my people...
between those I can trust and those I cannot.
Do you think you can trust Gun Woo...
and not me?
You have it all wrong.
You can't trust anyone in this world.
What matters is if your goals align.
Be simple. Don't make it so complicated.
If you want to become our legal counsel,
come to the underground bar in Hangang Hotel by 9pm tonight.
If you miss this chance,
you won't ever get your revenge on Il Jae.
And I won't ever...
reach out to you again either.
Lawyer Kang says he's running late due to traffic.
Okay. Get me a drink.
It's Soo Yeon.
Call Lawyer Kang and change our meeting location.
You made the right decision.
I was afraid you might not show up.
Can you promise me the legal counsel position?
Of course.
I always keep my promises.
Especially the ones...
with women.
What are you doing?
Don't act so innocent.
Didn't you expect this on your way here?
We already have someone picked out for that role.
We'll have to kick him out before giving it to you.
A promise won't cut it.
You and I really have to be on the same side.
Watch it.
I want you...
to be my girl.
I'll be waiting for you.
Cancel my meeting...
with Lawyer Kang.
That jerk...
What does he take me for?
What are you doing?
Is this how low you've become?
Low?
Don't you know what Gwang Woo is like?
It's none of your business.
- What?
-  Do you know how my brother died?
Do you even know how I feel?
What do you know?
I can do much worse...
than what you're thinking.
There's nothing I won't do.
Here's my secret weapon.
Gosh.
It's been a while.
I already gave you the key.
Why are you ringing the bell?
You're getting me excited.
You...
Hey. What is this about?
How did you...
How dare you? You little...
You should know your place. Why do you keep bothering me?
Hey! Is this about Soo Yeon?
You're an animal.
What does it have to do with you?
Are you her boyfriend?
Shut your mouth!
Sir.
Sir, please calm down.
Are you serious? Take this!
You...
Hey.
Gun Woo.
I'll get you.
Gi Tan.
I'm fine, don't worry.
Tell the board members that we'll go with Soo Yeon...
as our legal counsel.
I'm sorry?
Kang Ga Din?
What's wrong?
It can't be. He's dead.
But he looks so much like him.
Shin Young is following you.
That's annoying. Let's speed up.
- Follow them.
-  What?
- Find out where they're going.
-  Yes.
It can't be Ga Din.
I've been working too much. I must be seeing things.
Was Shin Young the woman I liked...
- by any chance?
-  Why?
Did your heart ache?
It always aches.
It feels as if I have a hole in my heart.
There were rumours that Do Choong wanted you as his son-in-law.
Then is it really her?
You also know that she's a little princess.
I know that very well. I was her personal assistant.
Can you like her?
I don't know many women.
It's either you or Shin Young.
You never know. You may have liked her without anyone's knowing.
That'll be troublesome.
I must've been crazy.
You don't know this for sure.
No, I can tell by the way she chased after me.
There must be something here.
- Did you lose him?
-  I'm sorry.
It's nothing to be sorry about. I must be seeing things.
Anyways, what happened with the dinner invitation?
- He declined it.
-  Again?
He's insane, isn't he?
I think you should give up.
It looks like he's playing hard to get.
There are 3 strong candidates and 5 weak ones.
The ruling party, opposing party and Il Jae are strong candidates.
Other five candidates are classified as weak candidates.
Is there a chance for Il Jae to be elected?
Experts believe...
he'll become the strongest candidate at the end of this month.
In that case,
we should move before then.
Is there anything you thought of?
There is no one in Korea...
who knows more about Il Jae's weaknesses than me.
Your call has been forwarded to an automated voice...
Are you sure it's Chae Ryung's number?
I went and asked a staff of her gallery myself.
If you need to take it, you can go outside.
I'm sorry.
It's me, Il Jae.
Where have you been?
I was overseas.
Gi Tan is alive.
Did you know?
No, I've been away from everyone. I didn't know.
If you are lying because of your loyalty,
you will pay for it.
I'm not lying.
I really didn't know.
We did not get a patent in China with our new medicine.
Is this because of Jo Gi Ryang?
It probably is.
He has connections with many high-profile people in China.
We have much to discuss. Let's meet right now.
We'll take you.
Okay, Father.
- What did he say?
-  There are no exceptions.
We will move according to our rules.
What is that rule?
She'll be eliminated.
Gi Tan, can you do it?
Chae Ryung's life has been taken away...
the moment Boss wanted her dead.
- How can you kill a person?
-  If not, I'll get killed.
- Where's Chae Ryung?
-  She's inside.
I'll take care of her.
Wait here.
Unlike anyone else,
I trusted you.
So what?
Are you going to kill me?
It's our rule.
You know it better than I do.
I won't beg for my life.
I know I'll die, anyways.
Let me ask you one thing.
Why did you shoot Boss, not me?
If Il Jae wanted someone dead,
it should've been me.
But you shot Boss.
I only stepped in.
Why?
How could I kill you?
I can't kill you.
That's why I killed Cha Woo.
He wanted to blow up the car you were in.
I brought this upon myself. I have no regrets.
Kill me. If not, you'll die.
You're right.
If I don't kill you, I'll die.
I liked you a lot.
I'm relieved to know...
that I can die in your hands.
Mr Moon.
Take care of her body.
Yes.
- Everyone can go.
-  Yes, Chairman.
- Everyone, leave.
-  Yes, Sir.
Stay here just in case anything happens.
Get up.
Ok Chae Ryung is officially deceased.
If anyone finds out you're alive, Chairman will die. Understood?
I know.
Come with me.
Il Jae.
He thinks I'm on his team.
I will leave,
but I don't want to remain as a traitor to Gi Tan.
Will you be a double agent?
Yes.
This isn't for me to decide.
- Chairman will need to approve...
-  He won't approve of it.
He said he'll never see me again.
When I get any results from working as a double agent,
you can tell Gi Tan at that time.
Until then, I'll only contact you.
From now on, Mr Gong...
will be the only one taking care of my husband.
Mrs Do, what do you mean?
"Mrs Do"?
I'm the chairwoman.
Starting with his meals, laundry and other housework,
I want you to take care of him by yourself.
Do you want to ostracise him?
I never said such a thing.
I asked you to take care of him.
You know how difficult it'll be for him.
If you're not confident, you can go to the nursing home with him.
Why do you persist on staying in this house?
- Mrs Do...
-  Chairwoman!
If you're still displeased, you can leave for good.
I'll give you enough severance pay for you to live off of.
I can't leave...
without him.
Then keep your mouth shut!
You all heard me, right?
Starting today,
I'll fire anyone...
who tries to take care of my husband.
What's wrong with you?
You think that it's normal for me to sacrifice for you.
I want you to experience how I felt.
That's the only way you'll understand.
You're narrow-minded and evil.
You're right.
I'm narrow-minded and evil.
People say that you reap what you sow.
You were always so dignified in front of me.
You'd have an affair and bring in an illegitimate child.
You'd treat me harshly in front of others, and it was nothing to you.
I'm going to do the same.
I'll be confident and dignified.
If you're being like this,
I won't give Gwang Woo or Shin Young...
any of my inheritance.
Do you think I'm just a housewife?
Do you think I didn't do my research on your inheritance?
Even if you write a will,
half of what you own is legally ours!
It's called legitim.
Poor you.
You ran out of things you can threaten me with.
Gwi Ja.
What will you do...
if I get back on my feet?
I'm worried that you might actually die like this.
I feel so sorry for you.
Take this...
and live a long life.
You can't die so soon.
I suffered for too long.
I haven't cooked for so long.
I'm not sure how it'll taste.
You should eat with me.
I'm okay. You go ahead.
I feel lonely, that's why.
Come and eat with me.
All right, Sir.
Doenjang jjigae?
It's been a while.
What's wrong?
Does it taste bad?
I'm sorry, Sir.
Sir.
What do you think about leaving this place for a home?
Sir?
Mr Gong.
You remember, don't you?
A lot of people...
tried to pull me down until now.
Samgong Group's Chairman Oh.
Daehan Group's Chairman Park.
Prime Minister Kim Oh Joong.
Governor Ahn Goo Cheol.
They all ended up...
crawling back to me and begging.
That's the kind of person I was.
Sir.
But...
the woman I looked down the most...
turned me into this.
Everyone was scared of Do Choong.
But she turned me...
into this shabby...
and pathetic man.
"I lived in Seoul for over 50 years."
"When I was young, I lived in Ttukbang looking over..."
"In my 20s, I lived in Mapo, looking over Han River."
"Now, I'm near Mount Namsan..."
Hello?
It's me, Chae Ryung.
What happened that day?
I'm being changed by Huaping.
Where are you right now?
I'll send a car to you. Come to my house.
That'll be the safest.
Are you better now?
Yes. Thank you.
Gi Tan...
was trying to kill you?
Yes. He found out that I was on your side.
Where is he now?
He's staying at Dodo Hotel.
But the security is really tight.
It'll be hard to approach him.
Do you know his plans?
I know that his first plan is to make sure that Mr Byun...
doesn't get elected as Seoul's mayor.
It's just as we anticipated.
Then...
how does he plan on doing that?
I don't know the details.
I know someone close to Gi Tan, so I'll find out.
You're going to help us?
Unless Gi Tan disappears,
I'll have to live the rest of my life on the run.
Please let me help you.
If you come to our side,
we couldn't ask for any more.
Thank you.
If you need a place to hide, you can stay here.
Really? Can I do that?
We're family now.
We'll help each other out.
Is that okay with you, Honey?
Yes, it's fine with me.
I should get my belongings from where I was staying.
Mr Byun, will you come with me?
Sure. Get the car ready.
Okay, Sir.
Come with me.
What are you thinking inviting her to stay here?
What's wrong?
Are you suspicious of her?
We shouldn't trust anyone yet.
(Yeom Hyeong Gu)
Well?
Did you find out anything?
I talked to the Chinese side,
and it's true that Gi Ryang ordered Chae Ryung...
to be killed.
Gi Tan found out that Chae Ryung betrayed them.
Following their rules,
he decided to kill her.
Make sure...
no one finds out about her staying at my house.
Her life's at stake.
Yes. All right.
I don't think we have to be...
so suspicious of her at the moment.
I'll be going now.
All right.
You've had enough to drink.
I don't think I can sleep unless I'm drunk.
Gi Tan aimed a gun at my head and...
You don't know how that feels unless you've experienced it.
You're softer than I thought.
What did you think I was like?
Cold, strong and haughty.
No compassion at all.
I thought I was like that, too.
But it was all a mask.
I was trained by the Huaping.
That wasn't the real me.
I lived a fake life.
I left Huaping because I was sick of it.
Now, I don't know what I should do.
Be strong.
Everyone goes about life...
with a hint of lie.
And saints are of no exception.
That is life.
I'm in so much pain.
I'd rather die.
They say law is equal to everyone.
But in Korea, the powerful get off lightly...
and the weak suffer.
That is our heart-breaking reality.
Stay strong, have hope and contact our programme.
We won't make you pay.
We should use that woman...
to ruin Il Jae's campaign.
What?
Il Jae and Ji Soo had an affair before they got married.
I'll reveal that on television.
Find out what you can about Lawyer Oh Soo Yeon.
Don't you know her?
Should I?
Of course. You spent so much time with her.
- Chief Secretary.
-  Don't you remember?
Oh Soo Yeon...
Oh Soo...
- What's wrong?
-  Sir.
My head...
I need to go to...
- Sir!
-  Sir.
Sir! Get him to bed.
Why didn't you tell me he can't remember her?
I meant to tell you, but I forgot.
Let's be more careful.
He can't avoid her now that he needs her help.
This is a problem.
Don't be too disappointed.
Dodo Group isn't the only way forward.
He's right.
The programme you're on is a hit.
It'll all work out.
This is Min and Oh Law Firm.
What? Okay.
Okay! Thank you!
We got it!
What did we get? Did we win the lottery or something?
Dodo Group picked us to be their legal counsel!
- Is that true?
-  You heard me answer the phone.
Congratulations.
- Who called?
-  The CEO's office.
Which CEO?
I don't know. Was it Do Gwang Woo?
Gwang Woo's in pharmaceuticals and Gun Woo's in the head office.
Right. Then it must be Gun Woo.
He wants us in his office by 4pm tomorrow.
You made a huge call.
You hired Soo Yeon as our legal counsel.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Yes, I wanted it this badly.
Il Jae is your greatest supporter,
and Soo Yeon hates him more than anyone.
The decision's been made. Let's not talk about it.
When you punched me in the hotel room,
you acted like you didn't care,
but I could tell you actually cared a lot about her.
I said stop.
Soo Yeon kept showing up only to become our legal counsel.
She actually hates you very much.
She knows you're working with Il Jae.
I said stop!
She just used you.
You're such a fool.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
(Dodo Group
-  Min and Oh MOU)
What do you think they're saying?
Wait.
What's wrong?
I can't hear them.
What?
I can't hear...
what they're saying.
What do you mean?
I used to be able to.
Your first project will be the ship.
Our sources say that...
someone called K is in charge of the deal.
I want to see the files on B World, Mr Byun's company.
I never said I'd help you gain revenge.
Why did you hire me, then?
I hired you based on your strategy for appeals.
It was quite a good one.
Right.
There's a car in the basement parking lot.
It's a company car, so don't worry about expenses.
The Strategic Planning Department is looking into the man called K.
As soon as we find out more, come up with a strategy...
that will win us the deal.
I haven't seen him in a while,
but Gun Woo still looks like a jerk.
That Soo Yeon.
Is she dating him?
- Sir.
-  I don't believe they are.
Oh Soo Yeon.
Can she be trusted?
She holds a deep-set grudge for Il Jae.
Why?
I don't know if it's true,
but she thinks Il Jae killed her brother.
Does she?
If we let her help, she'll do well.
Don't you worry.
Mr Moon, you deal with her.
Yes, Sir.
Soo Yeon.
It's been a while.
Chief Secretary Moon?
Where are you doing?
To my office.
I'd like to have a chat. Can I join you for the ride?
Sure, my pleasure.
According to the opinion poll,
Hanguk Party's Lee Jong Cheol got 23 percent,
and Minguk Party's Heo Hyang Mi got 25 percent.
Independent candidate Byun Il Jae gained 27 percent.
- His support rose by five...
-  Byun Il Jae!
- Byun Il Jae!
Congratulations.
You'll definitely win at this rate.
You never know...
until the votes are counted.
Stay on your toes...
and concentrate on the campaign.
I will.
The gap is widening.
Ms Oh, please wrap up for us.
Next week, we'll invite Congresswoman Hwang Ji Soo...
who motioned for the T9 law.
Don't miss it.
Did you agree to appear on the show?
What was that about?
I declined.
Call the producer and find out.
Congratulations.
Thanks. Let's keep going until the last minute.
- Byun Il Jae!
-  Byun Il Jae!
- Go on.
- Byun Il Jae!
-  Byun Il Jae!
He's not answering.
Hello?
It's Oh Soo Yeon.
Lawyer Oh. What have you done?
Didn't they say I refused?
I think someone on the production crew messed up.
They'll issue an apology. Don't worry.
Of course they should.
It bothers me that I said your name at the end of today's show.
I'm afraid people might think you never keep your word.
If I refuse after they mentioned me on air,
would that harm your campaign?
Say you'll be on the show. Don't fear Soo Yeon.
I'll do it.
Bye.
If you're going to be on TV,
try to boost your husband's support ratings.
Will it be okay?
She mentioned Guk Cheol when you were on last time.
Don't worry.
That's all that she knows.
Will you not tell me who gave the tip?
He doesn't want to be seen in public.
He knows so much about Guk Cheol's case.
It must be someone I know.
If this works out,
you'll meet him one day.
- Well done.
-  Thank you.
Can you manage?
Don't worry. We'll do you proud.
If only...
reporters were there to cover Il Jae's campaign.
I'll see what I can do.
CEO Do Shin Young wishes to see you.
Shin Young?
Is it another dinner invitation?
He doesn't want to meet you.
He's not busy but...
He doesn't want to?
Please leave.
This is a very expensive champagne. I hope he enjoys it.
Here.
If I give him a gift, he'll give something back.
He doesn't like this.
He doesn't like anything I try.
Why is he so picky?
- What's wrong with him?
-  Ms Do.
Tell him to come out.
Let's see how great he looks!
I'm really sorry.
- Escort her downstairs.
-  Yes, Sir.
I don't care if we go bankrupt. Tell him to leave right now!
What a jerk!
I've had enough of this.
I'm Do Shin Young.
The only daughter of Do Choong!
After all I did for him, he doesn't want to see me?
He won't?
Come out! Let's see your face!
- Hey!
-  Ms Do.
Find another hotel! Put me down!
Get out of here!
You don't know who I am!
She was frothing at the mouth.
I'm positive.
I never liked Shin Young.
Consumers suffer out of no mistake of their own.
I wanted to help the people who lack power or money,
so I motioned for the T9 law.
I hope that Congress will pass it soon.
Today, we're accepting live calls from viewers with legal problems.
Let's take a call.
It's time to go.
Get to work.
We have someone on the line.
What's your name?
Hi, I'm Lee Tae Ri and I live in Hwagok-dong.
Lawyer Oh.
Can dead people clear their names?
Tell me your story first.
Then I'll tell you what I think.
The guy's name was Go Joo Tae.
He was my best friend.
I called because he was involved in a case...
you once mentioned. Jung Man Ok's murder.
How was he involved?
Joo Tae...
went to prison for killing Jung Man Ok...
for Lee Guk Cheol.
I know that.
He told me that...
he never killed Jung Man Ok.
Sir.
Why are you revealing this now?
Because I found a strange photo among his belongings.
What strange photo?
Sorry, but can we cut this short?
This is a live show. We can't edit anything.
What photo is it?
Jung Man Ok died on March 28, 2005.
But this photo was taken on that same day.
What is this photo?
It shows Congresswoman Hwang and Byun Il Jae...
Anyway, if this photo wasn't doctored, it means that...
the two were having an affair.
Did you just say they had an affair?
Yes.
Sir, could you send us...
a copy of this photo?
No!
Why would you object?
It's a lie. You can't air something that wasn't vetted...
That's what we're trying to do now. To check.
Dear fellow Seoul citizens.
I wish to create...
a city free of crime.
A city where the diligent are respected.
A city where...
no one has to suffer due to administrative disasters.
That is my goal and I will do this for you all.
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
Which candidate's van is that?
It's not a candidate's.
Kang Gi Tan's here again.
What is he doing here?
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
Who called the reporters?
It wasn't us.
- Byun Il Jae.
-  Byun Il Jae.
Il Jae. Wrap it up and leave.
I used to be...
a prosecutor.
To create a safer Seoul, I promise that...
What...
Byun Il Jae, one of the candidates for Seoul mayor,
and Congresswoman Hwang were having an affair at the time?