(Episode 30)
You're back.
Sung Ae called.
She said she'd check in from time to time.
Are you okay?
I can't breathe and my head hurts.
I'll bring some painkillers.
What happened?
I saw...
Gun Woo and some woman named Oh Soo Yeon.
But why does my heart ache?
Are they...
lovers?
Gun Woo is staying at this hotel with his team to win the contract...
for the ship for Dodo Group.
Your wounds are treated.
You should run to a hospital the first thing tomorrow.
Soo Yeon.
We have a lot to do tomorrow.
You should get to bed early.
Why didn't you tell Gun Woo...
that Gi Tan is alive?
He trusts Soo Yeon too much.
That's why he'll be hit by Gi Tan soon.
He'll understand better once he's hurt...
instead of me talking to him.
Hey.
Where is everyone?
They all went to eat.
Didn't they order room service?
What about our security?
We haven't decided on a price yet, so it's okay.
Get ready. Let's go eat.
That's okay. I'm not hungry.
I don't want to eat alone. Come with me.
How far are you going?
I feel so trapped in that hotel.
I want to go for a drive while we're at it.
Why are you only eating rice?
You should try the other dishes. Their food is good.
Thank you...
for last night.
I won't take it the wrong way,
so don't be awkward with me.
Yes, Sir.
Speak casually.
If it's just the two of us, you can talk comfortably.
It's such a nice day.
It's supposed to rain this afternoon.
It'd be good if it rains. I like rain.
I can't do this.
I was trying to use you.
I already knew that. Why are you bringing it up?
I can't do that to you any more.
I feel too bad.
Hae Il told me that Il Jae turned...
Gi Tan into a murderer.
But I can't forgive you either.
Once this bid is over, I'll give up my position.
I can't treat you like this any more.
You were never on my side.
Not even once.
Do you know what's the worst thing you can do to me?
It's for you...
to leave me.
Whether you use me or betray me,
I don't care.
Just...
stay by my side.
That's all I need, Soo Yeon.
Who was the person that used hypnosis to treat me in China?
Was his name Professor Jin Hye Ri?
Yes.
Contact him and ask him to come to Korea.
What do you need him for?
I think there is a problem with the treatment he gave me.
What problem?
I keep seeing someone in my head,
but the face disappears within a few seconds.
And then I go out of breath and my head starts to hurt.
Earlier the better.
Check his schedule and send him a flight ticket.
Yes, Sir.
Hello.
CEO Do would like for you to check the food for the event.
I'll be there after I get changed.
Okay.
She put in a lot of effort in choosing the menu.
Please try them.
Change this to something else.
This one, too.
Why? Does it taste bad?
You'll like that one for sure.
We used premium meat...
It's too tough. The sauce isn't good either.
Change this one, too.
Excuse me.
What kind of food have you been eating all your life?
Did you receive our guest list?
- What about it? - Did anyone have allergies?
What?
There are peanuts and shrimps in some of these dishes.
Did you check?
Why do we have to know if they have allergies?
Pick new dishes for everything.
Hey.
I want to talk to him in private.
Take everyone and leave the room.
Yes, Ma'am.
Please follow me out.
Hey, Ga Din.
Do you see this?
That's an expensive watch.
Not the watch. I'm talking about the cut.
I went into the kitchen with an apron...
for the first time in my life. I did it just for this.
But what did you say? Make it over?
No wonder it tastes so bad.
You should have left it to the chef.
I'm the host that day.
Don't embarrass me and prepare for it properly.
Jerk.
Wait.
Why am I accommodating him?
Did they really taste bad?
Dodo Hotel is famous for their delicious food.
It was delicious.
Why did you do that then?
Because Shin Young...
is now a part of my business plan.
- Sorry? - I need to train her right.
How is Il Jae doing these days?
He must withdraw from the election!
- Withdraw! - Withdraw!
He accepted bribery to found his business!
We can't allow him to become the mayor of Seoul!
- No way! - No way!
He's different inside and out!
Byun Il Jae must step down!
- Step down! - Step down!
Byun Il Jae should drop out from candidacy!
They've been protesting for days for Il Jae to step down.
What is Il Jae doing?
According to Chae Ryung, all he does is read.
Read?
How can he read at a time like this?
Who knows? He should just step down.
I should see him.
It'll be too dangerous to go through the protesters.
Go to the basement parking lot. It should be fine there.
(Parallel Lives)
Welcome.
Mr Hwang is here.
Sir.
Hello, Mr Hwang.
I'm sure you're not reading because you're bored.
I'm looking for an alternative way to win over the people.
I see.
So did you find anything?
There's something common...
to people that are titled as heroes.
There was always a war involved.
They avoided fights they would lose and only fought if they could win.
Also,
what creates a hero...
is the public in the end.
This election is already a lost game.
It's not a fight you can win.
I suggest you resign from your candidacy.
I...
barely started my war.
I haven't begun yet.
I will...
only look for battlegrounds.
I will only fight the battles that are favourable to me.
And...
I will move the people's hearts.
This is...
the perfect plan...
that I have for this election.
He'll try to win the hearts of people by finding battlegrounds...
and fighting only the battles he'll win.
It's very vague and theoretical.
Il Jae is a meticulous man. He didn't say it for no reason.
Are you saying that he has a definite plan to win?
I didn't think much of it at first,
but I feel that...
there may be something more.
Keep your eyes on him. If anything is suspicious,
make sure you report it to me.
I will.
Is Gi Tan well?
Yes.
I'll be in charge of Il Jae for a while.
He'll only be engaged in doing his business.
I won't die like this.
I can't die like this.
My goodness, Chairman!
Goodness.
You can't suddenly overwork your body.
It seems like that's light for you.
Give me that one, then.
You must eat.
Okay.
I got hungry after working out too hard.
Let's go.
Do you like what I've cooked?
Taste doesn't matter.
I was hungry enough to eat anything.
Please eat up.
Did you bite on a grit?
Did you wash rice thoroughly?
I'm sorry. I have bad eyes.
Should I get some instant rice?
I never eat instant food.
Please give me a minute.
I will run out and buy something you like.
It's fine. I'm sick of eating out.
Everything else was the worst,
but my wife was good at cooking.
I will try harder.
She was my wife, after all.
I miss her food.
Bok Shin, your cooking improved a lot.
Yours is much better than that woman's.
Thank you, Chairman.
That's a relief.
I'm glad you have your beloved Mr Gong with you.
You know, you should look for someone...
whom Gun Woo can marry.
Find someone with connections.
It doesn't matter if they are in business or politics.
Someone he can marry?
No one would be crazy enough to let their daughter marry a love child.
If I pass on the company to Gun Woo,
they will line up behind him.
So don't worry.
Honey.
What do you hate so much about Gwang Woo?
Don't you know?
He's incompetent.
You said I was incompetent, but I've been making profits.
Competency is nothing.
You are unbelievably ignorant.
Be honest.
You don't hate him because of his competence. It's because of me.
You always loved Ja Young more than you loved me.
That's why you like Gun Woo more than Gwang Woo.
I'm losing my appetite. Go away!
Are you giving the company to Gun Woo?
Let's settle this on competence, then.
We'll be late. Let's go.
I hope Gun Woo will get the contract for that ship.
I'm worried.
I believe in him.
He's very competent. He will make it happen.
Right. Set up a secret gathering...
for major stockholders.
I don't think you should do that.
It may backfire on you.
You should get better.
Double my schedule...
for rehabilitation exercise.
I will show...
the stockholders...
that I am...
still alive and well.
Yes, Sir.
I must eat a lot...
to work out a lot.
Did you hear him?
That's what's in his heart.
He's just too much.
Gwang Woo.
If Gun Woo gets...
this ship contract,
he may really end up inheriting the company.
You have to get your act straight.
Sir.
I found the hotel that K is staying in.
Really?
Where is it?
He's at Dodo Hotel's suite room.
Dodo Hotel?
Why didn't Shin Young tell me?
She doesn't know anything.
You should meet him right now.
Okay, Mum.
Don't you think I should get him a gift or something?
Don't be so cheap. He'll look down on you.
Go and be confident.
I'm all about confidence.
Mr Ahn.
Follow me.
How pitiful.
He was never loved by his father all because of me.
I came to meet Chairman K who's staying here.
What is this about?
This is a long story.
This is who I am.
Mr Ahn.
This is a son of Chairman Do Choong of Dodo Group.
He's CEO Do Gwang Woo.
So what?
What I mean is that I have to meet...
Chairman K for business.
You can't meet him without an appointment.
Please go back.
You are one inflexible man. We're all in this business together.
- Hello, Sir! - Hello, Sir!
What brings CEO Do here?
Wait, are you Chairman K, Chief Secretary Moon?
I work for him.
How can a credit delinquent work for such a man?
I became a credit delinquent because of money, not my competence.
Of course.
You were one competent worker.
Then why did you fire me?
It seems like you know me well.
Well... That was...
Chief Secretary Moon.
I'd like to speak a word with you.
That little...
Are you...
asking me to set up an appointment with Chairman?
I will give you enough money for the occasion.
Please make this work.
No one sees Chairman without an appointment.
This is why I am asking you, Chief Secretary Moon.
Here's a word for you.
Stop reaching for the stars and go on home, idiot.
Idiot?
As long as I'm around,
you will never meet Chairman.
No matter how important you think you are,
you are just his employee.
Chairman K and I are both employers.
The nobilities all share the same heart.
When I become friends with your chairman,
you'll be the first to be laid off.
Look forward to that day.
I think...
you'll be laid off before that happens.
I will see to it.
You better...
mark my words.
Why is that jerk...
working with K?
Gosh.
It's not going to be easy to meet with Chairman K.
Anyway, it's about time Gun Woo...
decides on the amount for the bid.
Soo Yeon.
What happened with her?
(Chinese Ship Contract)
Who is it?
Room service.
Let's eat first.
The bellboy...
will be our medium to communicate.
Once the bid price is set,
let the bellboy know through a written note.
They left for a walk. Let's go.
This way, Sir.
You don't look so happy.
No.
I'm a bit down.
You and Gun Woo were never close.
I don't think it's necessarily because of him.
Is it Lawyer Oh?
Is there a reason...
why I'd be upset because of her?
I'm not sure. I'm asking because you're upset.
We have three days left until the bid is over.
They say Gun Woo is putting his life on the line for this.
He plans on winning the bid to bring Chairman Do back.
Both his and Chairman Do's lives are under your thumb.
Why don't you show him what you got?
I have something else in mind.
I have a lot of Dodo Group's shares.
Shares? When did you manage that?
Don't you remember how Dodo Group...
borrowed money from me?
Will Il Jae get the money on Thursday?
Yes. A huge sum will be deposited...
from the defence industry.
That means we only have tomorrow to stop Il Jae.
I know where we can borrow 20 million dollars.
Do you want me to introduce you to them?
Are you saying that money was yours?
I purchased Dodo Group's shares with that money.
They rose quite a bit now.
Then...
what you have in mind is...
I plan on...
swallowing Dodo Group whole.
That will be true revenge.
For Il Jae, Gwang Woo and Gun Woo.
When you talked about training Shin Young...
It's business.
It's so that I can take over Dodo Group.
I see.
Il Jae is quiet. He hasn't been doing any campaigns.
I sent in an informant to their side.
You don't have to worry.
An informant?
Yes.
Here, here and here.
These regions are the problematic areas that are...
currently under a lot of lawsuits or legal disputes.
What's the cause?
There are many.
There are environmental issues, lease problems,
as well as redevelopment.
Out of them,
schedule the campaign first where there are gangsters involved.
Sorry?
What do you mean?
If we play...
like the other candidates, I have no chance.
I'll make a new public image for myself.
I'll become the hero for the less fortunate.
- Hello. I'm number three. - Byun Il Jae!
- Number three, Byun Il Jae! - Hello, Ma'am.
I'm an ordinary candidate standing up for ordinary people.
- Number three, Byun Il Jae! - Number three, Byun Il Jae!
Goodbye.
Hello.
I'm an ordinary candidate standing up for ordinary people.
I'm candidate number three, Byun Il Jae!
Hello. I'm an ordinary candidate standing up for ordinary people.
I'm candidate number three, Byun Il Jae.
- Kill me instead. - What?
You punks.
My goodness.
Gosh.
What happened?
Help us.
We have so much debt. If we're kicked out,
we'll starve to death.
Calm down.
I can only help you if I understand what's going on.
Don't butt in and walk away.
Who are you?
Our company was hired by the landlord to take care of business.
Is there a problem?
A company?
- You guys are gangsters! - You little...
What are you doing? Let her go!
- I told you to butt out. - You punk.
Did you just hit me?
Should a mayor candidate hit people?
"People"?
You are nothing but parasites!
You suck on the blood of the weak!
Hey!
Don't hit them. Just call the police.
We'll go by the law.
Law?
How dare you talk about law?
All right. Let's do it by law!
Sir, please calm down!
- Sir. - Come here.
A mayor candidate is beating me up!
Calm down.
He didn't do anything wrong.
He was just trying to help us.
Why would you take a just man instead of the gangsters?
- He's right. - The police are wrong!
- Good luck! - Cheer up!
Cheer up!
Don't worry about me and don't lose hope.
A just society will come...
one day!
- Byun Il Jae! - Byun Il Jae!
Is this what Il Jae was talking about?
A violent candidate of Seoul mayor...
Will this work?
Il Jae is quite confident about it.
Of course.
No one used such a strategy before.
Il Jae took his best shot.
Some people are praising him,
but most are still criticising.
I'm sure he took that into consideration.
We don't know when and how things will turn around.
Always keep your guard up.
Yes, Sir.
CEO Do has prepared a new menu.
Do you see this?
The band-aid by my lips?
I splashed hot oil on my face trying...
to come up with these recipes.
I almost died.
No one ever died of an oil splash.
Taste these.
Does that look mean he likes the food or not?
Why should I feel so worried over something like this?
What do you think? Is the food any good?
Come on. Do you like it or not?
It'll do.
I was going to kill you...
if you didn't like the menu again.
- Well done. - Where are you going?
We're done.
You can't just say, "well done," and leave.
Join me in the sky lounge for a drink.
Don't you see this?
Okay. Let's go.
CEO Do, your brother wishes to see you.
What?
Gosh, did he have to show up now?
What for?
I don't know.
He's waiting for you in your office.
Let's drink some other time. I hate Gwang Woo's guts.
Gosh.
Keep quiet.
The deal's off the second you tell anyone about me.
What rotten timing.
This idiot is always a hindrance and never any help.
Why do you keep showing up here?
"Can't I come to see my little sister?" is something I'd never say.
Shin Young.
Do you know the businessman called K who's staying in the suite?
Have you met him?
Yes. Why?
Can you tell me what you know about him?
What is he like?
I need to know. It's a business thing.
How old is he?
I think he's a little over 60.
So he's on the older side.
His business isn't something a young man could handle.
He has a receding hairline and a bulging belly.
He's about my height, I think.
What's his personality like?
Nasty.
Okay, nasty.
Then... Shin Young.
Could you...
introduce me to that old man?
He makes me want to puke.
That part is up to you, okay?
Wait, Shin Young! Shin Young!
That brat never lets me finish.
Based on her description,
he doesn't seem like a nice guy.
K...
I hope you're well.
What on earth are you up to?
I'm campaigning in my own way.
Do you know what the media is saying?
They say a gangster's running for mayor.
Every news outlet is making fun of you and your campaign.
Of course they are.
Because nothing hurts more than being boring.
I bet I just made myself look like a very delectable prey.
Did you do that knowing this would happen?
The real public opinion...
comes from the bottom.
Wait and see.
The common people will flock towards me.
Goodness.
To be honest,
I don't care if he wins or not.
I'm more afraid that...
he could harm your future plans.
He's already a liability.
It all depends on how I clean up the mess.
Make him give up.
He will be mocked for the rest of his campaign.
The mess will be easier to clean up if you start sooner than later.
He just won't listen to me.
Honey.
Thanks for getting me out.
Do you know how much it cost?
Gather more money.
We'll need to settle many more cases like this.
Honey.
If I stop now,
I will be remembered as nothing but a gangster.
I have to keep going.
That way, even if I lose, I can still break even.
They have a right to residency!
- They have a right! - They have a right!
Gangsters hired to evict residents are not welcome here!
Be quiet!
Let go!
Ladies and gentlemen! Justice will prevail!
- Justice will prevail! - Justice will prevail!
- Byun Il Jae! - Byun Il Jae!
Mr Byun.
This is your third time. Do you have any regrets?
I studied law in university,
but I value conscience more than law.
Our laws are too harsh on the poor and unprivileged.
Regrets?
I have none.
I trust my conscience more than...
a biased legal system.
What do you have to say about those who want you out of the race?
The other candidates are smart and great people.
They say all sorts of sweet nothings...
to attract votes.
Don't you need a candidate like me...
who can't accept injustice?
A lot more people support you now.
Do you have anything to say to them?
Seoul has many high-rises, but just as many...
dark alleyways.
If you want a mayor who will never...
compromise with the unjust,
then you must vote for me, candidate number three.
That's me, Byun Il Jae.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - That's all for now.
That's it.
Byun Il Jae's approval rate that had gone down to 11 percent...
has risen to 20 percent.
But the difference between Hanguk Party's candidate,
Lee Jong Cheol, is as much as 20 percent,
and analysts say Byun has an uphill battle if he is to win.
His approval rate is on the rise, but I doubt you have to worry.
It looks like he's going frantic trying to stay in the race.
I learned a lot from my past fights against him.
He has something up his sleeve.
He changed things around in a short while.
I'm quite impressed.
Don't be.
An election is no place to be second best.
He'll never get elected at this rate.
He needs a big something to make a huge impact.
What he's doing now is eye-catching enough.
I don't think he can do any more than this.
There is one more thing he can do.
What is that?
It's a bit risky.
If the three parts don't come together,
it could blow up in his face.
"Three parts"?
The offender, the victim and the assistant.
Why don't you plan it?
Me?
No one else...
can know about this.
Not even Il Jae himself.
Could you tell me what you're thinking?
The bidding takes place tomorrow.
We still don't know how much Geukdong is going to bid.
You're the Strategic Planning Department's chief secretary!
Do whatever it takes to find out by tomorrow. Do you understand?
Can we not even guess how much Geukdong will bid?
They're as secretive as we are.
Geukdong's Mr Um is here.
Hello, Mr Um. Please sit.
When will you tell us how much you're going to bid?
I'll get the call some time today. Don't worry.
We haven't even decided on a price.
Like I said, you don't have to worry.
So,
as soon as I tell you what our bid is,
will you sign the MOU?
Of course, I will.
Lawyer Oh, your nose is bleeding.
- Tilt your head back. - I'm fine.
I said, tilt your head.
I'll be fine.
Go on with your meal.
As soon as you decide on a price,
call for room service and give a note to the bellboy.
- You must come with me. - Where to?
It's work-related.
We're off. Keep working.
- Yes, Sir. - Yes, Sir.
Where are we going?
Just follow me.
Why get off here?
What are you doing?
Come in first.
You got the wrong idea.
I'll come back at around 9pm.
Get some rest until then.
No thanks. I don't want any special treatment.
I'm not doing this for you. It's for my peace of mind.
You didn't sleep last night and you can't tonight.
We'll have to stay up.
Have a good sleep.
Our final bid.
What if I were to inform our rival?
Do what you want.
Even if the deal falls through,
I won't blame you.
(KT Corporation Auction)
Dinner will be served as soon as the bidding's over.
We will provide live classical music throughout the meal.
Inform the companies that the auction will take place here.
Yes, Sir.
What?
Is there something on my face?
You aren't bad.
You're the best.
- You're the best. - "The best"?
Kang Ga Din.
If I did that good of a job, shall we drink to celebrate?
Ga Din!
(Do Gwang Woo)
Hello?
It's me, Soo Yeon.
Lawyer Oh.
So...
have you decided on a price?
Yes.
Write it down.
I'm ready. Give it to me.
It is...
62,277,770 dollars.
Okay.
They tried to get in as many sevens as possible.
It's too low.
We can't beat that price.
All you have to do is beat this by one dollar.
It's still too low.
One dollar would look suspicious.
Let's take off the last 70 dollars.
It can't be helped.
We need to win the bid.
Well done, Lawyer Oh.
I'll see you there tomorrow.
It's done.
Can they keep a secret?
I hired them myself.
Are you sure about this?
He's your son-in-law.
Listen.
We won't kill him. We'll only injure him.
If this helps him win the mayoral election,
he won't hold it against me.
Wear this necktie today.
Red neckties bring good luck.
I bought this for you...
at a department store yesterday.
Do you like it?
Yes. It's lovely.
I've never worn a red tie before.
Not the tie.
What were you two doing?
I bought him a necktie.
So what?
Did you tie it up for him?
What are you thinking?
You can tie your own tie.
I'm really sorry. I didn't think you'd be upset.
Watch how you act.
Don't make me suspect you.
Why are you here?
I'll join you today.
The election's coming up.
We have to try our best.
Let's go, then.
You have a lot of grievances against Il Jae.
That's why you're doing this.
Then Mr Byun...
will end up getting hurt while fighting for justice.
That will make him a hero.
Remember that you must only injure him.
Not too big, not too small.
Hello.
Let's have a productive day.
Thanks for coming out.
- Hello. - Thank you.
Let's make it a good day.
Hello.
I'm a friend of the people and the justice of Seoul.
Candidate number three, Byun Il Jae.
Ji Soo. Ji Soo! Ji Soo!
Wake up!
Someone call 911! Call an ambulance!
Ji Soo! Ji Soo!
Wake up.
What?
He hit Ji Soo?
You idiots!
How is she?
Which hospital is she at?
Why are you here?
I have to be here. This is an important occasion.
Concentrate more on your drugs.
Your stock prices are falling fast.
Are you actually showing concern?
You won't have to.
You'll hear some shocking news very soon, all thanks to me.
Hello, everyone.
I planned this event. What do you think?
Can't you have told me if you knew the auction would be held here?
You didn't ask.
Have you met this Mr K?
Why do you all want to know about him?
Have you met him?
No.
Oh, hello. I haven't seen you in a while.
Lawyer Oh.
Who do you think will win the bid?
It has to be us.
But I think...
we have some fierce competition.
The shipbuilding industry is struggling.
So everyone put their life on the line today.
What is Mr Moon doing up there?
Don't you know?
He works for K now.
He keeps coming back like a weed that never dies.
First of all, on behalf of my chairman,
I would like to thank all the companies taking part.
Could the representatives please put their proposal...
into the box to my right?
We will announce the result as soon as we review the bids.
We prepared a reception for you.
Please enjoy yourselves as you wait.
Did you call Professor Jin?
The hypnotherapist?
He's at a seminar in Europe.
He'll come when it's over.
I can't help myself.
Hey.
Shall I tell you something funny?
Dodo Group's bid.
It's 62,277,770 dollars.
Isn't it?
How do you think I know?
She told me.
Are you done?
Yes.
How interesting.
There's only 10 dollars in it.
Tell the winner...
to come and see me.
Yes, Sir.
I shall announce the results.
The lowest bid...
was 62 million 277 thousand...
and 690 dollars.
Dodo Construction won the bid.
Soo Yeon.
What happened?
Can't you tell?
Geukdong lost...
by just 10 dollars.
You betrayed me in court.
How dare you do it twice!
You're the betrayer.
You tried to ruin Dodo Group's chances.
Zoom in on Oh Soo Yeon.
That necklace.
Why does it look familiar?
I didn't know you worked for Chairman K.
Remember one thing.
Neither of you are allowed to ask personal questions.
Mr Moon, Dodo Group isn't a small corner shop.
However large your company is,
you now work for us.
Will you really not tell me who gave the tip?
He hates being at the centre of attention.