(Episode 31)
I didn't know you worked for Chairman K.
Remember one thing.
Neither of you are allowed to ask personal questions.
Will you really not tell me who gave the tip?
He hates being at the centre of attention.
Kang Ga Din!
Sir!
Ga Din, what's wrong?
Why did you collapse?
My head hurts.
Call Dodo Hospital and ask Dr Kim to come over immediately.
Hurry!
Ga Din, are you okay?
What is wrong?
Kang Gi Tan!
(Lee Soo Tak)
Excuse me.
Yes, speak.
Really? Okay.
You'll have to see him next time.
What's wrong?
Something suddenly came up.
What is it?
I can't tell you the details.
We'll contact you later.
Hey, Mr Moon.
- Thank you.
-  Sure.
Has Gi Tan always been this weak?
The doctor said he's just tired. He'll be fine.
No.
He's been through so much, going to jail and everything.
He looks all right, but he must be a mess inside.
It's nothing like that. Don't worry, and you can leave now.
No. I'll stay.
Pardon?
I'll be with him until he wakes up.
You can leave.
Chairman may not want you here.
I will look after him. Is there a problem?
This is his private area.
This is my hotel.
You can't do this.
Whatever.
I'm not leaving if he's not.
Do you understand?
I don't think you understand.
(Ok Chae Ryung)
Hello?
Ji Soo was attacked.
Tell me more.
Gi Tan.
Everyone left for the hospital, so I don't know the details.
I can't go there since there will be a lot of reporters.
I guess it'll be on the news tomorrow morning.
It'll cause trouble if they spot you.
Don't go out for a while.
I won't.
I'll let you know if I find out anything.
(Restricted Zone)
How do you feel?
It hurts a bit,
but I can stand it.
You're lucky it's not any worse.
It could have been dangerous.
Are there reporters outside?
Yes.
Doctor.
Get us a trustworthy doctor...
and book an operating room.
What do you mean?
Are you telling me to get a surgery?
All you have to do is lie in bed and kill time.
- Honey.
-  This is an opportunity.
We can't miss it.
Even if it's sympathy,
we must win the hearts of the public.
What if they find out that it's all an act?
This is no time to be afraid of that.
It's your chance to regain your honour.
It'll become a big help for my election as well.
Doctor.
Will you help us?
Yes, Sir.
Honey! Wake up!
- Honey!
-  Ji Soo!
What happened?
Ji Soo is in a critical condition.
What?
Honey!
My greed...
stabbed me in the back.
I can't believe I hurt my own child.
Keep it down, someone will hear you.
How can this happen?
Ji Soo. Ji Soo!
- Sir.
-  Let me go.
You can leave.
How long do I have to wait?
Your husband asked me to take as long as I can.
My head hurts.
Thinking about this whole thing hurts my head more.
You should take a nap.
It'll do you good.
(Operating Room)
How is Congresswoman Hwang doing?
Right now,
it's not looking good.
According to the doctors,
they'll have to see after the surgery.
The assailant the police caught said...
that he has a grudge against you.
During my campaign,
I got involved in a fist fight because some tenants...
were about to be kicked out...
by the people who were hired by the landlord.
The assailant...
is the same man from that fight.
You must have mixed feelings.
He should have...
attacked me instead.
I feel so sorry.
It's so painful.
Do you regret any of the campaigns you've run?
If a person...
dares to swing a pipe at a mayoral candidate,
I can only imagine what kind of...
harsh treatment our citizens were facing.
Regardless of the election's result,
I won't stop fighting...
for the weak people...
of our land.
I think you can go home after this coffee.
What are you talking about?
- A fake surgery?
-  Yes.
I heard from that man.
With your bait, Il Jae caught a huge fish.
You two are amazing.
Rude jerk.
Why didn't he tell me?
There were some mix-ups,
but we achieved our goal.
Make sure...
to keep that...
assailant's mouth closed.
Don't worry.
He'll be reading the script I wrote for him...
at the station right now.
You said Chae Ryung is staying at your house, right?
It's probably best to keep it a secret from her.
You were the one who told me...
that she's being chased by Gi Ryang.
There's no harm...
in being careful.
Hey, Ga Din.
You should consider yourself lucky.
I don't nurse just anyone.
Are you all right?
Yes.
What happened to Shin Young?
She wanted to nurse you and wouldn't budge. I'm sorry.
Let me ask you one thing.
You told me that I used to know Soo Yeon before, right?
- What?
-  I'm sure...
that you told me I knew her.
I saw you watching the television programme she's on.
So I assumed you knew.
But...
why are you bringing her up?
I think there must be something...
between her and me.
What do you mean?
I want to meet her. Do you have her number?
- Yes.
-  Call her and tell her that...
I'd like to see her.
Yes, Sir.
(Lawyer Oh Soo Yeon)
The number you're calling...
She's not picking up.
Do you know where she lives?
Sir. It's too late right now.
Soo Tak must know. Call him and ask.
Cheers.
Bottoms up. I'll kick you if you don't finish it.
We already drank a lot at the bar.
Why are you forcing us to drink?
Hey.
We got the contract...
and helped as the legal advisor.
If we aren't going to drink today, when will we ever drink?
Soo Yeon.
Congratulations. Bottoms up.
I already had a lot to drink.
It's all right.
This is your home. You can sleep right away.
I'll drink it for her.
It's okay. You can't take your alcohol.
- Drink it.
-  Drink it.
I won't stop dancing if you don't drink that.
Okay, I'll drink it.
My gosh.
Are you okay?
Mr Do.
Yes?
You like Soo Yeon, don't you?
You've been looking out for her.
Mr Min.
Stop it.
Can't I speak what's on my mind?
Yes, I do.
My gosh! We need more alcohol.
Let's go and get some.
What? You can go alone.
My gosh. This is why you're single.
Come on. Hurry.
We'll be back.
Stay here, okay?
Put on your shoes.
Thank you...
for turning down Gwang Woo's proposal.
So what?
Did you tell him what our price is?
I did. Geuk Dong will write down 70 dollars less than what we'll do.
I want to give you a proper reward.
If you'd like, I can find you another place to live.
That's not necessary, Sir.
You can speak casually when we're by ourselves.
Does Il Jae know...
any of your weaknesses?
It looked like...
you were in a trap.
Did you think...
you can just leave?
Not at all.
Our relationship...
will only end when one of us is dead!
Il Jae is someone...
who'd take advantage of another's weakness.
Do you want to work with me?
I'm not trying to use you.
I am saying that I will become your side.
Do you want...
to fight Il Jae together?
You don't have to answer me right now.
You can turn it down if it's too hard.
I've got nothing to fear...
if you're beside me.
I will give you some reports on his company by tomorrow.
I promise.
I will...
never leave you...
before you do.
How far did Mr Min go to get beer?
Does Lawyer Oh...
live in that rooftop house?
Yes.
Where's your assistant?
He'll be here soon. You should go back and get some rest.
It's okay. I'll see you off.
We can do a handshake, right?
We're partners now.
They are dating, aren't they?
Chairman.
Let's go back.
Aren't you going to meet her?
I thought wrong.
I don't need to meet her.
- Let's go.
-  Yes, Sir.
Soo Yeon, that little witch.
I asked her for help,
and she threw me away like trash.
I am so frustrated,
but I can't hold back my tears like an idiot.
Are you crying?
No one is crying.
I'm just frustrated that I messed it up.
What a fool. How could you trust her?
You were embarrassed again by the girl who sent you off to prison.
Stop bringing it up. You're going to make me cry again.
It's too early to give up.
What are you talking about?
Chairman K pushed back his contract with Gun Woo.
Is that true? Why?
I don't know that far.
There are many instances where contracts get annulled.
Yes, there are. Many companies break up...
even after signing their MOU.
Now, you can run over and settle the contract...
before Gun Woo does. If so, this will become yours.
Gun Woo won't accept it.
Don't worry.
I'm going to take his position away at our board meeting tomorrow.
I love how you work.
I'm not the chairman for nothing.
I don't do lukewarm business like your father does.
I make sure I get things done.
Okay, Mum.
I will settle this for once.
What in the world is Shin Young up to?
She didn't even tell us that she held the event.
Shin Young is...
just like Dad. She's inconsiderate.
I must've been crazy.
I slept in someone else's bed.
But why didn't Ga Din wake me up?
Congresswoman Hwang Ji Soo's past records are...
receiving attention after her accident.
Not only did she help patients who suffered from T9 coating agent,
but she also helped them work through their lawsuit...
against the company which distributed T9 coating agent.
She is recovering quickly from the wounds...
she got in this attack.
Il Jae and Ji Soo became the people's heroes...
after this attack.
I told you.
Il Jae isn't an easy fight.
Do you believe this attack was staged from their side?
It could be.
I will look into that.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
I slept on the couch because of you.
What were you thinking?
I'm sorry.
I'll take off a day's fee from your bill. Happy?
You need to settle the contract.
Call Dodo Group and tell them to be here by 4pm.
Yes, Sir.
Excuse me,
can you seal that deal with me?
Why don't you seal the contract with me?
This isn't some kind of a joke.
Everything has its formality.
I'm also on Dodo Group's board, and I'm Chairman's daughter.
There is nothing wrong with my signing off the contract.
Why are you stepping in?
Gwang Woo and Gun Woo are...
fighting each other to become the successor.
I want to take part.
Then come to the meeting room by 4pm.
Sir.
Will you let me do it?
I'll think about it.
There's nothing to consider.
You don't like Gwang Woo, and you hate Gun Woo.
- I don't like you either.
-  Gi Tan.
I'll give it a thought.
See you in the afternoon.
Shin Young.
Yes? Why?
Make sure I don't pay for yesterday.
Are you thinking about giving the contract to her?
It'll be worth watching those three fight.
I want to think about which one of them will...
bring me more advantage.
Okay. We'll be there by 4pm.
Who will be attending?
It'll be me and Lawyer Oh.
We'd rather not have Lawyer Oh here.
You should come here alone.
Is this necessary?
It's best we keep Soo Yeon away from him until...
Professor Jin gets here.
Okay.
I don't mind.
I think we should do what they say until we sign the contract.
He's just like the rumours. What an odd man.
Sir, this is bad. The board let CEO Do take charge...
of the ship's contract during the board meeting.
The board meeting?
Did they hold a meeting without me?
Yes, CEO Do just left for the hotel.
We must go over to Dodo Hotel right now, too.
Yes, Sir.
Where do you think you're going?
If you've been notified, you should quietly sit here.
You became rather straightforward.
I don't have any reason to hide this.
You've been telling everyone about how you'll reinstate your father.
We got this project because of me.
Great job, so now, rest!
Gwang Woo will take care of the rest.
- I won't back down.
-  It's the board's decision.
If you make any rash moves, you'll take the responsibility.
You can do whatever you want, but I'm not backing down.
It looks like he doesn't even care that I'm his boss.
It's me, Gwang Woo.
Gun Woo just left.
I thought you were going to stop him.
He ran off. What could I do?
Get the contract signed before he gets there.
The meeting is at 4pm. What if Chairman K won't meet me?
In that case, do whatever it takes to stop Gun Woo.
Gun Woo will take the responsibility.
It's a great loss to our company.
That's not what's important.
This is about my control and your becoming the successor.
Get a grip, you idiot!
Open it.
Where is the meeting at?
- It's in the diamond room.
-  Right.
What brings you here, CEO Do?
Why do you ask? I'm here to seal the contract.
Gun Woo is supposed to come for that.
The person in charge changed to me during our board meeting today.
Why? Don't you trust me? Do you want to see the contract?
I'll tell Chairman. Lead them to the diamond room.
Yes, Sir.
Follow me.
- Gwang Woo is here?
-  Yes.
It looks like the three siblings are starting their fight...
just as you expected.
Gun Woo will be here soon, too. Whose side will you take?
Oh my goodness.
Hey, Gun Woo.
Why are you here?
You've ruined so many things before. You should learn your place.
What?
What? Ruined things?
You should play fair if you want to play this game.
Stop trying to steal others' food bowls like a stray cat.
Hey, I'm not the stray cat. You are.
Dodo Group was mine to begin with!
If you are the real owner of this group, you can't sell off...
this business to Geukdong Group!
- What?
-  If you want to keep your place,
you'd better stay quiet. I'm holding myself back.
Hey, do you really want to die?
You can try if you want, but you'll probably die first!
Are you kidding me? Do you really want to die?
What are you doing in my hotel?
Are you dogs? You're always growling at each other.
How embarrassing is this?
Shin Young, you are well-acquainted with Chairman K.
Gun Woo's trying to take over our company,
so you have to help me out.
Chairman K said he'll sign the contract with me.
- What?
-  You can't barge in like this?
Why can't I step in?
I'm neither a love child nor an ex-convict.
Ex-convict? You little...
Why? Are you going to hit me?
You can try if you want to go back to jail.
Shin Young, come on.
I am your brother. We're blood-related.
That's why you're more embarrassing.
- Shin Young.
-  Don't speak.
I don't even want to speak with you.
You should make your decision.
Whose side will you take?
Who do you like, Mr Moon?
If we need Do Choong, we should go with Gun Woo.
If we need Hwang Gwi Ja, we'll go with Shin Young or Gwang Woo.
Chairman asked the contractor to come on up.
And who would that be?
Who do you think? It's me.
Gun Woo.
He's looking for you.
CEO Do Gun Woo? Not me?
Look here.
You did tell him that I'm now in charge, right?
Please follow me.
Is Ga Din insane?
Kang Ga Din?
CEO Do Gun Woo is here.
It's been a while, Gun Woo.
I thought you'd be shocked, so I've prepared some drinks.
Have some.
Kang Gi Tan?
Chairman K is Gi Tan?
Yes. Stop asking. I'm so frustrated.
Wait... Wait... Shin Young,
what are you talking about?
Gi Tan is dead.
How can a dead man be alive?
He didn't die. That's why he's alive.
Stop asking obvious questions.
You must be wondering what happened.
Well...
Is that even important right now?
We're here to do business.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Why did you choose me?
You're a little better...
at business compared to Gwang Woo and Shin Young.
I came here to represent the Chinese shipowners.
So my reputation is important.
One shouldn't let personal feelings...
get in the way of business.
Here, sign on this.
As you can see from the contract,
you can consider this...
as a type of an agreement.
We'll try to adjust the details to the agreement,
but keep in mind that we might cancel it last minute...
if our conditions don't agree.
You better keep your word about leaving personal feelings...
out of this.
(Do Gun Woo)
By the way, why didn't your legal counsel tag along?
I thought you two were always side by side.
Did you have a fight?
Are you talking about Soo Yeon?
Never mind. I'm not interested in other people's love lives.
Gi Tan.
- Did you just say...
-  Sir.
You have dinner plans with some bank presidents.
You should wrap this up.
Go see him out.
I'll see you out, Sir.
Tell me. What's wrong with Gi Tan?
- What about him?
-  Is he acting that way...
or does he really not know her?
I don't know if I should tell you or not.
Who is it?
What happened? You didn't pick up my call.
He doesn't remember Soo Yeon?
No.
So I think it'll be best if they are kept away from each other.
What's wrong?
Did the deal go wrong?
No, we signed it.
I'm glad. I thought that maybe you didn't get it.
Soo Yeon.
You'd say no if I asked to hold you, right?
Gun Woo.
Never mind.
I'm hungry. Did you eat yet?
Will you wait for me? I'll just dry my hair.
Move.
Hey, Gi Tan!
Gosh.
What do you think you're doing?
You.
Do I look like a joke to you?
You used to hate Gun Woo.
Are you saying Gun Woo is better than me?
The contract is already signed. Don't bother.
That really hurts my pride.
I'm going...
to seduce that man.
Is that possible?
Do you know how many lives I've ruined to date?
If I put my mind to it,
it's over for him.
By the way, Ma'am.
Have you tried seducing before?
Why would I ever do that?
They're always crawling at my feet.
Those men's lives were ruined because they liked you first.
The problem is that you never...
seduced them first.
I just never tried it before.
It'll be easy to win over a man like him.
In my opinion, it'll be hard to make him budge.
Watch me...
and see how I cook him up.
I'll make him obsess over me...
before I dump him like trash.
Sir?
Should I go for a dip?
I knew it. He won't be able to help himself.
What's wrong with him?
What about now?
Okay, Ga Din.
I got you now.
That's right, I'm Shin Young.
Shin Young, the femme fatale.
Shin Young! Are you all right?
I can't move...
Don't come near me. Go away, Ga Din. Go away!
Where does it hurt?
I told you to go away. Don't look at me.
Let's go to the emergency.
Do you think you can wrap your arms around my neck?
What are you looking at? Is this a show?
Hold me.
Go on.
I'll get up on three.
It might hurt.
How embarrassing.
What if he can hear my heartbeat?
Ma'am! Ma'am!
I think you should give up now.
Shut that mouth!
Are you all right?
Kang Ga Din.
I came to see your boss.
If you're here to thank me, don't mention it.
I'm not here to thank you.
I came to warn you.
You.
You'll fall in love with me in a week.
Are you hoping I'd go crazy in a week?
I'm Do Shin Young.
I can write up a book full of the names of men...
who tried to commit suicide because of me.
I can understand how they felt.
They must have been suffering a lot.
Go out for dinner, watch a movie and have a drink with me.
It'll only take three days.
I don't think that's enough to make me go crazy.
Are you scared you'll fall in love with me?
I'm already scared of you as is. Just leave.
We'll see if you can still act like this...
a week from now on.
Do you hate Shin Young that much?
If you plan on using her to take over Dodo Group,
you should accept her.
I'm going to leave it as business.
Things might go astray if personal feelings are involved.
Gun Woo signed the contract.
Aren't you worried?
Starving won't help anything.
So, what now?
If Dad is reinstated at the general meeting,
it'll be over for us.
There's still time.
Think of something instead of worrying.
I can't think of anything and I really tried.
Don't you have any ideas?
I have many.
The problem is picking the best one.
You do have something up your sleeve then.
Don't worry and eat.
I won't go down that easily.
Okay, Mum.
That's so hot.
It's boiling.
I burned my mouth.
A bit more.
Just a bit more.
That's it. Keep going. One more step.
You can do it. Hang in there.
Sir.
I told you not to push too hard.
When did you say that?
You just told me to hang in there and take one more step!
I apologise.
But you did much better today than you did yesterday.
It's far from good.
At the general meeting,
I will walk in on my own two legs.
You will do that. I'm sure of it.
Hang on.
Do I smell patjuk?
Your wife...
made some earlier today.
Did she?
She makes some mean patjuk.
Shall I go and bring some in secret?
Don't.
Not eating patjuk won't kill me.
You need to eat well to get well.
You didn't eat much for dinner.
If you get caught,
- say it's for you.
-  What?
Yes, Sir.
It's so hot.
It's hot, so take your time.
It looks delicious.
- Where's the spoon?
-  Sorry.
I'll get one for you.
Forget it. I have one somewhere.
Here it is.
- Go and lock the door.
-  Yes, Sir.
Ma'am! It's your wife.
What are you doing?
Let me in!
Open up!
Ma'am.
What were you trying to keep from me?
Look at me.
What is it now?
Did you eat patjuk?
What nonsense is that?
Hey, get her out of here!
Then what is this?
Did you want it enough to steal some?
I did not...
No one stole anything!
Why are you hiding that?
That's my portion, Ma'am.
How dare you? Get out of here!
Honey.
Let's stop fighting.
There isn't much to life.
Enjoy my food, grow old in comfort and die peacefully.
What?
Now that the general meeting's coming up,
are you afraid?
You can live happily...
as long as you don't want your title back.
Do you want me...
to give up being chairman?
You know very well that...
if I fight tooth and nail, you can't come back.
Fight the best you can. If you can't stop me,
you'll wish you were rather dead.
This is me...
making a peace offering for the last time.
I want us to reconcile.
It's too late.
Let's fight to the end.
Very well, then.
To the end, it is.
I will amend my will.
Call Lawyer Kang.
He sided with your wife.
He can't be trusted.
Then call Gun Woo.
Tell him to find me a lawyer I can trust.
Yes, Sir.
That witch.
(Police Station)
Is it true that you settled with the assailant?
Not only that,
I handed in a petition requesting he be punished leniently.
Why?
He lives with his elderly mother and young children.
They're poor, too, so if he goes to prison,
no one can support the family.
Did your wife agree to this?
She's the one who came up with the idea.
I promised to work for and support the poor.
She told me I shouldn't ignore the plight of a desperate man.
Your approval rating soared. How do you feel?
I did what was right and natural.
I'm lost for words that the public thought highly of it.
Was his wife's surgery fake?
Yes, we can trust the tip.
Then the whole attack could have been staged.
We both know him well.
He would never forgive anyone.
I want to meet the assailant.
Do you want to use him?
If it was staged, he took a fee.
Someone bought by money can be bought again with ease.
I will arrange a meeting.
I work for the people.
Candidate number three, Byun Il Jae.
That's me. Remember who I am.
Vote me in as your next mayor.
Candidate number three, Byun Il Jae.
Independent candidate Byun Il Jae is gaining support.
His approval rating has risen 10 percent higher than last week's.
He's right behind Lee Jong Cheol who is currently in the lead.
For now...
It was all worthwhile.
It's now down to the swing votes.
That will make or break us.
How long must I stay here?
Not for long.
The swing votes...
are up to you.
Gi Tan approached the man we hired.
Are you sure?
Someone called Moon Tae Gwang asked for his help.
- What now?
-  They'll meet this evening.
Okay, Father. I will.
Can you do something for me?
My father wants to amend his will...
and he needs a trustworthy lawyer.
Could you help him?
That's my duty.
I'm Dodo's legal counsel.
Hello, Mr Kim.
I'm nearly there.
Bye.
Will the gathering end late?
TV station people love to drink.
It'll rain later. Shall I come for you?
I'm not a kid. I don't need to be dropped off and picked up.
Don't drink too much. Call me when you get home.
Stop nagging.
You're our legal counsel. You're very important.
- See you.
-  Bye.
The restaurant's somewhere nearby.
I'm here.
Where's the restaurant?
Is he there yet?
I'll be there.
Gi Tan.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
It was him.
Gi Tan.
When someone comes in,
you should offer them a seat.
Did you invite Mr Hwang as well?
I only invited the man he hired.
Showing up when you aren't invited.
Isn't that your speciality?
You're here, there, everywhere.
Your presence...
proved two things.
That you staged the attack on your own daughter,
and that it was your idea and not your son-in-law's.
Add one more thing to that list.
Now that...
I got involved,
there's no way you can win this fight.
I'll add to that.
The second you came in,
your dream of becoming president went out the window.
What you just said...
was better off unsaid.
It's the one comment...
you'll regret ever making.
Give up on Il Jae now.
If you don't,
you will regret it for the rest of your life.
Like you did with the defence industry case.
I am...
not at all like Il Jae.
You will realise that...
not so long from now.
I think we poked too large a beehive.
No poking means no honey.
If he keeps defending Il Jae,
he will have to go.
Will you attend the entrepreneur's meeting?
I might as well.
(Producer Kim)
(Missed calls)
Why is she standing there in the rain?
I don't know. It seems like she's looking for someone.
Congratulations.
Your approval rating went up.
It's all because of you.
Thank you.
You must miss me because I'm not at home.
Don't worry about me and get well soon.
There's nothing to get well from.
What about food? Do you eat out?
Honey.
Are you listening?
- Honey?
-  Yes.
I eat out sometimes. I'm managing.
Tell Chae Ryung to cook once in a while.
You need to eat at home.
I'll do that. I have to hang up now.
Bye.
I love you.
I know. Me, too.
Chae Ryung.
Check if you hung up first.
You're too cheeky.
Dinner's ready. Come and eat.
Try this.
You should join us.
Don't worry about me.
You're a good cook.
I can cook whenever you ask me to.
Right.
Here's your speech for tomorrow.
You'll be in a rich neighbourhood, so it mentions safety and welfare.
Well done.
Chae Ryung.
What are you up to?
Stop it.
Stop what?
Your people locked me up and almost killed me.
Whatever you do,
I don't trust you.
So what?
I won't let you...
toy with Mr Byun.
Are you afraid I'll take your job?
What?
Get a grip.
You and I are from two different classes.
Hey, Chae Ryung.
Do you want to see who he drops first?
If you want to be loyal,
see what your boss wants to see, not what you want.
Your eyes, nose, mouth and ears.
They all exist for your boss.
Do you get that, kid?
What do you mean?
Soo Yeon's missing?
She didn't show up to the dinner.
It's pouring and she won't answer her phone.
Goodness. I don't know where she is.
Okay. I'll look for her.
Gi Tan.
Are you tired?
The few drinks I had...
made me sleepy.
That woman.
She's still there.
You're right.
Is something wrong?
Lawyer Oh. Wake up.
Soo Yeon!
Gi Tan.
(Monster)
We showed all our cards.
- Say no.
-  Dig him up by the roots.
So that there's nothing left.
It'll be harder to get my revenge if he becomes mayor.
Ga Din, you finally fell for me, didn't you?
I'm sure it was Gi Tan.
Do you miss him that much?
Say what you want now.
Soon, you'll be crawling before me.