(Episode 32)
That woman.
She's still there.
You're right.
Is something wrong?
Lawyer Oh. Wake up.
Soo Yeon!
Gi Tan.
She has a high fever. Let's get her to a hospital.
Get in.
(Do Gun Woo)
(7 Missed Calls)
The police say they don't know.
I filed for missing person,
but could this be...
Il Jae's doing?
Why would Lawyer Oh suddenly disappear on us?
Maybe someone kidnapped her.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
Soo Yeon, where did you go?
It's me, Gi Tan.
I saw that you called her a few times.
What happened?
I saw her fainting as I was passing by.
We're at Hangang Hospital.
You should come and nurse her.
Soo Yeon is at Hangang Hospital.
At a hospital?
Yes. Did you take a taxi? You should come with me.
Okay.
I wonder...
why she was standing there in the rain.
I'm not sure.
I think she was waiting for someone.
It must have been Gun Woo.
If it's Gun Woo,
I'm sure she would have picked up.
It's late. We should go, Sir.
Yes. We're on our way right now.
Hangang Hospital is closer to you. You should go first.
Who called you earlier?
Just an acquaintance.
I'm glad someone she knows found her.
Can we go slower?
What happened to her?
She has a fever, but she should be better by tomorrow.
Thank goodness. I'm glad it's not serious.
I'll stay here. You two can go.
You don't have to. I can stay.
We can let him take over. Let's go.
- I'm really okay.
-  Gosh.
- We'll come early tomorrow morning.
-  Let go of my ear!
(Hangang Hospital)
Oh Soo Yeon!
It was Gi Tan for sure.
Gi Tan...
is alive.
Soo Yeon, are you okay?
Yes.
Who brought me here?
Was it you?
Someone found you while passing by and brought you.
You're up.
Do you know how worried we were?
I'm sorry.
You must be tired.
Leave her with me and go to work.
I'll call you.
Bye.
Thank you.
You didn't get any sleep because of me.
Take care of yourself.
He is...
a good guy the more I look at him.
Do you know how worried he was yesterday?
I saw Gi Tan yesterday.
Did you have a dream? What are you talking about?
It was really him.
Gosh. It's time for you to let him go.
How long are you going to wait for a dead man?
Gi Tan brought me here.
You make no sense. How can I believe you?
Here is the date schedule to be sent to Chairman K.
Cancel the play and change the dinner location.
Everything needs to be high-quality.
Understood.
Just take the bait, Ga Din.
I'll win you over.
Sir.
CEO Do has sent you the date schedule.
- Decline it.
-  Okay, Sir.
What time is the meeting with the American investors?
You should leave now.
Coward.
What?
You. You're scared of falling in love with me, aren't you?
I'm busy.
Don't run away and just accept it, you coward.
Don't waste your time.
I will never...
go on a date with you.
I'll make sure you date me. You won't have a choice.
So I was looking over the numbers and I think there's a big problem...
He's in a meeting right now! If you have something...
Hey, Coward.
Are you that scared of me?
Excuse me, what is going on here?
Shut your mouth.
Tell me, you sly coward.
Do you know how much this investment is worth?
How much is it?
I'll just pay you, you coward.
Could someone please just tell me exactly what is...
- Okay. Yes.
-  going on here?
You! Shut your mouth! Get out!
She's crazy.
This is actually our meeting.
Miss. I don't know what your problem is,
but this is our meeting, so...
You're a coward. You little coward.
Hey! Kang Ga Din!
We sent Shin Young away, so don't worry.
I wish I could report her to the police.
It was so hard making up excuses to the investors.
I'm so embarrassed.
Tell me.
You're scared of falling in love with me, right? You coward!
Shin Young is so persistent.
Sir, you have a fax.
What is it?
CEO Do sent you the date schedule.
I think it's best that you go on a date with her.
You know her well enough.
She'll latch onto you until you listen to her.
How many times do I have to tell you that he's dining?
My goodness, you can't do this!
My gosh.
How can you eat right now, you coward?
We can eat, grab a drink and watch a movie, right?
Is a week enough?
You'll probably beg for more after a week.
Fine.
Let's go on a date.
- Really?
-  But I'll schedule it.
I'm all for that.
You have to look good on our date, okay?
You've made a wise decision.
Hey, Soo Yeon.
Why are you back here again?
This is where I first saw Gi Tan.
He's going to come here at least once more.
Okay, let's just say that it was Gi Tan.
If he's really alive,
shouldn't he have contacted you first?
You probably mistook someone for him.
- Don't waste your time here...
-  My eyes are never wrong.
It really was him.
I know Soo Yeon very well.
It's either one of the two if she insists like that.
She's either awfully ill...
or she really saw him.
Who is this guy who took her to the hospital...
that day?
You said you know him very well.
It was Gi Tan.
Chairman K, who signed the ship contract with us,
is Gi Tan.
Why didn't he call Soo Yeon?
There's a problem. He can't remember her.
I'll tell Soo Yeon myself.
I'd appreciate it if you could keep it low for now.
It's not hard to keep quiet,
but will you be okay?
Once she meets Gi Tan,
I think that'll hurt you a lot.
Gi Tan?
Yes.
I'm pretty sure I saw him.
But it's strange that he hasn't called me.
I've seen someone like him.
- Where?
-  At a coffee shop.
He looked really similar to Gi Tan, so I thought it was uncanny.
Gi Tan is definitely alive.
What will you do?
I'll wait for him.
What if he never calls?
He will.
There must be a reason why he can't call.
Congresswoman, many people were worried about you.
Will you say a word?
I am sorry to make you worried.
Thanks to everyone's love and support,
I've successfully overcame this attack.
I will return...
your love and support with great policies.
Thank you.
What's Il Jae's current approval rating like?
He's about 10 percent behind the lead.
But we never know what'll happen once Ji Soo steps in.
If Il Jae gets elected as the mayor,
it'll be harder to get my revenge.
We have to make him lose.
Do you have evidence that he staged the attack?
To be honest,
it's difficult to find evidence at the moment.
(Ok Chae Ryung)
We've used up everything we have.
That's why we're flustered.
Il Jae defended all of our attacks and he's still standing strong.
But it's not like we can wait until the election is over.
Il Jae is also very anxious.
That's true.
He doesn't know if he'll be elected.
There is one more thing you can use.
Il Jae will do...
anything to get elected.
You can get him to do something corrupt by himself.
Is that possible?
We must try.
That's the only strategy we have left.
Oddly enough, Il Jae's election...
is all down to you.
Be careful.
I was supposed to be dead, anyway.
Gi Tan saved me.
The least I can do is help him get Il Jae.
You've gone through a lot at the hospital.
You probably suffered more because I wasn't around.
Please, try these.
Ms Ok, please sit.
You can enjoy your family time together. It's been a while.
You did so much for us while Ji Soo was in the hospital.
Please, sit and have a drink.
Yes, take a seat.
To be honest,
I'm very disappointed with you.
Why won't you help Il Jae's election?
Well...
I did give him a supporting speech.
No one knows how this election will turn out.
Can't you step up to the occasion and do something about it?
Il Jae.
Do not think about...
cheating...
for the rest of the election.
What happened?
I met Gi Tan.
He is...
dying to find our weakness.
If we let him see one,
he will definitely get us.
Gi Tan...
wants me to lose.
If I lose the election without trying anything,
that's like letting him win.
Il Jae.
If we continue like this,
we have a 50 to 50 chance.
But if we start cheating because we want...
to win the election,
you will definitely lose because of Gi Tan.
Take this to heart.
I didn't know...
you were this afraid...
of Gi Tan.
What?
I will do the rest of the election my way.
Nothing I do will harm you, so don't worry.
Honey.
Honey!
Let him be.
He may be disappointed for now,
but he'll understand later on.
Your schedule's packed for tomorrow.
You should stop drinking.
I know my father-in-law very well.
He's not someone who'd be afraid of a scum like Gi Tan.
Then...
why did he say that?
He's trying to be careful.
He doesn't want any harm...
if I lose my election.
He doesn't even care if I become the mayor or not.
I've been looking for you. Your phone was off.
I didn't know it was off.
I have something to tell Mr Byun in private.
Choong Dong, go out.
Sorry?
We need some privacy.
Yes, Sir.
I don't get Congressman Hwang.
He's more than capable of helping you.
That's enough. I want to enjoy my drinks.
What did you want to talk about?
Do you know...
how Congresswoman Hwang won her election?
She didn't have a high approval rating at that time.
Congressman Hwang changed the tables around last minute.
I heard they won over...
the independent candidates to get more votes.
That's right.
The way they did it was so skilful.
Are you telling me...
that you'll reveal his secrets to winning the election?
Yes.
You sure are brave.
How can you bribe an opposing party in broad daylight?
What will you do if I report that painting?
Go ahead.
That painting...
is a fake worth 50 dollars.
But if you sell it to her,
she'll give you...
at least 500,000 dollars in cash.
If you use that strategy, there won't be any troubles later.
You won't have to ask Congressman Hwang for help either.
How interesting.
But there's something we have to prepare before then.
Money and trust.
Trust?
We'll fail if we don't trust each other.
How much do you trust me?
How much should I trust you?
All of it.
You look fantastic today.
I bet Kang Ga Din will fall for you.
Kang Ga Din?
How dare you call him that?
I'm sorry.
Kang Ga Din.
Go ahead and ask me out.
I'll dump you...
on that day.
Good. You pass with your outfit.
You failed.
I hate people who are late.
I was late while dressing up for you.
I'll try not to be late next time.
Where are we going?
To eat.
I know. Where are we going to eat?
It's somewhere special, so follow me.
Special? Where?
Are we going to Japan for sushi?
I'm in.
Is this place what you call "special"?
You can leave if you want. I won't stop you.
Not at all. It looks delicious.
You should eat it with kimchi.
Are you trying to make a fool out of me?
I won't let you win.
What is it? Is it not good?
It's so good that I might cry.
Why aren't you eating then?
I ate before coming out.
Why is this place special anyway?
I extended my life thanks to their dog's food.
Dog's food?
No wonder. Your tastes are similar.
Don't you believe me? It's true.
Why would I believe that?
What's our next stop?
You wanted to eat, watch a movie and go for drinks.
Let's go watch a movie. What kind of movies do you like?
I like blockbusters.
Exciting action films.
I got tickets for an artistic film. Is that all right?
An artistic film after eating dog food?
Forget it then.
No way. I love art.
Wake me up when it's done.
Hey, watch your manners.
I've watched this already. I came here for you.
Crazy jerk.
Are you talking about me?
That male lead is crazy.
I thought you were mad at me.
No way, this is so much fun.
Do you want to lean on my shoulder?
No thanks.
Keep it in.
Just think about the day you'll take revenge on him.
Are you crazy?
The main character just died.
Why did you laugh then?
Keep it down over there.
Where should we go now?
For drinks.
What do you like to drink?
I'm not sure.
How about some wine at some place classy?
Have you tried soju before?
Of course not, you punk.
It's my favourite kind of drink.
What about pork skin?
I never knew this was edible.
I can't get enough of it.
Cheers.
Let's drink with bigger glasses.
You didn't eat anything all day. Are you sure about that?
Forget it if you can't handle it.
It was you who suggested it.
Here.
Bottoms up.
You're falling. Fall.
Did you fall in love yet?
You did.
You're making me dizzy.
I'm putting a spell on you.
You have to fall in love with me.
Don't do something so useless.
You smiled for the first time.
Kang Ga Din.
Did you finally fall for my charms?
I think that's enough. We should go. I'll get this.
What?
Did you drink?
I had soju. Why?
You can't drink soju.
You've never had it before.
Be quiet. Goodbye.
You can't get drunk. Do you understand, Ma'am?
Hello? Hello?
It looks like she's already drunk. This is bad.
What's wrong? Can't she drink?
She gets very odd when she's drunk.
What do you mean? What does she do?
There are a few steps.
First, she begins to fight.
Hey, do you want to die?
Hey. You with the slit eyes!
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry, my sister is too drunk.
Don't be sorry!
He glared at me first!
Open your eyes. Open them!
Are you kidding me?
- What are you trying to do?
-  Open your eyes!
- They are fully open!
-  They are!
- I'm so sorry.
-  I'll show you my eyes!
- Okay.
-  Open your eyes!
- I did open them!
-  Please, stop.
- Where are you going?
-  I did open my eyes!
After that, she gets very cheerful.
Kang Ga Din, run. Run!
Giddy up!
Run! Run to the end of the Earth!
Let's go!
I guess he can deal with her that far.
The problem begins now.
Hey!
She bites?
Yes. Her pet dog was also bitten by her once.
After that,
she begins to cry.
Everyone hates me.
Why?
Because they all envy me.
I am too good for them!
Why did I have to be so pretty?
I haven't gotten any friends.
I will settle this once and for all.
It's because of your personality.
Kang Ga Din.
You can't leave me, okay?
I'm going to kill you if you betray me.
Okay. There, there. Stop crying.
Let's go home.
Stop crying and let's go home.
Simply put,
she is the worst drunk on Earth.
(Dodo Group)
Why don't you say hello?
You have a very stiff neck.
Why would I do that?
You started to speak rather casually to me.
If you don't treat me like a brother, treat me like staff.
I'm the CEO of headquarters.
We have different bloodlines.
You're fake, but I am from an original bloodline.
Look forward to this general shareholders' meeting.
What should I look forward for?
Are you trying to fire me once Father gets reinstated?
I will do that. There are way too many parasites in this company.
Parasites?
You haven't seen a real parasite, have you?
Your mum.
Do you know how she was?
When I was young, I thought she was an angel.
She was much nicer than my mum and she loved me.
But...
that same woman took my father and my everything.
You call...
someone like that a parasite.
Someone like your mum. Do you understand?
Do not speak ill...
of the deceased.
Do I have to forgive her because she's dead?
Who says so?
You can say whatever you want.
After the general meeting,
you won't be able to keep your head up in front of me.
I really despise him.
Why are you so late?
It's almost time for Choong to come back after his workout.
I'm sorry. I received the medication a little too late.
Fill them up.
Yes, Ma'am.
Those are fake pills for his blood pressure, right?
Yes, they are just health supplements.
Did he use up all of the pills he brought from Australia?
That's why I'm filling them up with health supplements.
He was overly healthy because of those pills.
I see.
This is a secret from Gwang Woo and Shin Young, okay?
Of course, Chairwoman.
But will it be all right?
Dr Hwang once said if he collapses again,
he may not ever get back up.
You do not have to be worried about that.
I'm sorry.
You may go.
He practically asked for it.
Why did he dream of returning?
Mum, Gun Woo said he'll fire me to my face.
How can you play the piano?
Don't worry. Your father will never get reinstated.
Did you finally find a way around this?
It's not good to have a rotten tree around.
You must root it out...
without hesitation.
What are you saying? Is Father the rotten tree?
Then is he a healthy one? He's always sick.
Stop beating around the bush. What's your plan?
You can leave it up to me.
Take a look at this.
Who's this? Her credentials are amazing.
She's the second daughter of Seogang Group. What do you think?
Forget about it.
It was really hard for me when I got my divorce.
Be quiet. Marriage is a part of business.
Give it a thought.
Marriage?
Welcome home, Honey.
Oh, okay.
What's okay?
What? It's nothing. Nothing at all.
My gosh, what's wrong with me?
Yes, Father.
We're almost there.
Okay.
Where were you last night?
I couldn't reach your phone.
To be honest,
I saw Gi Tan...
the day I was hospitalised.
You don't have to believe me.
I was at the place where I saw...
Do you...
miss him that much?
Hey, Soo Yeon, to be honest...
Let's talk about something else.
Why is Chairman suddenly changing his will?
Tell them you're the company's lawyer. They'll let you in.
Aren't you coming?
I can't...
enter this house.
Let go.
He will see me.
Are you sure about this?
Let go.
Gun Woo.
Father.
Hello. I'm Oh Soo Yeon, Dodo Group's legal counsel.
Hello. Thanks for coming over.
Come inside.
- Father!
-  Sir!
I'm fine.
I'm just tired because I exercised a bit too much.
When did he get so bad?
This is actually a huge improvement from...
- Don't say such nonsense!
-  I'm sorry, Sir.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
You should've told me you weren't well.
You're making me look bad.
You're busy with work.
I don't want you to worry about me, too.
Without you,
the company means nothing.
I want to be around you for a long, long time.
So please look after yourself.
I guess...
not everything about my life was a total waste.
At least one member of my family likes me.
- Let's go inside.
-  No.
I have to go.
Help him as best as you can.
I will.
Go back to work, then.
(Land Registry)
I don't know exactly...
how much I have.
To revise your will, we'll need to update your list of assets.
That's right.
That will take a lot of time.
Also,
find a way to get back the assets...
I gave to my wife and Gwang Woo.
- Pardon?
-  I want...
to get back everything I gave to those two.
Yes, Sir. I'll look for a way.
Dinner is ready.
Do you prepare the meals yourself?
Did you have to come in wearing that? You're embarrassing me, too.
I apologise.
Come downstairs and eat.
I'm not hungry. You can eat alone.
You skipped lunch and exercised.
I shouldn't have eaten that patjuk.
It ruined my appetite.
Do you want patjuk?
I'm good at making it.
Forget it. Nothing beats the patjuk my wife makes.
Can I use the kitchen?
I said, forget it.
CEO Do told me to serve you well.
I won't be long.
- Go and help her.
-  Yes, Sir.
I don't eat what doesn't suit my taste.
Don't take it personally.
I won't. Please try some.
How is it?
Is it not good?
I'm sorry. I hadn't made it in a while.
- It's delicious.
-  Sorry?
It's fantastic.
My wife's patjuk is nothing compared to this.
The little dumplings are great, too.
- Are they good, too?
-  Yes.
Eat all you want.
We're here...
What are you doing here?
What's going on?
What's this patjuk?
He craved it, so I cooked some for him.
Do you know how to make this?
You're his legal counsel.
Are you here to cook?
How dare you interrupt my meal?
So...
do you like the patjuk someone else made for you?
What you made wasn't the real thing.
It's delicious.
Some lies fall apart right away.
No one can beat your patjuk. You used to sell it.
Let's see.
It's really good.
It's not tasty at all. It's bitter.
No. Your patjuk really isn't the real...
It's bitter.
Everything you do rubs me the wrong way.
Lawyer Oh, once I finish this bowl, I'll have another.
Sure. You can have as much as you want.
- Me, too.
-  Sure.
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
I'm here as the legal counsel.
To give your father some advice.
Really?
You.
Do you want to have some wine with me?
- No. I have to go.
-  Come on.
Why are you in such a rush?
Your job here's done.
Do you know that...
Gun Woo's going on a blind date?
No.
He's going to marry someone else.
Do you mind?
What does that have to do with me?
I thought you'd given up on trying to get back at Il Jae...
and had decided to stick to Gun Woo instead.
Can I leave?
What about me?
How do you mean?
I mean...
What do you think of me as a prospective husband?
Think about it seriously.
You betrayed me twice, but I still can't stop you...
from zooming about in my head.
Anyway,
I keep thinking of you.
This is a first for me, too, so I'm very perplexed.
No. Will that do?
Think about it before you answer.
Take some time.
Thoughtfully and slowly.
I'll think about it all I want and reach the same conclusion.
So don't ever mention this again.
It's torture.
Why? Why can't it be me?
I love someone else.
She's in love?
When did she meet the guy?
Nothing works my way.
Seriously.
These are the independent candidates who are out of the running.
You're second within the error range,
so if just one of them supports you,
you will win the election.
Who's the target?
Number six.
He has the least amount of assets,
and although he was acquitted, when he was head of a borough,
he was investigated for bribery.
Are you suggesting...
we buy his support?
This is what Mr Hwang is against.
The timing...
We ran the simulation.
There will be no trace, so don't worry.
What will you do...
if this becomes a problem later on?
What will you do if Mr Byun loses by a tiny margin?
I can risk my life!
But...
you can run away.
I give up, then.
If we can't trust each other,
this plan will fail.
Stop it, Choong Dong.
Sir, as your loyal assistant...
I make the decisions. You just follow them.
Why are you acting up all of a sudden?
I apologise.
Chae Ryung, loosen up.
The results of this election are in your hands.
If this goes sideways, it's on you for jinxing it.
- What?
-  That's enough.
We have a plan. Put it into motion.
Okay.
This vase costs 10 dollars.
I'll put a 20-dollar bouquet in it.
That's 30 dollars altogether.
It's not enough to cancel anyone's election.
Understood?
You all did well today.
Welcome back.
What's this?
It's from a supporter.
It's pretty.
Candidate number six, Cho Cham speaking.
I'm with Mingook Daily. I'd like to interview you.
I'm free right now.
I have an hour.
Yes. I'll see you there.
- Mr Cho.
-  Ms Park.
I'm Park Young Ji.
- Come inside.
-  Sure.
Welcome, Mr Cho.
Mr Byun.
Why are you here?
Please, have a seat.
(Moon Tae Gwang)
It's me.
The countdown has begun.
Do you want me to pack up and support you?
Your approval rating is 10 percent.
You'll never get elected.
But if you make the right choice,
that 10 percent can be of great use...
to the both of us.
You know I'll refuse.
Will two million dollars do?
I think that's a decent amount.
People like you still exist.
I thought you truly cared for the people.
I'll give 2.5 million dollars. Take it or leave it.
I will not quit my campaign unless it is to ensure that...
you don't get elected.
You've already accepted...
the 2.5 million dollars.
The vase on your table.
That's worth 2.5 million dollars.
You scumbag.
Will he do what we want?
He'll get back to us...
when he sees the vase.
- Hello, this is...
-  Mr Cho?
I forgot to tell you something.
Don't report the vase to the police.
It's only worth 10 dollars and you'll be mocked over it.
Take the vase to a store in Insadong...
and they'll buy it for 2.5 million.
You gain a lump sum without leaving a trace.
If you're not up for it, smash the vase.
I can do without 10 dollars.
You have until 3pm to get back to me.
It's past 3pm.
I think this means no.
Mr Cho. I'm listening.
That vase.
I smashed it.
If that is your decision,
I feel sorry for you.
Could you...
send me another vase?
Of course I can get another one.
You made the right decision.
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message...
after the beep...
It's me. I can't reach Soo Yeon.
The thing is...
She's there again.
The place where she saw Gi Tan.
Okay.
I'm looking for someone. Thank you.
Call me if you see this man.
(Kang Gi Tan)
You'll catch him making a deal?
One half has taken the bait.
We can get them both if we pull at the right time.
Who is your contact in Il Jae's camp?
I'll tell you that later.
It's me.
- What do you want?
-  Let's meet up this evening.
I haven't received the order yet.
- If this is about the contract...
-  It's not about the ship.
Then I don't see why else we should meet.
At 7pm.
See you at Dodo Hotel's cafe.
Why does Gun Woo want to see you?
I don't know.
Have you seen this man?
Have you seen this man? Call me at this number.
Gun Woo.
Will it take long? Can I help?
No. I'm almost done.
I'm meeting Chairman K at 7pm.
- Today?
-  Yes.
Come to the cafe in Dodo Hotel. I'll see you there.
Okay.
Shin Young.
Why haven't you...
Let's get a drink some time.
How can I ever see him again? I'm so embarrassed!
I'm here. Where are you?
I think I'll be a bit late.
Meet up with Chairman K and stall for a while.
Okay.
How will I know who he is?
They know you.
Okay. Don't be too late.
Who is K?
I'm sorry.
It's her again.
Gi Tan.
I knew you'd be alive.
How do you...
know my name?
Gi Tan.