(Episode 33)
How do you...
know my name?
Gi Tan.
It's me, Gi Tan. I'm Soo Yeon.
Who are you?
I'm Soo Yeon. Oh Soo Yeon.
What's wrong, Gi Tan?
Are you the one...
who saved me...
with the MK2 vaccine at the lab?
Yes.
Gosh.
Have we...
Gi Tan, what's wrong? Gi Tan.
Are you okay?
Sir!
Get him to a room and call a doctor.
Yes, Sir.
I don't understand why you let Lawyer Oh meet Mr Kang.
Soo Yeon's heart is broken because of Gi Tan.
I didn't think I could hide it.
But still,
you don't have to be the only one who's hurt in this.
Bring him.
Over here.
Find out what's going on.
Yes, Sir.
Wait. Lawyer Oh, you'd better not come.
Soo Tak, you can explain.
Talk to me, Soo Tak.
What happened to Gi Tan?
Professor Jin is on the phone.
Professor Jin, Chairman isn't doing so well.
If it's all right, could you come to Korea right now?
If I leave now,
I'll be at the airport by 12am.
I will see to it. Please leave for the airport right now.
So there's a bullet in his head?
Yes. That's why he got hypnotherapy to relieve the pain.
But whenever he thought of you,
he got this severe pain, just like you saw.
Can't he get it removed by surgery?
It's very dangerous.
He may die.
What about treatments? Is there any way to deal with it?
The man who did the hypnotherapy will be here tonight.
He said he'd find other ways to relieve him of his pain,
so we'll wait and see what he can do.
- My goodness.
-  Here.
Take it. It's probably from your awaited customer.
Mr Cho.
Did you get the vase?
I did.
Now, tell me...
what I must do.
You can announce the resignation of your candidacy,
then come over to my office to announce that you support me.
I will do that.
What about...
the promised amount?
You can choose either cash or a bearer bond.
I think a bearer bond is a safer choice.
Okay.
My assistant will give you a call early tomorrow.
You can discuss the details with my assistant.
Are we about 80 percent there?
What will you do for me...
if you win this election?
Tell me anything...
you want.
I have a lot of things that I want from you.
Can you really do them all?
Thanks to you,
I'll become the mayor of Seoul.
So what can't I do for you?
Here's my first wish.
Don't think about anything else,
but just drink with me.
That would be my pleasure.
(Wife)
I must be a bad girl.
I really wish...
that you wouldn't take this call.
Isn't he picking up?
No.
I heard he left his office late afternoon.
You should keep...
an eye on him.
It's probably nothing.
He can barely sleep at night because of the election.
You must pay attention...
to what I've said before.
He must not do anything...
that will give a handle to his opponents.
You couldn't have made it more clear.
I'm sure he's not up to anything stupid.
When one is smitten with power,
there is nothing else one will care about.
I'm his father-in-law. He could easily disregard me.
Father.
Keep your head straight...
and make sure you keep him grounded.
If he does anything out of line,
I won't...
forgive him.
Goodnight, Father.
Why isn't he picking up his phone?
I think I drank too much.
I'm so dizzy.
Chae Ryung.
Keep your distance.
Oh, gosh, Mr Byun.
Mr Byun, please wake up.
You're almost home.
You're so annoying.
Just drive.
Honey.
Why did you drink so much?
It's my wife.
Are you insane?
The election is very near. How can you drink so much?
I had to drink because of a great occasion.
My goodness.
- Take him to his bedroom.
-  Yes, Ma'am.
- This way, Sir.
-  All right.
I'll get going then.
Ms Ok.
Did you drink, too?
Sorry?
Yes. Just a little.
I don't think this is just a little.
Were you two alone?
Of course not. Why would I drink with Mr Byun?
Who else was there?
Tell me. Who else was there this late at night?
Well, I...
He had a meeting with his colleagues.
His colleagues?
Yes, Ma'am.
She attended to help host the gathering.
Everyone drank so well.
It was so hard to keep up.
I'm sorry.
Not at all. I drank too much.
You did well today.
You should go in and rest.
Thank you for helping me.
Don't be stupid.
I was only looking out for Mr Byun.
Either way.
No wonder he puts his trust in you.
Don't cross the line with him.
If they find out that you're up to something,
they'll get rid of you without a problem.
Don't worry.
I'll rip this household apart before then.
Honey. Take your clothes off.
Where on earth did you get this?
Thank you for making your way here.
Is she the one you mentioned over the phone?
Yes, I'm Oh Soo Yeon.
Can you explain to me what happened?
This never happened to me before, so I'm surprised myself.
Why was the hypnosis lifted?
He must have loved Ms Oh enough...
to break through the hypnosis.
There's no other explanation for it.
Can he be treated?
We can get rid of his pain altogether,
but if that happens,
he will also forget everything related to you.
Can't we revive his memories...
about Soo Yeon later on?
I'm trying to find a solution for it,
but I can't guarantee when I'll find it.
Please erase...
any memories of me in him.
Soo Yeon.
Please heal him so that he won't ever be in pain...
because of me.
I beg you.
What do you see right now?
I see...
a beautiful house I've always dreamed of.
Who came out from that house?
Brother!
Dong Soo.
It's Guk Cheol. Hello.
Dong Soo came out.
He welcomed me with a smile.
What did you do after that?
I'm...
going inside that house.
There's a woman waiting for me.
Who is she?
Gi Tan.
Soo Yeon...
Oh Soo Yeon...
It's the woman I love.
I'm so happy...
I wish time would stop right now.
Now,
you will enter that house again.
You will look in every corner,
but no one...
is in that empty house.
Your memory...
is an illusion the bullet in your head made up.
There's not a single memory...
of Oh Soo Yeon left in your head.
All of the things that caused you pain...
will be gone forever.
Now,
you're at ease.
He won't be hurt any more even if he sees you.
It's okay if you don't remember me.
Don't try to remember me.
I won't be greedy any more.
I'm just so thankful that you're alive.
I love you, Gi Tan.
Soo Yeon.
I'm sorry, but I want to be alone.
Soo Yeon asked him to erase any memories of her.
She can't bear to watch Gi Tan in pain.
(Spokesperson for Ordinary Citizens!)
Gun Woo. Why are you here so early?
These are some internal documents from Il Jae's company.
Let me know if you ever need anything.
I'll fight with you against Il Jae until the end.
Thank you.
Hey...
Will you do...
one thing for me?
Don't act as if you're okay.
You can cry in front of me if you have to.
You can do however you feel like.
I'm going to focus on how I'll make Il Jae pay.
I won't think about anything else.
I was about to go eat. Do you want to have breakfast?
What do you think about her?
She looks like a nice person.
She has a great face.
She's the daughter of Chairman Kang from Woojung Group.
Isn't Chairman Kang's son the son-in-law of the president?
His company is not very big, but their family is powerful...
in politics.
Gun Woo...
needs someone...
that can help him become more powerful.
I'm not sure if they would like him.
What's wrong with him?
The fact that he was born outside of marriage...
I know Chairman Kang well.
After the general meeting,
I'll announce Gun Woo as my successor.
Then they won't turn down the marriage.
Are you ill again?
I'm not sure what's wrong. I've been taking my medicine.
I think you've worked out too much recently.
Here's your pills.
Here you are.
Engagement?
Why suddenly?
Your father is dying to arrange a marriage for him.
So?
Are you trying to arrange one for me?
No way. I'll never get into an arranged marriage.
Shin Young, the company is about to go into Gun Woo's hands.
You should play along.
You can do it, then.
He will. He's marrying Seogang Group's second daughter.
No way, I don't want to.
I won't get married twice.
Are you two serious? This isn't all for me.
It's all for your future.
Whatever. I'm not doing it.
Hey.
Do you like Chairman K?
Chairman K?
Isn't that Gi Tan, who came back as a huge businessman?
Yes, I heard from the hotel manager...
that she is crazy for him.
What are you talking about? I'm not crazy about anyone.
I'm having such a hard time because he's dying to get me.
Is that true?
Is Gi Tan crazy for you?
It's awful. He's been dying to go on a date with me.
That's even better.
You should definitely go for him.
Mum.
What do you mean?
Do you want me to get married to him?
You don't have to marry him.
Just announce an engagement just before the general meeting.
That will help you get the shareholders' trust.
But I'm sure he's already feeling pretty down...
because I've been really bad to him.
That's weird.
What I've heard was that you're all crazy for him,
but he doesn't want anything to do with you.
Don't you know anything about her?
She's not someone who'd go crazy for anyone.
Mum, that's what I thought, but...
Shut it. You don't know anything.
Anyways.
I will set up a meeting for you and Gi Tan.
You should make up with him.
You can do that, right?
No way!
Don't mention this to him, okay?
He's not the man he was before.
Stop playing hard to get and just date him.
No way!
My work is already straining enough. Don't ever call me about this again.
At least go on a blind date!
Kang Gi Tan.
Why don't you also get married again, Sir?
Stop it, Mr Han.
I think it would be useful to become the successor.
I think I am very sick.
What's wrong?
Well, it's that...
Whenever I hear about engagements and marriages,
Soo Yeon's face always magically appears...
inside my head.
Like this!
Oh, Soo Yeon.
Hey.
You should at least say hello when you meet someone you know.
I'm a bit busy right now.
Hey, wait.
Why don't you and I go over there...
and talk?
What?
You told me...
last time that there is someone you love.
I gave that a thought, and I think...
you were lying.
I'm sure it's not Gun Woo because he's Il Jae's man.
Who could it be?
You can tell me.
See? You can't.
I never got good grades, but I catch onto things quickly.
- So what?
-  Why do you ask?
I already...
told you how I feel.
You said you were betrayed by me twice.
What if I betray you again?
I will probably go insane.
That's my answer.
Don't ever make me hear this nonsense again.
Come on.
Date me just for a year.
No.
Let's date seriously for three months.
Hey, CEO Do.
I will be really good to you.
I will make you feel loved.
So...
Lawyer Oh.
What are you doing here?
Well,
I had to talk to her about some business...
He asked me to marry him.
What a big mouth you have!
Did you think I would keep this nonsense a secret?
Mr Kim,
take Lawyer Oh to my office.
Okay, Sir. This way, please.
How much lower will you get?
What?
- Lower?
-  I will let it pass for today.
But don't say anything stupid to Soo Yeon ever again.
Hey, why do you care about whatever I do?
Is she yours?
Yes. She's mine.
What?
I love her.
So don't come near her.
This is my final warning.
Sir.
Did you hear him?
He said Soo Yeon is his.
I don't think Soo Yeon is right for you either.
What if Chairwoman Hwang finds out?
I am not giving up.
Pardon?
Gun Woo likes her, too. I won't let him have her...
even if I have to break up with her later.
Sir.
From now on,
the real war begins.
Get the head of SPD...
and ask what those two have been up to these days.
Do it.
My goodness. I can't believe I'm still embarrassed.
Why are you hiding?
I wasn't hiding.
No one ever cleans up around here.
This is so dirty.
Next week, Chinese shipowners are coming.
They'll stay at this hotel,
so please redo the interior and make sure...
all the home appliances work.
Make sure they get personalised meals, too.
What else?
Don't you have anything else to say?
We're still dating, you know.
Don't you remember?
Do you know what I went through because of you?
Kang Ga Din!
Run! Run faster!
Hey!
No, I don't remember.
Did something happen?
I never knew anyone could behave so indecently when they were drunk.
Indecently?
I'll let this pass because I don't remember it.
I thought you'd given up on dating me that day.
I thought that's why you behaved the way you did.
You're right.
I remember now.
It was because you were an awful person to date.
That's great.
We can only talk about business from now on.
Goodbye.
Yes, Mum. I will go on that blind date.
Find someone who is much better than Gi Tan.
Kang Ga Din.
I will find someone who's so much better than you...
and I'll make you regret this.
You just wait and see.
I resign...
as the candidate for the mayor of Seoul.
And I officially support...
Byun Il Jae from now on.
At today's press conference, Candidate Cho stated that...
Byun Il Jae is the candidate...
that he thinks is the most ideal person for the mayor position.
What if Il Jae actually becomes the mayor?
Don't even say that.
It'll be trouble if he becomes the mayor of Seoul.
They just said that he's the most ideal candidate.
We're the only ones who know what he's really like.
There's no way he'll become the mayor.
I'll make sure he doesn't make it.
With the support from candidate Cho Cham,
Byun Il Jae will have a foot ahead in the race...
whilst the candidates are narrowing down.
The bait I mentioned before is Cho Cham.
Il Jae took a bite...
like a dumb goldfish.
Do you have proof that Il Jae bribed him?
They haven't given him any money yet.
I'll be there when they move...
to get the evidence. You don't have to worry about it.
Call Lawyer Oh.
Why do you suddenly need her for?
Television is the most effective medium...
to reveal Il Jae's corruption.
We should prepare in advance.
Will you be all right?
Is there a problem?
Do you remember seeing Lawyer Oh...
two days ago?
I had a huge headache, so we didn't get to talk much.
Do you remember seeing her faint on the streets?
We moved her to the hospital...
and informed Gun Woo.
Why do you keep asking me?
It's nothing. I thought you might've forgotten due to the treatment.
Call her and ask her for lunch.
If she's busy, ask if dinner works.
Yes, Sir.
(Lawyer Oh Soo Yeon)
B World is probably under the suspicion of dodging taxes.
I'll look for materials in that matter.
Thank you.
Yes, Soo Tak.
Right now?
No, I'm free.
All right.
Who was that?
Gi Tan wants to see me to talk about business.
Will it be all right?
According to Soo Tak, his hypnotherapy went well,
so it should be all right.
I'm not talking about him. I'm asking about you.
Can you act like you don't know him?
I have to.
I think I can do it.
Let's go.
Sir.
It's nice to finally meet you.
I'm Kang Gi Tan.
I'm Lawyer Oh Soo Yeon.
It's nice to meet you.
Please take a seat.
Thank you.
I heard a lot about you.
I heard your brother...
passed away because of Il Jae.
I also heard that you have a grudge against him.
Is there a way to get revenge at him?
I'm certain that...
illegal funds have been involved during his campaign.
I intend on researching Il Jae's company, B World,
on embezzlement of public funds.
We're tracking any illegal activities with his campaign.
When the time comes, we would like to disclose it on your show.
There's no reason for me to decline.
I feel like I'm meeting an old friend.
I'm sure we'll have to help each other out a lot.
I'm also glad to have met you as well.
Have you eaten?
Their course meals are great.
I have another meeting to go to.
I'm sorry.
We'll do it another time then.
Take care.
I'm back, Mr Hwang.
Why is Cho Cham...
supporting you instead of running for himself?
Didn't you see the press conference?
I thought I warned you.
You must not cheat this time.
What have you done to him?
Honey, go to our room.
- Honey.
-  Go inside.
You're the one...
who cheated to turn this election into a mess.
- What did you say?
-  Did you think...
I wouldn't know that you organised the attack on Ji Soo?
You...
You probably aimed for me at first.
Then Ji Soo accidentally got hurt in my place.
If you can't solve it,
then that becomes cheating.
That incident will never be revealed to the world.
However, what you've done...
It will be completely buried.
I'm capable of doing that.
When I become the mayor of Seoul,
I'll use all my power...
to support you in the presidential election.
Put your trust in me for the last time.
It's already too late.
He's confident about this.
We have no choice but to trust in him.
Il Jae...
I'm not doubting his capability.
It's Gi Tan.
He's a scary man.
It's him that worries me.
If...
things turn out the way you're worried about,
what will you do?
Then it'll be over between ll Jae and me.
It doesn't matter if he's my son-in-law.
- Tonight?
-  Yes.
Mr Cho will be visiting the antique store tonight.
Is the owner of that store trustworthy?
I've been working with them for years. You don't have to worry.
What about the money?
When he brings in the vase, Il Jae will give me the money.
I'll give you the money once I get it.
Our hunt for Il Jae is finally starting.
Welcome.
I came to sell something.
Let me take a look.
It's worth 2.5 million dollars.
You want it in a bearer bond, right?
Yes.
If you write down your contact, I'll send someone over to you.
Is this all you need?
Yes.
Don't worry. You can go now.
Great work.
Here's a little something for you.
Thank you.
If something goes wrong, deny everything.
You'll be fine since there's no proof.
Cho Cham just sold the vase.
Do you have the money?
(10,000 dollars)
Who will give him the money?
The owner of the antique store.
That way, no one can trace the money back to us.
You should go.
Okay.
Follow her.
Sorry?
Follow her and see if she gives the money...
to the store owner.
Yes, Sir.
(Moon Tae Gwang)
Hello, Mr Moon. I'm on the way.
You're being followed.
I came just in case. I'm glad I did.
Let's not meet right now.
You just saved my life.
I used to work at the NIS.
What will you do now?
I'll go to Insa-dong.
Pick up the money there.
We're closed for...
Why are you here?
Mr Moon will come by later.
Give him this suitcase.
I will.
It's me, Sir.
You don't have to worry about her.
I didn't think Il Jae still doubted me.
You should quit...
and move out soon.
No.
I think I should be more proactive.
Even if he isn't elected this time,
he won't go down that easily...
as long as his wife and father-in-law are around.
We started this.
Let's finish it.
I have something for you.
Get in.
Were you followed?
Don't worry.
How much was it?
2.5 million dollars.
2.5 million?
That's odd.
Mr Byun said two million.
Mr Byun promised me 2.5 million dollars.
Would I quit campaigning for any less than that?
Well... Maybe I was mistaken.
Here. Check the amount yourself.
Is it correct?
2.5 million. It's all here.
I'm sorry. I guess I misheard.
It's a large sum. Where will you keep it?
Why do you ask that?
Mr Byun is afraid something could go wrong.
I won't spend it for a while.
I'll put it in a safe deposit box.
Don't worry.
Mr Byun promised me 2.5 million dollars.
Would I quit campaigning for any less than that?
I won't spend it for a while.
I'll put it in a safe deposit box.
Don't worry.
This recording shows who gave whom how much...
to do what.
The election...
is no longer a worry.
Well done.
When will you release this?
Let's see how the voting goes.
I'll release it...
if Il Jae is voted.
It hurts more...
to fall from the 10th floor than the 2nd.
Do I have...
some land in Yongin?
Yes. You bought it years ago.
The price has risen a lot.
Did you look for a way...
to get back what I gave my wife and Gwang Woo?
I'm studying the relative laws.
Find a way before the shareholder meeting.
I want...
to make sure they end up penniless.
Yes, Sir.
You look very tired.
I'm fine.
When am I meeting Gun Woo for lunch?
You have to leave now, Sir.
Lawyer Oh.
Join us.
Sure.
Where are you going?
Knock before you come in, woman!
Are you that ignorant?
Do you insult me in front of others because you're educated?
I'd do anything...
not to see your face for one whole day!
Three, four.
One bottle's gone already.
He should be feeling the symptoms.
- Give me that.
-  Yes, Sir.
Here.
Look inside.
It's the daughter of Woojung Group's Chairman Kang.
See if you'd like to marry her.
Sorry, Father.
I don't want to get married yet.
Marriage isn't about what you want.
It's all about timing.
Father.
Right now, you need to get married.
I know what's best for you. Do as I say.
Where are you going?
To the men's room.
- Sir! Sir!
-  Father!
Call 911, now!
Father.
- 150. Charged.
-  Clear.
Once more.
- Charged.
-  1, 2.
- 200.
-  200.
How is he?
He just woke up.
That's a relief.
He takes his medicine every day...
and exercises, too.
He was getting better.
What happened?
His condition went downhill fast over the last few days.
(Wife)
It's the chairman's phone.
His wife's calling.
I'll take it.
Hello?
Why are you picking up?
Put your father on.
He went outside for a moment.
Outside? Where?
Did your father collapse?
He was making good progress.
Why would you say that?
It's obvious.
He's always grasping the back of his neck.
Where is he that he'd leave his phone behind?
Sir.
- How is he?
-  Take him to the ward.
Sir. Sir.
I have to go.
The pills...
finally did their job.
It could've ended very badly if he got here any later.
Dr Hwang, I want you to run a thorough blood test.
Do you have his blood pressure medication?
I always keep a bottle on me.
Test these pills, too.
I prescribed him these. There shouldn't be a problem.
It's odd how he suddenly deteriorated.
We'll keep him here for a while. Please run all the necessary tests.
Sure.
(Kang Gi Tan)
Lawyer Oh speaking.
I have something urgent to discuss. Can we meet?
- Where should I go?
-  Come to Dodo Hotel.
Okay. I'll be right there.
The chief secretary called me.
Gun Woo gave the files on B World to Soo Yeon.
What does that imply?
Doesn't that mean Gun Woo betrayed Il Jae for Soo Yeon?
I think that's what happened.
If Gun Woo lost his greatest support,
this shareholder meeting will be quite the surprise.
- Good job.
-  Good job.
Thank you. Thank you.
- Fight on.
-  Fight on.
It's been a while.
You must be excited.
Your approval rating is through the roof.
Are you here to see me?
But your approval rating isn't the real issue.
You might end up in prison...
instead of your new office.
What are you talking about?
We need...
to talk in private.
Do you know that Gun Woo's trying to get our father reinstated?
I need you to support my mum instead.
You're on the board.
You have a lot of influence.
Did you ask to see me to talk about that?
I was hoping you'd promise so I could go from there.
You know how things work.
Tell me what you know first.
Do you know that Gun Woo gave confidential information...
on your company to Soo Yeon?
Why would she need it?
She wants to track your funds.
To put you behind bars.
Do you expect me to believe you?
Too bad if you don't.
You go down, not me.
I just don't get it.
Why do you trust Gun Woo?
Am I worth less than him to your political career?
I get your point. You can go.
Give up on him and side with me.
My mother's a much better bet...
than my father.
I said I got it!
Then I'll assume we have a deal.
Give me a call.
Find out where Soo Yeon is.
Yes, Sir.
I won't spend it for a while.
I'll put it in a safe deposit box.
Don't worry.
We will play this recording...
on your show.
Even if we stop him from becoming mayor,
he'll get off with probation or a fine at most.
That's not good enough for you.
It's nothing compared to...
what he did.
I agree.
Do you have any evidence on the murder...
of your brother?
The doctor who did the autopsy...
left the country.
Give us his details.
We'll look for him.
- Thank you.
-  For now,
let's focus on the election.
Will you have someone call the show to report this like last time?
Yes.
This time, I'll make the call myself.
I'll mention how he embezzled from B World.
See you soon.
Call me any time.
It's me.
I think Gwang Woo told the truth.
Gun Woo...
Soo Yeon...
- I'll turn on the light.
-  Don't.
Leave it off.
I can't stand it that...
two people half my age...
are trying...
to ruin my whole life.
I was looking for a way...
to vent my frustration and fury.
Did you find one?
Choong Dong.
Yes, Sir.
Let's...
kill her.
That is...
the only way.
Sir.
Do you remember what she said to you?
If something happens to her, people would suspect you.
There is...
a way.
First...
Yes, Sir.
What are you thinking about?
Lawyer Oh.
Don't we get along well?
It's as if we knew each other for years.
You share a common goal.
That must be it.
Instead of seeing her off,
I should've asked her out for a drink.
Oh, I see.
I have to go home.
What?
Aren't you waiting for Gun Woo?
I'll call him on the way.
See you tomorrow.
Take care.
Bye.
That's Soo Yeon's car.
Soo Yeon, I need you to wake up.
Soo Yeon. Soo Yeon.
(Monster)
Lawyer Oh is like a ticking time bomb.
You didn't listen to me.
Her blood is on your hands.
She's Dodo Group's chairman's daughter. She's quite an airhead.
She tried to kill me!
I will deal with it.
Congratulations, Mayor Byun.
I should go and congratulate him in person.
This will be the last time you feel any happiness.