(Episode 34)
That's Soo Yeon's car.
Soo Yeon, I need you to wake up.
Soo Yeon. Soo Yeon.
What happened?
I got her.
Great job.
Make sure everything ends cleanly.
Of course.
You mustn't leave any evidence that Soo Yeon's been murdered.
Make it look like she killed herself because of her brother.
Where are you?
Go to the bridge in Yangsu-ri.
That's a pretty desolate place...
and a lot of people commit suicide there.
(Moon Tae Gwang)
Chairman, something happened.
What is it?
Lawyer Oh has been abducted by Il Jae.
They're headed to a bridge in Yangsu-ri.
We'll leave immediately.
You don't have to go yourself.
Her abduction is not...
completely irrelevant with me.
Drive as fast as you can.
Yes, Sir.
Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon!
There isn't anyone on the bridge.
- What about the police?
-  I think we got here before them.
Sir, over there!
Soo Yeon, no. Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon.
No, Soo Yeon. Don't die.
Soo Yeon, no.
Soo Yeon.
Good job. You did it.
My cottage is nearby, right?
We should move them there.
Okay, Sir.
Il Jae...
must have decided to give up being human.
It could have been really dangerous if we were late.
The police want to question the victim. What should we do?
I want...
to remain dead to Il Jae until the day of the election.
Il Jae...
will make it seem like it's Choong Dong's doing.
My bag disappeared.
I'm sure they'll think that we're going for the slush fund.
It'll be best to do as she says if we want to make...
the surprise announcement on her show.
Why don't you stay in China?
It's close enough and it'll be a good place to hide.
There's no need.
I won't be tricked in the same way.
You don't have to help me.
You're like a bomb to Chairman Kang.
- I know that already.
-  That's why...
I would prefer if you didn't stimulate him.
Don't be too close or too distant from him.
I understand.
I'm sorry, Lawyer Oh.
Once they find a cure for him, I'll let you know first.
I don't expect them to.
I'm just thankful that Gi Tan is alive.
I think it's best for you to go to China.
There isn't anywhere safer right now.
I would appreciate it if you can help.
- Soo Tak, leave with her tomorrow.
-  Yes, Sir.
You should file for a missing person as well.
Lawyer Min will take care of it.
This is what Soo Yeon had with her.
I'm sure Gi Tan has this document as well.
Fortunately, it's not an important document.
He couldn't have found out anything from this.
I'll get rid of Gi Tan after the election is over.
Good job, Choong Dong.
I followed your orders,
but I'm a little concerned.
There is no need...
to be concerned for what hasn't happened yet.
But...
That's how I lived all my life.
Just do your best in every moment.
That will become your path.
What do you plan on doing with Gun Woo?
I'll take care of him...
after the election as well.
Have a safe trip to China. I'll call you.
Thank you, Gun Woo.
If it wasn't for you,
I would probably still be in that cold river.
If something happens to you, there would be no point in living.
Eat and sleep well in China.
Call me if anything bothers you.
Go to bed.
You should tell me if anything bothers you as well.
I'm a little slow, so I might...
Don't be so complicated.
You can let me comfort you. I'll console you.
That'll make me happy.
Goodnight.
Chae Ryung.
Aren't you a little underdressed for breakfast?
I'm sorry. I just woke up.
Right. Congratulations, Mr Byun.
The rating for the second candidate in line is eight percent lower.
There's still a lot of room for changes.
You must stay on your toes.
Yes, Mr Hwang.
- Are you eating?
-  Yes, come in.
If you didn't eat, come join us.
- Yes.
-  That's okay, I ate.
I heard a strange news on my way here.
What strange news?
A police friend of mine says...
that Soo Yeon has gone missing.
Soo Yeon?
What do you mean?
I don't know the details,
but her law firm has filed for her missing.
Honey, can I have more soup?
Sure.
It seems like you're enjoying the hospital food.
After eating your food,
anything tastes good.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
He even took a walk this morning without the crutches.
It's so strange.
I get worse when I'm at home.
Are the test results out?
This was the problem.
What?
You gave me those pills.
These are just supplements.
Supplements?
Are you saying I took supplements instead of...
my blood pressure medication?
I swear I prescribed medication for your blood pressure.
I don't know what happened.
Who picked up the pills until now?
I did and then stored them at home.
That means...
someone switched them at home.
That witch!
- Sir!
-  Chairman!
Is she trying to kill me?
How can she?
We shouldn't act rashly from having suspicions.
I'll take care of it.
No.
You're busy with the EGM.
I'll take care of it.
- You're not well yet.
-  This is a family problem.
I'm sure it's my wife.
I'll deal with it.
Yes, Father.
I want to be discharged right away.
Give me some other pills.
- Yes, Sir.
-  Also!
Don't tell anyone about this.
It's just between us.
It'll be a secret, okay?
Understood, Sir.
You should pick that one.
That's very elegant.
Mum.
It's my blind date. Can I wear what I want?
His family is very conservative. They like neatly dressed people.
Is he handsome?
It's all about looks for me.
Of course he is.
He's got manners, a good family and good education.
He's a perfect guy. Don't worry about it.
I'm going to make him regret this.
Wait. Why would you make him regret this?
I wasn't talking about him.
There's this awful guy.
Mum. Dad is here.
Is he discharged already?
What are you talking about? Is he sick?
Dad.
What's wrong? Are you really ill?
Shin Young.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I couldn't visit you often because I was busy with work.
What did the doctor say?
He received thorough examination,
but we still do not know what's wrong.
It must be very serious if Dr Hwang doesn't even know.
He said his blood pressure medicine doesn't seem to be effective.
So we got new ones.
Is he changing medicines?
Yes. Dr Hwang thought it would be a good idea.
Why didn't you let us come to the hospital...
if you were doing this badly?
Seeing your mum...
makes me worse.
It looks like he's not doing so bad.
He still has the energy to hate me.
Shin Young.
I need to talk to you.
- Let's go.
-  Yes, Sir.
What if something happens to him?
It's not the time to worry about him.
You don't know what will happen to me at the general meeting.
It looks like he's pretty sick.
I don't think we need to worry about his reinstatement.
Is he changing his blood pressure medicine?
You have to be on my side...
at the upcoming general meeting no matter what happens.
I want to do that.
- But...
-  But what?
I heard you're giving the company to Gun Woo.
I am completely against that.
Gwang Woo fell out of my favour,
but Shin Young,
I don't want to lose you.
But if you stand...
with your mum,
I have...
no choice but to abandon you.
Dad.
Keep these words...
in your mind.
It's all for your sake.
What did he say?
I don't know. I don't want to talk about it.
Come on, tell us. What was this secret meeting about?
Did he ask you to support him instead of me?
- Yes.
-  What did you say?
I really hate...
how you two are fighting.
I should just get married.
- Shin Young. That little...
-  Mum, leave her alone.
Shin Young's a simpleton, so I can talk to her later.
What happened to Il Jae's support?
He will abandon Gun Woo in no time.
Trust me and don't worry about it.
You've failed my trust so many times before.
I'm... I'm... I'm serious this time around!
Why do they all leave me?
Anyways,
I wonder what Soo Yeon's doing.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
Your call has been forwarded to an automated voice messaging system.
Please leave your message after the beep.
Gun Woo lost his sponsor...
so he's as good as gone.
It's time for me to talk Soo Yeon into this.
Let's see. Chairman, where should I put this camera?
Over here? No.
How's this?
- Give that to me.
-  Yes, Sir.
That's good.
This is perfect. It's done.
Yes, Chairman.
Once I have the evidence,
she will be charged...
for attempted murder.
Yes. I'm on this blind date just for fun.
It's Dodo Group's daughter.
I heard she's crazy and that she's pretty dull.
I heard she's insane.
My gosh, Darling. Don't worry.
You're the only one for me.
(I love you, Darling.)
Who is that guy?
- Hello.
-  You're early, Mr Park.
I just got here, too.
He's not that bad.
Say hello. This is Do Shin Young, my daughter.
Nice to meet you. I'm Do Shin Young.
I'm Park Je Soo. Nice to meet you.
Have a great time then.
- Okay.
-  Bye.
Shall we go eat?
Sure.
What a great timing.
This is my hotel, so I'll lead the way.
Sure.
Kang Ga Din, you're probably mad, aren't you?
You should've been good to me while I was still around.
This feels great.
That's Gwangjin Shipping's Chairman, Mr Park's son.
Gwangjin Shipping?
Isn't that the company that's investing in us?
You're right. He's the CEO of foreign division.
He seems like a jerk.
Sorry?
Let's go eat, too.
Sure.
I can't believe someone as beautiful as you are in hotel business.
I'm impressed.
You look like the type who'd be popular with girls.
Everyone says that, but it's not true.
I've been focused only on my work.
So I haven't dated many women.
I see.
You're just like me.
(Assistant)
I'm sorry, I have to take this.
Sure.
(My love, do not worry.)
(Other than the fact that she's rich, she's nothing to you.)
(She doesn't even know I'm talking about her. She's smiling.)
(We'll use her just for business.)
(Don't worry. I will never let you go.)
I'm sorry. It was a business call from Spain.
I'd like to get married right away...
without an engagement period.
What do you think?
(What a jerk.)
(I lived in Spain for five years.)
What did you say? "Just for business?"
"I'll never let you go, so don't worry about that"?
You're fluent in Spanish.
I didn't know you lived there for five years.
- What?
-  Hey, Shin Young.
Everyone in the business world knows that you're crazy.
Do you think you can get married with that kind of personality?
You're lucky it's me. At least I'm eating with you.
You jerk.
Let her hand go.
Are you Chairman Park of Gwangjin Shipping?
This is Chairman K...
of KT Corporation.
Oh, really?
Nice to meet you. I'm Gwangjin Shipping's...
Did you decline my proposal...
for someone like him?
Chairman K, you must be mistaken.
Are we investing in Gwangjin Shipping?
- Yes.
-  Cancel it.
Sir.
I won't forgive anyone...
who treats Shin Young like this.
Let's go.
Chairman K! I really didn't know! Sir!
Do you think I'll thank you if you do this?
I can't bear to watch other people look down...
on my business partner.
Business partner?
Yes.
You will be doing business with me.
Fine.
When the shipowners come from China, I'll give them room...
You can't call yourself a business partner with something like that.
Then what are you thinking of?
How long are you going to let your brothers take everything?
When you mean business, do you mean...
I plan on partnering with you.
You should take part in fighting...
for your father's company.
Answer me. Are you going to accept my offer?
I will. I'll do it no matter what.
I'll listen to anything you say, Ga Din.
Oh, Shin Young. Goodness, you.
Hey, Shin Young.
What is it? You don't want to?
I'll think about it.
Forget it then.
Wait, I'll do it.
I'll become your business partner.
Don't be so childish.
You need to become more mature.
I'm already...
mature as I am right now.
Not that kind of mature.
You need to act like a businesswoman.
That's the only way you'll get to work with me.
Don't we need to have meetings if we're partners?
Hey, Ga Din!
- Good luck!
-  Good luck!
Thank you very much.
- Hello, Ma'am.
-  Hello.
I, Il Jae, will make Seoul for our ordinary citizens.
- Good luck.
-  Do you plan on seeing Mr Byun?
If he kidnapped Soo Yeon,
he must know that I had a change of heart.
I, Il Jae, will make Seoul for our ordinary citizens.
- My goodness.
-  Thank you.
- You must be hard at work.
- Good luck.
-  Good luck.
- Please vote for us.
-  Okay.
Things seem to be hectic at the office, prior to the EGM.
Soo Yeon disappeared.
She has gone missing.
So?
I remember clearly...
that you said you would get rid of Soo Yeon...
if I didn't.
Do you think I killed her?
I never said she died.
I said she disappeared.
What did you do to her?
I don't know anything about it.
However, you brought it onto yourself...
if anything happens to her.
It's because you didn't listen to me.
You killed her yourself.
I hope she never shows up again.
That way, there's no reason for you to hate me...
nor for me to be suspicious of you.
If you didn't do anything to Soo Yeon,
there's no reason for me to hate you.
I swear to my mother's grave...
that her disappearance has nothing to do with me.
I'm glad to hear that.
Gun Woo.
I'm not fighting desperately for this election...
just for myself.
Once I become the mayor, I'll use all my power...
to help you.
I didn't give up my trust in you.
I just hope...
you'll come back to your place soon.
Gun Woo.
Through this election, our ill-fated relationship...
will come to an end.
Gosh.
What's with you again?
Last night, he slept with the air conditioner on.
He caught a cold.
Even dogs don't get colds in the summer.
You've become so weak.
I think he should have some samgyetang to get better.
Mr Gong.
I'm starving, let's go.
Yes, Sir.
We'll be back.
It's so hot.
Good work, Sir.
Do you think...
she'll switch the pills?
I'm sure she'll be anxious because of the EGM.
You have my blood pressure medication in a safe place, right?
Yes, Sir.
I hope...
she gets caught.
What took you so long? I told you to hurry.
I ran here as soon as I got your call.
What about the pills?
They're right here.
- Are they supplements?
-  Yes, Ma'am.
Go stand guard outside.
Here. Play it.
Yes, Sir.
It's your wife.
What took you so long? I told you to hurry.
I ran here as soon as I got your call.
- What about the pills?
-  They're right here.
- Are they supplements?
-  Yes, Ma'am.
Go stand guard outside.
We got her.
This is the evidence that she tried to kill me.
What do you plan on doing now?
I'll wait until the EGM.
I'll pay her back in a bigger way.
If that still doesn't make me feel any better,
I'll send her to jail.
Why are you distracting me?
I came...
to listen to your playing the piano.
They say people change when they're about to die.
You wanted to break this piano before.
Like you said,
I don't think I'll live long.
I want to ask...
if you can give me...
one last chance to sit at the chairman's chair...
at the next EGM.
Are you begging me?
I put my entire life...
into building this company.
Please let me keep my dignity.
What's with you? You're scaring me.
You were the one...
who declined my offer to reconcile.
You were a lion all your life, so you can't pretend to be a cat...
just because your teeth and nails are removed.
Gwi Ja.
Stop being a hypocrite and be yourself!
I became...
the worst woman in history all because of you.
You can live the rest of your life like that.
As the worst man in history.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You will soon get to see...
how bad I am, Gwi Ja.
My goodness.
- Hello.
-  Hey, how have you been?
Everything here would look great on Soo Yeon.
I'll take everything here! Everything!
Sir.
Lawyer Oh probably has her taste. I don't think you should...
I've never seen any woman who didn't like expensive things.
Wait and see.
Soo Yeon will be mine soon.
I don't understand why you like her so much.
You don't like someone for a reason.
I just like her. That's a reason enough.
You know what?
Soo Yeon has a great relationship with Father.
Once Soo Yeon likes me,
I feel that my relationship with him would improve, too.
I want to get along with him again like the times before.
Have you ever been on good terms with him?
It was probably back when I was about 12...
or maybe 13.
I got along with him until then.
Whatever.
Anyways, Soo Yeon will be a lucky girl for me.
You just wait and see.
Oh my gosh.
Hold this. Hold it.
I'll put this on Soo Yeon and go abroad right away.
Let's go.
(Huaping's hideout in China)
I can't find anything in Il Jae's books.
We should search harder. I'm sure he made a slush fund.
You know what?
When Chairman was hit with that bullet,
he stayed here in a vegetative state for a year.
Chairman.
What brings you here all of a sudden?
I had to come for a discussion. I'm taking Lawyer Oh back tomorrow.
Did you find everything okay?
Yes.
Boss is in Italy right now.
I talked to him.
See you later.
Take him.
What happened? I thought he couldn't come.
He found new evidence of Il Jae's slush fund,
so he changed his schedule.
A paper company in Hong Kong is related to Il Jae.
Did you give her the documents?
- Yes.
-  I looked into it.
Il Jae made an investment to that paper company.
I'm sure we can find something from there.
I heard you barely ate.
You're probably sick of staying here.
Do you want to go for a ride?
There are great places around here.
It's okay. I'll get going.
Do understand.
She's a little dry.
I don't feel bad.
Pardon?
She didn't make me feel bad.
That's a relief.
Yes, Lawyer Min.
What?
Gwang Woo sent me presents?
Yes.
He sent you designer bags, shoes and clothes.
My gosh, he even sent a swimsuit.
Anyways, he sent a lot of stuff.
How much do they add up to?
Delivery!
Here's another delivery.
- Go and get that.
-  Delivery! Hurry!
We're coming!
You can open up a department store in here. What should I do?
He must have no idea that I went missing.
He wouldn't have sent these if he knew.
He's such a fool.
Leave them. I'll return them when I get there.
Bye.
Yes, Gun Woo.
Are you doing okay over there?
Yes. I'm doing very well.
I heard Gi Tan went there.
Things are fine. Don't worry, Gun Woo.
My father's looking for you.
I'll tell you once you're back.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Lawyer Oh.
What's she like?
Why do you ask?
It seems like...
both Gwang Woo and Gun Woo like her.
She must be two-timing them.
I don't think so.
Sorry?
I think she's dating Gun Woo,
but it seems like Gwang Woo is a one-sided thing.
Whatever it is, she must be vulgar to let both brothers fall for her.
Why are you smiling?
Can't I smile?
There must be a reason.
I don't know.
Seeing Lawyer Oh makes me smile.
I hope his hypnosis isn't getting undone.
It doesn't look like it because he has no headaches.
Professor Jin needs to find a way soon.
Aren't you nervous...
to see Gi Tan...
around Lawyer Oh?
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't.
What do you like about her?
Who on earth are you?
Your mum will be okay.
She really misses you, Ye Bin.
You're such a good kid.
What are you doing?
Fine. You aren't good. You're really bad.
Are you happy now?
Is it that difficult to make an honest...
and trustworthy company?
Did you have to take only your profits...
regardless of your customers' death?
Without her,
I'd be...
a jerk who only thought about myself.
So...
Soo Yeon is like an angel who saved you from a pit.
Is that right?
Soo Yeon is...
really pretty when she smiles.
You're really blinded by love.
Worse than I thought.
Are you okay?
You stayed up last night reading the documents.
Let's lock Il Jae up for violating election laws...
and use the slush fund later.
You'll work yourself sick.
Don't worry about me.
I know it's for women.
I can't remember why I've been wearing it.
The truth is,
I lost part of my memory in an accident.
It seemed like an important item,
so I still wear it.
Soo Yeon.
Are you crying?
Can you tell me...
why you're crying?
I don't want to discuss personal issues.
I need some sleep.
I think you're trying to avoid me.
Am I wrong?
I'm interested in you.
As a colleague with the same goal.
Is that wrong?
No, it's not.
Do you know what you say to me the most?
"No. I'm okay. It's fine."
I apologise if it bothered you.
I'll be more careful.
We have a lot to do.
Get some rest.
(Vote for the People, Vote for Seoul's Next Mayor)
Mr Byun, a lot happened to you...
during the campaign.
How do you feel?
I can tell you two things with certainty.
Never once did I do something...
that went against my conscience.
I am also positive that I felt the love and support...
of the citizens of Seoul.
Those two...
make me feel like I won the election already.
Could you pose for the cameras?
(Byun Il Jae, Candidate for Seoul mayor)
Enjoy it while you still can.
This will be the last time you feel any happiness.
It's time to tape the show.
We should go.
Will this broadcast tomorrow?
Yes.
We need everything to be kept a secret until then.
I talked to the chief producer.
What about the police?
Mr Moon's at the National Police Agency.
Don't worry about them.
They're ready for you.
If this is all true, then this is a shock.
It's hard to believe that the man at the centre of all this...
is Byun Il Jae.
Is there proof that the voice belongs to Cho Cham,
who was an independent candidate?
I believe the police are investigating right now.
Mr Byun promised me 2.5 million dollars.
Would I quit campaigning for any less than that?
Is this your voice?
We could have it analysed.
I will not answer.
He'll break very soon.
Come in.
It's time for him to head to his office.
I'm almost done.
You did well throughout the campaign.
Congratulations on getting elected, Mayor Byun.
No one knows the result yet.
There are ways to tell.
She's right. You topped the polls by at least 10 percent.
That can't be overturned.
I love you.
I have to go.
- Bring your father along soon.
-  I will.
It's time to reveal the result of the exit polls...
carried out by the three national broadcasters.
Independent candidate, Byun Il Jae, leads with 47.5 percent.
Hanguk Party's Lee Jong Cheol has 32.4 percent.
Mr Byun beat Mr Lee...
by over 15 percent.
I expected it,
but it really blows.
The show airs tomorrow, right?
This should be exciting.
Some will be crushed.
I'm worried about you, Soo Yeon.
Why? In case Il Jae tries to hurt me again?
He'll lose the mayoralty for violating election laws,
but it won't be the end of him.
This election isn't the end for me either.
It's the beginning.
I'll go to the end.
With 49.1 percent of the votes, Candidate Byun Il Jae...
beat Hanguk Party's Lee Jong Cheol...
to become the 38th Mayor of Seoul.
- Byun Il Jae!
-  Byun Il Jae!
Congratulations.
Well done.
Thank the others.
- Honey, I'm so proud of you.
-  Thank you.
Congratulations.
- Byun Il Jae!
-  Byun Il Jae!
-  Thank you!
Thank you.
- Byun Il Jae!
-  Byun Il Jae!
Fill your glasses.
A toast to my son-in-law Byun Il Jae,
and his great future and career.
- Cheers!
-  Cheers!
Thank you.
Il Jae.
Forget everything I did to upset you if there is anything.
There is nothing. I wouldn't be here if it hadn't been for you.
- I will help you run for president.
-  All right.
Talking too much on such a good day will jinx everything.
Empty your glasses.
I think I should get some sleep.
We can't celebrate without the guest of honour.
Let him sleep. He has a busy day tomorrow.
- Thank you, Sir.
-  You're welcome.
We can continue this tomorrow.
- Sleep well.
-  Goodnight.
Father, let me pour you a glass.
Sure.
- What?
-  Are we out already?
I'll get another bottle.
I want to be congratulated, too.
Give me a hug.
I'm so jealous of your wife.
Don't do this. They're right outside.
Exactly.
We're the only people in this room.
Please. Don't do this.
I said, don't.
You said you'd do anything I wanted if you were elected.
Let's stay like this for one minute.
That's enough.
The minute isn't up yet.
Goodness.
Get some rest. Sweet dreams.
Oh dear.
I thought you went to bed. Why did you come back out?
Well... I decided to have some fresh air instead.
I should go to bed.
Yes, you do that. Go on inside.
Goodnight.
What to do...
You look upset.
Did something happen?
Il Jae, that fool...
I think he and Chae Ryung...
are having an affair.
What?
I just saw the two hugging each other.
If he'd lost this election,
I would have beaten him to a pulp.
We have to pretend we don't know.
He left his first wife...
to date and then marry Ji Soo.
I should have seen this coming.
He's such a scoundrel.
Oh dear...
What's your schedule for the day?
In the morning...
In the morning, he will attend a service at the National Cemetery.
In the afternoon, he'll give a talk to underprivileged children.
You seem to know his entire schedule.
Sir!
Sir.
This is bad.
Turn on the television.
What's going on?
Wait. What is he doing on television?
You want to report someone for violating election laws.
Yes. He currently has the highest support rating.
It's Byun Il Jae.
What is he talking about?
Sir.
They just issued a warrant for Il Jae's arrest.
I should go...
and congratulate him in person.
Mr Byun promised me 2.5 million dollars.
Would I quit campaigning for any less than that?
I won't spend it for a while.
I'll put it in a safe deposit box. Don't worry.
Il Jae, Il Jae!
I told you not to do something...
My head hurts.
Sir, you can't pass out.
I won't.
What a loser.
My head...
What would you like to say?
By the time this airs,
Mr Byun might be the new mayor of Seoul.
What angers me...
is that he sold his conscience and sense of justice...
to deceive the whole city.
Those of you watching...
must not fall for it.
Byun Il Jae...
deceived us all.
He is the worst fraud ever.
You said that pretty nicely, Sir.
You look good on TV, too.
I will end by saying just one more thing.
The poorest people on Earth...
are those without a dream.
Hang onto your dream...
and you are already the richest person in the world.
It was nice to meet you all.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Goodness.
Oh, thank you.
(Special Lecture by Mayoral Elect)
Congratulations, Uncle.
I'll visit you in prison.
What are you talking about?
Byun Il Jae.
You're under arrest for violating election laws.
Honey!
This is the teaser.
There's more to come.
Murder, abduction, illegal slush funds and more.