(Episode 35)
- It was nice to meet you all.
-  Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Congratulations, Uncle.
I'll visit you in prison.
What are you talking about?
Byun Il Jae.
You're under arrest for violating election laws.
Honey!
This is the teaser.
There's more to come.
Murder, abduction, illegal slush funds and more.
Gi Tan, how dare you...
Honey.
Honey!
Now he's cheating children as well.
There's still a long way to go...
in order to reveal his true self.
Do you admit to the contents of the recording released on broadcast?
I haven't seen the broadcast yet.
Cho Cham, the candidate that supported you,
confessed to the prosecution that he received bribery.
Is that so?
That means this incident must be...
a political conspiracy.
Are you saying someone is trying to frame you?
There is no way he would say that otherwise.
You've been elected as the mayor of Seoul.
Please comment.
For all the Seoul citizens who have given...
their precious votes to me,
I will fight against all of these suspicions...
and conspiracies until the end. Please watch me.
Please move out of the way.
Are you saying that you're innocent? Are you?
Please give us an answer.
Why are you so surprised? Did you see a ghost or something?
Are you surprised to see someone...
you thought was dead?
I'm Oh Soo Yeon.
The one you tried to kidnap and murder.
I was wondering who would frame me,
but it must have been you and Gi Tan.
Say that in the interrogation room.
The more you talk about the past,
the better it is for us.
My brother and Gi Tan's parents...
Right, there's one more.
Your late wife.
Once the world finds out what you did to those people,
you'll never...
see the light of day again.
A lawyer...
should be more careful with her words.
You should only say things you can be responsible for.
Okay, Lawyer Oh?
If it's bothering you, sue me for defamation.
That's what I prefer.
That's enough, Lawyer Oh. You'll scare the detective.
Poor thing.
He doesn't have any honour left to be ruined.
How can he sue you for defamation?
Are you going to keep listening to them?
Let's go.
We're late. I have to go see Cho Cham.
Can you find out how it's going at the prosecutor's office?
Why?
We should find out what his prosecutor is like.
Okay. I'll put in a call. Go to the fifth floor...
and ask for Detective Yang Jin Soo.
He's the informant here, so he'll tell you almost everything.
Okay.
Let's go.
Seoul Mayor Byun Il Jae claimed innocence,
but the prosecution is said to have already acquired...
the confession of the independent candidate Cho Cham...
Will Gun Woo be all right?
He has...
the support from the shareholders thanks to Il Jae.
You make no sense.
Why would Gun Woo and Il Jae part ways because of Soo Yeon?
I'm sure of it.
The EGM is around the corner. Gun Woo would never do this.
Anyway,
Gun Woo...
is nothing but a bird without wings.
I just got a call from the secretary's office.
Gun Woo is holding a dinner with the shareholders.
See?
Gun Woo must be nervous.
That's why he's meeting with the shareholders.
Get me the list of attendees for the dinner.
I'll call them myself.
Yes, Ma'am.
Those disloyal shareholders are trying to flatter Gun Woo.
I don't like them.
Even if you don't like them, it's time for a carrot, not a stick.
Don't even think about losing your temper.
The sun is right above us.
What are you scared of? We should say whatever we want.
History changes...
not because of the loyal subjects but because of the disloyal ones.
You'll see.
They'll be the ones that help us take over Dodo Group.
Wow. My mum became so smart...
after becoming the chairwoman.
Do you think your father was so smart to begin with?
The position makes the person.
Mum.
It's Gun Woo.
Where are the shareholders?
They're already in our room.
The shareholders are in a different room.
What do you mean? It was supposed to be here.
Chairwoman Hwang snatched them away.
Where are they meeting?
You all heard that...
Chairman Do can't move around...
without his wheelchair, right?
Is it that bad?
I heard that he'll be participating in the next EGM.
Of course he would like to.
But he collapsed just a few days ago...
and was sent to the hospital.
All right. I won't take long.
Raise your hands if you agree...
on dismissing Vice Chairman Do during the EGM.
Listen.
Can't you see that things have changed?
If you want to extend your contracts, you should be wise.
Well... What about Director Byun?
Director Byun...
had a falling out with Vice Chairman Do.
Is that true?
Why would I make things up?
Vice Chairman Do.
What do you think you're doing?
That's what I'd like to ask.
These people had a meeting with me. Why did you snatch them away?
Do you think...
I dragged them over here?
They came on their own will.
Chairwoman, don't get so upset.
Since Vice Chairman Do is here,
why don't you check?
Is it true that you and Director Byun had a falling out?
Don't bother lying.
It'll make you look pathetic.
It's true.
All right. Let me ask you again.
Raise your hands if you agree...
on dismissing Vice Chairman Do during the EGM.
Hey! Is that up or down?
All right, all right.
We can gather at the EGM with our chairwoman in the lead.
For Chairwoman Hwang!
Vice Chairman Do.
Are you going to stay there?
You're making everyone uncomfortable.
Hey, Gun Woo.
Did you see that?
You're nothing without Il Jae.
Soo Yeon will just use you and abandon you, too.
It doesn't matter what happens between Il Jae and me.
Dodo Group is my father's company and it's where I work.
Are you still lost?
Hey!
Dodo Group is mine. I'm the heir.
Only the people I approve of will be working here.
That's why you should just get lost.
Stop embarrassing the family. Do you understand?
Shouldn't Lawyer Oh know about this?
She should know what kind of trouble you put yourself in to help...
It was my decision so I should deal with it myself.
Don't say anything to Soo Yeon.
Yes, Sir.
Gwi Ja and Gwang Woo.
You should've left while I was still nice.
I couldn't have been taken down like this...
without a traitor inside.
Before that, I have to prepare something.
Money and trust.
- Trust?
-  Without trust,
this scheme will fail.
How much do you trust me?
How much do I have to trust you?
Completely.
Could it be?
Could the traitor be...
Chae Ryung?
You don't have much time, Sir.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Call my father-in-law first.
Yes, Mr Oh.
It's me, Father.
I have a favour to ask you.
Hang up.
Sir.
I have no intention of helping you,
so don't even think about it!
Who was that?
Il Jae.
Father.
Won't you really help Il Jae at all?
I told you, I've abandoned him.
Don't make me repeat things.
Father.
Ma'am.
Let him be alone.
He's like that because he's upset.
Once he calms down, he'll help Mayor Byun.
My father-in-law is treating me like an abandoned child.
I'll go over...
and find out what he's thinking.
Keep your eyes on Chae Ryung, too.
I've always been suspicious of her.
Head over to the interrogation room.
Why are you here instead of the chief prosecutor?
I'll start the interrogation.
Interrogation?
Hey, what's your name?
Park Yeong Sik.
Okay. Prosecutor Park.
Tell your boss, Chief Prosecutor Ko, to come in immediately.
I will tell him about the truth behind the incident...
and teach him what the course of the investigation should be.
Please keep your manners.
You're sitting there as a suspect.
So did Cho Cham say that he got money from me?
Bring him here.
You'll save much of your time if you conduct a cross-examination.
Conduct the cross-examination.
Yes, Chief.
Please, sit.
Please wait.
If you don't like the question,
you have the right to remain silent.
Okay.
You have already...
become his lawyer.
You're quicker than I thought, Lawyer Min.
You shouldn't try anything.
I've already given all the evidence to the prosecution.
Did you say it was a voice recording?
Hey, Mr Cho.
Do you know who reported the voice recording?
It's a man named Kang Gi Tan.
Also, there's a woman named Oh Soo Yeon...
who broadcasted the recording and she works with Lawyer Min.
They're all in this together. How can you fall for this?
See? Wasn't that exactly the same?
I told you he'd say that.
My goodness, you almost said it word by word.
I should be in fortune-telling business.
Mr Byun.
Let's stop sinning.
What?
Do you have...
anything more you'd like to say?
In my opinion,
I think you should keep it...
and say those things in front of the prosecutor.
Excuse me.
I have to get my insulin shot for my diabetes.
Right, of course. Go ahead.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Tell Soo Yeon this.
I will make sure...
to hold the broadcast production crew...
legally responsible for this.
Oh, I should deliver that message to Chairman K...
instead of Lawyer Oh.
It looked like he was already getting ready for a lawsuit.
If not, that's fine too.
Chief.
You should take Mr Byun in custody for the investigation.
- If you get in deeper...
-  I'll take care of that.
Go back to the room.
Yes, Sir.
There was a tip-off that Chief Prosecutor Ko is...
in a close relationship with Il Jae.
If he lobbied the prosecutors with the money...
from his paper company,
he's probably not the only one.
The door is closing.
This is the menu for those Chinese shipowners.
Let Chief Secretary Moon see it.
Aren't you going to check it yourself?
I'm busy.
Anyways,
why are you two together?
It's none of your business.
Why are they together? I really want to know.
Wait, I thought Soo Yeon had a thing with Gun Woo.
Soo Yeon is much prettier in real life than on television.
Did you say Soo Yeon is pretty?
Of course.
And she must be smart since she's a lawyer.
Stop speaking nonsense and find Chief Secretary Moon.
Okay.
My goodness, I really don't like how she's with Ga Din.
It's not the time to stay still, Father.
The man who was bribed turned himself in. What can I do?
You've taken care of incidents that were larger than this.
Will you please help?
Ji Soo.
Have you thought about divorcing Il Jae?
Father.
I don't trust him.
There will come a day when he abandons you.
- So now...
-  You once said...
he was the most precious person to you.
- Ji Soo.
-  You only do what's good for you.
Is this who you really are?
If it was for me, I wouldn't abandon him.
It's all because of you, you idiot.
I don't need your help.
I will step up and save Il Jae.
And...
once this is over, I'm moving out of this house.
My goodness.
Why didn't you tell her that he's having an affair with Chae Ryung?
I don't need to make things worse.
I'll first conduct a background check on Chae Ryung.
It won't be too late to break the news after that.
I'm on my way.
What about you, Mr Moon?
I'll be arriving shortly.
There's a car that's been tailing me.
Hold on.
If you think someone is following, let's meet another time.
No.
I was being too sensitive.
I think I'll be about 20 minutes late.
Chae Ryung is near the intersection.
Where are you?
I found her.
I'll tail her starting now.
I think it's best...
for you to stop being a double spy.
The prosecution will likely investigate him without detention.
If he's released, we don't know what he'll do before the trial.
You probably still need my help.
Il Jae...
must be suspicious of you by now.
This isn't the first time for me to be in a situation like this.
Don't worry about me.
This has a GPS on it.
If you press the side, we can track you.
If you're ever in trouble, send us a signal.
You're really prepared.
Mr Moon!
How is Gi Tan?
He's in touch with Soo Yeon, right? Is he all right?
I heard from Professor Jin.
The chairman wanted to erase his memories about Soo Yeon...
I guess Gi Tan must know by now...
- that it was my doing.
-  I didn't tell him.
Let's just finish this job first.
Thank you.
Sir.
I have evidence that Chae Ryung is betraying us.
Great.
Good job.
Chief Prosecutor Ko.
What are you doing?
Finish your meal first, Sir.
Suspend the prosecution and let me out.
It's too late for that.
Then...
let me out without detention and give me an acquittal at court.
I wish I could,
but I'll be punished by my superiors.
Who? Tell me who.
I'll ruin them for you.
Please.
You were delighted when you took my money, but now you're acting...
like you don't know anything?
Do I look that easy to you?
They can hear you. Please lower your voice.
Tell them to go ahead!
The moment I'm convicted,
there will be many of you leaving here with me!
First,
I'll try my best to get you out without detention.
That's as far as I can go.
Are you...
recording this?
I turned it off.
First, get Kang Gi Tan and Oh Soo Yeon,
and ruin them.
Charge them for tax evasion or lobbying.
If you do enough research, I'm sure you'll find something.
If we can tie them down,
I won't be convicted at court.
That's...
the only way for all of us to survive.
How can I help you?
We're from the National Tax Service. You're convicted for tax evasion.
Tax evasion?
Excuse me.
How can we dodge taxes when we haven't earned anything?
How can you just barge in here and talk of such nonsense?
We need to investigate. Please cooperate with us.
Wait...
What do you think you're doing?
Can you at least tell me who reported us?
Yes, Lawyer Min.
What? Tax evasion?
It's a mess over here.
Do you know anyone that could have reported us?
Yes. I'll come to the office right now.
What do you mean, tax evasion?
I'm not sure. I better go back to the office.
Sir.
There are detectives outside.
Why?
Are you Chairman K?
What is this regarding?
- Are you Moon Tae Gwang?
-  Yes.
The two of you are charged for illegal lobbying. Come with us.
Illegal lobbying? On what grounds?
I can tell who's behind this.
- Pardon?
-  A sudden investigation...
on tax evasion and illegal lobbying?
Are you saying that it's Il Jae's doing?
I'm almost certain about this.
Don't worry and just go back to the office.
Let me make a call.
It's me, Father.
There's a problem with the business.
Look who it is. It's Gi Tan.
Chief Prosecutor Ko, why are these people here?
They were charged...
on suspicion of illegal lobbying.
I'm on my way out after getting my leave without detention.
This is what one's power can do.
I'm not the same man who used to crawl at your aunt's feet.
You're trying to reveal my corrupted doings?
Once I start my term as the Seoul Mayor,
you won't even get to see me eye to eye, Guk Cheol.
Chief. We just received...
a call from the Chinese Consulate.
The charge has been dismissed,
so you may leave.
Are you Chief Prosecutor Ko?
We will be looking into...
this incident in detail.
My apologies.
There must have been a mistake.
What are you talking about?
Power, you say?
I'm not the same Guk Cheol you used to know.
It's an eye for an eye.
I'll put up a good fight,
so get yourself ready.
What happened?
A complaint came into...
the Chinese consulate through a high office in China.
We don't have enough evidence.
If this gets out of hand, we'll be the one in trouble.
I'm glad you're out.
I was hoping you'd come.
You must have read my mind.
I'm sorry, Sir. I should have been more careful.
I just met Gi Tan.
It's not your fault.
It was just because...
his moves were a bit smarter than ours.
It is my fault.
I will do anything for you to receive...
a judgment of acquittal.
I also let my guard down, too.
We can't do this together if you continue to blame yourself.
Honey.
I am sorry that I worried you.
I have something to say to you.
Let's talk.
I have...
advised and warned you many times...
not to cheat in any way.
I have...
nothing to say.
What is...
your relationship...
with Chae Ryung?
You must know...
why I am asking.
It is nothing like...
what you think it is.
Open this.
What will you do...
with Chae Ryung?
Now that I know she's a traitor,
I'll use her for my benefits.
For your benefits?
If we use her well,
she will give us a lot of benefits, too.
This is bad.
The independent prosecutor act has come into effect.
What?
The independent prosecutor act?
The independent prosecutor act has come into effect...
regarding Mayor Byun's violation of election law.
National Assembly's Committee on Ethics decided...
to put this into effect...
to relieve the people's suspicions on corrupt politicians.
What happens after the act has gone effective?
The chairman of the National Assembly...
makes a request to the president.
Then a special prosecutor is recommended among lawyers...
of Korean Bar Association.
The tides are high,
so there will be many big fish.
It's not small enough for Il Jae to cover,
so Jae Man will step up.
What kind of a man is the chairman?
He's known as an honest and an upright man.
He wasn't on good terms with Jae Man since they were representatives.
If Jae Man decides to step in,
he'll approach the chairman.
Do you have any connections?
I can ask the Chinese ambassador.
He can get him to have a meal with me.
Right, there was the Chinese ambassador.
Why don't we eat Chinese tonight?
(Father)
Welcome.
Chairman got here a bit early because there wasn't much traffic.
Thank you.
Please tell the ambassador that I will...
thank him myself.
Sure. Go ahead.
Hello.
I am Kang Gi Tan.
Welcome.
I've heard about you from Ambassador Wang.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
It's fine.
I'm a bit too meticulous, that's all.
It's been a while, Mr Hwang.
Yes.
Sure.
I love how straightforward you are.
Yes, let's meet there.
Sure.
Will he meet you?
We're meeting...
at Buyonggak in two hours.
Can you persuade Chairman Kim?
You two were never on good terms since National Assembly days.
This is possible because he's my enemy.
I know what he likes.
I know everything from his taste to his likes and dislikes.
Whatever we do, we have to stop the independent prosecutor from arising.
Please, Mr Hwang.
I have to stop him before he meets with the president.
Tonight is...
our final chance.
This is it, Father.
Okay.
Father.
Chairman said he had to go to the Blue House early in the morning,
so he asked me to go instead.
Have a seat. We've already ordered.
The independent prosecutor will be appointed as scheduled,
and someone from our side will be appointed.
After this,
Il Jae will receive a sentence of imprisonment.
The problem comes after.
What I want is...
to completely ostracise Il Jae from this society.
Hey, Gi Tan.
I've been giving it a thought on...
why you couldn't just abandon him.
Maybe...
my aunt's death...
has something to do with Congresswoman Hwang.
I thought that could be the one weakness Il Jae knows about you.
Stop speaking nonsense.
How dare you?
So what?
Why...
are you here instead of Chairman Kim?
If you abandon Il Jae,
I will help you...
with your presidential election.
I have nothing against you.
But if we fight because of Il Jae,
that will leave us both with great wounds.
What you're saying is...
that you'll pay me...
to control me around.
Hey, Mr Kang.
I'm the person holding the sword, not the sword itself.
If you can offer yourself as a sword,
I don't think anyone would decline.
But...
if you want to be my sword,
you first...
have to let go of Il Jae.
You'd have to deal with me after you get rid of him, anyways.
Once I have...
the presidency,
what will happen to you?
Revenge will only bring another revenge.
But...
the revenge I have in mind is...
something beyond anything you can imagine.
So you should just...
stop here.
We're beating around the bush.
I don't care if I'm the sword. My opponent won't change.
I just hope...
you won't get hurt by the tip of the sword.
Father, will the independent prosecutor act really be effective?
I'll hold a press conference tomorrow.
Call the press.
For what?
From what I heard,
Jae Man and Il Jae are as good as over.
I guess blood is thicker than water.
By the way,
what you said to Jae Man...
about abandoning Il Jae...
Were you really going to help his presidential election?
The wrong president will bring the country down.
Getting my revenge is important,
but I will never help anyone like him.
You're a patriot.
A special inspection was requested.
I, Hwang Jae Man,
strongly support the need for an investigation...
to find out if Mayor Byun Il Jae really did...
violate any election laws.
Do you believe he's innocent?
Of course, I do.
Why did you arrange this press conference?
If he is to lead Seoul Metropolitan City,
I believe that...
he must be cleared of all suspicions and doubts.
This is what my son-in-law, Byun Il Jae, wants.
He can't divert the current, so he's floating a boat.
Mr Hwang's onboard now.
We can sink them both.
Now that he got involved,
it'll be more than just a raft.
Is Lawyer Oh going to be named the lead investigator today?
She'll be at the Blue House now.
The president will give her the certificate.
Lawyer Oh is the special investigator?
The Bar Association must have recommended her.
I think Lawyer Min's behind it.
Their witnesses will be Cho Cham...
and the antique dealer.
How did Gi Tan...
get his hands on the recording?
Do you think...
there's a spy?
Huaping...
had all sorts of listening devices we'd never seen before.
I should have been more careful. This is my fault.
Apologising won't change anything.
Why did you even start what you couldn't handle...
It was my call.
Don't take it out on her.
Call me as your witness.
Would you really do that?
That won't be necessary.
Honey.
If I say Gi Tan bribed me into helping him,
you won't need any more witnesses.
We need to find a way to silence Cho Cham.
The problem is that we can't.
If all else fails, we can get rid of him.
Don't say something like that.
It just came out. I'm frustrated, that's all.
Don't say what you don't mean.
You'll become mayor once this is all over.
If you take the stand, it could backfire.
Don't give a statement.
Who will defend me?
Lawyer Nam Ji Cheol, a previous High Court judge.
Set up a meeting right away.
Yes, Sir.
She volunteered to be a witness.
Why did you refuse?
Out of concern.
You can't worry about her when you're in this mess.
I'm worried about the trial, not about her.
I don't trust her.
If she takes the stand...
and betrays me, then I will definitely go down.
I thought you were defending her.
We need to silence Cho Cham.
The whole trial hinges on that.
(Ok Chae Ryung)
You meet with Lawyer Nam for me.
Honey.
Who called you?
I'll explain later. Get going.
(Ok Chae Ryung)
What you said earlier. It didn't sound like a joke.
That is the only option...
we have.
We must kill him.
He's in a cell. It won't be easy.
Insulin shots.
Insulin?
Cho Cham has diabetes.
If he's injected with...
potassium chloride instead of insulin,
his heart will go into overdrive.
It's a perfect crime.
You found a way out of this trial.
I wish you victory.
Il Jae is going further and further.
He's trying to kill a witness, too?
You have to protect him.
We can do that.
Thank you, Chae Ryung.
Mr Moon.
During the trial,
put me on the stand as your witness.
Chae Ryung.
If I give a statement,
you will definitely win.
That means you'd have to admit to criminal activity.
I'll go to prison and do time.
That doesn't scare me.
If Huaping finds out you're alive, your life will be in danger...
whether or not you're behind bars.
This is a chance...
to clear my name.
What do you mean?
Il Jae took the MK2 vaccine.
If my statement helps cancel his election,
nothing would please the Huaping more.
What if they don't forgive you?
I'll accept my fate.
I can't spend the rest of my life a fugitive.
I know my boss.
Trust me. Put me on the stand.
(Prison)
Once a day, the prison doctor...
will administer the insulin shot.
I told the doctor to be careful, so they won't be able...
to switch the syringes that easily.
When he isn't with the doctor,
the prison guards will watch him around the clock.
Don't worry.
I explained it all to the witness and told him to be wary.
You don't have to worry.
If they're caught switching the syringes before the trial,
we can add attempted murder to Il Jae's list of charges.
You're very thorough.
You're a great partner.
Are we done?
- Yes.
-  Sir, your next appointment...
Cancel it.
Soo Yeon.
Stay for dinner and a chat.
Sorry, but I have to meet a client.
Why are you lying?
You were on the phone saying you'd go straight home.
I'll be honest, then.
Joining you for a meal would make me feel uncomfortable.
Would the reason for that...
be Do Gun Woo?
If so, then I really can't give in.
Tell the chef to prepare his special.
Sir.
- As a witness at the trial...
-  Is Gun Woo very jealous?
Please don't ask personal questions.
- I won't.
-  At the trial,
we'll add one more witness that Il Jae won't even expect.
Someone to incriminate him.
That's our hidden card.
Who is it?
Chae Ryung will be our witness?
I need you to keep it from the chairman until the trial.
Chae Ryung's...
working for Il Jae as our spy.
Then this whole corruption case...
It was her design.
You and the chairman cut and sewed along the lines.
Thanks to her,
we have a prison uniform...
that will fit Il Jae perfectly.
Who's that hidden card?
The witness asked to remain unknown until the day of the trial.
I can't say any more.
We're on the same side.
I'm a lawyer and a specially appointed investigator.
I have to protect the witnesses.
Now, I'm too curious to eat.
I love meat.
You're pretty when you smile.
- Pardon?
-  It's not a personal question.
Can I say how I feel?
Your smile makes me feel better.
I'd like to see it more often.
Is that too rude?
Sir.
I guess it was.
I'll buy you a drink.
- What?
-  I was rude.
I'll buy a drink to apologise.
I know I make you feel uncomfortable.
I'm trying to get close to you, so don't shoot me down yet.
He's with her again.
Have you ever seen him smile like that?
Never.
Do you think...
they're dating?
Why are you calling me?
Explain why Soo Yeon is having dinner with Gi Tan.
Why are you asking me that?
You and she have sort of a relationship.
Did you know they were meeting often?
Yes.
Really?
They're discussing business, so don't get involved.
Why would they be smiling while discussing business?
I'm too busy to talk about this.
Hey.
You avoided me when I invited you out for dinner.
Now, you're too busy grinning to eat.
It's a post-meeting dinner.
Stay out of it.
A meeting?
I should go.
Soo Yeon.
I have a trial to prepare for.
Thanks for the meal. The next one's on me.
Soo Yeon.
- You can't go.
-  Let go.
Let's have a meeting. Right now.
Shin Young.
We're business partners.
Let's have a meeting.
Then we can eat.
Are you really going to kill Cho Cham?
No fool...
would kill a witness right before a trial.
Then why...
I gave Chae Ryung false information.
I will...
make noise in the east and then attack from the west.
While Gi Tan is obsessing over the syringe,
I need you to travel to the US.
What for, Sir?
Just do as I tell you.
Then I'll come out of the trial...
an innocent man.
Ms Ok.
Do you have some free time?
I was about to go to the office.
Why?
I need to go to the hospital...
and there's no one to drive me.
I will drive you.
Are you feeling unwell?
Anyone my age...
is bound to have a few kinks in the machinery.
Don't say that. I still think you could take down an ox.
- Do you?
-  Yes.
Your hospital is far from the city centre.
It is.
I've been seeing the doctor for many years.
(Haneul Care Centre)
There aren't that many patients.
It's a care centre that doubles as a hospital.
Most of the patients are seriously ill.
Why would you need to come here?
I'm not the one who will be checking in.
I'm here to check you in.
What?
They're ready for her.
You have been...
under a lot of stress trying to help Il Jae.
I set a room aside for you.
Mr Hwang.
A few days' rest...
will make you feel brand new.
Mr Hwang. Why are you doing this?
Mr Hwang. Mr Hwang!
Where are you?
I brought Chae Ryung...
to a care centre.
Don't worry about her.
Prepare for the trial.
I will, Sir.
The doctor says...
you are...
very weak in body and mind.
This is...
illegal confinement.
Right here I have...
a consent form...
with your thumbprint.
You will remain here for treatment...
according to the centre's rules.
Tell me why you're doing this to me.
The charges you framed Il Jae with.
I know you planned it all.
Il Jae will go down if you so much as take the stand.
I can't leave a bomb out in the open.
What will you do to me?
Kill me?
No, no.
I'm not like Il Jae.
I won't break the law.
Even if you sue me once you get out,
no one can charge me for helping a sick person.
Until the trial's over,
stay here, get looked after and rest as well.
What will happen after the trial?
That is up to Il Jae.
What I did isn't illegal.
Sleep well.
Is the trial today?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Sir.
I just got a call from the prison.
Someone tried to kill our witness.
With what?
A syringe.
It must contain potassium chloride.
Have Soo Yeon put him on the stand.
Check what was in the syringe.
Yes, Sir.
Il Jae did what we expected.
Come in.
I got a call from the prison officer...
that Soo Yeon has collected the syringe already.
Today's trial is going to be quite entertaining.
(Court)
Will you be claiming innocence?
Not only will my innocence be proven today,
but I'll reveal all of the crimes made by those trying to frame me.
Who are the people trying to frame you?
That would be them.
What do you think about Mayor Byun's comment?
It's a false accusation. You should charge him for defamation.
Lawyer Oh...
is telling me to sue you.
I guess you'll have one more offence...
to go on your list.
(Monster)
We must save them.
That's the only way we can stop Mayor Byun.
It'll be over if he finds even the slightest weakness.
I'm the chairwoman!
Don't call me Mrs Hwang!
Just watch and see...
how evil I can get.
You'll find out how stupid...
your decision was.
Your Honour.
I would like to call out another witness.