(Episode 36)
Will you be claiming innocence?
Not only will...
my innocence be proven today,
but I'll reveal all of the crimes...
made by those trying to frame me.
Who are the people trying to frame you?
That would be them.
Get them.
What do you think about Mayor Byun's comment?
It's a false accusation. You should charge him for defamation.
Lawyer Oh...
is telling me to sue you.
I guess you'll have one more offence...
to go on your list.
Your call has been forwarded to an automated voice messaging system.
Please leave your message after the beep.
I hope you didn't forget about the trial.
Call me when you see this text.
This is a GPS tracking device.
Send out a signal if anything happens.
(Witness waiting room)
You have to keep your promise.
Don't worry.
This independent prosecutor...
will sentence you as promised.
I was talking to Chairman Kang.
Tell the truth at the court.
I will give you enough money for your family...
to live comfortably in the US.
You all are like Il Jae.
You pretended to be just,
but you've also bribed me like him.
If so, you can just tell the truth without the money.
Do you know what I was relieved about?
The fact that I can reveal the truth at the stake of money.
This is how I narrowly gather and wisely spend.
Stop it, Chairman Kang.
Our witness must be nervous.
Is the result out for the content of the syringe?
- Not yet.
-  It's taking longer than I thought.
You should run over to the NISI with the investigators.
Okay, I will.
Are you okay?
- Pardon?
-  You look rather anxious.
I'll be fine soon.
I need some fresh air.
Sure.
She's never been like this.
She must be nervous because she's fighting against Il Jae.
It's me, Soo Tak.
Can you get some Xanax?
It's me, Il Jae.
I'll make this short.
I don't want to speak with you.
If you hang up,
you'll regret what will happen afterwards for life.
What do you mean?
Shortly,
you will receive a phone call from the US.
You'll find out...
what I'm talking about...
after that phone call.
Soo Yeon.
You're working so hard.
I can't make any mistakes in front of Il Jae,
but I keep forgetting my questions.
Give it to me. I haven't got time.
You've prepared more than enough for this.
I thought I did, but I don't think it was enough.
He needs to be proven guilty in this trial.
Look at my eyes for a second.
Gun Woo, the trial will be...
Calm down and look at me, Soo Yeon.
What are you doing?
Do you remember...
how I asked you to put on my tie when you were my assistant?
With the presentation coming along,
I was really nervous back then.
But when you put that tie on me, I felt more relaxed...
and gained courage.
You'll do great today.
I guarantee it.
Thank you, Gun Woo.
Should I give her the Xanax myself?
I think that would be better.
Lawyer Nam, you can go ahead first.
- You should go in.
-  Okay.
I believe...
I gave you enough chances so far.
I turned a blind eye to things...
while hoping for you to come back to your place.
Gun Woo. You'll realise how foolish...
your decision was today.
I'm fine with that.
I don't care if I make mistakes or even break and tear.
At least that way,
I won't become a monster like you.
A monster?
The real monster is the world, not the person.
Once Dodo Group goes under Gwi Ja and Gwang Woo's power,
you'll see what a monster really looks like.
Did you see that?
Look at that. If his eyes could kill,
he would have killed Gun Woo already.
You're right. By the way,
which side should we be cheering for?
Since it came to this,
it'd be better for Il Jae to be convicted.
That's true. If Il Jae is found guilty,
the two of them will never work together again.
That, too.
But Soo Yeon is their prosecutor.
We should support her fully.
In any case, all we have to do...
is sit back and watch.
Let's enjoy this.
Case number 4958.
We'll start the hearing on the violation of the election law...
by the Seoul mayor.
Prosecution. You may interrogate the undertrial.
During the Seoul mayoral campaign,
you've handed over money to an independent candidate,
Cho Cham, to come to an illegal agreement. Do you admit to this?
I never had an illegal agreement.
Cho has already confessed this to the prosecution.
It's a conspiracy.
2.5 million dollars of bearer bond was found in Cho's secret safe.
Wasn't it given to him in exchange for giving up his candidacy?
He was moved by my campaign...
and decided to support me.
All I did was accept his offer.
You can meet with my aide, who was with me...
when I met with Cho,
to see if I'm lying or not.
Defendant, we're at court.
- If you give false testimony...
-  Prosecutor Oh.
Do you still believe that I'm involved in your brother's death?
Defendant.
It's the prosecutor that asks the questions.
Are you unfairly targeting me...
based on personal feelings?
I said, I'm the one that will ask questions.
Prosecutor Oh, please calm down.
Defendant,
please do not bring up issues irrelevant to this case.
It's related to this case.
Candidate Cho...
might have been asked to do this by someone else's request.
However,
the prosecutor...
never considered the possibility and ruled it out from the start.
Your Honour.
I would like to call Cho Cham as a witness.
Il Jae is putting up a good fight.
By the way,
doesn't Soo Yeon look so cool?
(Witness)
I think the game is over now.
You have received 2.5 million dollars' worth...
of bearer bonds for supporting...
Byun Il Jae during the Seoul mayoral election.
Is this true?
Please answer my question.
Witness.
That...
never happened.
You already confessed during the interrogation.
I was forced...
to confess a lie.
What's wrong with you?
Are you being threatened by him?
Shortly, you will receive a phone call from the US.
Honey. Eun Sol, it's Dad.
Dad.
Honey, today's the trial. Right?
I didn't go because you told me not to...
Don't worry about your wife and your daughter.
I'll give them a tour.
Eun Sol, say bye to your dad.
Bye.
You... Why are you there?
The number is currently turned off. Please leave a message after...
Did you say her name was Eun Sol?
You have a beautiful daughter.
Hey...
What do you think you're doing?
How I'll act...
depends on you.
I'm sure you already know what you have to do at court...
without my explaining it.
Look here, Byun Il Jae!
The man who's currently with your family...
tends to get very violent at times.
I'll see you in court, Mr Cho.
Your Honour. There was an incident this morning...
at the detention centre where our witness almost lost his life.
We have suspicions that the defendant instigated the attack.
I object.
The prosecution is defaming the defendant without any evidence.
We will find out in this very court if I'm defaming him or not.
Witness.
Have you ever felt that your life was in danger?
No.
Someone attempted to murder him with poison in a syringe.
The syringe you're talking about is...
the insulin I take for my diabetes.
Something seems off.
I have a bad feeling about this.
The result from the chemical test to find the components...
of that syringe has arrived.
Prosecutor. What was in the syringe that almost killed the witness?
Announce the verdict.
It was...
his insulin.
Prosecutor Oh,
why did you have to frame me and conduct...
a targeted investigation?
Your call has been forwarded...
Is she still not picking up?
Something must've happened.
Are you sure she didn't change her mind?
That won't happen.
If something did happen, Il Jae is definitely...
Independent prosecutor, you've made a fool out of yourself.
The second trial isn't over yet.
You will never prove me guilty...
because I have never sinned.
Competence lies in winning,
but it also lies in knowing when to give up.
Stop wasting your time...
and order a suspension of prosecution, Prosecutor Oh.
May I have Chae Ryung's mobile number?
I'll chase her from the place of her last phone call.
We'll get some people to find her, too.
I thought things were already over.
I didn't know it would take a turn.
- Mr Moon.
-  Yes, Sir?
Let me ask you a question.
Is Chae Ryung...
our missing witness?
That's what I thought.
Why didn't you tell me?
Chae Ryung...
insisted on helping you.
Who do you think you're working for?
I'm sorry.
Mobilise everyone...
and find her.
You have to find her alive.
Yes, Sir.
Hey, Gun Woo.
How did you know I was here?
You had a lot to drink.
It's because I feel awful...
and angry.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Today's trial is...
all my fault. It's not yours.
What are you talking about?
It's because...
I tied your scarf the wrong way.
- What?
-  It should've been on the right,
not the left.
I'd rather see you smile.
You haven't even brought up Il Jae's illegal slush fund.
You'll win in the end,
so don't worry.
I believe in you.
Have a drink.
No, thanks. I drove here.
I'll take you home,
so have as much as you want.
Have some. I'll take a taxi.
Chairman Do asked me...
to find ways to confiscate...
all the assets which he gave to Ms Hwang.
You're too busy to mind that.
I'll talk to Father and...
I found a way.
You barely had time to sleep.
How did you find that?
Don't you want to know what that way is?
Tell me.
Is that possible?
Yes, definitely.
Did you say your second hearing is in four days?
- Yes.
-  Don't worry, Father.
If the judge doesn't change, he'll be proven innocent.
I won't let my guard down until I'm finished, Mr Hwang.
Ji Soo. Can you bring more wine?
Okay, Father.
What will you do with Chae Ryung?
(Haneul Care Centre)
You should've seen the trial.
Gi Tan took a huge blow from me.
I've benefited much...
by using you against him.
It's all thanks to you, Chae Ryung.
If you're going to kill me, kill me now.
Or else...
You really are a professional lobbyist.
I thought you'd beg for your life.
You know what?
I'm not going to kill you with my own hands.
There's something called a double jeopardy rule.
Once a verdict is given for a specific charge,
it can never be overturned.
Once the trial is over, I'm going to release you...
and let you die in Gi Tan's hands.
That's probably the worst way to die for you.
I've never seen that bracelet before.
This is too uncomfortable. At least set my arms free.
This care centre is strict on its rules.
Especially...
for the patients who have mental problems, like you.
Breathe in and push your legs.
Put more strength on your ankles.
Push them. That's it.
That's good.
That hurts!
You're doing well, Chairman.
Your legs are much more flexible now.
Stop it! It really hurts!
The general meeting is around the corner.
You need to show the people that you are healthy.
Chairman, are you okay?
I told you to stop.
I'm sorry.
That hurts!
That hurts! Come on!
Father, what's wrong?
Hey, Gun Woo.
It's nothing. Don't worry.
This isn't nothing!
You almost ripped my legs apart.
Did you find out who switched your medicine?
- We did.
-  Come on!
I told you not to tell him.
Is it Ms Hwang? Or is it Gwang Woo?
I need to know this before the general meeting.
Who is it, Father?
It was...
Gwi Ja.
My own wife...
tried to kill me.
Show me the evidence.
Do we have a laptop in the car?
Yes, Sir.
- Let's go out and eat.
-  Yes.
What took you so long?
I came as soon as you called.
- Where's the medicine?
-  Here it is.
- These are supplements, right?
-  Yes, Ma'am.
Keep watch.
Leave this to me.
I'll take care of it.
Don't get so upset, Gun Woo.
This is attempted murder. She tried to kill you.
It won't be revenge if you give back what you got.
You have to give them...
a lot more than what they gave you to make it a real revenge.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Gun Woo. There's nothing as unsightly as a family feud.
It doesn't matter who the victim or the perpetrator is.
The world will find...
all of us hideous.
I don't want you to get your hands dirty.
That way, if you lead Dodo Group in the future,
no one will be able to pick on your weaknesses.
I'm not scared of that.
Gun Woo.
If they badmouth me, I'll crush them with my capability.
Watch me during the EGM.
I won't disappoint you.
Make up?
You want me to make up with your dad?
I feel bad for him. He lost his company and his health.
I reached my hand out.
He's the one that declined.
Mum. To be honest,
I want to get along with Dad.
If he was in my shoes, do you think he would ask me to make up?
If it was him, he would watch me shrivel up and die.
He should feel lucky that I'm treating him nicely.
Father, did you go for a walk?
He did.
You don't seem to have an appetite these days,
so I got you some sushi.
- Mr Gong.
-  Yes, Sir.
But this place is really delicious.
You don't know if it's a dog or a wolf until you get bitten.
How is he going to run the company if he's soft like that?
Here.
Try some. It would have been more tasty if you had it earlier.
If you have something to say, say it.
Enough with beating around the bush.
Mr Gong, can you get my dad a glass of water?
Sure.
I've been watching until now,
and it hurts me so much to see you suffer.
I wish you could just...
live in comfort now.
Do you even know...
what makes me comfortable?
This EGM...
is just a formality.
The shareholders already agreed to kick Gun Woo out...
and put Mum as the chairwoman.
So...
please let me take over the company.
I mean... I really intend on taking good care of you.
I don't want to see you get embarrassed by the shareholders...
at the EGM.
You'll take good care of me?
Yes.
I'm confident I can help you live a comfortable life.
Then...
stop your mother from becoming the chairwoman...
and you should resign.
- Father.
-  If you can't do that,
then stop with the act. Forget about trying to be nice!
I've had enough of your sugar-coated nonsense.
Mr Gong.
Throw out this sushi in the garbage.
- Pardon?
-  Throw it out right now!
Father.
Do you really want me to go astray?
You've already gone astray.
I don't care what happens to you.
You should just go back to your mother.
I said, get out!
He acts exactly the same...
as his mother.
What?
You want me...
to live in comfort?
I'm really going to go astray now.
You just watch, Father.
At the location where Chae Ryung disappeared that day,
were there any individuals from Il Jae's side...
that were also there?
From the investigation materials we got,
there wasn't anyone.
How many phones were used within a 100m radius?
There were a total of 89 phones.
- Can I get the list?
-  Here.
Why don't we split it up and call them?
I need to check after, so make sure you record everything.
Okay.
Shall we get started?
You'll reimburse me for the calls I make, right?
Thanks a lot for ruining the mood.
I will, so don't worry.
We have to try and talk to them for a long time.
That'll give us substance.
Who would come at this hour?
Who is it?
Soo Yeon, it's CEO Do Gwang Woo.
We're already busy as it is. Why is he here?
Gosh, he's such an idiot.
I'll be back. Keep working.
Hello?
Is this Yang Ok Ja's number?
No.
Ok Ja! It's me, Hong Man!
I said, it's not me.
I'm sorry. You have the same voice.
Did she change her number?
I'm sorry, but when did you start using this number?
I see.
Why would you come here at this hour?
I was feeling down.
Somehow,
I ended up here.
I'm not your joker.
Why would you come here when you're down?
Don't be like that.
I was so upset that I drank alone.
- I'm busy. You should go.
-  Hey.
I sent you so many gifts. Why haven't you said anything?
Do you know what I went through to pick them out for you?
They're wrapped up, so you can take them with you.
Hey.
Do you know...
how I feel these days?
I'm reminded of you whenever I'm eating something delicious.
I'm reminded of you whenever I see anything beautiful.
I'm reminded of you whenever there is something fun happening.
Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon. Oh Soo Yeon!
All I can think about is you.
If Il Jae...
wins this trial,
he'll give you a really hard time.
Gun Woo has been abandoned by Il Jae and is useless now.
You should think realistically.
I'm the only one who can protect you.
You should go see a psychiatrist.
- What?
-  I only see you as a mad man.
Hey, watch it.
Get treatment.
I hope you'll realise why I despise you so much.
How could you?
I barely controlled myself from going astray...
and came here.
I don't care what happens to you.
Get lost.
Why are you...
saying the same thing as my father did?
I said, get lost.
Otherwise, I'll report you for trespassing.
I guess you still don't realise...
how much of a scary person I am.
What do you think?
Is it good enough for the Chinese shipowners?
Well done.
Do you mean that?
You can do well if you put your mind to it.
Ga Din, are you finally acknowledging my skill?
I wouldn't partner up with someone I don't acknowledge.
Give me any job...
and I'll make your jaw drop.
Why is she here?
You're grossing me out.
It's time for our meeting, Sir.
Come upstairs.
Sure.
The meeting should be with me.
Kang Ga Din. Kang Ga Din!
It's an important meeting. You can see him later.
I should just...
Did you see him change as soon as Soo Yeon came in?
I think you're the one who changed.
- "It's time for our meeting."
-  What?
Nothing.
Gosh.
I wanted to have dinner with him.
Cho Cham wants a new lawyer.
I don't think we can persuade him.
Where is Chae Ryung?
Two of the numbers on the list...
were suspicious burner phones.
One number is no longer listed,
and the other has been turned off for days.
We can't locate it unless it's turned on.
This is bad. The second trial's nearing.
As soon as I get a warrant,
I'll search Il Jae's office.
We have to find proof of his illegal funds...
I have bad news.
Prosecutor Park just called.
The search and seizure warrant was denied.
Who turned it down?
I'll meet him.
Don't.
However bad things turn out, we must stick to the books.
If we slip up now,
the trial's over.
Find Chae Ryung.
She's the only one...
who can stop Il Jae.
I was wondering how you hurt your wrist.
You were trying to escape.
Untying yourself...
won't get you anywhere.
Your lips are chapped.
Here.
You must be very thirsty.
I don't need your pity.
The trial concludes tomorrow.
Once I'm acquitted, you'll be set free.
So don't exhaust yourself.
Drink.
If I didn't find out that you were a spy,
I'd have sold my soul for you.
Of all the women I've met,
you're the most charming...
Of all the men I've met...
you are the worst.
I love your fiery personality.
It's such a pity to think...
it'll die with you.
Sir, Sir.
You're wife's coming up.
Quickly.
What did you say to Gwang Woo?
What?
What did you say to him to make him drink so much?
Mr Gong.
Get her out of here. She's draining my energy.
He's your son.
He's the son we made together.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Gwang Woo...
is your son.
He isn't mine.
What?
Gun Woo is my only son.
The woman whom I loved...
Ma'am, the chairman is in a weakened...
I'm the chairwoman!
Don't call me Mrs Hwang!
All these years,
you've hurt me and I bore it through gritted teeth.
But...
I will not let you...
bully my son.
Remember that if you want to die an old man.
You...
No, Sir. Calm down.
You must hold back. Relax.
That didn't hurt at all.
Right here.
My heart.
It hurts.
I'll get you some cold water.
Now,
I even...
get slapped by my own wife.
Mr Han's here.
Why did you want to see me, Sir?
I don't care...
who you're loyal to or how you rise above others.
But...
your corrupt way of life threatened my father's life.
That, I cannot forgive.
Sir.
I have no idea what you mean.
His medicine.
Sorry?
The ones who swapped his medicines...
were you and Chairwoman Hwang.
In this is a video that shows what you did.
Please forgive me.
I only did what I was told.
No excuse can save you now.
It's attempted murder.
I'm so sorry. Please forgive me this once.
Call the shareholders...
for a meeting in her name.
Sorry?
She can't know about it.
Do it now.
Mr Han.
Why does the chairwoman want to see us again?
Please wait just a bit longer.
You'll find out.
She's running late today.
She's always on time.
Are they all here?
Yes, every one of them.
What are you doing here?
I'm the one who called you.
It wasn't Chairwoman Hwang.
Mr Han, what's going on?
Mr Ko.
Can I ask you one question?
What do you shareholders fear the most?
A drop in the share prices, of course.
What could cause the share prices to drop?
So many things could.
A scandal involving the leader.
What effect would that have on the stocks?
Vice Chairman Do, what are you trying to tell us?
Watch this.
- Where are medicines?
-  In here.
- They're supplements, right?
-  Yes, Ma'am.
Watch the door.
What you saw in that video...
was Chairwoman Hwang swapping out...
her husband's blood pressure medicine.
She wanted his title,
so she did this to get rid of him.
If that video is leaked, Dodo Group's stocks will drop...
beyond point of recovery.
If you agree...
to vote for Hwang Gwi Ja and Do Gwang Woo's dismissal,
lift the glass in front of you.
If just one of you does not,
that video will go viral.
Mr Kim.
Lift your glass.
Do you want to see Dodo crumble?
A toast, then.
To the reinstatement of Chairman Do Choong.
- Cheers.
-  Cheers.
Will you go, Sir?
- What time's the trial?
-  11am.
I'll stop by after work.
Right. How is Chae Ryung doing?
She can't get out unless she can fly or dig underground.
I had a strange dream last night.
If you're calling the care centre, I advise you use the burner phone.
Right.
I forgot.
Hurry up, Nan Jeong.
I'm ready.
Lawyer Oh! Lawyer Oh!
Lawyer Oh!
My investigator friend called. The burner phone's on!
Where was it?
In Hongeundong.
Hongeundong...
Hwang Jae Man lives in Hongeundong.
So it was them.
Let me check.
Hello?
Is this...
Are you Mr Hang Chi Man?
You called the wrong number.
No, it is you.
Chi Man, it's me, Hong Sik.
Your buddy from Yeongdeok.
You called the wrong number.
It definitely was him.
Mr Kim, we just called a burner phone.
Could you tell us where it went that day?
Jae Man kidnapped her?
Yes. According to Lawyer Oh, he went to quite a few places...
that day.
We can't find her in time for the trial.
It seems so.
We can't be sure she's still alive.
Sir.
I located Chae Ryung.
- Where is she?
-  The address belongs...
to a care centre in Yongin.
That's where she is.
She's still alive.
Tell Lawyer Oh to postpone the trial and request a warrant...
Let the trial happen.
- Pardon?
-  Sir.
If we apply for a warrant,
Il Jae will hear about it.
That would put Chae Ryung in danger again.
But we can't enter the centre without a warrant.
We can't bring her back in time for the trial.
There is a way.
What is it?
Call the local police...
and say you witnessed a murder in the care centre.
Make a false report?
- Can you hire a helicopter?
-  Yes, right away.
We'll get there first and wait for them.
Once the police go in,
we can get Chae Ryung out.
I'll hire a helicopter right away.
Tell Soo Yeon our plan.
Yes, Sir.
Thanks, Soo Tak.
Gi Tan thinks he can bring Chae Ryung over.
- Really?
-  He came through in the end.
I told you to drop the charges. You love to hassle people.
Let her be. The embarrassment from last time wasn't enough.
Mayor Byun.
I'll call you that only for the duration of the trial.
Once it's over, you'll lose the mayoralty...
and gain a convict number instead.
Enjoy the sweet dream while it lasts.
All your scheming to bring me down...
has hurt Gun Woo instead.
What do you mean?
He could've become the next chairman if it hadn't been for you.
You just ruined his life.
Don't talk such nonsense. Gun Woo...
See how the general meeting goes.
Both Do Choong...
and Gun Woo will lose their footing within the company.
Don't worry, Soo Yeon.
I'll reinstate my father at the upcoming meeting.
You can focus on today's trial.
You do that. Il Jae just tried to shake you into ruining your day.
Lawyer Min.
Gather the investigators.
- What?
-  Right now. There's no time.
Okay.
You look confident today.
Watch me.
Bring all the canvassers who worked...
for Mr Byun and Mr Cho.
Lawyer Oh, why do you need them?
They'll be my witnesses.
Listen carefully.
In today's trial, we won't be fighting...
Mr Byun or Mr Cho.
We're fighting time.
- Time?
-  Yes.
It's a race against time.
The longer the trial goes, the better our chances.
We lose if it's too short.
Get going.
Why is a helicopter flying that low?
Are you there?
We just got here.
We'll arrive later than I thought. Can you buy us some time?
Don't worry about that. Just bring Chae Ryung.
The police just arrived.
Stay on the phone.
Who made the report?
I did. This call's for you.
- Who is it?
-  Prosecutor Oh Soo Yeon...
who is investigating Byun Il Jae.
Hello, Prosecutor Oh. I'm Inspector Jang Joon Soo.
Sure. Don't worry.
Prosecutor Oh.
The trial's about to start.
We need to be in touch. Keep texting Mr Min.
I will.
- Let's begin.
-  Sure.
It's the police. We're here to investigate.
What's going on?
We received a tip.
A tip about what?
Where is Ok Chae Ryung?
Ok Chae Ryung?
Who's that?
Ok Chae Ryung!
Come back!
Stop!
Let's begin...
the second trial of the allegations against Mayor Byun.
Prosecutor Oh, you may begin.
Your Honour.
I would like to call a new witness.
Did you find a new witness?
Yes.
Can the witnesses come forward?
I found her!
Stop them.
Yes, Sir.
Let me see.
Sir, she's over here!
Mr Moon.
Gi Tan.
There's no time to waste.
We have to go.
- Get up.
-  I told Father about you.
Did he tell you what to do?
He left it up to me.
Without my permission,
don't take such a risk again.
We did not sanction these witnesses.
They were canvassers on Mr Byun...
and Mr Cho's campaigns.
We are looking into whether Mr Byun violated the election laws.
We need their statements.
Prosecutor and defendant.
Come forward.
What are you doing?
We'll need a whole day just to question all those people.
Your Honour.
Not only is the media following this trial,
but the president himself is very interested.
We cannot accept this.
There must be no shred of doubt.
If you refuse to question any of those people,
- then you will face the scorn...
-  Prosecutor Oh.
Are you threatening me?
I apologise.
Return to your seats.
I accept the witnesses.
What is she trying to do?
I'm not sure. If they worked for you,
it shouldn't be a problem.
(Chae Ryung's safe. We'll be there in 90 minutes.)
They got Chae Ryung.
You have to stall for an hour and a half.
It should be over by now.
Il Jae will finally be appointed as the Mayor of Seoul.
I should be here to witness it.
Sir.
Look.
What is it?
What?
Did you just get here?
Thanks to you, I got to rest and recharge my batteries,
Mr Hwang.
Let's see what happens.
Your son-in-law might become the mayor.
Are you saying that...
Mr Cho quit his campaign all of a sudden?
Yes.
Your Honour.
The prosecution is asking the same question 10 times.
That's because the witness could give a different answer.
Don't you think Soo Yeon's trying to buy time?
I don't know. How would I know?
Defendant.
Question your witness.
I'll pass.
Then give your final statement.
Chae Ryung is here. Buy a bit more time.
Hang in there.
Your Honour, I would like to request one last witness.