(Episode 37)
Your Honour,
I would like to request one last witness.
Prosecutor Oh, didn't you finish with your interrogation?
Your Honour,
the last witness, Ok Chae Ryung...
I won't accept any more witnesses.
- The defence lawyer...
-  Your Honour.
Byun Il Jae illegally imprisoned Ok Chae Ryung...
in an insane asylum in order to hide evidence of lobbying.
It's a false accusation.
I swear...
Just two hours ago,
Ok Chae Ryung was imprisoned in a hospital.
I can prove it to you by confirming with the police.
I accept the witness.
In return for giving up candidacy and for supporting him,
Byun Il Jae gave Cho Cham...
2.5 million dollars.
What role did you play in it?
I was the broker who passed on the money...
to the gallery in Insa-dong.
He must have imprisoned you...
in order to keep that fact a secret.
Yes.
By the way, did you tell everyone...
that you were kidnapped by Byun Il Jae as well?
Prosecutor Oh,
what is the witness talking about?
It's the truth.
The defendant kidnapped me...
and attempted to kill me.
It's a lie!
The prosecution...
planned this with the witness...
I'm not finished yet.
Calm down.
You should know better.
But why...
didn't you mention it?
That's because...
She has no evidence. Why else?
I have the evidence.
If you would allow me to stand as a witness,
I'll tell you everything about Oh Soo Yeon's kidnapping.
Get ready...
to cut off the tail.
I'm sorry?
This case has nothing to do with me.
Prepare for anything and everything...
that could happen.
Sir.
It's over...
for Il Jae.
I knew that she was kidnapped,
so I tailed behind.
Byun Il Jae's aide, Oh Choong Dong,
threw her into the river.
Luckily, I was there.
Soo Yeon!
I was able to save her.
All of this is recorded in my car's camera.
If you'd like, I can hand it in right now...
as evidence.
Ji Soo.
Seoul Mayor Byun Il Jae was sentenced to five years in prison.
The defendant claimed that the ruling is unreasonable...
and declared that they would go for appeal.
In addition, Byun's aide Oh Choong Dong...
will also get three years of imprisonment.
Everyone is curious how this case will impact...
Hwang Jae Man of the Hanguk Party.
Did Gun Woo give...
an unfavourable testimony against Il Jae at court?
It was a big hit.
Ji Soo fainted.
I guess this marks an end...
to Il Jae and Gun Woo.
He raised a dog...
and it bit him in the neck.
But for us, they prepared a feast.
Then we should grab our forks.
Should I call Uncle Jae Man?
Let's give him a little breather.
Just because we're hungry...
doesn't mean we should pig out at a funeral home.
I knew this already,
but Gun Woo...
is a complete idiot.
When I saw him testify,
I was so surprised.
My goodness.
Why did you drink so much?
Are you all right?
I'm not all right.
I trust you, Gun Woo.
I think your wife and Gwang Woo...
will meet with Mr Hwang soon.
I just talked to Gun Woo.
He has a plan in store.
I'll trust him.
Chae Ryung got a suspended sentence.
Yes.
I understand, Father.
You're a free person now.
I persuaded Father.
- I should be beside...
-  I know you wanted to leave.
Combined with your asset,
you can probably buy out a hotel overseas.
- Boss.
-  I thought that was your dream.
Do what you want...
and live happily.
Let's go.
Chae Ryung.
Thank you.
My life is yours.
Call me whenever you need me.
You don't have to fake a smile, Uncle.
That won't hide your thoughts.
I told you.
This is just the beginning.
But it seems like everyone's shocked.
This is only the tip of the iceberg.
I won't stay in prison for long, Guk Cheol.
I'm disappointed, too.
You're paying too little for what you've done.
I will get you an expensive one next time.
When I come back out,
you will get a taste of a blazing inferno.
I already have tasted that inferno.
Let me escort you to that inferno.
Great job, Soo Yeon.
I think I deserve to be a part of this.
You do. You helped out big time.
But I was surprised...
that you betrayed Il Jae.
I promised something with Soo Yeon.
We need to make Il Jae rot in prison forever.
What happened to tax evasion documents?
He's clean. He was really ready for this.
Where's evidence on money laundering from his paper company?
I'm looking for it.
Il Jae will soon make an appeal.
If we can't get it until then...
He won't get out that easily.
Chairman Kang and I will make sure.
Isn't that right, Chairman Kang?
Don't worry, Soo Yeon.
I have a favour to ask.
Can you talk to Shin Young...
and make her back up my father during this general meeting?
Why are you asking me?
I heard that you are on good terms with her.
I wouldn't ask you if it wasn't for my father.
I'm not sure if she'll listen,
but I will talk to her.
What is this weird and odd combination of people?
How did you find us?
I asked her to come.
Shin Young, come and have a drink.
Stop drinking. You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
Why do you keep saying that I'm drunk?
You said the same thing that day.
That again!
Will that go on forever?
Kang Ga Din.
Can't you see my glass is empty?
You need to stop.
Shin Young is an awful drunk.
Stop!
You. Don't smile at other girls.
He's mine now.
You. Stay away from him.
I'll kill you if you get close.
She's drunk right now, so don't mind her.
Gun Woo seems to think of you as a business partner.
I don't trust him.
You saw him, too.
He betrayed Il Jae like it was nothing.
I don't trust Gi Tan.
Then why did you ask him for help?
I decided to take the first step.
CEO Do is the one...
who asked Il Jae to kill...
Gi Tan's parents.
He's the one...
who almost killed me by framing me for a murder.
Gwang Woo and Gun Woo are my next targets.
His approaching Shin Young is...
to get to Gwang Woo and me.
Our next battlefield will be the general meeting.
Gun Woo and Gwang Woo...
will be finished in this upcoming general meeting.
Don't worry, Jae Man.
We'll help Il Jae on his appeal with the best lawyers...
in this nation.
He won't be found not guilty,
but he can at least be on a probation.
Is this because of the general meeting?
Yes.
This general meeting is a head-on fight with Gun Woo.
All right. So what do you want?
We just need a piece of paper from Il Jae.
A commission of authority giving over his rights to me...
for this general meeting.
He has a huge amount of shares.
With that commission, we can turn over the meeting...
Don't do it, Father.
Ji Soo.
You never helped us while we were in trouble.
I can't watch them...
trying to be friendly, now that they need us.
We should be taking down Gun Woo.
Aren't you angry with the thought of his rising into power?
You're all the same to us.
- I won't let him sign that.
-  Hey.
Why are you so stubborn?
Do something, Jae Man.
I also understand...
where Ji Soo is coming from.
Uncle.
We can get good lawyers, too.
If you want a signed commission from us,
you should offer something else.
What do you mean?
Ji Soo, if you want something, tell them.
Hand over Dodo Hotel to me.
Wait, that's...
for Shin Young...
You didn't give it to her yet.
If you give me the hotel, I'll get you the commission.
Hey, Congresswoman, aren't you a bit too selfish?
Forget about it then.
Let's go, Father.
It's a deal.
- Mum.
-  We need the management rights.
I'll give you the hotel. Bring me the signed commission.
Sounds good.
It's me, Mr Han.
Great job, Mr Han.
Request a meeting with Il Jae.
Yes, Sir.
How can you do this?
Why are you eating by yourself? We should eat together.
How dare you think about sharing a table with him?
You can eat when he's done.
Got it, you criminal?
Okay, Sir.
4984, you have a visitor.
Are you going to stand there all day?
Or do you want me to get up?
I thought you'd try to avoid me forever.
This is rather earlier than I imagined.
There's something I realised after meeting you.
You can never win if you play...
by someone else's rules.
So?
Are you going to make the rules?
If you take a look at this,
you'll understand what I mean.
Tax evasion, embezzlement and money laundering.
You committed every illegal crime possible when running a business.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I learned all this from you.
The document...
you passed onto Soo Yeon was just the tip of the iceberg.
Why didn't you...
give her everything?
They threw in their nets already.
There's no need for me to waste my energy.
I'll save it to catch the whale later,
just like what I'm doing now.
What is it that you want?
There are two things.
Give me the recording where I admitted that I'm a murderer.
What else?
B World.
What?
I'll give you handsome money for it.
Hand it over to me.
You have to do it before the EGM.
If I don't hear anything until then,
all those documents will be sent to the prosecutors' office.
Once that happens,
your appeal and your life will be over.
I guess...
I failed to recognise...
my true enemy.
The enemy you know about isn't your true enemy.
I hope you like...
the rules I've made,
Chairman Byun.
Did something happen?
I told you, you stupid.
Did you just laugh?
Pardon? No.
I'll kill you!
I'm sorry.
How dare you laugh at me?
Do I look like a joke to you?
Die! Just die!
- Please stop.
-  Let me go!
- Chairman Byun!
-  Die!
Please stop.
Calm down.
Who was the visitor?
I was fooled by Gun Woo.
He got me good.
He came to visit you?
I don't get him.
I don't know how much of it is true...
and how much of it is fake.
I have no idea.
I can't get a grasp on him.
Yes. I'll come and get you, Soo Yeon.
Okay.
Let's go to Min and Oh Law Firm.
Okay. By the way, Sir.
You allowed Lawyer Oh and Gi Tan to meet before.
That was on purpose.
How do you know my name?
What's wrong, Gi Tan?
We were...
I knew that he had...
a bullet in his head.
I made them meet on purpose.
That's the only way...
Soo Yeon will give up him.
I did it to win Soo Yeon.
I'm going...
to make her mine.
Sir.
One of our guards at the prison called me.
Apparently, Gun Woo came to visit Il Jae.
What did they talk about?
They used a special visiting room, so they have no idea.
I'm sure he went to make a deal or a threat.
Either way,
it means the two of them will partner up.
Call Shin Young and ask her for lunch.
Yes, Sir.
Are you finally going to use her?
The tide's coming in faster than I thought.
We better get our ship ready.
Quit drinking.
No.
If you don't, I won't do business with you.
You're so childish.
Fine, let's talk business.
But...
let me ask you one thing beforehand.
If you were planning to work with me,
why did you sign with Gun Woo for the Chinese ships?
That was the best question...
you've ever asked me.
Really?
Then give me your best answer.
It costs a fortune...
to win the bid for building a ship.
But the banks won't let you...
get insurance since it's too risky.
- That's why we...
-  Too complicated.
Simplify it for me.
What he's saying is,
people will get on the ship thinking it's a cruise ship.
But in fact, it's a very dangerous one.
We never know when it'll sink.
I see. You're making...
Gun Woo proceed with the ship contract...
and then make him sink along with it?
Bingo.
There's something you have to do before then.
What is it?
Do you have shares to Dodo Pharmaceutical?
Of course. It's Dodo Group's holding company.
There's something called Shareholders' Voting Agreement.
You should sign it.
Shareholders' Voting Agreement?
Yes. It's an agreement to prove that those shares...
can be managed by the both of us.
Are you a thief?
Why should I share that with you?
I'm not asking it for free.
Which affiliate are you most interested in?
Are you going to get it for me?
That's how deals work.
I want Dodo Hotel.
I want to make it mine.
It's my dream to turn it into a global hotel.
It's not a dream.
I'll make that hotel...
yours.
All right.
Then I'll sign the agreement.
In return,
you have to sign...
a memorandum for me.
All right.
Mr Moon, could you prepare the documents?
Yes, Sir.
(If Kang Gi Tan fails to keep his word, he must marry Do Shin Young.)
What's written on there?
If I don't keep my promise,
I have to marry Shin Young.
No matter how important business is, you shouldn't put your life on...
May I get this notarised?
Of course.
Sir.
Don't worry. Things will proceed as planned.
This is the Shareholders' Voting Agreement. Please sign it.
We'll be on the same team for the rest of our lives, Ga Din.
Call Gwang Woo right now for a meeting.
Are we starting already?
We're running out of time. Mr Moon, you can meet Gun Woo.
Yes, Sir.
Oh, yes, Shin Young.
Are you ready?
What?
Does he want to meet me?
Oh, okay. I'll be there.
Mum, Gi Tan wants to meet me.
Really?
It looks like Shin Young successfully lured him in.
She has an awful temper,
but she's good with men.
Il Jae's on our side, and now, it's Gi Tan.
You look glad, Chairwoman.
My victory day is coming soon. Why wouldn't I be glad?
We won't know if it will be victorious or disastrous for you...
until the day comes.
I heard you're busy gathering shares.
No matter how hard you try, the scale won't get turned over.
They're all in vain.
Everyone has their own scale.
If it's set as they please, they'll believe it as it is,
not realising that it's broken.
People are foolish, you know?
That's what I want to tell you.
Please...
throw away your broken scale.
Don't embarrass Father because of you.
You don't need to speak to him.
- Let's go, Gwang Woo.
-  Okay.
What time was our meeting with Mr Moon?
You can leave right now.
Hey, Gi Tan.
I mean, Chairman Kang.
I was going to say hello when we were at court.
We have a lot to talk about.
Let's do that later.
Yes, business first.
Take a seat.
What's wrong with your eyes? Why are you twitching them?
Oh, I have something in my eyes.
Does he want to exchange stocks?
Yes.
We'll exchange Dodo Hotel's stocks, held by Chairman Do,
and CEO Do Shin Young's stocks for Dodo Pharmaceutical.
But why are you here to step into this problem?
Chairman Kang and CEO Do Shin Young...
signed the Shareholders' Voting Agreement.
Half of the stocks for Dodo Pharmaceutical are...
Chairman Kang's.
Management rights will be decided with stocks for Dodo Pharmaceutical.
I don't understand why she'd want to exchange those.
CEO Do Shin Young is more interested in the hotel...
than the management rights.
Chairman respects that.
What? Are you giving me all of your stocks for Dodo Pharmaceutical?
It's not for free. I want to exchange it with your hotel shares.
I'd be so thankful if you would do that.
I knew you'd be the one who'd look out for me.
You should thank him.
Chairman K is the one who persuaded me.
Thank you, Chairman Kang...
for supporting us.
What's the exchange rate?
The price differences are like this.
For 100,000 shares of Dodo Pharmaceutical,
it's reasonable to give you 200,000 shares of Dodo Hotel.
Are you kidding me?
It should be more. That's the holding company.
I'm saying that's what the price is, Shin Young.
I'll throw in another 50,000.
I'll exchange 100,000 for 250,000 shares for the hotel.
It's me, Mr Moon.
How much did CEO Do Gun Woo offer?
What? Gun Woo?
Is Gun Woo in this, too?
Okay. Don't hang up.
He offered 300,000 shares per 100,000.
What? Did he say 300,000 shares?
Okay, then. I'll add another 50,000.
It's 350,000 shares for me.
You don't even have that.
Mum has some.
Gun Woo is saying that with Father's shares, too.
I'm not backing away!
He just offered 350,000 shares.
Gwang Woo offered 350,000 shares.
You wanted to get the highest price by putting us against each other.
You should hold back a fight and bargain on businesses.
That's what business is, isn't it?
I'll give you 400,000 shares and no more.
He's offered 400,000 shares.
Gun Woo offered 400,000 shares.
What? He must be insane.
I know it's the holding company,
but there are lines.
How much more do you want?
He won't give up. The general meeting is right around the corner.
Mr Moon.
- It looks like he's giving up so...
-  I'll give 500,000.
I'll give you 500,000.
Let's make it 5 to 1.
Are you serious?
Mum will be so mad.
This is about the management rights.
I can't give it up.
Tell Gun Woo that we're sealing the deal with this one.
Yes, Sir.
He gave up 500,000 shares.
Things are overheating. We should end things here.
I'll give you 550,000 shares.
I will talk to Chairman.
Forget about the past. Let's walk to our bright future, Chairman Kang.
Anyways, if you two are holding a joint agreement,
are you two by any chance...
We don't have that kind of relationship.
That's why relationships are called relationships.
They get all tied up and get very confusing.
Sometimes they become something, don't they?
You should leave if you're finished.
Okay, Shin Young. I'll get going.
Help Chairman out with his business...
and be nice to him, okay?
You're a genius.
You just got five times as much.
I'm really amazed.
Just follow me. You'll become the first in line of Dodo Group.
Kang Ga Din.
Be careful, Chairman.
For what?
Those people are eyeing us in strange ways.
Don't worry about those trash.
- Where are you going?
-  To the restroom.
- I'll take you there.
-  2757!
What is it?
Honey.
Wait. What...
Hello, Sir.
What happened?
It was nothing.
Don't say that.
Let me see. Is it bad?
I'm fine.
Were you attacked?
Yes.
By whom?
The wardens said they're men...
who held a grudge against me...
from my days as a prosecutor.
But I don't remember them.
Then the one who did this to you...
It has to be Gi Tan.
It's too dangerous here.
I'll apply for a transfer.
It'll be the same anywhere.
I'm safer here.
Hang in there.
We'll win the appeal...
and get you out of here.
Thank you.
This is from...
Chairwoman Hwang Gwi Ja.
She wants you...
to sign over...
your Dodo Pharmaceutical shares.
We'll take Dodo Hotel instead.
We're giving up on Gun Woo, so this works for us.
Do you really think that Gwang Woo and Chairwoman Hwang...
can beat Gun Woo...
at the general meeting?
What do you mean?
It's practically a done deal.
Gun Woo is...
more cunning than...
I ever imagined.
Why?
Did something happen?
I can solve it...
once I get out.
You don't have to worry.
(Power of Attorney)
Welcome, Sir.
Did you find a way...
to confiscate everything I gave my wife and Gwang Woo?
Have a seat first.
Ms Hong, bring some tea.
- Yes, Sir.
-  Forget the tea.
Tell me. What's the plan?
When you gave your wife the shares,
she signed a contract.
If any of her actions are the cause for divorce,
you can take back everything you transferred to her.
Was there such a clause?
Yes. See for yourself.
That's right.
I remember now.
What your wife did after you collapsed...
is grounds for divorce.
As her son,
Gwang Woo will also have to give up his assets.
Put things in motion.
At the general meeting,
I will crush them both.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Civil cases take time.
It can't be done by then.
That's too bad.
After the general meeting,
apply for a warrant...
of provisional attachment.
Yes, Sir.
Father.
Can you organise a family meeting as soon as possible?
What for?
I want to confirm something.
Why is a sick man always out and about?
Don't say that.
Can't you try to be nice?
You're the one who verbally abused me.
We wouldn't be in this mess if you were nice.
Tonight,
call the kids over.
What for?
To write a will?
Before the general meeting,
we need to get our stories straight as a family.
Or else,
everyone will find out what a mess we are.
Are you trying to save face?
To rich people like us,
our reputation is our brand, you foolish woman.
Who are you calling foolish, you senile, old rat?
Mr Gong.
Start looking for a house.
What for, Ma'am?
Once the general meeting's over,
I will kick you both out of my house.
Find a place before then or you'll end up on the streets.
She's going too far.
First, she slapped you.
And now, she's kicking...
I told you not to mention that.
Sorry, Sir.
Find a place.
A small and run-down place.
Pardon?
That hag and Gwang Woo...
will need to move out...
after the general meeting.
Yes, Sir.
I can't believe...
you're attending our family gathering.
Our father invited her...
as Dodo Group's legal counsel.
Will her presence change anything?
It won't, so don't mind her.
Welcome, Chairman Kang.
Hi, Mum.
How have you been?
Money really does change a man. You look so much more handsome.
Thank you.
Where is Dad?
He'll be here soon.
Have a seat.
Sir.
What are you doing?
I was hungry.
The others are downstairs waiting for you to join them.
What for?
Is it someone's birthday?
Didn't you tell everyone to come over?
Did I?
Right.
I did.
It's a very important day.
Sir. Sir.
Sit in the wheelchair.
That's right. I forgot.
Let's go.
Come on, push me.
If you're too tired, you can postpone...
I'm fine. Take me downstairs.
I called you all...
so we could...
go through the details...
before the general meeting.
Everything's sorted. What's left to discuss?
- Jae Man.
-  Yes.
My son-in-law signed this.
This power of attorney states that he'll transfer his shares...
to Chairwoman Hwang.
Don't worry, Father.
Shin Young's shares of Dodo Pharmaceutical...
That deal's been made already.
I'll be getting those tomorrow.
This isn't what we agreed on.
I thought the deal with you would stand, but...
Gwang Woo's terms were better.
Business is about profit.
It can't be helped.
Sorry, Dad.
Mum said that...
she'd give me Dodo Hotel.
What does she mean?
You said it would be mine.
It turned out a little differently.
I'll give you the golf course in Yongin instead.
A golf course isn't a hotel.
You can't have Il Jae's power of attorney.
- Ji Soo.
-  Add to that...
the home shopping channel.
Jae Man, the home shopping channel...
I want that instead.
That might be enough to placate me.
Mum, isn't that a bit too much?
Be quiet.
Fine. The golf course and the home shopping channel.
Someone wants to make his illegitimate son his heir.
What wouldn't I do for my own flesh and blood?
Hey!
All of you.
What are you doing with my assets?
Every company in Dodo Group...
I built up from scratch!
How dare you?
What makes you think you can split them among yourselves?
Do you still think they're yours?
You're wrong!
Everything will become mine...
at the general meeting!
The meeting hasn't happened yet.
Don't celebrate before the fight even begins.
That's just foolish.
We're celebrating because we can.
We're used to partying.
Did you see this?
Other than you and I, the rest are like hyenas.
What? Hyenas?
I'll toss them some rotten meat and sort them out.
Don't you worry.
I think I should leave.
Already? You haven't eaten yet.
You can take your time.
Gi Tan.
I guess you don't keep your private life and work separate.
It's a business transaction. Watch what you say.
When it comes to business, I'm the better catch.
Gwang Woo, don't get ahead of yourself.
I did it to benefit Shin Young, not to help you.
Let's go.
If this is it,
we should leave, too.
Okay, Dad.
Jae Man.
What did you bring as my birthday present?
Don't tell me...
you came empty-handed.
Bok Shin, go and get...
the birthday cake.
Right now.
What cake?
Today's my birthday.
I'll cut the cake...
and blow out the candles.
You were born in the winter.
What are you talking about?
You cooked me birthday soup.
Thank you so much.
Father.
Gwang Woo.
Go and get your grandmother.
Let's eat.
What's wrong with you?
Get the cake.
When did this start?
He'd been a bit forgetful, but it was never this serious.
Wasn't he tested when he was last admitted?
The doctor said he was fine.
What happened to him then?
It must be the drug's side effect.
Side effect?
The doctor said this could happen if the drug doesn't suit him.
Is he on his way?
He'll be here soon.
It won't be dementia.
No?
To me, it looked just like dementia.
The test he got a few days ago came back clean.
You can't be sure. Have him tested again.
If we can have him ruled mentally incapable,
we could take...
everything under his name.
That family is much more twisted than I thought.
It's gotten worse than when I was Chief Secretary.
I'm glad we were there.
I got to see the family for what they're really like.
They all have different ideas. That leaves us with many openings.
I think...
we can push ahead as planned.
Don't worry, Gun Woo.
He won't give in just like that.
The general meeting's the problem.
Now, Gwang Woo owns Shin Young's Dodo Pharmaceutical shares.
My chance of beating them is now much slimmer.
If I lose,
Father will suffer even more.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to be of help to you.
Gi Tan hates me...
and I understand.
I was duped into it by Il Jae,
but I played a part in framing him for murder.
Stop. You've had enough to drink.
I'd like to be alone tonight.
Mr Kim.
Take her home.
Yes, Sir.
You don't have to. Look after him instead.
Don't drink too much.
Why didn't you tell her you have a plan B?
Do you know...
what the hardest thing in the world is for me?
It's to make a woman love me.
I need a strategy.
A plan to make Soo Yeon...
side with me completely.
It's me, Soo Yeon.
I'd like to meet you.
It's a bit late.
Have a seat.
I came to ask you for a favour.
Go on. Any request from you is worth hearing.
It's about Shin Young's shares of Dodo Pharmaceutical.
Can you give them to Gun Woo?
He feels terrible...
for what he did to you.
He even betrayed Il Jae, knowing what a loss it would be.
It wouldn't have been a loss had I helped him.
- Sir.
-  I'm a businessman.
I do the math.
I showed you favour...
because I thought we were on the same page.
The loss of a sibling hurts.
Gun Woo wouldn't know, but I do.
You're soft-hearted so I understand why you're doing this.
But Gun Woo isn't the good man...
you think he is.
If you ask for such a favour again,
I will cut all ties with you.
I think a lot of them still want you dead.
Guk Cheol.
You tried to kill me...
when I was in prison, too.
Was it another nightmare?
Gi Tan now tortures me in my dreams, too.
4984, the superintendent wants to see you.
What for?
Did you ask to be transferred?
I did not.
Maybe your wife did.
- What's going on?
-  I'm sorry.
Mr Do wouldn't stop begging.
Bring them some coffee.
The general meeting's in two days.
You gave your shares to Gwang Woo.
Did you actually think I would help you?
Can I release the evidence of your embezzlement?
Sure.
I have a lot on you to give to the media.
So we both go down?
The more you have to lose, the weaker you become.
I'm in here, you're out there.
Who has the upper hand?
Let me tell you one thing.
Even without any of your shares, in this general meeting,
I will win.
What I really want is B World.
Your company.
Don't even dream of it.
Even if a knife's at my neck,
I won't give it to you.
The knife is already in your neck.
What?
The coffee...
you just...
took a sip of.
Soon,
you will...
fall asleep.
And I will have your thumbprint on every page of this contract.
You can't...
take my company with a forged document.
I will...
not let that happen.
Listen carefully before you pass out.
You can't do anything. Why not?
You'll be in solitary confinement tonight.
While you're in there, your company will become mine.
And the game will be over.
You...
You can't...
Hold him down.
You can't do this to me.
I... I made you what you are now.
That's why...
you shouldn't have touched Soo Yeon.
Didn't I warn you?
I said you'd make your worst enemy.
Do Gun Woo...
You took from others all your life.
How does it feel to lose something?
Gun... Gun Woo...
Did you pay them both?
Yes.
You can split it.
Put him in solitary confinement from now on.
Hello, Father.
What?
Okay.
What did he say?
The MK2 vaccine.
They got it patented in Korea and America.
Then B World's influenza vaccine will take a huge hit.
If we sell ours at half price,
we could ruin them for good.
Is Il Jae in solitary confinement?
Yes. According to our contact there,
it was Gun Woo's doing.
- Can I meet him?
-  It's against the rules,
but the superintendent won't be able to say no.
Apply for a visit right away.
You shouldn't have touched Soo Yeon.
You took from others all your life.
How does it feel to lose something?
4984. You have a visitor.
How are you?
This brings back memories...
of the day you visited me.
I enjoyed the pizza you brought so much.
I'll return the favour.
Have some.
(Monster)
I gave you a clear warning.
Do you think I did it?
Marry me, Soo Yeon.
Stop Gun Woo from going to the banks.
It's me, Gun Woo. Your father's acting weird.
Chairman Do Choong...
has dementia.
Cut your poor and useless son-in-law off.
Kang Gi Tan.
This is the last opportunity to avoid going against me.