(Episode 38)
You look beat up.
Who was it?
Who beat up the Seoul mayor?
If I tell you,
are you going to get them back for me?
Of course.
How dare they touch my precious meal?
Was it Gun Woo?
I guess I got it right.
You must be really hurt...
to get stabbed in the back.
I know very well how that feels.
I've been betrayed by people before, too.
How did you get stuck in solitary confinement?
Seoul Mayor is now in solitary confinement...
Your life is so pathetic.
It's too early for you to celebrate. Don't make me laugh.
Do you know why a food chain exists?
It's not because the weak committed a crime.
That's just how the food pyramid is built.
Money and power determine who goes to the top of the pyramid.
I've let my place go for a moment,
but I still have power left in me.
I'll be out soon, Guk Cheol.
B World.
Your goose that lays golden eggs...
will soon be put to death.
I'm going to eat that goose, and that will be the end of it.
Your supporter Hwang Jae Man will abandon you without B World.
I'm curious to see how you'll get out of jail.
Enjoy, Uncle.
This is...
my last goodwill to you.
Kang Gi Tan...
Do Gun Woo!
Mum, what do you think about this jacket? It's for today's meeting.
I think it's the new blood pressure medication he started taking.
What's wrong with the new medication?
It doesn't seem to suit him. Also, the stress must have...
caused a temporary mental derangement.
By temporary, do you mean that he'll be back to normal?
Of course. It's not dementia, so please do not worry.
Can he still attend the general meeting?
I think we should wait and see when he wakes up.
Mum.
Come on, what do you think? Is it too much?
Tell your father to come out for his meal.
Are you going to make him food?
I need to check how he's doing.
Okay. All right.
Do you think...
you can attend the general meeting today?
I have to go.
I won't do you a favour by not going.
Dr Hwang was right.
Why does he have to be normal today?
You're not very well.
I think you should rest today.
Are you telling me to just sit and watch...
while the two of you try to steal my money away?
That's not what I meant. I was just worried about you.
When this general meeting is over, you two will get...
what you deserve!
Go ahead.
No one will care about you even if you come.
Mr Gong.
Why isn't Mother eating?
Father...
Go and get her right away.
I should greet her before I'm off to work.
Chairman...
Your mother...
didn't want to eat because there's no meat today.
Why didn't you make any meat dishes?
This is the reason why I'm always being scolded!
I'm sorry, Honey.
We ran out of meat today.
Go and buy some meat right now.
If you don't, I won't let you...
step inside my house!
Did you see that?
This is how your father treated me all these years.
He treated me like a maid and a slave.
He was arrogant and commanding.
We won't have to worry about today's general meeting.
Let's go.
Okay, Mum.
She's gone. You should finish your meal.
That witch.
How can she treat my mother like that?
- I told you, she's gone.
-  This is a problem.
I'm going to take Mother out for a meal.
Go and get prepared.
Sir, your mother passed away.
What are you talking about?
I just said goodnight to her last night!
Weren't you putting up an act?
Your mother died 20 years ago.
What do you mean my mother died?
Sir.
She suffered so much.
I was going to treat her well now. What do you mean she died?
No, Sir. I'll go and get her right away.
Good.
I knew it.
You were...
just joking, right?
Yes. I'm sorry, Sir.
Hurry.
Go and get Mother. Go on.
It's me, Gun Woo.
The chairman has really gone strange.
I don't think it's temporary.
Are you sure it's not dementia?
Why would I lie to you?
Then what is this shot for?
It's a kind of sedative to reduce your anxiety.
You can attend the general meeting since you got the shot.
I knew it. It's impossible...
to get dementia at this age.
Please rest up.
The general meeting is at 4pm today, so rest up until then.
Who else has seen the video...
of her switching pills?
Just the shareholders on our side.
I guess it won't be leaked then.
Gun Woo.
What's your plan?
You know that your father won't be at the general meeting, right?
Didn't Mr Gong call you?
He's on and off. It's impossible for him to leave home.
How can we let him be the chairman in that condition?
I don't need him there, so don't worry.
You're still so proud, aren't you? You're just like your father.
How disgusting.
- Did you find yourself a house yet?
-  What house?
Father told me that he told you to move out.
I guess you didn't start looking yet.
How did he even remember to tell you that?
Your mum's life came to an end because she trusted him too much.
You should find another way to live, too.
You're so pathetic and poor.
Goodbye.
I guess today is...
the last day I'll see you.
Right now,
we have 4 hours and 47 minutes until the general meeting.
Do you want to resign beforehand?
If so, I'll give you a lot of severance pay...
so that you can live the rest of your life doing nothing.
It's detestable...
to see a broken family like us.
You can find a way to live,
the company will be saved...
and our home will regain peace.
How does that sound?
Do you want to resign?
We have 4 hours and 46 minutes left.
If you give up before that,
I'll let you keep your position as a CEO.
Do you have earplugs stuffed in your ears?
You seriously have trouble understanding.
You idiot.
Gun Woo may have played that well, but I know he is...
probably frustrated.
You know what?
Maybe I should have...
become the chairman...
instead of backing Mum.
Gun Woo...
sent me a video.
What?
- Are these supplements?
-  Yes, Ma'am.
Take watch.
Hey, why did you send me this video?
Take a look.
That's her...
switching Father's blood pressure medicines with vitamins.
What in the world are you talking about?
You should ask Mr Han to clarify...
what in the world you just heard.
Did Mum switch Dad's blood pressure medicine?
It's true.
That little...
Hey, get him.
My gosh, I'll get you.
My goodness. This is frustrating!
Hey.
What will you do with that video?
What do you think?
Gun Woo.
Don't do anything rash.
I'll send our dear Ms Hwang Gwi Ja to prison.
She tried to kill my father. Did you think I'd let her go?
Hey, stop joking.
If you were going to send her to prison,
you wouldn't have shown me that video.
It's something that happened within our family.
Let's make this look good.
- Mr Kim.
-  Yes, Sir.
(Commission of General Meeting Attendance)
That's a document saying that you're giving your shares to me.
Sign that paper.
There aren't heaters in prison.
I thought our dear Ms Hwang Gwi Ja can't take the cold.
Once this video goes public,
your life will be over, too.
I'm making this offer...
Go ahead.
Tell everyone about this.
Are you keeping your shares over your mum?
Hey.
If you let this go public,
do you think you'll be fine?
Not only you,
but Father will be done for for ruining the company's image.
Sure then.
I'll get to become a chairman, thanks to you.
You should be careful, too.
I didn't know he would react in such a way.
Father, Gwang Woo turned down our offer.
I'll release the video during the general meeting.
You can't do that, Gun Woo.
They're taking drastic measures. We have to end this.
You'll ruin the company.
Father.
Not only the company, but you'll be in danger, too.
I'll take care of this.
You can back out now.
Please gather as much asset as you can.
Are you going to buy out...
Dodo Pharmaceutical's shares?
It's a close fight.
I need at least one more share than them.
We have only two more hours left.
Get everyone on SPD...
and buy out any shares of Dodo Pharmaceutical.
Yes, Sir.
He's here.
Tell him to come in.
Yes, Sir.
Will Gun Woo publicise that video?
He can't.
Father wouldn't want the company to go down.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Gun Woo showed that video to the controlling stockholders.
- What?
-  They have already...
sided with him.
How can you tell me that now?
I'm sorry.
He threatened to send Chairwoman Hwang to prison.
In this case, there is no guarantee that we'll win.
That's the case for them, too.
Chairwoman Hwang. No, Mum.
Mum.
Did Uncle really say weird things again this morning?
Exactly.
Anyways, he can't be at the general meeting.
Are you sure that he doesn't have dementia?
Doctor Hwang stopped by yesterday.
He said it's only temporary.
I thought he went to the hospital today.
You should check yourself, Aunt.
Doctor Hwang, it's me.
Was my husband at the hospital today?
Did you give him a check up?
I did and he does have dementia.
It is dementia?
Yes, he definitely has dementia.
My goodness.
Can you come...
and testify at the general meeting?
Thank you, Doctor Hwang.
The whole world is for me.
I should go to a church or a temple to make some donations.
Mum! Mum!
Mum, this is bad.
We need to gather as much money as we can...
to buy out shares.
What are you talking about?
Well... That's...
I'll explain later.
Just give me the money!
What?
Ms Hwang believes me.
Thank you for lying.
She just asked me to come to the general meeting.
That sounds good.
I was going to take you, Anyways.
It's almost time. You must go.
(Dodo Pharmaceutical)
Chairman!
Dodo Pharmaceutical's shares are suddenly sky-rocketing.
Gun Woo must be buying them out.
It seems like they took the bait.
Now, all we have to do is bomb that ship and make it sink.
- Mum.
-  Hello, Shin Young.
- Hello, Chairman Kang.
-  It's nice to see you again.
You and I...
need to talk.
My son-in-law...
was beaten up in jail.
Do you think that was my doing?
There aren't very many...
that dare to touch Il Jae.
I'm curious to know who those few are.
Are you saying that it wasn't you?
If I do the same thing Il Jae did to me,
that wouldn't be revenge.
My revenge...
will be more beautiful...
and classy.
I gave you my warning.
I told you to let go of Il Jae.
You have a great set of lawyers lined up.
I admit, I was amazed.
If he gets probation or acquittal, your name will be added...
to my hit list.
The day his mayoral position was nullified,
you already went on my hit list.
I guess one of us will have to disappear then.
You're holding the key right now.
If you give up on the revenge,
there won't be any fights.
What should I do?
My fight already started.
I ate dog food when I was a homeless.
I will never forget its taste.
That's why I plan on letting Il Jae try some.
Do you understand what I'm talking about?
I'll turn...
Il Jae into a homeless.
He'll be poor and useless.
Just abandon him then.
That's the only chance you can avoid...
a fight with me.
(The 32nd Dodo Group's General Meeting)
Why is my seat here instead of over there?
You sold all of your Dodo Pharmaceutical shares.
What about my uncle?
Byun Il Jae must have delegated the rights.
It hurts my pride to sit here. I can't stand it.
Come sit at the front with me.
Why should I?
You signed the Shareholders' Voting Agreement. Get up.
Don't embarrass me.
Get up.
Let go of me.
Hey, why are you sitting here?
I can if I want to. Leave me alone.
Just let her be.
Even an illegitimate child is sitting here.
What's wrong with your sister taking a spot?
The items for today's meeting...
include a report on 2nd and 4th quarter sales' performance,
the new chairman election and the dismissal of Vice Chairman Do.
I'll invite Chairwoman Hwang to the podium.
Now, we'll start the 32nd...
Dodo Group's general meeting.
Mealtime.
Sir.
Are you all right?
- Choong Dong.
-  Why are you in confinement?
Contact my father-in-law right away...
- and ask him to come visit.
-  Pardon?
This is urgent. You need to contact him as soon as possible.
Yes, Sir.
Now, we'll vote on the new chairman position.
Where is Chairman Do Choong?
His condition has gotten worse. He won't be able to attend.
I heard that he was getting better.
I'm not sure who is spreading such rumours,
but he can barely take care of himself.
What is his condition? How bad is it?
That's his privacy, so I'll tell you in person later.
Just know that he won't be able to attend today.
What are you doing, Mr Han? Continue with the meeting!
Since Chairman Do isn't here,
we'll go directly into voting.
Please use your smartphones to access the website...
to vote.
Please take out your phones.
Chairman Do Choong is here.
What is this about?
Mum.
I thought you said he couldn't come.
Don't worry.
His condition will only put him at a disadvantage.
You're not well. Why did you bother coming here?
Mr Han.
The chairman can't go up here alone. Get people to help him up.
Long time no see.
I'm Do Choong.
Please sit down.
There are vile rumours about me...
going around.
As you can see,
I'm healthy as I can be.
Don't be fooled.
Chairman Do Choong has dementia.
Dementia?
I don't have dementia.
That's enough.
It's a crime to lie to our shareholders.
Gwang Woo, check where Dr Hwang is.
Okay.
Dr Hwang. Where are you right now?
I see. He's almost here.
Once his doctor arrives,
you'll all find out that he has dementia.
Even if he's the founder,
we can't let someone with dementia run the company.
Don't you agree?
May I ask you a question, Chairwoman Hwang?
- Go ahead.
-  During your tenure,
there was zero improvement in the company's performance.
Why don't you explain yourself?
I'm sure all of you know that the business sector is in depression.
Our rival Geukdong Group was in the red.
Same goes for Samjoong Group and Taeyang Group.
It was thanks to me we managed to stay afloat. If someone else...
Chairwoman Hwang!
Is it currently...
worse than when we had IMF?
What?
During IMF,
numerous companies went bankrupt!
But I expanded by creating 10 more subsidiary companies.
Our growth rate was 145 percent!
It's still considered a legend in the industry.
I found Dodo Media then.
Where is Mr Choi?
I'm right here, Sir.
- Dodo Electronics' Mr Park!
-  Yes, Sir.
- Dodo Chemicals' Mr Kang!
Dodo Fashion's Mr Yoo.
Dodo Insurance. Dodo Investments!
Dodo International. Dodo Foods.
All of you! What happened to you?
We used to sweat and cry together!
We'd debate over drinks...
and support each other as a team!
Why can't you work like you used to?
I'm sorry, Sir. It's our fault.
It's not your fault.
It's all my fault.
I couldn't hold my place.
This all happened because...
I was too weak.
It's not your fault, Chairman.
Please return, Sir.
We missed you, Sir.
Chairwoman Hwang.
I have memories with these people.
Dodo Group is...
all about those memories!
It's sustained by our blood, sweat and efforts...
from those days.
People like you...
will never know what it's like!
That's why...
this company...
stopped growing. Do you understand?
So what?
You have dementia?
Dementia?
Memories?
Your brain is dying and you're saying some weird things.
What will those memories do for you now?
Hey, Mum.
Look, it's Dr Hwang.
Welcome, Dr Hwang.
Chairman Do Choong is fooling our shareholders right now.
Please tell them...
that he has dementia.
Chairman Do Choong...
does not have dementia.
It was a side effect from wrong medicines for his blood pressure.
He does not have dementia.
Mr Han, please proceed.
Let us begin voting.
Don't worry.
We don't know what will happen.
You said we have about the same number of shares, right?
Yes. It's worth the fight.
(A request for provisional attachment of assets)
Court sent us documents to request for a seizure.
Thank you.
It's awfully hot today.
Why isn't the door fixed yet?
Did you fill out the document to seize Gwi Ja...
and Gwang Woo's assets?
Yes.
Do you think the general meeting is over?
Why? Are you worried?
Things don't seem well,
but Gun Woo isn't saying anything.
He's being considerate.
Don't worry.
Gun Woo is...
the most competent man that I know.
It's about time he called.
We'll announce the results.
Please take a look at the screen.
(Voting Result)
The result is 57 percent to 39 percent.
Chairman Do Choong has been appointed once again as Chairman.
- Mum.
-  Mum.
Mum.
Mr Han, get her.
- Come here.
-  Yes, Sir.
- Take her.
-  Wait.
My goodness.
I, Do Choong,
will bring back our glorious days...
just like the ones during the IMF crisis!
You can't collapse right now.
We're almost here.
Hold on just a little more, Father.
Chairman Do Choong is amazing.
It's as if an old lion is roaring one last time...
for his pride.
The problem is that this is his last time.
His era...
will end soon.
Then...
Gun Woo's era will begin.
Before that,
we must take over Dodo Group.
Did you...
get this from Gun Woo?
Mum. How can you do this?
What if Dad passes away?
Your dad isn't the problem! I'm about to die!
Don't blame me.
This is all your doing!
I didn't do this just for myself!
I did this for you two!
I didn't want Gun Woo to take this company!
No one asked you to do this!
Stop it, you idiot!
Okay, Mum.
What happened has happened.
We have to find a way to live now.
Let's go kneel down and apologise to Father.
I am not kneeling down to him.
Never!
If you won the vote, that'll be fine.
But right now, we really will be finished.
Your father...
can't publicise this video.
He would've done it at the general meeting.
The problem isn't the video.
Are you going to sit and watch...
Gun Woo take this company?
If I kneel down and apologise,
do you think your father will accept it?
In your dreams!
Your father would...
throw down those who stand and trot on those who fall!
We don't have any other way!
We already have...
enough shares in this company and enough inheritance, too.
We can rise above your father whenever we want to.
I'll talk to Dad.
You?
Dad listens to me.
I'll talk to him and ask him to forgive you, Mum.
Shin Young, you are finally coming around like her daughter.
Shut it.
You never came around like a son should.
Wait.
She is unbelievable.
My head hurts.
My gosh.
How many times...
am I to be betrayed in one day?
My goodness.
(Chairman Do Choong)
Father, you were great today.
I respect you.
Congratulations, Chairman.
But it feels like...
a part of my heart is...
empty.
Shin Young is here, Sir.
Where's your mum?
Dad.
Can you forgive her?
Your mum should be here to ask for forgiveness.
Why are you here?
She's regretting everything that she's done.
She can't bring herself to face you.
Lawyer Oh.
Yes, Sir.
Begin the procedure...
on the seizure of Gwi Ja and Gwang Woo's assets.
Yes, Sir.
A seizure on their assets?
What are you talking about?
Shin Young, listen carefully.
If you help your mum and brother,
I'll take away your assets...
according to the undutiful child law.
Dad.
Chairman, please share a word on your return.
I'm sorry, he's on his way out. We'll do this later.
CEO Do Gun Woo, is it true that you'll marry Lawyer Oh?
Who proposed first?
Since when did you two date?
We are not dating.
Will you announce your engagement first?
Did you two date since your new recruit days?
We won't take any personal questions.
Get the car ready. Father, I'll get going.
Please move.
- Excuse me.
-  Do you have a venue?
When will you officially announce this?
Please tell us.
What's going on?
Who is he marrying?
They said he's marrying Soo Yeon.
It's a rumour that's been spreading.
My goodness.
Sir.
Thank you.
Am I to spread a rumour on your marriage with Lawyer Oh?
Yes, spread rumours about it.
Mention it to the reporters today as well.
So many people would want to drink with you today.
Do you really want to drink at a place like this?
I like to drink with you at a place like this.
I'll become the chairman of Dodo Group soon.
I know.
I'll congratulate you in advance.
That means I'll be very busy with work.
Did you expect it to be all fun and games?
I want to scream, shout and jump up and down.
I'm so happy I want to act like a madman!
Don't. My neighbours will report you right away.
I tried so hard to hold it back.
But I just can't tonight.
Soo Yeon, you're the only woman who makes...
my heart beat faster.
The only one in the world.
That's you.
Marry me.
- Gun Woo.
-  I know I'm rushing it.
I'll wait.
Whether it be 10 years or 100.
Until you say yes.
What made you want to drink at a place like this?
If I lived an average life,
would I be happy like everyone else?
Ever since I was young,
I never lacked anything...
but I was never happy.
Mum and Dad always fought,
and Gwang Woo only cared about himself.
That's how I ended up caring about what was mine.
I'm not used to this.
You're like a different person.
Should I just get married?
That's fine for you, but not your husband.
I'll marry you.
What?
Do you dislike me that much?
Tell me.
Am I not even worth considering?
I'm not capable of loving someone.
Why not?
My scars run too deep.
So I can't make anyone happy.
You don't have to force yourself.
I'll make myself happy.
Let's drink.
What has gotten into you?
You used to hate it when I got drunk.
Today, I think you deserve a drink.
Do you trust me now?
Cheers.
I love you to death.
Why can't you.
Stop screaming in my ear!
What? Are you saying you can't stand my singing?
You dog bone of a jerk.
Leave my ear alone!
(Do Choong Returns to Dodo)
You can't...
do this to me.
You took from others all your life.
How does it feel to lose something?
B World.
Your goose that lays golden eggs...
will die soon.
I'm going to eat it so it can't lay any more.
Gi Tan, Gun Woo.
You two.
I will make you...
fight each other until you die.
4984. You have a visitor.
We have to take Dodo Group back.
Give up.
Gun Woo was tough to beat,
but now that Choong is back, it won't be easy.
Soon, Gun Woo will take over B World.
What do you mean?
He stabbed me in the back.
Gi Tan said he'd make you a beggar.
That means he plans to attack B World.
That is why I wanted to see you.
Gun Woo will purchase B World...
for much cheaper than the market price.
In exchange for that, ask for the golf course...
and home shopping channel Ms Hwang promised.
There's no way...
he'd accept that offer.
In my safe, I have files and evidence...
of the corruption Gun Woo committed...
while he was in management.
You can use that.
I knew it. I knew you wouldn't give in so easily.
I'll sell the home shopping channel and golf course for a premium...
and invest it in Hong Kong's Z Capital.
Z Capital?
It's a private equity fund. They're corporate hunters.
The money you siphoned away from the paper company.
Is that where it went?
Yes.
If we put in that much more money,
then we will have a lot of influence...
in where Z Capital invests.
While Gi Tan and Gun Woo are fighting over Dodo Group,
you will get between them?
That's my plan.
I will see to it that they both go down in flames.
Il Jae.
I won't be able to help you much longer.
I would like you to do me a favour as well.
I will do anything you ask.
I will tell you what that is...
when you get out of here.
What will you ask him to do?
Of course, he will fund your campaign.
I need him to divorce Ji Soo.
Il Jae is branded...
with a scarlet letter.
If I'm to run for president,
I need him not to be my son-in-law any more.
Will your daughter sign the divorce papers?
I will make her sign them, even if it means...
threatening to cut ties with her.
Sir.
The Chinese shipowners arrived at Dodo Hotel.
They're in a meeting with Gi Tan.
(We'll pay the price once the ship is completed.)
(That is the current trend.)
You speak fluent Mandarin.
You did well today.
Did I really?
They seem to like their accommodation.
They'd better.
I put so much work into their rooms.
Shouldn't I meet with the shipowners?
You can talk to me.
Heavy tail payment?
It's a 600,000-dollar deal.
Do they want to pay it later?
That's their demand.
It's out of my hands.
But from our perspective,
it's too large a risk.
Chairman Kang.
Even banks these days don't do refund guarantees.
That's your problem.
The shipowners won't sign unless it's a heavy tail payment.
It's up to you.
There are other shipbuilders.
We could help you with the finances.
Let us invest.
I don't want...
to borrow your money, too.
What should I tell the shipowners then?
Make up your mind. They're impatient people.
They can pay us later.
- Sir.
-  It's done, then.
I'll tell them that.
Is that it?
Gi Tan, wait for me.
Are you sure about this? It's too risky.
Mr Kim, set up a meeting with the bank presidents.
Stop Gun Woo from meeting people from the banks.
I doubt that will make him come to us for help.
Do Choong is back.
Gun Woo might ignore me, but he won't.
For Shin Young's sake.
I understand.
When will you release the MK2 vaccine?
First, I'll control their finances.
Then I'll go for Dodo Pharmaceutical.
If the holding company falls,
they will rot from the roots up.
Once it starts to rot, even a thousand-year-old tree...
will fall in an instant.
Gi Tan, Gun Woo.
They'll already be at loggerheads.
They just need some fanning.
When the fire rages,
one of them will go down in flames.
Why aren't you eating?
I'd rather eat sand.
I have no appetite.
Me, too.
So...
where will you stay tonight?
Let's go to Dodo Hotel.
We'll ask Shin Young to give us a suite.
Okay...
135 dollars, please.
Sure. I can afford that.
Here you go.
The card was suspended.
It can't be. It's a premium card.
This is unbelievable. Fine.
Try this one.
This is suspended, too.
Mum.
Try this one.
This, too.
Dad must've cut us off.
The old mule...
How dare he?
Calm down or you'll faint again.
Do Choong...
Il Jae asked me...
to give this to you.
(Do Gun Woo's slush fund)
Tax fraud, lobbying and illegal loans.
Gun Woo's management style...
is a lot like yours when you were younger.
Chimney sweeps get soot all over...
and fishmongers reek of fish.
A businessman...
is bound to touch dirty money.
That's what you think.
Did you...
rob Il Jae of B World?
What do you mean?
You said the process was sound.
When making a deal, both parties...
always think they got the worse end.
Buying it for half the market price is stealing.
What do you want?
In exchange for taking B World,
I want the golf course in Yongin...
and the home shopping channel.
Say no, Father.
The minute you do,
all this will end up in a prosecutor's hands.
I have proof of Il Jae's corruption as well.
Chairman Do.
I can do...
without a son-in-law.
But can you do...
without a son?
Chief Prosecutor Kim.
Aren't you busy investigating corruption in large companies?
I'm thinking of giving you a tip.
Hang up.
Let him be, Father.
I said, hang up.
I will...
call you back.
The golf course...
and the home shopping channel...
are yours.
Father.
I can't swap you with Il Jae.
Get the contract.
Yes, Sir.
It's right here.
This clause mentions...
the period and amount.
I got an audio file but I don't know who sent it.
Play it.
Did you lose the mutant virus vaccine?
This is Il Jae's voice.
It's the MK2 vaccine made with Gi Tan's blood.
This is Gun Woo.
The Huaping will retaliate.
The target...
will be on Gi Tan's back, not ours.
I will see to it.
This confirms that...
Gun Woo was the one who framed you...
for murder.
Who sent this?
Il Jae.
What for?
To start a fight.
He wants us...
to get rid of Gun Woo.
I don't care what Il Jae wants.
I now have a clear reason...
to get rid of Gun Woo.
I thought I'd taken B World for cheap.
But it turns out I had to pay the full price.
I'm glad if you think so,
but very soon, you'll lose B World.
You can't take it from me.
I won't. Gi Tan will.
He told me that...
he'll make sure B World goes bankrupt.
It would go bankrupt if you had it.
But I'm not you.
No one can touch my company.
I wondered why Gi Tan was so confident,
so I did some digging.
He has a powerful weapon with which...
he can ruin B World in one blow.
He plans to sell the vaccine in Korea and America,
and he holds the patent for both countries.
If he sells the MK2 vaccine for scrap value,
B World will get pushed out of the competition.
Your influenza vaccine will go straight to the dump.
Gi Tan can ruin you completely.
Il Jae is trying to make you go against Chairman Kang.
I know that.
Then don't fall for it.
Gi Tan is already someone...
I must get rid of.
What Il Jae is doing is giving me one more reason to do so.
If I weren't framed for murder,
I wouldn't have a bullet in my brain.
Gun Woo was the one who shot it into me.
By turning me into a murderer.
(Do Gun Woo)
I have something to say. Let's meet up.
Where at?
This way, Sir.
Soo Yeon.
Why are you here?
To meet Gun Woo.
He's in a meeting that will run late.
He's the one who asked to see me.
Shall we go somewhere for tea?
I'd like to look around the Strategic Planning Department.
I'll see you some other time.
Your photo's here.
I did pretty well for myself back then.
This is a photo of our colleagues.
Who's this ugly guy?
It's Soo Tak.
Now that I see that photo again, I really was ugly.
Why is this photo here?
Was Soo Yeon an employee here?
Yes.
Were Soo Yeon and I this close?
- Well...
-  Kang Gi Tan.
I'm going to marry Soo Yeon.
So...
forget about her.