(Episode 39)
Why is this photo here?
Was Soo Yeon...
an employee here?
Yes.
Were Soo Yeon...
and I this close?
Well...
Kang Gi Tan.
I'm going to marry Soo Yeon.
So...
forget about her.
I just got out of the meeting.
I'll come by the office.
Okay, Mr Min.
Soo Yeon.
Chairman wants to see you.
Where is he?
Congratulations.
I heard you patented the MK2 vaccine.
- What about it?
-  I'd like...
to buy the patent.
You were right.
Why are you here, Soo Yeon?
I called her.
Join us, Lawyer Oh.
If you don't need me here...
We're talking business.
We'd feel comfortable...
with a legal representative.
It's fine. Have a seat.
Lawyer Oh, let me ask you something.
It's about B World, Il Jae's old company.
Did you know Gun Woo purchased it?
You didn't.
How did you take over?
Is it wrong to acquire a company?
It's not.
I find it odd that Il Jae sold his goose...
that lays golden eggs to you.
Don't you, Lawyer Oh?
This is what I think.
Either he and Il Jae had some sort of a deal,
or Il Jae was threatened by him...
and had no choice...
but to hand over the company.
The B World information you gave Lawyer Oh before the trial...
If I'm right, those files were meaningless.
I think you kept the real deal...
and used it to threaten Il Jae.
Your novel's quite appealing.
But...
in exchange for B World,
I gave up the home shopping channel and golf course.
Isn't that a reasonable deal?
It was a foolish one.
Once the MK2 vaccine's released,
B World will go down.
That's why I made an offer.
I want to buy the patent...
for the MK2 vaccine.
You know that...
I won't sell it.
Gi Tan.
If B World goes down, Dodo Pharmaceutical...
will take a hit.
Attacking the holding company...
means you want to start a war against Dodo Group.
I'm running a legitimate business.
The threat to Dodo Pharmaceutical...
is the result of your foolish transactions.
We're done talking.
I tried to give you a way out.
An obedient donkey gets a carrot.
But an insolent one...
gets a whipping.
I hold the rein...
and you're my donkey.
Why didn't you tell me you'd taken over B World?
As your legal counsel, I had to know.
You know I was busy with the general meeting.
You could have told me after the general meeting.
Don't tell me you believe all that nonsense.
I'm looking for evidence of Il Jae's corruption.
Why do you think I paid so much for his company?
Embezzlement, tax fraud, illegal lobbying.
If I find proof of these,
I can lock him up for good at his upcoming appeal.
I'll give you the files as soon as I find them.
So don't believe the script Gi Tan wrote.
Soo Tak.
Mr Moon.
We're listening.
Lawyer Oh and I...
How close were we?
The photo we saw...
shows that we weren't always this polite.
What happened between...
Lawyer Oh and me?
You two were very close.
"Very close"?
How close do you mean?
When you were framed for murder and on the run,
Lawyer Oh tried very hard to clear your name.
And that is why...
her brother died.
Her brother died...
because of me?
It wasn't your fault exactly.
- Il Jae...
-  That's the same thing!
Why did you...
keep this from me?
The memories of her are the cause of your headaches.
That's why Professor Jin erased them.
I don't remember anything.
Don't try to, Sir.
The headaches might return.
Is that all?
What do you mean?
About my relationship with her.
Is that it?
I think you were close...
since you started as colleagues.
That is...
all we know, Sir.
Chairman Do is here.
Are you working on getting rid of my wife's allies?
We have a list of names and reasons to fire them all.
Gather them all.
Yes, Father.
I plan to shuffle the personnel around...
including all the CEOs.
Thank you for working for and putting up with...
such an incompetent chairwoman.
It's time you all retire.
What do you mean, Sir?
You're all fired.
Hand in your resignation letters.
This is unfair.
It's too sudden.
CEO Hong.
At your daughter's wedding, a supplier gave you...
50,000 dollars in the form of a gift.
CEO Yang.
You sent your wife and her family on a trip, and got reimbursed for it.
CEO Cho.
You bought an apartment for a female supplier.
Does your wife know about it?
The first mistake Gwi Ja made...
was placing disloyal men like you in key positions,
thinking that you'd be of help.
Of course, the root will rot...
if the water is rotten.
If you do not turn in...
your resignation letters within this morning,
the police will find out...
about all these disgusting things you've done.
The choice is yours.
Reinstate all CEOs of our subsidiaries...
whom Gwi Ja fired.
Yes, Father.
Why is Mr Han still here?
I will be loyal to you, Chairman. Please give me another chance.
He helped out significantly during the general meeting.
He can do a lot of things, so please leave him to me.
Gun Woo, you need to get a promotion, too.
I am satisfied with what I have.
I will promote you as the vice chairman.
Oh, right.
What is this about your marrying Lawyer Oh?
I understand that she's a good woman,
but she's not someone for you to marry.
My in-law needs to be one of the best families in Korea.
It's probably a rumour made by the reporters.
I have never...
thought about marrying Lawyer Oh.
Good.
Remember this, Gun Woo.
You are...
the next chairman...
who'll lead Dodo Group.
Yes, Father.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Congratulations, Vice Chairman.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
That means CEO Do took over B World to help you.
He gave up the home shopping channel and the golf course.
Lawyer Oh, you should grasp his heart...
while you have the chance.
No, thanks. Stop saying that.
Look around. You won't find anyone like him.
I really respect him as a fellow man...
for what he does to you, Lawyer Oh.
Gi Tan helped out Soo Yeon a lot, too.
Right, Soo Yeon?
Who cares? He has no memory of her.
They are as good as strangers.
It's still left in Soo Yeon's memories.
That's the problem.
She is the only one who's suffering from this.
There's a song that goes like this.
If love hurts you a lot, it probably wasn't love at all.
That's not how you sing it.
Don't ruin a perfectly good song.
I'm sorry.
It's simply because I'm drunk.
Why isn't he coming?
Who else is coming?
What? Well...
Who is it?
Well...
Cheers, guys.
- Chairman.
-  You can go home.
CEO Do, you're here.
How did you find us?
I called him.
I asked him to pay for our little gathering.
Who's the guy you called?
Oh, no one.
- CEO Do, have a drink.
-  Sure.
You don't have to use both hands.
(Soo Tak...)
Soo Tak, I don't think Gi Tan should come today.
Chairman, Nan Jeong says that you shouldn't come today.
Let's leave for today, Sir.
Let's go.
You didn't have to walk me home.
Have you...
given it a thought?
About asking you to marry me...
I am very thankful for it and I know that I don't deserve it.
- But Gun Woo, I...
-  My father...
told me today...
that I can marry you.
I was also appointed as the vice chairman, too.
My father's health is failing, so he won't be around for long.
So can we at least get engaged?
- Gun Woo...
-  I only live like a crazy man...
because of you.
You just have to make the decision.
I'll wait for the answer.
Chairman.
Hello.
I am Kang Gi Tan.
I am Lawyer Oh Soo Yeon. Nice to meet you.
It feels like you're avoiding me on purpose.
Am I wrong?
It's not like that.
I'm going to marry Soo Yeon.
So...
forget about her.
Chairman!
Are you okay?
You look troubled.
Is this because of Lawyer Oh?
Thanks to you,
I feel much better.
How is your headache?
I'm okay.
That's a relief.
I just received a call from someone in SPD.
He said Gun Woo is...
promoted as the vice chairman.
- We have to make a move...
-  How is the vaccine received...
among pharmaceutical companies?
Geukdong Pharmaceutical is the most interested.
They were always behind Dodo Pharmaceutical.
- I'll seal the deal tomorrow.
-  Yes, Sir.
This new MK2 vaccine is...
much more effective and cheaper...
than mutant influenza vaccine produced by Dodo Pharmaceutical.
This is the opening of a new generation of vaccines.
Dodo Pharmaceutical has always defended their position on top,
but things do not look promising thanks to this brand new vaccine.
The fall of Dodo Pharmaceutical will affect the entire group.
Vice Chairman Do, what's our plan?
There is one way to walk out of this crisis.
We'll put some of our subsidiaries through a paid-in capital increase.
- Paid-in capital increase?
-  Yes.
Based on last year's sales,
we'll issue new stock shares...
for companies that lost money.
Ga Din, I'm in a meeting now.
What's a "paid-in capital increase"?
Gun Woo will put out Dodo Hotel for a paid-in capital increase.
That will damage the percentage of your shares.
Shin Young, it's me.
Walk out of the room and talk to me.
I'm outside. You can talk.
That means he'll issue new Dodo Hotel stocks.
What will happen then?
If Gun Woo gets those shares,
your ownership of the hotel...
could be threatened.
What?
He's up to something then.
We have to stop the recapitalisation.
Can you do that?
Don't worry. Trust me.
Dodo Corporation, Dodo Insurance, Dodo Engineering...
and Dodo Hotel will be recapitalised.
Not the hotel.
For as long as I'm around, there's no way you can...
recapitalise on the hotel.
You lost over 10 million dollars last year.
If you keep going...
Don't be like that, Vice Chairman.
Don't mention last year's numbers.
Don't you know I turned it around since I took over this year?
Sir, Dodo Hotel must be recapitalised.
Why are we in this mess?
It's because you bought B World...
and that threatened Dodo Pharmaceutical.
Why are you trying to make someone else pay the price?
Gi Tan has the patent to the MK2 vaccine.
Why did you sign...
a Shareholders' Voting Agreement with our enemy?
What?
That's because I plan...
to marry him.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to marry Kang Gi Tan.
Shin Young...
It's not a bad idea.
He's involved in many of our transactions,
including the shipbuilding deal.
If Shin Young were to marry him,
that would help us overcome this crisis.
We can discuss this later.
Let's conclude this meeting.
Shin Young.
You manage a hotel.
Don't you know what recapitalisation is?
I studied fashion.
Have you heard of "windowpane gingham check patterns"?
You don't make clothes.
If you want to be my partner, start studying.
Studying?
I can do that.
However, you need to be the one to teach me.
I'm not bored enough to tutor you.
Do it. I want to study hard...
with you.
She wants to study, not have fun.
Say yes, Sir.
Very well.
- I'll teach you.
-  Really?
No homework or exams.
Then I'll really study hard.
How did you prevent the recapitalisation?
I told my dad that I'd marry you.
He didn't object.
When should we get married?
This autumn?
We'll go on our honeymoon in the Mediterranean.
Mr Moon, I think you should tutor her.
Sorry?
Are you going back on your promise?
I'm too scared to teach you.
I'll come by to your suite...
- this evening.
-  Shin Young.
Shut your mouth before I have the hotel recapitalised.
(Dodo Pharmaceutical Shares Drop)
- I won this time.
-  You did.
Well done.
Hey! Be quiet.
The mayor's reading the paper.
4984, you have a visitor.
Who could it be?
Gi Tan or Gun Woo?
I set them at each other's throats.
The wounded one would need my help.
You're here often.
Do you need my help?
You won't offer it even if I did.
If you're willing to get rid of Gi Tan for me,
I'd be willing to help you.
You'd say the same to Gi Tan if he were here.
"I'd be willing to help if you're willing to get rid of Gun Woo."
Why are you here?
You played on both sides.
Congratulations.
I thought long and hard about you.
"How much of you is real..."
"and how much is a mask?"
That's interesting.
And?
Your betraying me...
wasn't only because of Soo Yeon.
Did you...
come to Korea with the sole purpose of...
taking me down?
Do you still think...
I killed my stepfather by accident?
Where is your mum? Where is your mum?
I don't know.
I thought that...
if I only had the gun,
I could protect my mother from that monster.
But...
it took me 10 years to get a hold of that gun.
My stepfather...
was as suspicious as you are.
Come here, you dirty tramp!
That monster...
was high on drugs and alcohol, and started hitting my mother.
The time had come.
I could have pleaded self-defence.
- But...
-  Gun Woo.
That day,
you came by.
- Don't shoot.
-  They're here...
to see you.
I'll call you when the time is right.
Until then, use the fury inside to prepare yourself.
Turn your hatred for the world...
into ambition.
What do you say?
You only live once.
Isn't it worth a shot?
You planned to use me...
to swallow Dodo Group whole.
My plan...
was to use you...
to do the exact same thing.
You said...
you didn't want to become a monster like me.
Did you pretend...
to love Soo Yeon to deceive me?
There was one thing I didn't foresee.
I actually...
came to love her...
with all my heart.
If you hadn't touched her,
then our alliance...
could have lasted a little longer.
Too bad.
Had I understood you a little sooner,
we could have become amazing partners.
It's not too late.
If you take out Gi Tan,
I'm willing to join hands with you.
Just leave Soo Yeon alone.
Mum.
Forget about your pride just this once...
and beg Dad for his forgiveness.
He fired everyone who sided with you...
How dare he?
How dare he temporarily seize my assets?
He's threatening to send you to prison.
This is no time to get angry.
I won't apologise to your father.
Never.
We need to appease him somehow.
Then we can start over.
You said there's nothing you can't do for me.
Father.
Mum has something to say.
Mum.
I...
was wrong.
- Were you?
-  Yes.
So let's reconcile.
What are these?
Your clothes.
Take this...
and get out of my house.
- Honey.
-  Father.
Both of your names will be deleted forever...
on my will.
Will you really be like this?
I just changed my mind to apologise to you.
Mr Gong.
What did Lawyer Oh say about...
inheritance of assets?
You can leave out anyone who tried to kill an immediate family member.
What?
Father, are you serious?
You and your mother shouldn't be saying a word!
Mr Gong, what are you doing? Kick them out right now.
Please leave.
I won't leave.
This is my house.
I have...
washed your dirty uniform and made dozens of lunch boxes...
for our employees to build up this house myself.
I would never leave.
What are you doing? Kick her out!
Did you think I'd give up?
Not at all.
Half of Dodo Group is mine!
I will claim my rights!
Why are you standing around?
Kick him out.
Let go.
Father.
I am your eldest son.
That is why I am...
more disgusted and disappointed in you.
Do you think we have failed you?
Our household is like this not because of me or Mum.
It's because of you. You made us like this.
Get out of here!
Let go!
Watch me.
You will regret...
this day when you have...
kicked us out.
You should sleep if you're tired.
I'm fine.
There will be no more trouble...
now that I've kicked them out.
Let go of me!
How dare you touch me?
You idiots!
I am Hwang Gwi Ja.
I'm the chairwoman of Dodo Group!
Mum!
Do you want to die?
How dare you push her?
Mum. Are you okay?
Mum, I'm sorry.
It's all because I'm incompetent.
You're not incompetent.
Don't ever say that.
Mum.
It's all my fault.
My greed has ruined you.
Don't say that, Mum.
It's not your fault.
It is.
I should have protected you no matter what it takes.
I told you, don't say that.
This is...
all because of Gun Woo.
If he didn't suddenly appear,
Father would have never done anything like this.
Mum, get up.
Come on.
Do you have anywhere to go?
You probably don't have money.
Get lost...
if you don't want to die.
If you're willing to go to the US, I'll help you with your living cost.
Gun Woo.
When we get a divorce, half of his assets is mine.
Tell him that I am not afraid of getting a divorce!
Even if you do get alimony, you'd have to give it back.
You have damaged the company very much while you were in charge.
What?
My mum suffered much more than this!
I think now I know how you felt back then.
Get lost, you jerk!
Brother.
- What?
-  Oh, right.
You didn't want me to call you that.
If you'd been a brother to me, I probably would have saved you.
You two...
probably never have starved.
My mother and I...
know what it is like to starve.
If you can't take it,
you should beg.
You can beg me.
Chairman's son is here.
Unbelievable.
Gwang Woo.
What am I going to do...
about this humiliation?
Just wait, Mum.
Gun Woo.
I will get him.
We have chosen the subsidiaries, Father.
We need the board's approval to go into paid-in capital...
Who are you?
Mr Gong.
Who allowed this stranger in here?
Chairman, what is with you?
It's me, Gun Woo.
You're not my son.
Mr Gong, go and bring Gwang Woo.
It's me, Gun Woo.
You idiot.
How dare you act like my son? Get out of here!
Chairman, he's your former secretary...
Yoon Ja Young's son.
What? Ja Young?
Right.
She had an affair with one of my employees.
Are you his son?
- Bring Doctor Hwang.
-  Yes.
I was going to take Mother...
to my father's graveyard. Where is my wife?
Chairman, please hang in there.
Just let him be, Mr Gong.
Maybe she's upset that I forgot our anniversary.
Honey! Gwi Ja!
I'm so sorry.
Where are you?
Chairman, Chairman.
Are you sure that it's not dementia?
It's a side effect caused by his medicine.
It continues to worsen for a simple side effect.
Don't worry and make sure he takes his pills.
Don't forget the shots either.
You may leave.
How long will you hide that he has dementia?
I can't bring it up yet.
When will you tell everyone?
We're currently editing his will.
Once Gwi Ja finds out, that will won't have...
any lawful significance.
If this continues, his muscles will be paralysed...
Just do as I say.
You're getting paid for this. Why do you have so many opinions?
I'm sorry.
After we're done with his will,
I'll send him off to a care centre.
After that, you will become...
the chairman of the board of Dodo Hospital.
Do you understand?
It's unbelievable how the wife of Dodo Group...
had nowhere else to go but to return to her family's house.
You don't have to add to this.
I am already embarrassed as it is.
How long will you stay here?
Do you want us to leave?
I can't take care of you because I'm really busy.
Can you cook your own food?
Be nice, will you, Congresswoman?
We aren't refugees.
Mr Han.
Are you ignoring my calls, too?
Do you think I'm down and out?
It's not like that at all, Sir.
What?
Give me a moment.
This is embarrassing.
Why is he always so frivolous?
Hey.
Do you know that Yang Dong Yi was released?
Where is he right now?
I heard he opened an office in Yeongdeungpo.
Get me his address.
I'm staying at my uncle's in Hongeun-dong.
Yes, Sir.
It's me, Han Sang Goo.
I was hurt.
You said you'd take me back.
Why did you avoid me?
I'm here right now, aren't I?
Forget it.
I can make a living without your help.
I need to ask for a favour.
Do you need a loan?
I charge a lot, you know?
Do Gun Woo.
Get rid of him for me.
I don't care if you kill him.
I don't do that any more.
- Please leave.
-  One large cheque.
How about that? Isn't it worth it now?
Everyone knows you're penniless.
Can you really pay up?
I'm Do Gwang Woo.
The heir of Dodo Group.
So what if you are?
I heard Do Gun Woo's the man in charge.
The company will be mine once he's out of the picture.
I'll pay you then.
I don't take after the fact payments.
Okay, then. 1.5 biggies.
I want 1.5 million.
Do you have to drive a hard bargain?
Take it or leave it. Find someone else.
Wait!
Fine.
1.5 million dollars.
Then...
Please sign this contract.
What... What's this?
"Waiver of Body Parts"?
I'm a loan shark.
Did you expect an insurance form?
You're funny.
Read it carefully before you sign it.
It's a serious document.
Promise that...
you won't mess this up.
Don't you worry. Just wire the money in time.
We have too little on B World.
This isn't enough to win the appeal.
I'm looking for more files. Give it some time.
The prosecutor in charge of the appeal...
Is he trustworthy?
I'm meeting him this evening.
You can see for yourself if you care to join me.
- Soo Yeon.
-  Yes, Gi...
I heard we used to be close.
He saw a photo you two took when you worked at Dodo Group.
Could you excuse us?
Yes, Sir.
I heard...
your brother died because of me.
I'm sorry.
I found out too late.
It's in the past.
Don't concern yourself.
Dong Soo, was it?
His name, I mean.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to visit his place at the charnel house.
You don't have to.
We used to be friends.
How about we speak freely like we used to?
It must feel awkward trying to be polite to a friend.
I prefer things as it is right now.
I'll have no reason to see you after Il Jae's trial.
Are you...
afraid I'll suffer?
Prosecutor Choi.
We'll leave right now.
Sure.
What is Prosecutor Choi like?
His peers know him for being upright and honest.
My prosecutor contact said...
he has enemies because he's so transparent.
Then we can trust him.
Prosecutor Choi is here.
Hello.
- I'm Kang Gi Tan.
-  I'm Moon Tae Gwang.
Hello.
Lawyer Oh told me a lot about you.
Have a seat.
I went over the files you sent.
Il Jae is worse than I thought.
If you knew him,
you'd be even more shocked.
I find it embarrassing and infuriating that...
he used to be a fellow prosecutor.
He has many contacts.
I hope that...
you won't give in to pressure.
Don't worry.
I'm not the kind of person who gives in to temptation.
Hello?
I'm away from the office.
Can I come in, Sir?
Come in.
Welcome.
You must know...
Congressman Hwang Jae Man.
Hello, Sir. I'm Choi Jeong Gook.
This is his daughter, Congresswoman Hwang Ji Soo.
I'm pleased to meet you.
Take a seat.
He was a rookie when I was a deputy-chief prosecutor.
That's when...
I noticed his potentials.
Next week,
I will announce that I will seek my party's nomination...
to run for presidency.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
But it just so happens that...
my son-in-law's trial begins on the same day.
You control...
the future of my campaign and our country.
Do you get what I mean?
Yes, Sir.
If Mr Hwang becomes President,
he will make you the youngest ever superintendent public prosecutor.
You could go even higher than that.
Don't say such a thing, Mr Jang.
I'll be direct.
This appeal to the Supreme Court...
Please turn it down.
I will.
Let me...
pour you a drink.
Here you go.
Sir.
I have it.
Will you really...
give this to Lawyer Oh?
It's me. Where are you?
At my office. Is something wrong?
I found evidence of Il Jae's corruption.
I'll give this to you. Let's meet right now.
Okay. Where should I go?
I know that place. I'll be there.
Gun Woo found evidence of Il Jae's B World corruption.
I told you...
that Gun Woo would find it.
You were right. We didn't need to do this.
I'll be back.
Oh, wait.
Be nice to Gun Woo.
Think about it. He's helped you out very often.
- I'll be back.
-  Okay.
- Follow him.
Yes.
We're following Gun Woo.
Don't make a mistake.
One mistake will kill us all.
Okay. Take care.
Chairman.
I found Dong Soo's charnel house.
- Gun Woo.
-  Hey.
Stay there. I'll go over.
Who are you?
Gun Woo.
Gun Woo!
Gun Woo. Gun Woo.
Gun Woo.
I think I was stabbed with a knife.
Please help us!
Is anyone there?
Gun Woo, hang in there.
Help us! We need help!
That's...
Lawyer Oh's little brother.
My beloved brother, Dong Soo.
Don't ever get sick again...
and rest well up there.
I can't believe I had no idea...
when I've hurt her this deeply.
It's not your fault, Chairman. Don't blame yourself.
Since when...
did I have this necklace on?
I don't know.
His necklace and mine...
are the same.
There are a lot of the same necklaces.
But not a lot of men wear women's necklaces.
It's definitely the same necklace.
Gun Woo, hang in there.
Stay with me, Gun Woo.
Gun Woo, hold on.
(Kang Gi Tan)
Your call has been forwarded to an automated voice messaging...
Gun Woo, can you hear me?
Gun Woo, look at me.
Gun Woo.
You can't go in.
(Emergency Room)
Gun Woo.
Hello?
Soo Yeon?
Who is it? Chairman Kang.
I'm sorry to bother you so late.
- Is Soo Yeon here?
-  She's not.
She's not at the office either and won't pick up her phone.
Is everything all right?
She went to meet CEO Do to receive evidence...
of Il Jae's corruption.
Gun Woo?
Tax evasion and embezzlement. He took a lot of money.
Great job.
Go overseas for a while until everything is settled.
Yes, Boss.
Hello, Sir.
- What happened?
-  Everything went as planned.
Did you get rid of Gun Woo?
We stabbed him real good,
so at the very least, it's a serious injury.
Great job. Don't let this cause any trouble.
He needs to go overseas tomorrow.
Make sure you give me the money.
If you don't, I can...
Don't worry.
Once Gun Woo is gone, Dodo Group is mine.
Are you okay?
Soo Yeon.
All right.
He recognises you. He must be okay.
It's a relief.
The doctor said that it could've been bad...
because you bled a lot.
Are you hurt?
My gosh, you're worried about her as soon as you wake up.
I'm fine.
They took the evidence.
That's the only copy which I found in B World.
I'm sorry, Soo Yeon.
Hey, that's not important.
You almost died and met your deceased beloveds.
This must be Il Jae's doing.
I'll report to the police.
Don't.
Without evidence, we may get charged...
for making false accusations right before his appeal.
I'm sorry, Gun Woo. It's all because of me.
Don't cry, Soo Yeon.
I'm really fine. It hurts me more...
to see you cry over me.
I'll be leaving. Lawyer Oh, take good care of him.
Get well soon.
I'll go see the doctor.
(Kang Gi Tan)
Soo Yeon, where are you?
Soo Yeon, are you listening?
Where are you?
Have you regained your memory?
But you're a month too late.
Soo Yeon is completely mine.
That's what happened.
- Put Soo Yeon on.
-  Even if you've regained it,
nothing will change.
Put her on.
Listen carefully, Gi Tan.
You did win that one with MK2 vaccine.
We lost a lot of money.
But give up on Soo Yeon.
I won this.
Sir.
Gun Woo's in the hospital.
What?
I just spoke with Lawyer Min.
Il Jae sent someone to kill him.
They lost the files, too.
Il Jae felt cornered and did something drastic.
I will visit him in prison tomorrow.
Okay, Sir.
You showed Gun Woo who's in charge.
The prosecutor will add...
"attempted murder" to the charges.
What do you mean?
Gun Woo was stabbed...
by someone you sent.
- What?
-  I'm impressed.
You instigated murder from behind bars.
Did you do it?
Kill Gun Woo...
and frame me for it?
Guk Cheol.
I'm an expert at all crimes that a person can commit.
Did you think I'd fall for one of your flimsy tricks?
Uncle.
Would I use such a flimsy trick?
If it wasn't me or you,
then it must be Gwang Woo.
He lost everything to Gun Woo...
and now, he lost his mind.
But you're a month too late.
Soo Yeon is completely mine.
That's what happened.
It could've been staged.
He did it to himself.
Gwang Woo must think I'm at death's door right now.
I believe so.
I'm listening.
Destroy the files on Il Jae which you took from me.
Yes, Sir.
I hope you're not badly hurt.
My boys are experts.
When do you think...
you can pay me the rest of the money?
My secretary will bring it to you right now.
I like your style. You're so straightforward.
Look after yourself.
Hang on.
If Gwang Woo pays me, too,
it'll be like earning twice as much for just one job.
This is great.
Yes!
Burn, baby, burn.
This will turn into money.
You're so smart, Dong Yi.
Do you think he staged this?
I'm positive.
Why would he?
Drive to the hospital.
Yes, Sir.
Where is the patient?
He went to the roof garden to get some air.
I'm glad you can go home soon.
Soo Yeon.
Did I ever...
make your heart flutter?
make your heart pound?
Mine flutters and pounds all the time.
Don't you...
want to know...
how that feels?
Well... I don't...
(Monster)
He's deceiving Soo Yeon, too.
We have to reveal the truth...
before it's too late.
We have to stop it. If Gi Tan gets his hands on it,
Dodo Group will collapse.
Didn't you come here to ruin Dodo Group?
I shall leave you, Sir.
It should be give and take.
I'm impressed, Gun Woo.
I didn't think he'd do this.
Some things can only be attained by risking your life.
I will judge Il Jae myself.