Were Soo Yeon and I this close?
I'm marrying Soo Yeon.
Let me ask one thing. What's the relationship between...
Lawyer Oh and me?
If you can eliminate Gi Tan,
I'm willing to team up with you again.
Who are you?
You are not my son.
How long will you hide that he has dementia?
We're currently editing his will.
After we're done, I'll send him off to a care centre.
I found evidence of Il Jae's corruption.
Who are you?
This must be Il Jae's doing.
I'll report to the police.
His necklace and mine are the same.
Soo Yeon, where are you?
Have you regained your memory?
But you're a month too late.
Soo Yeon is completely mine.
That's what happened.
Give up on Soo Yeon.
I won this.
Did I ever...
make your heart flutter?
make your heart pound?
It doesn't look like you feel the same way.
- Gun Woo.
-  Don't say anything, Soo Yeon.
I don't want to hear anything...
unless you're saying, "I love you."
You can take your time.
Take as much time as you need.
It's okay.
Chairman.
Chairman, what's wrong?
Who knows everything about Soo Yeon and my history?
I believe Chae Ryung knows everything.
Where is she?
I heard she's in China but...
Get my plane ready.
- Pardon?
-  I need to find out...
the history between...
Soo Yeon and me.
What about the CCTVs around the area?
Don't worry about it, Vice Chairman.
Before we stabbed you,
our boys sprayed all over the CCTVs around the area.
Make sure you destroy the car you used.
My goodness.
It's already been scraped and torn down piece by piece.
May we report this to the police now?
Of course, you may.
There is no evidence...
and people involved have already went overseas.
Are you feeling okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
I didn't know he'd go this far.
There are things you can reach out to take...
and things you need to risk your life to get.
I don't understand why you had to risk...
Report my attack to the police...
and let the reporters know, too.
You should say there was a fight in Dodo Group to become the successor.
Weren't you going to put this on Il Jae?
There is nothing like Il Jae to destroy Gi Tan.
I have to protect him a little.
It's been reported that Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo...
of Dodo Group was attacked by unidentified attackers.
He's currently receiving treatment in a hospital downtown,
and thankfully, his life is not in danger.
Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo has been recognised...
for his management skills, and he became the successor...
of Dodo Group in place of ex-CEO Do Gwang Woo.
What kind of news is that?
Gun Woo never became the successor.
He's very persistent.
I should've just killed him.
The police are...
focused on this fight between...
the two princes to become the successor of Dodo Group...
and are searching for signs of personal grudges in this incident.
I think Gun Woo set this up himself.
He's letting people know that he's the successor.
He's completely fooled Soo Yeon, too.
She needs to know who he really is...
before it's too late.
Sir.
You should just give him pressure with business...
Gun Woo is dirty and evil to the point that he'll take...
a knife to his stomach.
He'll side with Il Jae...
to do away with me.
Soo Yeon is the only one who'll suffer in the midst of this.
You're right.
Sir.
You must head to the airport.
Did you give Chae Ryung a call?
She'll be waiting for you in China.
Let's go, Sir.
- Gun Woo.
-  Yes. Welcome, Soo Yeon.
This is the prosecutor who's in charge of this retrial.
My name is Choi Jeong Gook.
Nice to meet you.
Hello?
It's me, Gun Woo.
Can we talk?
Hello?
Are you listening to me?
So you're the prosecutor for Il Jae's retrial, right?
I have a guest over.
I'll talk to you later.
I heard you lost evidence of Il Jae's corruption in this attack.
Yes, I was about to hand it over to Lawyer Oh.
You didn't mention this to the police.
They probably destroyed the evidence already.
If I mentioned it, I could be filed for making false accusations.
Do you also believe that this is his doing?
They took the evidence. Isn't it obvious?
The media has been saying that it's a fight between successors.
Yes, I did that on purpose.
I needed to catch Il Jae off-guard...
before the retrial.
Do you not have a copy of the evidence?
Yes. Had I known this would've happened,
I would've made a copy.
Will it be difficult for Il Jae to receive additional sentence...
during this retrial?
We'll try even if it doesn't happen.
I have to return to the office.
I'll be back soon.
Did you hear that?
I had my doubts.
Did you stage this yourself? You're amazing, Gun Woo.
You catch onto things quickly.
Gwang Woo wouldn't stage an attack...
to get that evidence.
What happened to the evidence?
I destroyed it. It went up in flames.
Destroyed?
Yes, as you've heard,
your other crimes won't be proved during the retrial.
Do you want me...
to get rid of Gi Tan?
Yes. Life is about giving and taking.
Gi Tan is the one...
who told me that this attack was staged by you.
He already knew.
You should get ready.
I don't care. There is no evidence left.
Come and visit me before the retrial.
I have to talk to you.
I'm hanging up.
Who was that?
What?
Nothing important.
You were talking about evidence.
It's a reporter. Don't mind it.
It's too stuffy in here. Let's go for a walk.
Once I get out,
I'll take care of Gi Tan.
I will not let him interfere with your presidential election.
Don't worry, Mr Hwang.
What do you mean...
you'll take care of him?
I'm going to destroy him.
If that doesn't go well,
I will get rid of...
Darn you!
You're pathetic.
What if you're found out?
It'll be more than just ruining my presidential campaign.
You'd be putting a knife on my throat.
What do you want me to do then?
Here.
(Divorce Notice)
This is...
your stamp.
Stamp...
the divorce papers.
- Sir...
-  If you disappear,
Gi Tan won't try to ruin my campaign.
Are you cutting your ties with me...
because you're scared of Gi Tan?
Il Jae!
Even if I'm a dragon...
flying up into the skies,
I should be careful no stray dogs are barking at me.
It's not because I'm scared.
I'm just saying that the presidential campaign...
must be treated seriously with extra caution.
It's not just dogs that could ruin a dragon's path.
I didn't want to say this to you but...
The prosecutor...
assigned to your appeal was chosen by me.
Unless you want...
to rot in prison forever,
forget about trying to threaten me...
with the fact that Ji Soo is a murderer.
I'm not telling you two to separate forever.
Once I'm in power,
you two can get back together at that point.
I can promise you.
Did Ji Soo...
agree to the divorce?
If you stamp on the papers first,
I'm sure she'll accept it.
You look upset.
I just...
stamped my divorce papers.
What do you mean, a divorce?
Are you getting a divorce with Congresswoman Hwang?
That sly, old man...
spat me out like a tasteless chewing gum.
You lost your mayor position as well as B World.
If you lose her as well,
it'll be hard for you to make a comeback.
Choong Dong.
If you break an egg from the outside, it'll be an egg fry.
But if it breaks from the inside out, it'll become a chick.
I am...
having a battle against the wall of reality.
If I manage to break out of it,
I'll become a rooster that will...
open up the morning.
I have no doubts.
Just watch. When I get out of here,
you'll see how I transform.
The ones that put me in this situation...
and the people who looked down at me with contempt...
will all be put in prison by me.
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
How is the boss?
He's inside.
Professor Jin, please wait here for a moment.
Boss.
You can speak casually with me. It's fine.
I heard from Mr Moon already.
Tell me everything you know about Oh Soo Yeon.
All of my memories that I've lost...
You must know everything since you were always by my side.
Why do you suddenly want to know?
Whenever I think of her,
my heart aches.
I don't know what it is,
but it makes me sad and I long for her.
My heart hurts so much that it drives me crazy.
Who is Oh Soo Yeon? Who was she to me?
Did Soo Yeon give you that necklace?
This?
That's Soo Yeon's necklace.
You gave it to her as a present when you were young.
I picked it out for you because you asked for my help.
Soo Yeon...
knew me since I was young?
Her name used to be Jeong Eun.
Cha Jeong Eun.
Where is the needle?
When you were infected by the MK2 virus,
she's the one who saved you.
Please...
Soo Yeon...
saved my life?
Yes.
He died because of your father! Bring back my husband!
She went through a lot of trouble after that.
That's when she changed her name to Oh Soo Yeon.
Aren't you Oh Soo Yeon?
I am.
When you were falsely accused of homicide,
she worked really hard to prove your innocence.
I trust you. Something must have gone wrong.
I finished drawing.
In the end,
she lost her little brother.
Who are you?
Dong Soo! What's wrong, Dong Soo? Open your eyes!
Dong Soo...
Dong Soo. Dong Soo...
I remember that much.
But what happened after that?
Did I...
love Soo Yeon?
You two...
loved each other dearly.
Did Soo Yeon...
love me, too?
Yes.
To the point where I was jealous.
Soo Yeon...
thought you were dead.
That's why she partnered with Gun Woo to take revenge.
Are you going to be all right?
The hypnosis won't come undone that easily.
If he finds out about his past with Soo Yeon,
I'm sure he'll try to have the same relationship again.
I think it's best to stop that from happening.
Are you saying that the pain will come back?
It's hard to predict.
That's why you should stop him.
If he starts to get the pain again,
hypnosis might not work this time.
Gun Woo is out of the hospital.
I have to meet Soo Yeon right now.
I think we should started with the other...
Didn't you hear me?
I need to meet her.
What are you going to do?
Soo Yeon and I were in love.
How can I forget about that like a fool?
So what can you do?
Mr Moon.
Gun Woo saved Soo Yeon's life when she sank under water.
He even got stabbed in front of her.
That's why I need to get her from...
What if she won't come back?
You're a man of her past, and he's her man at the moment.
How will you deal with the disappointment...
if she won't come back to you?
If you want Soo Yeon back, you have to ruin Gun Woo first.
She isn't your priority.
Why did you come back to Korea?
Weren't you going to get your revenge...
on Il Jae and Gwang Woo, and take over Dodo Group?
We just managed to fix our gunpoint on the target.
If you want to live in the past,
I will...
leave your side.
They are animals.
How blinded are they to stab you?
I'm okay, but I'm worried about you.
I doubt...
that they will assault me.
We never know.
Why don't we give the video about your medicine over to the police?
I can't do that.
It's better...
to take care of family business within the family.
I feel nervous, Father.
I need to at least...
file for a restraining order so that they can't get near you.
I'll think about it.
Lawyer Oh.
What happened with my inheritance?
As you said,
I arranged 60 percent for Vice Chairman Do...
and 40 percent for CEO Do Shin Young.
We'll rearrange that.
It'll be 80 percent for Gun Woo...
and 20 percent for Shin Young.
Father, I'm grateful but...
Come to think about it,
I'm disappointed in Shin Young, too.
Just do as I say.
Yes, Sir.
When will you be finished with Father's will?
He has to file a lawsuit to retrieve what he gave...
to Ms Hwang and Gwang Woo.
It'll take a while for his will to be finished.
I want this to be settled as soon as possible.
Only then will Gwang Woo give up on trying anything.
I'll find a way.
Is Chairman still doing bad?
What?
Oh, I heard he doesn't have dementia,
so don't worry, Soo Yeon.
I think his side effects are taking too long to wear out.
Dinner was too salty!
You haven't had dinner yet, Chairman.
Tell my wife to come.
Chairman.
Ms Hwang left the house.
Leave the house? Where did she go?
She's at Hwang Jae Man's house in Hongeun-dong.
What's with her?
She burnt all of my shirts while ironing them today.
She must have ran away because she was scared, right?
What's with this pan?
Mum, I don't want those eggs.
Aunt.
What are you doing?
Why do you ask? I didn't like the side dishes,
so I wanted to make fried eggs for Gwang Woo.
You can't rub this all over the pan.
It's completely ruined. Look at this.
It's not my fault. It's because of this cheap pan.
I'm sure it's cheap for you,
but it was rather expensive for me.
My goodness, Congresswoman. You're awful.
I'll get a truck full of these pans if you want.
Take that truck out and make some money.
Stop watching television all day long.
You're so lazy.
How can I be treated like this?
Mum, let's get out of here.
What can we do? Do you have money?
I'll get a private loan and get us a house.
I really can't take how these people are treating you.
Hello?
Where are you?
Who is it?
It's your father.
Where are you?
Why do you want to know that?
Come back home right this second.
Are you...
telling me to come home?
I will forgive you.
Don't be scared and come back.
Honey.
I hope...
you're serious.
People make mistakes.
It's okay, come back.
Thank you, Honey.
I'll be there soon.
He's forgiving us.
Are you serious?
Pack your stuff.
Let's get out of this house.
Okay, Mum.
- Let's go.
-  Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
- Honey.
-  I'm here, Dad.
Mr Gong.
Why are they here?
You called them today...
What do you mean?
You told us to come back and that you forgive us.
Who forgave whom?
I heard you talk to Mum...
I will never forgive you two even if that's the last thing I do.
Mr Gong, get rid of them.
Are you joking with us?
You're the one who joked around with my life.
What kind of nonsense is this?
What? Nonsense?
Get rid of them.
Is this why you called us?
Did you want to get rid of us again?
If you're a chairman, act like one.
Don't be cheap and childish!
I can't eat like this. Let's go, Gwang Woo.
You should...
just hit me with a golf club.
Even I won't...
play a prank like this.
Mr Gong.
Look into how I can get a restraining order.
Yes, Sir.
Give me a glass.
Do you know why...
I bought in shares for Dodo Hotel...
instead of the holding company's shares?
Didn't you expect its price to fall thanks to MK2 vaccine?
When I gave over Dodo Pharmaceutical's shares,
the patent for MK2 vaccine was not yet given.
Did you want CEO Do Shin Young...
to own the hotel?
I wouldn't sell the holding company's stock...
just for that reason.
Then why?
I'm going to change...
the holding company...
to Dodo Hotel.
Then...
is that why you went into the Shareholders' Voting Agreement?
With my shares...
and Shin Young's shares,
I may be able to become Dodo Group's chairman.
Are you...
pulling the trigger soon?
Just as you said,
I'll forget about Soo Yeon for now.
I'll first destroy Gun Woo...
and bring her back after that.
If you stop me again then,
I'll fire you.
You have a meeting with the bankers tomorrow.
I was about to cancel it. I'm glad I didn't.
Chairman Kang.
You're always too busy to go play golf with me.
Why did you gather us today?
You meet with the vice chairman of Dodo Group often, don't you?
That's because of the Chinese ship order.
We're in the process of reviewing his application for a loan.
- Mr Moon.
-  Yes, Sir.
Dodo Group's bidding price is...
62,277,690 dollars.
This is a detailed outline of our agreement conditions.
To be honest,
I'm not sure if they'll be able to meet the conditions listed here.
Are you saying...
that you will break the agreement?
The contract will stay as it is. The problem is...
I'm not sure if they can make ships of great quality.
What is he talking about?
There are a lot of banks that go bankrupt after giving out loans.
If you need this document, please do let me know.
I intend on sharing it with you...
if you would like to see it.
What do you mean you can't give us a loan?
This deal is worth over 600 million dollars.
Our bank isn't doing too well.
You said you would just a few days ago.
I'm afraid I was too hasty...
in giving you my personal opinion.
Is it Congressman Hwang's doing?
It's not just you. The other banks also declined to give us a loan.
It seems like someone is behind this.
I'm sorry. I have to rush to another meeting.
Is it KT Corporation's Kang Gi Tan?
I'll see you another time.
We'll be in big trouble if we can't get that money.
It's Gi Tan. He's controlling everything from the behind.
Gun Woo is asking around everywhere for the loan.
Soo Yeon's helping Do Choong rearrange his assets, right?
That's what I've heard.
Soo Tak.
Can you check with Soo Yeon on the status of his inheritance?
I might be able to find out if I ask Nan Jeong.
Please meet with the Korean director of Gold Bank in Hong Kong.
Gold Bank is the one that's supervised by us.
Why do you want me to meet with them?
- We'll ask them for a loan.
-  Pardon?
Not for us, but for Dodo Group.
Are you saying you'll help Dodo Group?
Gun Woo may be struggling now,
but he'll end up finding the funds for the project.
You're right. Dodo Group will manage to find it.
That's why we should help.
I'll give the Korean director a heads-up.
Kang Ga Din.
We have to study.
Is it already time?
Who would dress like that to study?
Do you think I'm here to study?
I came to seduce my teacher.
I study better when I dress like this.
What kind of book is this?
- What is this?
-  It says right there.
"Economics for Dummies, Introduction to Economics".
You can study this on your own.
I've prepared your textbook. Follow me.
Wait for me, Ga Din.
What is all this?
You need to study all of them.
Finances, accounting, statistics, production management and more.
Are you telling me to study for the rest of my life?
Everyone is supposed to study all their lives.
When am I supposed to marry?
First, read all of them. Read and then debate over and over.
By then, your light head will become heavy.
Fine. I'll give it a try.
I'm smart.
I know. It's just empty, that's all.
I'm sensitive when I study. Don't bother me.
I'm going out for an hour.
Don't fall asleep and study.
"Debate"?
I'll surprise you, Ga Din.
Do Shin Young.
Wake up. Shin Young!
When did I fall asleep?
I even drooled.
How much did you read?
A lot.
- Let me check.
-  No, not this book.
It's too fun. I won't give it to you.
Is that why you were so deeply in sleep?
- Give it to me. You...
-  No!
Hey.
In a situation like this, the man usually...
kisses the girl in movies.
- Chairman Kang.
-  The inheritance...
- My apologies, Sir.
-  We'll come back later.
No, it's okay.
Shin Young was...
You're a naughty teacher.
You should mind your surroundings.
What? Shin Young, you...
It's okay. We'll get married anyway.
So...
What is happening with Chairman Do's inheritance?
Gun Woo is going to receive 80 percent...
of Chairman Do's assets.
What are you talking about? What about me?
You get the remaining 20 percent.
How can he divide the inheritance like that?
What did I do?
Sorry. I got angry.
I'm going to pay my dad a visit.
What do you plan on doing?
What do you think? I'll confront him.
Shin Young. Who am I?
Who else? You're Kang Ga Din.
We signed the Shareholders' Voting Agreement. We're partners.
- So?
-  Just do as I say.
I'll make sure you get all of Chairman Do's inheritance.
- Really?
-  Mr Moon,
how did it go with Gold Bank?
It went well.
How long...
do I have to get these shots?
The side effects from the medicine are severe. You need it for a while.
Please take care.
Repeat what you said earlier.
The banks are declining your request for a loan?
Yes, Father.
If you can't even persuade a mere banker,
how can you run a business?
I'm sorry. The fund problem will be resolved soon.
When?
Do you think the shipowners will wait for you forever?
Please trust me.
- Mr Gong.
-  Yes, Sir.
Set a time for me with the bankers. I'll solve it myself.
He can't meet with the bankers.
I know that. He might talk nonsense in front of them.
If that happens, our company will be at a risk.
Please stop him.
Don't worry about that.
Are you Doctor Hwang Seung Man?
- Yes.
-  Chairman Hwang wants to see you.
Here is Dr Hwang.
Long time no see, Dr Hwang.
It has already been a year since we had a drink.
Yes, that's right.
Why did you want to see me?
Do Choong.
What does he have?
The side effects of his medication...
Are you saying his medication caused dementia?
It's not dementia.
Dr Hwang!
You appeared on TV...
and we gave you a plaque for your outstanding services.
Must I...
reveal your true colours to make you tell the truth?
Do Choong.
What illness does he have?
It is...
dementia.
getting worse.
Gun Woo.
Did he pay you off...
to keep quiet?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I see.
Does he really have dementia?
Gun Woo told Doctor Hwang...
to keep it a secret until...
the inheritance has been distributed.
That means he's hiding Father's illness...
so he can take what isn't his.
It's pretty obvious what he's up to.
He's so evil.
How could he do such a thing?
You're just as bad.
You swapped his medication.
Are you...
fanning the flames?
Who are you calling?
We can't waste time.
We have to tell Father...
what Gun Woo is really up to.
Goodness.
- Hello?
-  It's me, Gwang Woo.
Hang up.
You're being deceived.
What do you mean?
You...
have dementia.
What? Dementia?
Yes, dementia.
Gun Woo and Doctor Hwang...
ganged up on you to hoodwink you.
Are you listening?
Keep talking.
You're rewriting your will, aren't you?
Stop it right now.
Gun Woo's putting you in danger...
so he can take everything you have.
Where are you right now?
I'll come over...
and explain everything.
Gwang Woo.
Yes, Father.
Dementia?
Why don't you pray that I die?
How dare you talk such nonsense!
Father.
I filed for a restraining order against you.
Come by and see what happens.
A restraining order?
What?
For as long as I live,
I will fight to take back the assets I gave...
to you and your mother.
Let's see you two end up without a penny!
Did he just say...
he filed for a restraining order?
Yes.
This is all Gun Woo's fault.
He is...
controlling Father like a puppet.
What should we do?
Help us, Jae Man.
How dare he make me...
as a dementia patient?
If I don't keep my wits about me,
they might take things from under my nose.
What?
I'd like to have dinner with you.
I'm in no mood for that. Let's eat...
This is Kang Gi Tan.
Are you busy preparing for the appeal?
We have to make sure Il Jae remains behind bars.
What's a vice chairman doing skipping meals?
I had a long day.
Can you not get a loan?
I can't.
I think Gi Tan got to the banks before I did.
Why would he?
I think he wants Dodo Group.
That might be why he keeps Shin Young close.
He approached her on purpose?
I'm sure I'm right.
He wouldn't do such a thing.
Have you...
heard from him?
No. I guess he's busy.
I was too busy with the trial to call him too.
His memory...
must be back by now.
What are you thinking about?
What?
Nothing.
(Kang Gi Tan)
What do you want?
I have something to say.
Shall we meet?
I'm on my way to a dinner appointment.
Do you want to join us?
Can I?
Of course.
You know everyone.
Give me the address.
Write it down, Soo Yeon.
Okay.
Are you...
with Soo Yeon right now?
Yes. I'm at her place eating dinner.
What is it?
Can't you breathe?
I'm fine.
You...
must be with Shin Young.
I'll text you the address.
Be there.
Am I allowed to be there?
I'm going to ask Gi Tan for funds.
You can offer some moral support.
Welcome, Gun Woo.
Hello, Lawyer Oh.
Have a seat.
Why are you here, Father?
Say hello.
He's the vice chairman of Gold Bank in Hong Kong.
Nice to meet you. I'm Johnny Kim.
I'm Do Gun Woo.
Gold Bank offered...
to lend you the money...
with a refund guarantee.
Chairman K negotiated the deal.
I should go, Sir.
I will walk you out.
I won't go far.
You helped us...
avert a huge crisis.
Thank you.
I saw you run left and right trying to secure funding.
It upset Shin Young, too.
She asked me to intervene.
Chairman K...
does anything and everything I ask him to.
What do you think?
Don't you think they make a lovely couple?
They do.
I wholeheartedly support their marriage.
What made you side with me this time?
There are rumours that Gun Woo will marry Lawyer Oh.
Do you have your father's approval?
No, no.
That's not true.
Gun Woo has no intention of getting married yet.
You know his condition.
Don't get upset.
You look sweet together.
Dad.
Don't you think Gun Woo and Lawyer Oh would get along well?
Let's stop talking about that.
Lawyer Oh.
Yes, Sir.
When I amend your will, I'll revise the percentage of inheritance.
Shin Young gets 50 percent.
So does Gun Woo.
Thanks, Dad.
Now, I know why you offered to finance...
the shipbuilding project.
Are you the one who talked to the bank managers?
One hand holds a carrot, the other a whip.
Thanks for the lesson.
I still have a lot to teach you. If you want to learn,
- try being humble.
-  Do you...
remember your past...
with Soo Yeon?
Is your memory back?
It is.
In its full detail.
You can take the upper hand in business,
but I will not give up Soo Yeon.
Don't dream of taking her back. Give up while you can.
I already did.
What?
I don't care about her.
You wouldn't say something like that.
I guess you spread the rumour that you two were engaged.
Don't worry. I will marry her.
Focus on the business.
Lose Dodo Group...
and you lose Soo Yeon, too.
What did you say?
Stop flirting with my Gi Tan.
Do you think I'm flirting with him?
Yes, I do.
I can see all nine of your foxy tails.
They squirm.
- Maybe you're just insecure.
-  What?
Do you think you're a match for me?
If you don't think so,
then don't mind me.
Soo Yeon.
Do you know what love is?
I do. I know very well.
No, you don't know.
It hurts you so deep...
Are you trying to lecture me?
If you want to love Gi Tan,
find out where he hurts the most.
Stop acting like a selfish child.
Being able to suffer with him...
gives you the right to love him.
What a brat.
Why do I feel like I just lost?
Are you leaving?
Yes.
You didn't eat much earlier.
Don't worry about me. I should go.
Soo Yeon.
I'll call you that from now on.
Please don't. It makes me feel uncomfortable.
We used to be close colleagues.
Maybe you thought we were close, but I didn't think so.
I apologise. I didn't mean to make you feel uncomfortable.
Here you go.
- Eat up.
-  Thanks.
Sir.
What brings you to our tiny office?
- Send everyone out.
-  Pardon?
They were just about to eat their noodles.
Get out.
You can take the noodles with you.
What do you want?
Drop everything else and keep an eye on Kang Gi Tan.
- What?
-  Find out where he goes,
what he does and who he meets.
I want a full report on everything.
Yes, Sir. I'll put my boys...
- Do it yourself.
-  Me?
I'm pretty high up the ladder now. I don't do...
Do as you're told.
Yang Dong Yi.
Don't try to pull anything. I'm not like Gwang Woo.
I get what you mean.
I'll do it myself.
They're quick to notice things. Don't get caught.
I won't, Sir.
Checkmate.
Oh dear, I didn't see the cannon there.
Dodo Group's loan from Gold Bank...
means we practically control their finances.
What should come next?
Out of check.
Wouldn't it be liabilities?
Correct.
Once we control their debt,
we control most of Dodo Group.
The audit files I saw when I worked there...
listed a lot of bonds that mature this year.
Could you get a list of the owners...
of those bonds?
That shouldn't be too hard. I still know people who work there.
But most of the owners of the bonds...
are loan sharks.
Loan sharks?
Checkmate.
You got me again.
Gun Woo is on high alert.
We have to buy the bonds...
before he notices.
Loan sharks?
He's sniffing around private money markets?
Gi Tan doesn't move in person.
Moon Tae Gwang's doing all the legwork.
It didn't look like he was borrowing money.
Bonds.
What?
The matured bonds.
That's what he's after.
I heard that someone there owns a lot of bonds...
belonging to Dodo Group.
We have to stop him. If Gi Tan buys those bonds,
then Dodo Group is doomed.
The day we get the matured bonds...
will be the day Dodo Group shuts down.
Don't you think you should meet one of the bigger financiers?
- I should.
-  I heard that...
he's pretty cranky.
Don't worry. I can deal with that.
Il Jae's appeal begins today. Shouldn't you be there?
I should.
I'd love to see him scrunch up his ugly face.
- How does that feel?
-  Good.
I wish you luck today.
I won't be coming back here.
I'll pray for you.
Choong Dong.
You might have to stay here a little longer.
Don't worry about me.
I'll do what I can to get you paroled soon.
Is Prosecutor Choi worth trusting?
He said he'd go for the highest sentence possible.
All rise and greet the judge.
Are you sure you want to announce your candidacy today?
Ji Soo.
I survived...
the corrupt world of politics...
for this day.
That's what worries me.
Il Jae's trial begins today and I don't want that...
to get you into trouble again.
Don't worry about that.
While I campaign to become president,
I will not have to worry about Il Jae.
It's time to leave for your press conference.
Sure.
Bye.
Byun Il Jae.
You bribed another candidate...
and we have clear evidence you tried to cover it up.
You violated election laws.
However,
the charges of abduction and...
attempted murder of lawyer Oh Soo Yeon...
lacks evidence.
I will not charge you for that.
Therefore, this court sentences Byun Il Jae...
to two years in prison and three years in probation.
Doesn't that mean he gets out?
What kind of a paralegal doesn't know that?
Mr Hwang Jae Man is here.
- Hwang Jae Man.
-  Hwang Jae Man.
Thank you.
Take your seats.
Could I ask you a question first?
Your son-in-law...
mayoral elect Byun Il Jae's appeal is underway right now.
Isn't this a bad time to run for president?
You're getting ahead of yourself.
I see you aren't aware that...
Byun Il Jae...
is no longer...
my son-in-law.
He is in the process...
of divorcing my daughter.
If you don't believe me,
once we are done here,
check the public records yourselves.
Where are you going?
The prosecutor broke every promise he made.
He didn't use the reports I gave him.
He didn't even ask any questions.
The trial's over.
I'll take him to Supreme Court.
Everything he did...
Prosecution refused to appeal!
That's the reality...
of the legal system...
we believed in.
I will...
judge Il Jae myself.
I can do better than this.
I, Hwang Jae Man,
will run for presidency of the Republic of Korea.
This is my promise to you.
Justice.
A society in which justice prevails.
As of today,
I declare war against...
corruption and all things illegal!
I am...
finally back, Guk Cheol.
(Monster)
He betrayed him?
He'll be willing to meet me at least.
It's worth the try if we get the timing right.
You must stick to me.
Did you have anything to do with Gwang Woo killing Gi Tan's parents?
I think we should let Dad go.
You stand a chance if we help you.
Are you suggesting we join forces?
It's about what happens next.
This is Kang Gi Tan. Could we meet?