(Episode 41)
I, Hwang Jae Man,
will run for presidency of the Republic of Korea.
This is my promise to you.
Justice.
A society in which justice prevails.
As of today,
I declare war against...
corruption and all things illegal!
- Hwang Jae Man! - Hwang Jae Man!
I am...
finally back, Guk Cheol.
Congresswoman Hwang Ji Soo, the daughter of Hwang Jae Man,
the presidential candidate, is said to be in a divorce with Byun Il Jae.
Because of Byun's violation of the election law...
during his Seoul mayor election, Hwang Jae Man seemed threatened.
People believe this is a desperate measure conducted by Hwang Jae Man,
who wanted to be in the next presidential election.
Hwang Jae Man has...
It seems like Jae Man is finally getting rid of Il Jae's traces.
He's a powerful man,
but I'm sure he was intimidated by your threat.
Why do you think...
the prosecutor didn't appeal his case to the Supreme Court?
Are you saying that Jae Man is behind this?
I'm sure of that.
Are you saying that they aren't really getting a divorce?
They will probably...
stay away during the election.
The problem will come afterwards.
If and when he becomes the president,
they may get back together.
That will make Il Jae...
the president's son-in-law.
Did you say he agreed on this divorce?
Take a look.
(Divorce Registration Form)
I've done everything I can...
for you two with the result of this retrial.
From now on,
you two will...
have to give way for my sake.
Hey.
You'll be away from him only for a short time.
After the election,
I'll make sure you two can get married again.
Where's Il Jae right now?
He'll go back to the prison first and leave from there.
I'm going over right now. Get ready.
Ji Soo.
Don't go.
We are still lawfully wedded.
He doesn't have anyone else.
If the reporters find you there,
I become...
a liar from the first day...
of my election campaign.
Hello?
It's me, Gi Tan.
Can we meet right now?
I saw that you made a very big decision.
A Firestone that can't start a fire is nothing but a stone.
I'm going on a long journey.
I can't carry around stones.
That's why I wanted to see you.
I want...
to light up your journey.
Will you become my Firestone in Il Jae's place?
I'll light up brighter than he did.
You probably need a lot of money for your campaign.
Money is even less trustworthy than people.
I don't even trust you.
How can I accept money from you for my election campaign?
Mr Moon.
I want to talk in private with Mr Hwang.
We should leave.
Yes, you can leave.
I'll be honest with you.
As a businessman,
I only use money where I'm certain of its purpose.
Are you saying you'll help me become a president...
and take advantage of it when I'm in power?
Out of all the conglomerate leaders in the country,
there isn't a single person who isn't an ex-convict.
Having the president on my side would be the best.
All those people...
end up getting arrested...
for trusting in people like me.
However, their companies would have grown by then already.
Korean law can be generous in front of money.
As a businessman,
it's a risk worth taking.
You're really...
forward.
I'm not as forward as you who threw away your son-in-law...
to become the president.
- I used to be with the NIS as well. - I already know.
You were well spoken of as an NIS agent.
Why did you go under Congressman Hwang instead?
The world is changing. I should see things eye to eye...
in order to survive.
Do you believe that this position is suitable for you?
You'll always live as the third-in-charge.
Congressman Hwang will never throw away Il Jae.
What is it that you want to say?
As you already know, we want to crush Byun Il Jae.
Are you asking me...
to help you?
I don't think there's any reason not to.
Nor do I have a reason.
I don't mind being the third-in-charge.
Sure, you may think so for now.
However, things will change once Congressman Hwang becomes President.
Power isn't something you can divide...
like a cake.
You'll be eaten up by the second-in-charge.
It's even more certain with Byun Il Jae.
Yes, Sir.
I'll be right down.
Make sure you separate Il Jae from Congressman Hwang for good.
If we help, it's definitely possible.
I'll be waiting for your call.
(Korea Penitentiary)
I was wondering who would come and greet me.
I didn't know it would be you.
- Lawyer Min. - Yes.
This is tofu made from organic beans.
It's super expensive.
Anyway, have some of this and never commit crimes again.
What's wrong with you?
You should be more respectful for the people who bought it.
Gosh, it smells.
It seems like the tofu has gone bad.
We probably had it out in the hot weather for too long.
It's really delicious if you eat it when it's just made.
I doubt you came here just to give me some tofu.
We came to visit a prisoner.
Your secretary, Oh Choong Dong.
Are you trying to get something out from Choong Dong?
I bet he knows the best about...
all the crimes you've committed so far.
Don't be so foolish, Lawyer Oh.
There is no way he will betray me even if the world comes to an end.
The thing with betrayal is,
it always happens with the person you trust the most.
Congressman Hwang gave up on you...
and Gun Woo turned his back on you.
How can you be so sure that Choong Dong won't betray you?
I realised it now.
A dignified strategy won't work for someone like you.
I won't be so careful with my strategies now.
Since there was a final ruling,
you can't convict me on the same charges.
What will you put me in jail for next time?
That's not what's important.
What's important is, when will you be released...
next time, if at all?
You won't ever get to taste tofu for your release again.
I'll make sure you rot in prison for the rest of your life.
Lawyer Oh.
Do you know what the biggest ordeal from the Pandora's box was?
It's the one that came out last. Hope.
Because of hope,
a whole new struggle begins.
You should rid yourself of any useless hopes.
You better...
mark those words.
Because the days when you struggle from hope...
will be upon you soon.
The taxis don't come around here much.
You have to go down that hill for the bus station.
You know how much buses cost, right?
We'll be late for our visit. Let's go.
Okay, we should go.
Gosh. You don't have a single person to pick you up. How sad.
I'll decline this visit. Please cancel it.
Officer Kim, how is your baby?
I'm sorry, but could you let him stay here...
for the visitation hour?
Yes, Sir. Hey, 2757.
I won't be opening my mouth until the time's up.
Then I'll just ask questions.
Did you kill my brother?
Or did Il Jae murder him...
with his own hands?
How many did you kill aside from Dong Soo?
Two? Three?
What on earth are you talking about?
I thought you weren't going to talk. Why are you yelling?
You killed Gi Tan's parents, too. Am I right?
Did you kill Su Do Hospital's Dr Jung Man Ok, too?
It wasn't me!
Then I guess it was Il Jae.
Yap all you want.
Officer Kim.
You're recording this, right?
Make sure you write down "Yap all you want."
Yes, Lawyer Min.
Oh Choong Dong.
When we reveal the truth,
Il Jae will blame you for everything.
Just to remind you, our country still has the death penalty.
While you keep your mouth shut for loyalty,
there is a rope...
dropping down to your neck.
Remember that.
I was released on probation thanks to you.
You got rid of all the evidence for me.
Why do you think they're all gone?
I still have a photocopy.
If you plan on putting Gi Tan and I into a fight...
while you snatch away Dodo Group,
forget about it now.
I was about to reach out my hand to you.
If anything, I'm the one reaching out.
You'll have to accept it if I do.
What if I decline?
I saw that you swindled a lot of funds through a paper company.
If I report it to the National Tax Service,
you'll have to give back all of that money.
Divorced and penniless?
I think it'll be very difficult for you to get back on your feet.
What is it that you want?
Make your Z Capital account in Hong Kong...
a joint account with me.
Do you want...
a portion of my money?
No, I don't care for your money.
But I want to make a deal so that you can't use any of your money...
without my permission.
Are you trying to tie me down...
with a joint contract?
You do not trust me and I do not trust you.
I think I need that much restraint...
for us to work together.
I have evidence...
of your corruption, too.
You can make that public.
I came to Korea empty-handed.
I don't mind leaving here...
empty-handed again.
Honey.
Welcome home, Il Jae.
If I knew no one was picking you up,
I would've went out myself.
I felt very sorry...
for those who had...
no one to greet them.
Where's your father?
He has a dinner appointment. He'll be late.
My goodness, I thought things were promising when he got elected,
but it was a matter of seconds before he became a trainwreck.
We aren't the ones to talk.
We're living off of someone else, too.
I have things in mind, Mum.
Just wait a little more.
I can't let this be.
Who are you calling?
I'm telling Shin Young that your father has dementia.
No, Mum.
Give that to me. Don't tell her.
The least she can do is stop him from doing weird things.
He's completely smitten with Gun Woo right now.
If she becomes a trouble for Father,
that's the end of you and me as I know it.
Are you going to sit around and watch Gun Woo take his assets?
I recently filed a form to declare Father...
incompetent...
to the domestic affairs court.
Didn't you think I knew about that?
It takes months before that gets processed.
If he finishes his will before that, everything is over.
Mum, sometimes you seem very narrow-minded.
We can ask Uncle to process it.
Come on, you should make use of your great connections.
That's a way.
If the court processes it...
without extra procedures,
a doctor will be...
dispatched to examine him...
within a few days.
If he's declared...
incompetent at that time,
he will no longer be able to edit his will.
You're so smart, my son.
You should've started thinking like that sooner.
Mum.
It's not too great to use your brain continuously.
You have to use it when you really need to.
Honey, we're still lawfully married.
You can stay here until the process is through.
Your father...
probably wants me to leave as soon as I can.
Honey, are you disappointed in me, too?
Tell me.
You aren't really leaving me forever, are you?
We can get married again after the election.
That's what Father promised me.
We can do that if he doesn't get elected.
But if he does get elected,
we can never be together.
Ji Soo.
If you don't want to part with me,
you must be completely on my side.
What is that like?
Think the way I want you to think...
and move the way I want you to move.
Are you...
holding a grudge...
against Father?
No.
I will make sure...
that I make Mr Hwang the president.
After that,
I'll make sure that he can never abandon me.
You must help me...
for that to happen.
Do not doubt anything I do.
Help me blindly.
There is no one else who's more precious to me than you.
Me too, Ji Soo.
That's why I need your help.
We can't be separated.
These are the lists of people who hold matured bonds for Dodo Group.
This man named So Gil Du holds a huge amount of bonds.
In other words,
he has half the lifeline of Dodo Group.
You should meet this man.
He probably won't see me.
You should go yourself.
Is he very particular about things?
Not only is he particular, but he's also odd and ill-tempered.
Let's go and meet him now.
I'll make a call.
I'm the one who called.
Come in.
Please.
Your guests are here.
Hello, Sir.
I am Kang Gi Tan of KT Corporation.
What does this KT Corporation...
or whatever it is do?
It's an investment company.
An investment.
That's a perfect business to draw frauds.
Sir, I came to ask you for a favour.
You don't even know me.
How can you ask me for a favour?
I'm sure...
you will be interested in this business plan as well.
Tell me.
I want to buy out your matured bonds...
for Dodo Group.
What will you do with it?
I plan to take over Dodo Group.
I see.
That means...
you are corporate hunters.
We're a legal investment company.
You can do a quick search to find out more about us.
When farmers use traps instead of sickles,
they become hunters.
Hunting or farming, if you sell your bonds to me,
you won't suffer any losses.
Do Chi.
Get rid of these men and sprinkle some salt.
And make that organic.
You should at least hear our...
I've been...
dealing with money in this business for 30 years.
I can tell very quickly if it's clean money...
or corrupt money.
A business plan?
You're trying to buy out...
a perfectly good company and sell it off in little pieces.
I see right through you.
- Sir. - I'm not your sir.
You don't even know me.
What are you doing? Kick them out right now.
Yes, Sir.
Get out.
Gosh.
How dare you throw salt at us?
Don't you dare come back to visit him.
I'm sorry.
I should've researched for more information about him.
Even if you did, the result would've been the same.
Why don't you buy out other people's bonds?
You can't take over Dodo Group with that.
So Gil Du.
We must persuade him.
I will look for more information about him.
Gi Tan is utterly mistaken.
So Gil Du is a tough man.
He won't move with such a visit.
Is he that powerful?
Not only does he hold a lot of bonds,
he is a big player in the private loan business.
I heard he has a huge amount of cash.
Anyway.
There are no rich men in this land who never borrowed money from him.
But he still goes to markets to retrieve daily instalment loans.
Thank you.
If someone can't pay,
he'd at least take what they sell to make up for it.
He's a cold-blooded man.
He's known as Chainsaw So among those merchants.
- Chainsaw? - It means he can rip them apart.
There are many people whose lives were ruined after using his money.
What an awful man.
He's awfully rich but still takes money from the markets.
He's really terrible.
You know Chairman Cho of Namsan Corporation, right?
He was bankrupt after turning his claims over.
They say, that's also why Chairman Cho committed suicide.
What Gi Tan is after are those mature bonds he has.
He will never sell them.
Think about it.
He receives interest every month from Dodo Group. Why sell it?
Gi Tan will do anything for whatever he wants.
We never know, so keep an eye on it.
Don't you worry.
Does Chainsaw So have family?
Well...
He lost his wife and daughter in an accident 20 years ago.
He's living alone.
Does he have a hobby?
He doesn't drink or smoke.
He doesn't have a girlfriend either.
His only hobby is playing go.
He's a hard one to win over.
One thing to note...
is that he might have paranoia.
- Paranoia? - Yes.
Aside from a few special days, he has the same schedule every day.
He goes to the same place at the same time every day.
He can't stand people or things that he's not...
familiar with.
No wonder he didn't look me in the eyes.
Study his daily schedule and report back to me.
Yes, Sir.
Yes, Mr Gong.
Gun Woo. We're in trouble.
The chairman has disappeared.
What do you mean he disappeared?
I thought he was taking a nap, but he's nowhere to be found.
Report to the police first.
Send out some people to check the places he often goes to.
Okay.
What's wrong?
(Han Sang Goo)
Where are you right now?
I'm at the office.
The chairman has disappeared. Can you go see if...
he went to Jae Man's house?
Yes, Sir.
Jae Man.
You know the Chief of the Family Court, don't you?
We have to make sure he's found legally incompetent...
before he writes up the will.
He just announced his participation in the presidential election.
Why do you have to ask him for such a favour?
It won't be good for you either if we become penniless.
There's no harm in it for us.
It will cost a lot for the campaign. We can help.
We don't need your help. We have enough money.
What is it? Are you getting compensation money...
from your divorce?
Hey! Why are you bringing that up?
Stop that.
Jae Man.
Please help us out.
Chairman Do is here to see you.
Why... Why is he here?
Why did you come here?
Honey. How are you feeling?
Honey. How are you feeling? Are you better?
He's at it again.
I'm sorry, Honey.
I've been so bad at taking care of you when you're pregnant.
What? Pregnant?
I bought a onesie for our baby...
on my way here.
The doctor said it's a son, right?
I thought about his name.
What do you think about "Gwang Woo"?
It means "bright and lucky".
He'll be a bright and lucky guy.
I bet you this boy...
will become an important figure.
You know how busy...
my work is.
Once this project I'm working on is finished,
I'll be...
really good to you.
Please trust in me, Gwi Ja.
You should have been good to me before you went crazy...
or you should have gone crazy earlier.
I'm...
hungry.
Give me some food.
Good work.
He's at Jae Man's right now.
He went there alone?
By now, they would have noticed...
his Alzheimer's.
We should hurry up and get him.
Your cooking is just my taste.
I made that.
Be quiet.
What's wrong with you, Jae Man?
If your sister came to see you because she's mad at me,
you should have persuaded her to go back home!
- Chew slowly. - Thank you, Honey.
Here. Have some water.
When did you buy this fish?
What do you think?
It's bad enough to prove that he's incompetent, right?
Yes. I'll give the chief a call.
Thank you.
Shouldn't we look after Dad?
Of course.
Luck just rolled right in.
You said he acts normal once in a while, though.
It doesn't matter.
We'll just hide him in a home where Gun Woo can't find him.
- Yes. - It's Gun Woo.
What a surprise. What makes you call me?
I know Father is there with you.
We're outside the door. Bring him out.
Mum. Gun Woo says...
he's just outside.
How did he find out already?
You know you're under a restraining order, right?
Don't make me call the police and bring him out.
I think we better let him go.
It'll be over once we can prove his incompetency.
Let him go.
Are you sure the chairman is all right?
I'm worried...
- It's true that he has Alzheimer's. - What?
I got the call from Dr Hwang today.
The result came out from a test.
The chairman has Alzheimer's?
That's why you must be careful that this doesn't happen again.
All right, Gun Woo.
I'll be extra cautious.
He leaves home right at 6am.
He takes the same route for his daily walk.
Good morning.
Whenever he goes on his walk,
he only stretches in front of a specific tree.
He then has an egg sandwich and coffee at a nearby cafe.
He'll finish his morning schedule by collecting money from the market.
After that, he goes to a restaurant he's been a regular at for 30 years.
He has either kimchi jjigae or doenjang jjigae for lunch.
In the afternoon, he works at home.
What kind of schedule is that?
It's like he's on a treadmill.
That's why there is no room for us to squeeze in.
Only if he was a tiny bit interested in what I had to say,
I'm sure I could persuade him then.
We don't have much time.
Let's give up on Chainsaw So and look for an alternative.
I asked around while tailing him.
He's a stubborn guy. A no is a no even with a knife to his neck.
Why are you so stressed?
The solution's right there.
Leave us alone. I can't think as it is.
Ruin his daily life.
What would happen to him then?
He'd go out of his mind.
I'm about to go out of my mind, so leave before I do.
You're dumb for someone who went to Stanford.
Just buy everything.
What did you just say?
Buy the cafe and restaurant that he goes to.
You said he's paranoid.
That will drive him crazy.
Shin Young. You're really...
Fine, I'll go.
You don't have to be so cranky.
You saved my life. You're the best!
We shouldn't do this in front of the others.
Mr Moon, did you get what she just said?
If we turn his life upside down,
he'll have to come to you.
I don't care how much it takes. Take Soo Tak and buy everything.
Yes, Sir.
Why do you need to meet Chainsaw So desperately?
I will buy out all his matured Dodo Group bonds.
Matured bonds?
Will you threaten the whole company?
You just have to trust me and tag along.
Okay.
I did something great for you. What do I get in return?
I said I'd make you Dodo Group's Chairwoman.
That's part of the deal. Kiss me.
Nothing's for free.
Kiss me now.
Close your eyes.
What? Okay.
Hey! Kang Ga Din! Come back!
Gi Tan's going around buying the stores in the area?
Yes, and I just can't figure out why.
Wouldn't it be easier for you to strike a deal with Chainsaw So?
Who knows what Gi Tan will do if you give him time?
When will he come home?
He should be here any minute...
There he is. That's him.
Chairman So.
Chairman So?
Who are you?
I was waiting for you.
I'm from Dodo Group.
Do Chi, did he make an appointment?
No, Sir.
Send them away and set an appointment.
Yes, Sir.
My father sent me.
Who is your father?
Chairman Do Choong of Dodo Group.
Chairman Do?
You're Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Come in for some rice punch.
Thank you.
Kang Gi Tan?
No one with that name was here.
He owns KT Corporation.
Oh, that hunter?
We met. What about him?
He's trying to buy your matured bonds.
So what?
Are you here because you're afraid I'll sell them to him?
He is much more cunning than you take him for.
Didn't your father tell me about you?
I've heard rumours about you.
You did not.
That's why you're here.
I will never fall for his tricks.
Get back to running the company.
Yes, Sir. I trust you'll do the right thing.
Wait.
How is your father's health?
Rumour says he is very unwell.
He isn't as ill as the rumours say he is.
How shall I proceed with your will?
Let's make a recording.
You said...
I need two witnesses.
Yes. Do you have someone in mind?
Him.
Mr Gong is one.
The other...
should be Gi Tan.
Chairman Kang?
He recently...
solved a huge financial issue for us.
He's also...
very close to Shin Young.
I think I can trust him with this.
Yes, Sir. I see what you mean.
When shall we do it?
Next Monday sounds good.
Tell Chairman Kang what I said.
I will, Sir.
Ga Din.
Is there anything that makes you sad?
Why would you ask that?
Someone said that...
I should learn to see if the man I like is hurting.
Try to put something in your head instead of breaking my heart.
You're so cold and mean to me...
because something inside is hurting.
I hate women who talk too much.
Stop avoid the situation.
Tell me if something hurts.
I'll help you with it.
Just try not to make things worse for me.
Don't mock me.
It's rude to mistreat me...
because I like you.
What's wrong with you today?
Do you know why my parents drifted apart?
It's because my dad looked down on my mum.
My mum used to love my dad a lot.
Then it turned to hatred.
I saw it all happen.
You will marry me.
Be good to me or I'll nag you forever.
How many times must I say that I won't marry you?
Sir, Lawyer Oh is here to see you.
Why is she here?
Excuse us for a minute.
No, I'm going to study.
Then study hard. I'll leave you to it.
Fine. I'll leave.
Have a seat.
Would you like a drink?
No thanks.
"Have a seat."
"Would you like a drink?"
He's cheap for a chairman.
Why doesn't he play hard to get like he did with me?
Miss. Miss!
Congresswoman Hwang is here.
Ji Soo? What's she doing here?
Why would you come to see me?
Do you like Kang Gi Tan?
Why would you ask that?
Gwang Woo's right.
You've fallen for him.
Why do you care where I fall?
Listen carefully.
He's using you.
Ji Soo.
Don't you have anything better to do?
Why waste your time with gossip?
- Shin Young. - I have nothing more to hear.
- Get out. - Gi Tan's parents.
Gwang Woo killed them.
Gun Woo killed...
Professor Na Do Gwang and framed Gi Tan.
If you think I'm lying,
ask Gi Tan to confirm it for you.
You're just a member of a family he swore to tear down.
He will use you for as much as you're worth...
then get rid of you.
It would be an honour.
It's quite meaningful to witness a will being written.
May I tell Chairman Do that you have accepted?
Yes.
Okay.
Mr Gong, this is Lawyer Oh.
Chairman Kang agreed to be a witness.
Yes, pass him the message. Bye.
I should get going, then.
You don't have to get up. You must be busy.
I have to take care of some business outside.
Did you wait until now?
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Let's not do this again. I feel terrible.
It'll be daybreak soon.
You wasted your time.
Oh, right.
Did you know that Soo Yeon and Gi Tan were first loves?
You didn't.
We meet again.
I'm very impressed.
You split up a perfectly fine couple.
Who is perfectly fine? Il Jae?
Or you?
Watch it, Soo Yeon.
You must still love him a lot.
I hope the divorce wasn't for show.
I plan to send you a little gift. When you see his true colours,
you'll thank me for it.
I did as you said.
Good.
Gi Tan's doing what he can to swallow the company.
I must do what I can to stop him.
So...
Gwang Woo's killing Gi Tan's parents...
has nothing to do with you, right?
He thinks you're his worst enemy.
I wondered if it was about that.
You killed Jung Man Ok, but he thinks I did.
Then I framed him for murder and sent him to prison,
and now he hates me even more on top of that.
I'm sorry.
It all happened because of me.
Let's not look back at the past.
We just have to go forward.
(Sudo Medical Foundation Director and Wife Die in a Car Crash)
Gwang Woo not only killed Gi Tan's parents,
but he set fire to the laboratory to cover up illegal research.
Mr Moon, Chainsaw So just left home.
(Private Property)
You can't touch that.
This is private property. You can't go this way.
"Private property"?
I took this path for over 30 years.
I see.
I bought this property.
(Land Register)
Don't step on my land.
Aren't you...
Turn around and take the longer route.
Go that way from now on.
It's over there.
Let's go, Do Chi.
All right.
Soo Tak, Chainsaw's headed your way.
This feels so good.
Are you new here?
Why?
You might not know, but this tree...
- is the chairman's... - Wait.
Didn't you come by to see me once?
You remember me?
I work for Chairman Kang.
Did he put you up to this?
Anyone can exercise on a hiking trail.
When will you be done?
When my chairman calls and tells me to stop.
This feels so good.
Let's go, Do Chi.
What about your exercise?
Skipping one day won't kill me.
This is great.
Mr Moon, he just left.
I'm hungry.
- Order my usual. - Yes, Sir.
Sorry, we're closed for the day.
Our chairman...
bought this place.
You'll serve him and not me?
The egg sandwich that you always have.
It tastes terrible.
This is a terrible spot for a cafe.
I think I'll turn it into a convenience store.
Are you...
trying to fight me?
I'm spending my own money.
Is that a problem?
Let's go, Do Chi.
I won't die if I don't eat my usual coffee and sandwich.
Goodbye.
Move.
I hope this works.
Ms Kim, two kimchi jjigae.
Try the tofu.
This is delicious.
The jjigae's good.
Hello again.
Did you buy this restaurant, too?
Yes. I paid the owner more than the market price.
You haven't eaten, have you?
I'll let you eat today.
Come and join us.
How many companies did you drive under this way?
People call you Chainsaw.
How many poor people did you steal from?
Kang Gi Tan.
You can't get what you want from me this way.
He remembers my name.
That's good enough for me.
Let's see what you can do.
I'm pretty stubborn myself.
Mr Moon, kick them out and sprinkle some salt.
What salt was it?
- Organic salt. - That's it.
Organic salt! That's right. Sprinkle that.
Get out of here, please.
Out. You aren't welcome here.
Get out.
Can I have more rice?
Gi Tan...
will be your witness?
Why?
Does it upset you?
No. I see why you trust him.
Gun Woo.
I gave up on Gwang Woo.
I'd like you...
to look after Shin Young for me.
I like her.
She's my only sister.
Pour me some water.
Here you go.
Gun Woo.
Why can't I move my hands?
It must be the stress.
You'll feel better after a nap.
I'll help you drink.
Father.
Doctor Hwang betrayed us?
I saw him meet with Madam Hwang at her brother's house.
You said he'd only live a few months...
once he starts feeling numb.
Yes. I'd give him less than six months.
How much did you tell Gwi Ja?
- Pardon? - Lying won't help you now.
Tell the truth.
I'm sorry.
Congressman Hwang forced me into telling him.
What do they know...
other than the dementia?
They don't know that...
Chairman Do doesn't have long to live.
That's the truth, Sir.
You can go.
We need to change our plan.
Find someone who can imitate my father's handwriting.
What for?
I can't let Shin Young take half.
I'll forge a written will...
that will make the recording null and void.
I know some document forgers in Insa-dong.
It has to be exact.
Yes, Sir.
Not doing what I usually do...
messed me up so much that I can't concentrate.
Here's your medication.
Sir.
Get Kang Gi Tan's number.
Will you meet him?
He's the first man...
to make me feel so uneasy...
in the last 10 years.
I need to find out...
what he's thinking.
How is Gi Tan doing?
He'll focus on work for now.
Once we're done with Il Jae,
I won't have any more business with him.
Okay.
Sir.
Chainsaw wants to meet you.
Thanks to you,
I had to take some pills...
I hadn't in 10 years.
You bought all of my regular hangouts...
just to meet me.
Isn't that too much?
Talent or wisdom you lack...
you can always borrow from someone else.
But not passion.
I wanted you...
to see my passion.
Do you want to take over Dodo Group?
Yes.
Do you have enough money to purchase the bonds?
What I lack...
I will borrow from you.
You will borrow my money to buy my bonds?
Do you know I charge a lot?
Once I take over Dodo Group,
whether it be a company or land,
I will give you everything you need.
There are many other companies.
Why do you want Dodo?
Chairman Do isn't in his right mind.
His three children...
are already fighting each other over the inheritance.
Madam Hwang is looking to make a comeback,
and now Byun Il Jae has jumped into the folds.
It's much more complicated than it seems from the outside.
That makes it an easy prey for someone like you.
If you're holding onto the bonds...
for the interest,
sell them to me.
If not, you will suffer a great loss.
I can't believe I'm being threatened by someone your age.
It's not a threat.
I'm telling you what will happen very soon.
My nickname is Chainsaw.
I never waver when I make a decision.
I will take your word for it.
You won't regret it, Sir.
You made him give in.
Once Gun Woo's done for,
I will propose to Soo Yeon.
I can get her back...
very soon.
(Civil Code...)
(Legally incompetent)
Soo Yeon, Gun Woo's outside.
Gun Woo?
Gun Woo.
What is it? Is something wrong?
My father...
has six months to live.
What do you mean?
What's going on?
Doctor Hwang just told me.
He has vascular dementia.
It's terminal.
I'm sorry.
I have to be selfish.
I can't wait any longer.
Before he passes away,
marry me.
If you can't marry me, let's get engaged at least.
Gun Woo.
(Monster)
Don't expect anything from me any more.
This isn't what you had promised.
I have an idea, Gun Woo.
Mr Gong, who is this?
You don't have much longer.
Are you saying that you can help me?
I will do what you've asked me to do.
I'm sure he's up to something, but I'm not sure what that is.
I'm sorry that my answer is so late.
Let's get engaged.