My father...
has six months to live.
Before he passes away,
marry me.
If you can't marry me,
let's get engaged at least.
Gun Woo.
Are you sure you won't regret it?
You might not be happy...
if you marry me.
All I need is you.
That's enough...
for me to be happy.
Don't think about anything else.
Please be brave for me...
just this once.
Can you...
give me some time?
It won't take long.
All right. I'll be waiting for you.
Gun Woo.
Don't be so upset...
about what happened to the chairman.
Thank you, Soo Yeon.
(Episode 42)
It's an agreement...
to show that Z Capital will be under both of our names.
(Joint Name Contract)
(Do Gun Woo)
With that, we're now partners.
When will we terminate the agreement?
Once Gi Tan is eliminated.
You better...
hand over the copies of my documents.
You didn't make more copies, did you?
We have to trust each other from now on.
If we break the trust, we can't be partners any more.
Soo Yeon won't be please to find your working with me.
I'm not trying to threaten you.
I'm just worried, that's all.
If you dare mention this to her, you won't be able to use...
any money from the Z Capital account.
If you try to get in my way,
I'll show this contract to Soo Yeon.
You might think that you've tied me down, but I don't think so.
This agreement...
will make our relationship stronger.
What's gotten into you? Why did you ask me out for drinks?
Good timing. I had to talk to you about Dad anyway.
You have no idea what's going on with the inheritance do you?
Gun Woo, that jerk,
is using Dad's sickness as an excuse...
Listen carefully because I won't treat you like a brother any more.
What's wrong? Are you drunk already?
I don't care what Gun Woo did to Gi Tan. It's not my problem.
However, it's different with you...
because you were my brother.
Hey.
Shin Young.
Murderer.
What?
I know you killed Gi Tan's parents.
Whom did you hear that from?
Did Gi Tan say that?
Don't expect anything from me from now on.
This is the end between us.
If we're no longer family,
do you think it'll work out between you and Gi Tan?
What?
Don't be so stupid.
Even if you try,
I'm still your brother.
Why do you think I did that?
I did it to save our company.
It wasn't for me. I did it for Dad and Dodo Group!
Do you call that an excuse?
Hey!
Why would I make an excuse to you?
Also,
I'm not scared even if you're no longer my family. But!
Remember this one thing.
You're nothing to Gi Tan.
He'll only use you like me.
All the sins and debt you've committed and owe to Gi Tan...
I'll repay them all.
So...
don't mind me and lead a proper life.
Sir! Sir!
Have you seen CEO Do?
No.
She missed her meeting and she's not picking up her phone.
I'm a little worried.
Maybe she went to the bathhouse.
She didn't say a word today and seemed down.
Shin Young can look sad?
Yes.
(Kang Ga Din)
Kang Ga Din. Did you get my telepathy?
I was just thinking about you, too.
- Are you drinking right now?
-  Yes.
I'm really craving drinks today.
Whom are you with?
With a handsome man.
- Where are you right now?
-  At a cart bar near the hotel.
Why do you ask? Are you going to take me home?
Are you crazy? Why would I go when you're drinking with a guy?
Right.
Don't come.
I don't need you to come.
Nothing happened, right?
This guy tells me he really likes me. What should I do?
Good luck. Don't get too drunk though.
I knew she'd pick up your call.
She says she's drinking with a guy. Don't worry.
With a guy? That's impossible.
It's not like she'd drink alone.
Gosh. Why is she worrying me?
Are you going?
What if she's drunk again?
Kang Gi Tan!
Why did you come? I told you not to.
What happened to your date?
He's right here. Inside me.
Why are you drinking by yourself?
Don't look at me like that. It makes me nervous.
I'm sorry, Gi Tan.
For what?
Just...
Everything.
Is this your new drinking habit?
I won't ever get drunk again in front of you...
and I won't do anything that you don't like.
Shin Young.
Do you know what's so attractive about you?
Being confident.
It doesn't matter whom you're with and where you are.
You're always confident and never discouraged.
That's your charm.
So don't say things like you're sorry. Okay?
You're Do Shin Young.
Okay.
I'll do everything you say.
We'll get busy starting tomorrow.
So let's drink today...
and start working hard from tomorrow.
(Dodo Group)
Yes, Mr Gong.
The chairman's condition is getting worse.
I think we should get him to a hospital.
I'll go home right now.
Thank you, Uncle.
Of course. I'll get him diagnosed incompetent...
to completely destroy Gun Woo.
Goodbye.
What did he say?
A doctor was just sent from the court to diagnose him.
Ji Soo,
can you take Mum home?
Why would I go there? You should go.
I have to talk to someone from the court today.
I need to get our restraining order lifted.
How would you lift that?
Hey, are you looking down on him right now?
No.
I'm not looking down on him.
Stop complaining and come right out.
Gun Woo.
You won't last much longer.
Is he doing very bad?
Yes. He's much worse today.
Mr Gong.
Who's this?
He doesn't recognise you, so make something up.
I am...
your new assistant as of today.
My assistant?
Did you hire him?
Yes, Sir.
He looks like someone I know.
Hey.
Why aren't we getting ready to go to Mr Hwang's house?
- Pardon?
-  I want to go see Gwi Ja.
He's been looking for her since early in the morning.
We should just let him see her.
Let's get him to the hospital.
Okay.
Sir.
Let's get dressed...
so we can go and see Mrs Hwang.
- Sure.
-  Okay.
- Mrs Hwang.
-  Who are you people?
They are here to diagnose him on a court order...
to announce your father as incompetent.
Honey.
It's me.
Mr Gong.
When did you hire...
a new housekeeper?
What?
You don't even...
recognise me any more.
He recognised you last time.
Get out of here. You're on a restraining order so...
Did you think I wouldn't know that he has dementia?
Excuse me.
He's my new assistant.
Did he do something wrong?
This is definite.
He doesn't recognise his wife and calls his son his assistant.
Diagnose him with dementia.
Yes, Ma'am.
Take him and go.
Mr Gong, Gwi Ja loves cake.
We should get some on our way.
Yes, Sir.
I never hid the fact that he has dementia.
Stop lying.
I already heard from Dr Hwang.
I just didn't see the need to tell you people.
Of course you needed to.
Your father wrote his will before he met you.
You hid his illness because you knew you didn't have a part in his will.
You're just like your mother.
You're a liar and are good at stabbing someone's back.
Let's go, Ji Soo.
What happened...
to finding someone who can write like Father?
I found someone.
What are you trying to do?
Meals here aren't that great.
Everything here was...
made by Lawyer Oh at home. They're very good.
Have some.
Il Jae never came to visit, did he?
I never saw his name on your records.
Dream all you like.
I will never betray him.
My goodness. If you were this loyal in the army,
you'd be a general by now.
Instead, you came to prison to rot because of Il Jae.
I told Il Jae that I'm meeting you.
I told him how you wouldn't give in, and he seemed very pleased.
But he is...
suspicious about everything.
I'm not sure if this will be all right.
We're going to come every day.
If you'd like a specific dish, you can tell me.
Oh Soo Yeon.
If you don't want to see me,
tell me at least where the doctor...
who performed Dong Soo's autopsy is hiding.
Do you think I'll tell you?
- That means you do know.
-  Exactly.
He does know.
Do you have anything that you like in particular?
Lawyer Oh is good at cooking meat dishes.
Do you think...
you can persuade me with this?
I have to try anything.
If you were me,
would you just sit around when your brother died a wrongful death?
I'll be back tomorrow.
You can take your time and eat them all.
Come on. Eat up. They look great.
If you don't eat everything, I'll sue you.
The chairman's writing is on the right...
and the left is a copy of his handwriting.
Put them together.
There are small differences.
Experts say they are 90 percent identical.
How long until 100 percent?
One more week.
Once it's finished,
let handwriting experts take a look.
Yes, Sir.
Once I have Father's handwritten will,
it wouldn't matter even if he's declared incompetent.
You're really late. I told you to be on time.
I'm not that late.
We're late. Let's go.
Wait.
Where are we going?
Do you remember Chainsaw So?
He's going to hand me his matured bonds.
It's a very important meeting. Do not make any mistakes.
To Gi Tan, you're nothing but a family member of his enemy.
He'll just use you...
and leave you in misery.
Say hello. This is Chainsaw...
I mean,
Chairman So Gil Du.
I'm Do Shin Young, Dodo Hotel's CEO.
I heard Chairman Do had a shrew for a daughter.
That must be you.
A shrew?
Do I look like a shrew?
Hey, Shin Young.
Sit.
Why did you...
bring this girl?
Shin Young...
will be the next chairwoman of Dodo Group.
The next chairwoman?
We plan on changing the holding company of Dodo Group...
from Dodo Pharmaceutical to Dodo Hotel.
Is that the best...
you came up with by using my bonds?
Ms Do and I have signed a shareholders' voting agreement.
I'll be participating in Dodo Group's management.
All right.
How much bonds did you get so far?
It's really nothing compared to...
what you have.
During the next creditors' meeting﻿,
a voting will take place on the extension of the bonds.
I have about 30 percent in bonds.
You have to persuade the others to get the majority to vote.
I'll be supporting you.
Are you telling me to secure the other 20 percent myself?
Then did you think that things would...
automatically sort out?
If the majority votes for you,
I'll pass over the bonds and give you the loan as well.
You're trying to test me.
This is a huge bet for me.
I should at least test you.
All right.
I'll get the majority on my side before the creditors' meeting.
It won't be easy.
Most of them are on Chairman Do Choong's side.
Ms Do will help me.
- Isn't that right?
-  What?
Yes, of course.
I'm not sure.
I just hope Vice Chairman Do will sit still.
You heard him, right?
Yes. About making me into the chairwoman?
Not that.
We have to persuade 20 percent of the creditors.
Don't worry, I'll help you.
We better meet the creditors right away.
Please set meetings with the ones that will be easier to persuade.
Yes, Sir.
- Gi Tan met with Chainsaw So?
-  Yes.
He even took Shin Young with him.
Doesn't this mean Chainsaw So is siding with him?
Find out where Chainsaw So is right now.
Yes, Sir.
Sir.
Hello, Vice Chairman Do.
If you didn't eat yet, why don't you join me?
I ate.
I've been coming to this place for 30 years now.
I almost lost it to Kang Gi Tan.
Why did you see him?
Did you promise him your bonds?
Not yet.
That means there's a possibility.
I'll see at the next creditors' meeting.
That's not what you promised.
Do you...
still believe in promises?
I don't believe in anything without a signature.
- Sir...
-  He'll be persuading the creditors.
You can try to stop him yourself.
I'm going to root for Gi Tan.
If 20 percent or more support him...
along with my 30 percent,
Dodo Group...
will be in trouble.
What if I block the majority?
If that's the case,
my 30 percent will be used on you.
When that happens,
Gi Tan won't ever get a chance to step into this world.
Are you saying that you trust Gi Tan more than me?
No, I don't trust either of you.
But what can I do?
I'll have to push out the one I trust even less.
Get the list of the creditors...
and set meetings in the order of percentage.
Yes, Sir.
Gi Tan already secured Chainsaw So's 30 percent.
How is this going to work?
I have to try my best until the creditors' meeting.
You won't extend the bonds?
- No.
-  I'm against it.
How is it any good for us if Dodo Group goes under?
The company won't be ruined.
I'm saying we'll revive the company through some restructuring.
Chairman Kang.
How much bonds do you have right now?
Over 30 percent.
Do you think we're blind?
I believe you only have 6 to 7 percent.
(Chairman So)
Chairman Kang. What is it?
Shouldn't I get you to sign a contract...
to support me during the next creditors' meeting?
You're as doubtful as me, aren't you?
I love contracts, that's all.
Come any time. I'll sign it for you.
Thank you.
You all know that Chairman So Gil Du...
has over 30 percent in bonds, right?
That Gi Tan...
He's borrowing my power...
to grab this golden opportunity.
Even if that's the case,
we're loyal to the Do family.
We can't betray them overnight.
- Why is she so late?
-  She'll be here soon.
CEO Do Shin Young is here.
Long time no see.
How are you?
Do you even know what this is about?
I came because Chairman Kang asked me. Should I leave?
Then...
Do you support Chairman Kang?
You all know what a mess my family is in.
The company is my priority.
In order to save it,
I believe Chairman Kang's plan is the right way.
Gi Tan is securing more creditors.
He seems to be doing well since he has Shin Young on his side.
Is she crazy?
I warned her, and yet she's still helping him?
I've never considered Shin Young...
in my predictions.
How is it looking on Gun Woo's side?
He's meeting with creditors with more bonds.
Since Chainsaw So is supporting Gi Tan,
he's at a disadvantage.
Shouldn't you help Gun Woo?
Gun Woo or Gi Tan, it's all the same to me.
You can't leave Gi Tan to take over Dodo Group.
If I bring Chainsaw So to my side,
I could be the winner of this battle.
Are you saying you'll try to take over Dodo Group?
Chainsaw So...
isn't going to be easy to persuade.
I'll have to offer him a better deal than Gi Tan did.
You have a visitor.
Who is it?
It's the ex-Seoul mayor candidate, Byun Il Jae.
I'm telling you this just in case.
If a man named Byun Il Jae comes to you, don't see him.
Is he interested in Dodo Group as well?
He's a greedy person.
I'm sure he'll be drooling somewhere.
Should I bring him in?
No.
I'll go outside to see him.
I'm So Gil Du. What is this about?
Nice to meet you. I'm Byun Il Jae.
I know you very well.
I voted you for Seoul Mayor...
and almost wanted to cut off my hand.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I have something...
I'd like to discuss with you.
Kang Gi Tan told me you'd come to see me.
He asked me to give this to you.
What do you think you're doing, Old Man?
It's best to put salt on things that smell fishy.
What?
Let go of me!
Don't obstruct my business!
Get out of here.
How dare you?
Let go of me.
Lock the gate, Do Chi.
What...
Are you okay?
He threw salt at Il Jae?
Yes.
I think Gi Tan got to Chainsaw So first.
Shouldn't you...
cut Il Jae off?
I can't lose...
a financial backer so close to the general election.
Didn't Gi Tan say he'd help you?
Dirty money...
can be spent wisely.
Dangerous money, however, you must never touch.
Il Jae's money is just as dangerous.
I can...
get rid of Il Jae at any time.
But once I let Gi Tan control me,
he will cause problems for me...
even after I become the president.
Thank you for your support, Mr Park.
I'm trusting you...
because of Chairman So and Ms Do.
Did you hear that?
I'm this influential.
I'll see you at the creditors' meeting.
See you soon.
Goodbye.
All right. Who's next?
I'll persuade them all.
That's all for today.
You did well.
Can I go now?
Goodbye.
Don't you think she's changed?
She's been acting strange lately.
On any other day,
she'd have bugged me to have a drink with her.
Do you think something's wrong?
Ga Din.
Why are you back?
Won't you praise me for doing a good job today?
- Well done.
-  Is that it?
Kiss me.
Shin Young.
Do you know what it means when a man and a woman kiss?
You like official seals.
So do I. Consider this a seal of sorts.
Go on.
Close your eyes.
So you can run away again?
I won't run away. I'm just shy.
Open your eyes.
- How was it?
-  Dreamy.
Don't ask me to kiss you over this again.
I understand why...
you're pushing me away.
(Dodo Group Creditors)
I marked Gi Tan's supporters in red.
I think he has over 50 percent already.
We might lose before they even vote.
We need...
to prevent Chainsaw So from attending the meeting.
We can't abduct him.
There is a way.
Do you know what loan sharks like me...
fear the most?
People from the police's Private Loan Task Force.
The Private Loan Task Force?
Yes.
If they get to him,
even Chainsaw So will have a hard time getting free.
I know one of the managers.
Shall I set up a meeting?
Chainsaw So is connected to many politicians.
If Gi Tan puts pressure through the Chinese Embassy,
he'll easily get out.
Set up a meeting with that manager.
Will you go for it?
There's no other way but to push ahead.
Whom are you calling?
Mr Hwang. I'm Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo.
I forgot about Hwang Jae Man.
I'd like to meet you urgently.
I will come and see you.
Thank you for sparing the time.
I happen to have plans to meet someone else here.
What time is it?
You have an hour, Sir.
That's more than enough.
First...
Read this, Sir.
(Joint Name Contract)
That proves that I'm...
a joint owner of Z Capital's funds.
Wait.
Il Jae...
didn't mention this to me.
I thought so, which is why I showed you that.
Let me explain what that means.
Without my permission,
you cannot spend a single dime on your election campaign.
Do me one favour...
and I will personally...
fund your campaign.
What do you want?
At the creditors' meeting,
a man called So Gil Du...
will be under inspection.
I need you to stop him from using his connections.
You want him...
to stay away from the creditors' meeting.
That's right.
You'll also have to stop Gi Tan...
from putting pressure through the Chinese Embassy.
This is only until the meeting is over.
It's nothing for a man like you.
In exchange for that,
I want you to release...
Il Jae's funds.
I can't do that.
I will fund your campaign with my own funds.
Don't worry about that.
I need to think about it.
I'll call you.
There's no time.
I need your answer today.
Oh dear.
Hello, Sir.
Il Jae.
You were right.
He used your joint name contract...
to ask me for a favour.
What was his request?
I can't tell from his facial expression alone.
Where's the task force manager?
He's on his way.
Do as Gun Woo asks, Sir.
Will you help him?
Gun Woo and Gi Tan's fight is a great opportunity.
Don't worry, Sir.
Once the creditors' meeting's over,
I will have full control of Dodo Group.
That man...
The man they call Chainsaw or Hacksaw So.
Get me a list of...
his backers.
And set up a meeting with the ambassador from China.
Yes, Sir.
Hello, Sir.
Your request.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
In return,
I expect you to keep your promise.
I will.
Did he say yes?
We did it.
Sir. Do you feel better?
Father.
What...
am I doing here?
Father.
Do I...
have an illness?
You have dementia.
Dementia?
Don't worry, Father.
You'll get better if you receive treatment.
Lawyer Oh.
What about my will?
You can make it once you recover.
Okay.
I'll do that.
You need intensive care.
I think you should stay here.
I agree.
Father.
Gun Woo.
I can't move my limbs!
I'll massage them for you.
Gun Woo.
I'm sorry.
I think...
it's over for me.
You should...
take over Dodo and...
Please stay strong.
I can't live without you, Father.
You can beat this.
You went through physical therapy and managed to walk again.
Gun Woo.
I will make you better.
Trust me.
Gun Woo.
Thank you, Soo Yeon,
for lying to him for me.
If he's losing control of his arms and legs...
He has less than six months.
It's terminal.
You should go home. It's late.
Will you stay?
I should stay with him.
I'm sorry I can't take you home.
Let's get engaged.
Before your father passes.
I'm sorry.
I took too long to answer.
(Dodo Group)
Sir, the Private Loan Task Force...
just left for Chainsaw So's house.
You're early.
I'm meeting the creditors before the meeting.
You look pretty confident.
Why put on a show when we both know the other's hand?
We have 58 percent, so you must have 42 percent.
The creditors' meeting is still three hours away.
No one knows what will happen by then.
Everyone knows but you.
Shin Young, let's have a word.
Don't you know why he wants the matured bonds?
We'll go bankrupt if the creditors don't extend it.
I know that.
If you're still helping him,
that means you betrayed your father and the company.
I trust Gi Tan.
He won't ruin the company.
Shin Young.
You don't know what kind of person he is.
I know very well.
He almost died when you framed him for murder.
I won't let Father accept and acknowledge someone like you.
That's why I'm helping him.
To get rid of you.
Do you know that Gwang Woo...
killed his parents?
- I do.
-  Then...
you must also know that Gi Tan's using you.
If he really wanted to use me,
he wouldn't have refused my wedding proposal.
He will not go back on his word.
He's not like you.
As soon as the meeting is over,
I will have you ousted from the company.
Don't regret it then.
Who are you? Get out of here!
- Mr So Gil Du?
-  That would be me.
How dare you barge in here?
We're with the Private Loan Task Force.
You have no business with me.
We got a tip.
Our search and seizure warrant.
Where did you get the tip from?
Search the place.
You must come with us.
Are you with the police?
Let me make a call.
(Police Commissioner Lee)
The phone has been turned off. Please...
Is he in a meeting?
(Police Commissioner Park)
The phone has been turned off. Please leave a message.
Sir.
No one's picking up. Something's wrong.
Is this deliberate?
It has to be. They'd never ignore my calls.
I'll ask Chairman Kang to help.
- Please do.
-  Get in.
Speak.
They just dragged Chainsaw So away.
Mr Moon.
The Private Loan Task Force just arrested Chairman So.
Well done, Mr Yang.
I think someone got them involved.
I'll go to the police station and get his power of attorney.
The meeting will have begun by the time you get it notarised.
You could call the Chinese Embassy...
and ask them to intervene.
I'll do that.
Is something wrong?
Chairman So just got arrested.
For illegal loans.
Are you behind this?
Don't blame me.
Blame Chainsaw So for his illegal business.
Wait, you can't talk to the Chinese Embassy about this.
It won't work this time.
Gi Tan.
(It's Chairman Kang.)
He says it's a call from Gi Tan.
If he feels too uncomfortable to take his call,
tell him that I can take it for him.
(If you don't want to take his call, Mr Hwang can take it for you.)
(Sure.)
(It's me, Kang Gi Tan.)
It's me, Hwang Jae Man.
Let me talk to Ambassador Wang.
Because of recent downfall in Sino-Korean relationship,
he feels a bit burdened...
to do you a favour.
Mr Hwang.
Are you siding with Gun Woo?
Hey.
I don't take any sides.
I'm hanging up.
I'm probably the only one who can take care of this.
Won't you even ask me for a favour?
You must not be too desperate.
I already know that you won't help me.
I don't like Gun Woo.
He's very impudent just like his father.
Does that mean...
you may help me?
That may happen.
Don't try to sound me out. Goodbye.
Who was that? My uncle?
Yes.
You should've let me talk to him.
He may do this if I asked.
Even if you asked,
I doubt Mr Hwang will help me.
Yes, Commissioner Lee.
It's me, Jae Man.
Isn't there...
a team named Private Loan Task Force?
One of my friends...
named So Gil Du was...
just arrested by them.
Chairman So.
I guess the Chinese Embassy is powerful.
The Chinese Embassy?
I heard Jae Man let me out.
Is that true?
I heard it with my own ears.
I heard Jae Man let me out.
Your call cannot be connected.
He can't take your call because the meeting already began.
- Let's go.
-  Your call...
cannot be connected. Please leave your message...
This meeting is...
about renewing the contract of your matured bonds.
Please share your thoughts freely...
if you'd like to speak.
(Creditors' Meeting for Dodo Group)
I'd like to make...
a formal request to Dodo Group.
If you'd like a renewal of our contract,
you will have to change...
your holding company...
from Dodo Pharmaceutical to Dodo Hotel.
The current speaker is the second large shareholder of Dodo Hotel.
He's currently plotting a scheme with the largest shareholder,
CEO Do Shin Young, to take Dodo Group for themselves.
Vice President Do Gun Woo.
Didn't you recently inspect your subsidiaries?
This is a report of his inspection,
which I got a few days ago.
According to this report,
there are seven subsidiaries...
that have more accumulated deficit than their capital.
That means seven subsidiaries...
may go bankrupt within the year.
You may refute me if I'm wrong, Vice President Do.
Here is the most important fact.
Among the subsidiaries, the biggest deficit...
belongs to Dodo Pharmaceutical.
- What does that mean?
-  Dodo Pharmaceutical?
I tell you,
if this goes on,
no one sitting in this room...
will be able to get his or her principal back.
That's all.
- What?
-  That's absurd.
I applaud you for trying,
but it's already over.
I own 42 percent...
and you have 28 percent without Chainsaw So's shares.
And now,
we will vote yes or no...
on renewing the contract.
Wait.
Before we vote, someone would like to say a word.
I was...
just arrested by the police.
Someone here...
reported me for giving out illegal private loans.
Well, need I say more?
Let us...
vote.
Are you saying...
not Gi Tan or Gun Woo, but Il Jae will be taking it over?
Yes. If things go as he planned.
Wait.
Did you let Chainsaw So out...
not to help Gi Tan but...
I've taken Il Jae's side.
I will announce the result.
(Yes, No)
Just as I promised,
I will sell my bonds to you.
I need a loan, too.
Make sure you pay your interest.
Thank you.
You should take him back home.
Yes, Sir.
Goodbye.
I do not understand why Jae Man took our side.
I'm sure he's up to something.
But I'm not sure what it is.
Who cares? Dodo Group is ours.
Soo Tak.
Will you take Shin Young back to the hotel?
Aren't you coming?
We should celebrate.
We'll celebrate later. You can go ahead, Shin Young.
Mr Moon.
Yes.
I am going to confess my love to Soo Yeon today.
I destroyed Gun Woo today.
You can't stop me any more.
I do not mind,
but I'm afraid your headache may start again.
I'd rather have that headache.
Whenever I see her,
my heart aches so much...
that I can't stand it.
Your fight against Gi Tan was...
very intriguing.
I thought you'd ask for my help,
but you went to Mr Hwang instead.
Do you see now, Gun Woo?
You can't win against Gi Tan without my help.
I want to be alone.
So please leave.
Don't change...
your holding company to Dodo Hotel.
In that case, Gi Tan will take out all of his matured bonds.
Let him do it.
We're in no financial position to prevent bankruptcy.
I have...
a plan.
You're late.
Why are you here?
I'd like to talk to you.
See you at home.
Let's go somewhere else.
What do you want to say?
A man...
fell in love three times.
Would you believe if I said it was with the same woman?
The first time,
the man was unable to see.
10 years later...
when he met her again after regaining his sight,
he didn't know she was the one he was looking for.
And he fell in love again.
Then the man...
lost his memory.
Being the fool he was,
he fell in love with her again.
Jeong Eun.
I'm sorry.
Don't avoid me...
for the fear of hurting me.
This is the third time.
Even if I die,
I won't lose you again.
(Monster)
Things will become tense.
We must go on the offence.
Choong Dong isn't enough.
We need to shake Il Jae, too.
Listen to what I say very carefully.
I'll get the information you want.
You're in no position to make demands.
Please don't side with Il Jae.
Call the family.
It's time to close the deal.
See you tomorrow.