A man...
fell in love three times.
Would you believe it if I said it was with the same woman?
The first time,
the man was unable to see.
Ten years later...
when he met her again after regaining his sight,
he didn't know she was the one he was looking for.
And he fell in love again.
Then the man...
lost his memory.
Being the fool he was,
he fell in love with her again.
Jeong Eun.
I'm sorry.
This is the third time.
Even if I die,
I won't lose you again.
Soo Yeon, no. Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon. No. Don't die, Soo Yeon.
I found the evidence of Il Jae's corruption.
Who are you people?
Gun Woo.
Gun Woo, stay with me.
Help! We need help!
Let's get engaged.
Before your father passes.
I'm sorry.
I took too long to answer.
I'm sorry, Gi Tan.
Gun Woo...
helped me a lot thus far.
I can't selfishly hope to be happy...
after abandoning Gun Woo.
Jeong Eun, Gun Woo is...
Once I get my revenge on Il Jae,
I will never see you again.
I do not...
love you any more.
I'm sorry, Gi Tan.
(Episode 43)
Nan Jeong told me...
Soo Yeon will get engaged to Gun Woo soon.
I should have stopped him from meeting Lawyer Oh yesterday.
I'm worried that he might get his headache back.
Sir.
What happened to getting the agreement from the creditors?
Here they are.
(Creditors' Agreement)
What about the contract we'll enter with Dodo Group?
It's all ready.
Tell Gun Woo...
to come to the hotel.
Yes, Sir.
(Dodo Group)
(Moon Tae Gwang)
Hello?
The chairman wants to meet you.
You can come to my office at 1pm.
Come to the hotel.
I have no time to go over.
If you don't come here by 1pm, the meeting will be cancelled.
He wants us to come to his office.
Do not change the holding company to Dodo Hotel.
In that case, Gi Tan will take out all of the bonds.
Tell him to do that.
If he does,
we cannot run Dodo Group with the capital we have.
I have...
an idea, Gun Woo.
I'll...
help you with the expiring bonds.
It's over 500 million dollars.
We only have 200 million in Z Capital.
Of course it won't be enough with what I have.
However, we can get a loan...
from Z Capital with what I have as security.
I've already discussed it with them.
I have a condition in return for helping you.
Break the joint account.
I have a condition as well.
I don't think you're in the position to demand conditions.
No, I told you.
I came empty-handed when I moved here from the US.
At the worst, I can just go back empty-handed again.
All right. Go ahead and tell me.
I'm...
going to get engaged to Soo Yeon.
Please don't interfere in our relationship any more.
All right. I won't.
Soo Yeon, can you come to my office right now?
Gun Woo must be confused.
He should have come running to us.
How dare he tell us to come here?
Did something happen yesterday?
What? Why?
You didn't pick up your phone and you look down today.
I'm just tired.
It's fine.
I shouldn't have asked you to come.
I'm your legal counsel. Of course I should be here.
Chairman Kang is here.
- Show them in.
-  Yes, Sir.
Take a seat.
I don't have time, so let's get to the point.
Mr Moon.
Here are the consent forms from the creditors.
If you want to renew the bonds,
switch your holding company to Dodo Hotel.
You're a coward.
How can you set me in a trap...
with the ship contract to win over Dodo Group?
You better talk properly.
You're the coward for turning Gi Tan into a murderer.
To me,
there were no problems with the way Gi Tan did his business.
It's your greed that set you in that trap.
You must be brainwashed after sticking by Gi Tan's side.
Enough with that nonsense.
Just change the holding company to Dodo Hotel right now.
Otherwise, it's over for you.
Here is a memorandum to state that you will switch to Dodo Hotel.
Please sign it.
If you don't sign it now,
we won't be renewing the bonds.
Think wisely.
Do as you wish.
I'll use my own money if I have to.
You don't have any money.
Oh, are you referring to Dad's inheritance?
Do you think you'll get that money in six months?
You better wake up.
Don't regret it later after losing everything to Gi Tan.
Are you...
getting help from Byun Il Jae?
What are you talking about?
We're tracking his financial movements.
I noticed that all the money he had in his paper company disappeared.
Are you still making up stories?
I do hope...
it's just my imagination.
Imagine all you want,
but give up on your dream to take over Dodo Group.
I won't let that happen.
I don't care what strategy you use,
but don't get Il Jae's help.
You should think about Soo Yeon.
It would be inhumane.
The negotiation fell apart, Sir. Let's go.
He definitely has something to rely on.
He wouldn't have ripped those documents like that if he didn't.
Once those bonds expire, the company will be ruined.
When will we know...
about Il Jae's finances?
He's very meticulous so it's hard to track.
But do you really think...
Il Jae is helping Gun Woo?
I believe it's quite possible...
also since Hwang Jae Man helped us.
Why don't we contact Yeom Hyeong Gu?
It might be faster that way.
- Go and meet with him.
-  Yes, Sir.
I saw Gi Tan on my way in.
It was funny to see them all confused.
It's the termination agreement on our joint account.
(Joint Account Termination Consent)
I'll stamp on it on the day the bonds expire in six months.
If you fail to help me then,
I will not sign this agreement.
That won't happen, so don't worry.
Also, don't come to the office to see me any more.
I'll tell you where to meet.
Is it because of Soo Yeon?
Remember this.
The moment she finds about us, we will no longer work together.
Sure.
Your life will end up being ruined because of Soo Yeon.
Come on in.
You were secretly waiting for us, right?
Sit down, sit down.
Have some gimbap.
You can't get me to talk even if you do this.
Don't bother wasting your time.
Dong Soo used to love gimbap.
If I was making some, he'd be so busy...
stealing pieces beside me.
I hate gimbap, so you two can eat it.
That's weird. Your mother said...
that you like it.
My mother?
These are from your mother back home.
She told me you hate spinach and added burdock instead.
You met my mother?
Don't worry.
I didn't mention that you kidnapped and murdered people.
That would be a bad idea. She looked quite old.
She's old, but she worked so hard...
to make this gimbap for her son.
Her hands are wrinkly but still strong.
Why are you doing this to me?
You know very well why.
I didn't kill Dong Soo!
I know. It was Il Jae.
Just tell me where the autopsy result is.
I don't know. I don't know! I said, I don't know!
You'll remember it soon...
because I'll keep coming back until you do.
Oh Soo Yeon.
Your mother still believes that you're a good son.
When I told her that you ended up here because of someone evil,
she grabbed my hands and cried.
She had to send her only son to prison.
How do you think she'd feel?
But...
it's worse for Lawyer Oh.
She had to say goodbye to her brother...
whom she raised like her son.
Let's go, Mr Min.
Okay.
This is all because of that awful man, Il Jae.
He'll be beaten to death again even after he dies.
Right, there is soda in that plastic...
Wait, are you crying?
Think about your mother.
Eat them all.
And eat slowly.
You're going through so much because of Il Jae.
I saw him crying as he ate gimbap.
I think there has been a slight change.
He still won't talk easily.
You're right.
Il Jae is like religion to him.
Can you check and see what Il Jae is up to?
I heard he got divorced and opened up a lawyer's office.
I think he's staying low.
We can't wait around for Choong Dong to come through.
We'll go and shake Il Jae, too.
Il Jae opened up a lawyer's office.
Gun Woo took over the company...
and Mr Hwang is no longer on his side.
He has nothing else to do.
It looked like he is meeting Ji Soo.
Really?
Why did you meet Il Jae?
Have you been following me?
You do meet him then. I thought I'd throw it out there.
I'm not afraid of enemies that are on the move.
An unseen enemy is a bigger problem.
Is Il Jae...
having meetings with Gun Woo?
I don't know.
I think you would at least know where he hid the money...
from that paper company.
Mr Moon.
You must have mistook me.
I never said that I'd help you.
But you will.
You'll work like a cow for Mr Hwang,
but you will...
end up getting eaten by Il Jae.
Are you cursing me?
I'm not. It's the reality.
Everyone knows this is the reality.
The problem is that you don't see it.
I hate Il Jae.
But I do not trust you.
Do not ever try to persuade me again.
We're always open.
You're welcome to come whenever you change your mind.
We'll be waiting.
Is there any chance Hyeong Gu will give in to us?
He won't budge unless Jae Man loses the presidential election.
Find someone trustworthy.
And let them track Jae Man, Il Jae, Hyeong Gu and Ji Soo.
Are you going to put a tail on all of them?
Things will begin to unfold very rapidly from now on.
We have to be more aggressive.
Now, I have to do the laundry with my own hands.
How did the chairwoman of Dodo Group get this low?
Gwi Ja, did you take all of the laundry on the hanger?
Why?
You have to look closely. You're mixing them up.
My goodness.
What are you doing? I just folded those.
Please ask me first before you do any chores.
You might kick me out if I rip any of your clothes.
That's why I'm asking you to not touch anything without asking.
My goodness.
Hey, those...
do not look like my brother's.
Are those Il Jae's?
Why do you care?
You're such a foolish girl.
How can you do the laundry for your ex-husband?
Aunt.
My goodness.
Mum. Mum. Mum, this is bad.
What's wrong?
The court called me today.
Gun Woo is filing to become Father's legal guardian.
Legal guardian? Why?
Why do you ask? Because he's diagnosed as incompetent.
Don't worry, Gwang Woo.
How can I not worry?
Only immediate family members are allowed to do that.
Gun Woo...
isn't your father's son on paper.
What are you talking about?
Hasn't Father added me to the family register?
It's not that he didn't.
He couldn't.
Without my consent,
Gun Woo can't be added to the family register.
Then who has the rights...
to inherit his assets?
For now, it's just Shin Young.
We can legally eliminate...
Gwi Ja and Gwang Woo from inheriting his assets.
Once he gets a divorce,
I can be added to the family register, right?
That's true.
I thought Chairman Do Choong doesn't have a long time.
I doubt Gwi Ja will agree to divorce him.
It'll take at least six months if they get into a lawsuit.
Can't you make him rewrite his will?
A will written by someone who has dementia...
has no legal force.
Then Vice President Do...
can't get any of the inheritance.
Hey. Go and get some tea for us.
What happened to the will?
His handwriting is almost 100 percent similar.
The problem is its contents.
Can you bring what you have back to my office?
- We're going to the office.
-  Yes, Sir.
The following is my will.
My wife and my eldest son tried to put me in danger.
Therefore, I will not give a penny to them.
My daughter...
neglected me most of the time.
Hence, I'll only give her the house in Samseong-dong.
My company and shares...
will be inherited to my second son.
However, my second son...
will need to grow the company in abundance after my wish.
For a will to have legal force,
it must include a date.
Father fell down and got surgery...
on June 12.
It needs to be dated to before his diagnose.
Let's make it May 7.
All right.
"My company and shares will be inherited to my second son."
Change "my second son" to "Do Gun Woo".
The person who copied his handwriting knows nothing.
That's why I took out all of the names.
He may cause problems later...
if he sees your name here.
In that case, change the wording to Yoon Ja Young's son.
That needs to be accurately stated because I'm not his legal son.
Yes, Sir.
Who will become Chairman Do's
legal guardian?
Do you want me to be the legal guardian of my father?
Gwang Woo and I can't do it...
because we're under a restraining order from him.
Why did you hide...
that he has dementia?
We didn't hide it.
We only found out later because of Gun Woo.
That's not what's important.
You should...
go to your house with Gi Tan and bring Father over here.
I don't want Gun Woo to be with him.
Once you bring him,
we'll take good care of him.
No, thanks.
I will take care of him at the hotel.
Why are you being so hard?
Hey, Shin Young.
Are you after Father's assets?
- What?
-  It's not even funny how you act...
like a good daughter all of a sudden.
People say it takes one to know one.
I'm not shameless like you.
What's with you? Did you eat something weird?
You tried to kill Dad!
Why did you have to shout?
People can hear us.
Do you even feel shame?
What?
Shin Young.
Will you continue to be like this?
I am so embarrassed...
and angry that we are a family.
I'll take care of Dad.
That... That wench.
What should we do, Mum?
We have to care for Dad.
I wish someone would just kidnap him.
That's a good idea.
What?
We'll kidnap him without anyone's knowing.
What can Gun Woo do then?
Don't do anything stupid.
If you end up in jail, I'll go crazy.
If it was up to me, I'd...
Don't you dare.
All right.
I'll stay by your side. Don't worry.
(2016 Presidential Election Analysis)
(Hanguk Party candidates and supporters)
Currently, the candidates for ruling party has come down to three.
How is Hwang Jae Man doing?
He's in the 20 percent range. The lowest of the three.
It's still early in the game. These numbers don't matter.
He's someone capable of turning the tables around.
Go ahead.
Okay, keep an eye on it.
Byun Il Jae and Hwang Ji Soo arrived at Hwang Jae Man's office.
The other candidates are strong.
I think you should forgo on doing the national tour,
and meet the previous presidents and politicians first.
Don't you know the meaning of doing national tours?
He needs to win the public over...
by going around and acting as if he's on their side.
How can he give that up?
That only works if you have a lot of supporters.
You need to focus on reality instead of ideals.
What do you know about elections?
If you knew so well,
why did you go to prison during your campaign?
What?
What did you just say?
We didn't come here to fight.
Tell me a realistic plan.
Enough with barking at each other.
I agree with the national tour.
I think that would be best to improve your public image.
Don't you know why his public image was ruined?
If it wasn't for the Seoul mayor scandal,
his rating wouldn't be so low!
Yeom Hyeong Gu!
I said, stop it.
What's your strategy then, Mr Yeom?
I'm trying to find out the weaknesses of the other candidates.
We need to ruin their public image to make it easier for us.
That's an old and foolish strategy.
What do you mean it's old?
Don't you know you have to find the smallest faults in order...
to win an election?
Do you think the other candidates will just sit still?
If they do the same thing,
we'll be at the most disadvantage.
I agree with Il Jae.
- Mr Yeom.
-  Yes, Sir.
Il Jae...
knows better about elections.
You can step back...
- during the election.
-  I'm sorry?
But, Sir...
Il Jae.
Tell me your strategy.
You'll draw in votes if you put yourself down.
During the national campaign tour,
try to show yourself as the everyday Joe.
You should then meet with the shadow cabinet that were forgotten.
After that...
You'll end up helping us.
You work so hard for Congressman Hwang,
but Il Jae will eat you alive.
He came here alone after meeting with Jae Man.
It's obvious there were disagreements during the meeting.
You better leave.
I won't betray Congressman Hwang.
We didn't say anything about betraying him.
I only mentioned that you should get rid of Il Jae.
Just tell us where Il Jae's secret funds are going...
and give us the proof that he evaded taxes.
Then what about the election funds?
I'll take care of it, of course.
The thirsty will look for the well first.
When they're in a financial problem after we get rid of Il Jae,
I'll decline Jae Man's request at first.
Then we'll act like you persuaded me.
That means you'll become the key figure to have made...
this campaign successful.
If Congressman Hwang becomes the president,
you'd become...
his right hand.
Of course, that's if Il Jae is gone.
By then,
Il Jae will be remarried to Ji Soo.
Don't worry about that.
I'll make sure that doesn't happen.
You should tell him the details later.
Let me repeat.
My target is Il Jae, not Congressman Hwang.
I'll look into...
the documents you need.
Did you wake up?
Mr Gong!
Yes?
My legs...
I can't move them!
Pardon?
Maybe you walked for too long earlier.
Are you sure I'm getting better?
Dr Hwang says so. That's what we have to believe.
My paralysis is getting worse.
Could Dr Hwang...
be tricked by Gwi Ja?
I'll look into it.
No, don't bother.
Ask them for my medical records.
I better get checked...
by another doctor.
Yes, Sir.
What are you talking about?
Why can't you show us the medical records?
The thing is...
I told him not to reveal it.
Could you give us a moment?
Sure.
Mr Gong, listen to me carefully.
Father is terminally ill.
What do you mean?
He's terminally ill?
He has less than six months.
It's best not to tell him.
Is there no hope?
Can't he have surgery?
No.
Why didn't you tell me before?
I couldn't tell you because the results weren't out.
We better tell his family.
- We can't do that.
-  What do you mean?
Are you going to let him die alone like that?
Don't you know why he ended up like that?
Those people are not his family.
I won't forgive them.
We should at least tell Shin Young.
I'll tell her myself.
Please focus on making Father as comfortable as he can be.
Sir.
Chairman Do has disappeared again.
What are you talking about? What do you mean he disappeared?
I'm sorry. He was gone when I came back from the washroom.
If he got changed, maybe he went to Congressman Hwang's again.
- Sir.
-  Have you checked the CCTV?
He was picking flowers in the garden an hour ago.
Flowers?
That must be it.
He went to find his wife.
Gwi Ja.
These are for you.
Take the flowers...
before his arms fall off.
You're so generous.
Jae Man.
Give me...
Gwi Ja's hand.
I want...
to marry her.
Oh dear...
I know...
you don't like me.
But...
I'm sure I can...
make her happy.
How will you make her happy?
Right now,
I am penniless.
But...
I'll make sure...
you can live a luxurious life.
Was this what he was like?
Yes.
But who cares?
We're practically enemies now.
I'm hungry.
Gwi Ja.
I'd like a chicken...
your mother cooked for me.
Tell Shin Young to come right over.
What for?
I need her permission to look after your dad.
Okay.
He came over...
with the flowers to propose to Mum.
Dad, come with me.
I'll look after you.
Who are you?
I'm Shin Young, your daughter.
No.
I'll marry Gwi Ja and live here.
He's gotten worse.
I think it's best for him...
if we look after him.
Be good to him.
If he makes one complaint,
I'll come for him.
Are you leaving already?
Don't just sit there. Get up.
What? Right.
They're likely to inherit his assets if he stays here.
He's practically a blessing to them.
Have some, Mr Hwang.
I'm fine. The chicken's all yours.
He thinks you're his father-in-law.
I think his memory...
is going back in time.
He might end up...
asking for a bottle of milk.
Don't worry about him and focus on work.
Gun Woo.
What are you doing here?
I know my father's here.
So what?
I'll take him with me.
You're so brazen.
Don't you know I'm his legal custodian?
He won't live...
much longer.
What do you mean?
He is terminally ill and dying.
What do you mean he's terminally ill?
Are you saying he'll die soon?
He has less than six months left.
I can't let him spend the rest of his life with these people.
Let me take care of him.
This mess...
only happened because of you.
- Shin Young.
-  Get lost.
You'll never see our dad again.
Never.
Thanks for coming.
I can't refuse my boss' call.
We need to make sure Il Jae...
and Ji Soo don't reconcile.
Mr Moon filled me in.
I brought what I needed.
Let's begin right away.
(Lawyer Byun Il Jae)
Hello, Honey. What's the occasion?
Dinner?
I packed food that you like.
Don't eat dinner. Wait for me instead.
(Kang Gi Tan)
Why would he send me a video?
I think I had too much to drink.
I feel so dizzy.
Chae Ryung, get off him.
Mr Byun.
Did you watch the video?
Where did you get this?
I said...
I'd send you a gift.
To show you Il Jae's true colours.
Kang Gi Tan.
Chae Ryung was your spy.
Do you think I'll fall for this?
I'll send you one more video.
The rest is up to you.
(Kang Gi Tan)
What will you do for me?
You said you'd give me anything once you become the mayor.
You didn't tell me...
what you want yet.
Tell me. I'll give you anything.
I...
want you.
I'm a married man.
Il Jae.
I want to steal you.
Do you really love your wife?
At our age,
love...
is second to responsibility.
Then...
which am I?
Chae Ryung...
I'm not your responsibility.
Is it love?
Or just a toy?
What I feel for you now...
is love.
Then kiss me.
I need to know that...
your love isn't a lie.
(Unknown Number)
Hello?
It's me, Chae Ryung.
How dare you flirt with my husband and then send me that video?
I did flirt with him,
but he was the one with the obsession.
You're doing this...
to make sure I don't get back with Il Jae.
Do you think I don't know?
You're right.
Why do you think we want that?
You're doing this...
because we took everything and framed Gi Tan for murder!
Gi Tan's parents...
died at Il Jae's hands.
What?
He also killed Soo Yeon's brother.
That's why...
Gi Tan and Soo Yeon...
got together to take revenge.
You had no idea.
But then,
Il Jae lies whenever it suits him.
No.
I don't trust you.
That's why he duped you...
for so long.
You.
How far did you go with Il Jae?
Did you...
sleep with him?
Check with him.
He will say no.
I'm telling you this because I feel sorry for you as a woman.
Stop letting him deceive you.
Why are you so late?
You didn't pick up. I thought you were in an accident.
Where's the food?
I need to ask you something and I want an honest answer.
- Okay.
-  Did you...
love Chae Ryung?
Why would you ask that?
I want an answer. Did you...
ever love her?
She was Gi Tan's spy.
I couldn't have loved her.
Did you kiss her?
- Ji Soo.
-  Did you kiss her?
You're being childish.
Am I childish?
I never loved that woman.
I never kissed her.
I don't know...
what you heard and who you heard it from...
What's wrong with you? Are you crazy?
Whatever they said,
I trusted and loved you.
I think...
I was mistaken.
Ji Soo.
We're divorced.
It's over.
Let's see how you do without me.
Have you forgotten that you're a murderer?
- What?
-  I did all the dirty work...
to cover up for you.
And now what?
You were mistaken?
- What about you?
-  What?
Gi Tan's parents. Soo Yeon's brother.
You killed them.
Gi Tan got to you and changed you.
This is it.
I'm done with you.
Where are you?
No, I need to see you right now.
I need to see you, no excuses!
Do you know...
where your father's secret safe is?
I'm looking for it. Why?
It's in Bando Bank.
Inside it...
is evidence of all the corruption Mr Hwang committed over the years.
Your father collected it for over 20 years...
to take Jae Man down.
So what?
I need you to get me those files.
Why do you need them?
Gi Tan set a trap and I walked into it.
I have a feeling Jae Man will try to cut me off.
Do you think...
he will become the president?
He will.
I will make it happen.
So you want to use those files later on...
to blackmail the president.
That wasn't my plan,
but the circumstances have changed.
I think this is a dangerous gamble.
That's why it's called a gamble.
You either succeed or fail.
You live or die.
I'm sorry, though.
I don't have access to that safe.
Gun Woo.
Do you know what mistake I regret making the most?
It's that I underestimated you.
You'll be able to come up with a reason to gain access.
You have to get those files.
If you don't,
I might have to break our deal.
I'll try.
Sir.
Why did you call?
Have you heard about the chairman?
I heard he's staying at Mr Hwang's.
I'd like to have a look at his medical records.
But the doctor won't let me.
Why not?
I think Gun Woo told him not to show them to anyone.
You need to get those files...
and ask for a second opinion.
That's why I called you.
I'll get to it.
Gun Woo's been acting strangely.
Could you give me the details?
He has too many secrets.
That's my opinion.
(Hwang Seung Man, Doctor)
If the chairman were to have surgery,
the success rate would be 10 percent.
Yes.
Why is he terminal, then?
If surgery is an option, we never say...
a patient is terminal.
Gun Woo is lying.
Is there a way to increase the success rate?
There's a Doctor Campbell at Johns Hopkins Hospital.
If he were to operate, the success rate can be 20 percent.
- Fly Doctor Campbell in.
-  Yes, Sir.
Don't you think it's odd Gun Woo gave up on him...
when there's a possibility he can be cured?
I don't get it either.
He can't get a dime if the chairman dies.
(Yoon Ja Young's son is to do my will...)
Is this a 100-percent likeness of his writing?
The expert said even the government can't tell the difference.
Forge a power of attorney.
A power of attorney?
My father has a safe in Bando Bank.
I need to gain access to it.
Why would you need to do that?
I think this will should be placed in that safe...
to be found after his death.
If it's found in there, no one will question its legality.
You're so meticulous.
Then...
Gun Woo's just leaving him to die.
It's not like that.
It is.
He didn't tell us that surgery was an option.
Calm down.
I'll make sure he gets that surgery.
It's not a decision you can make alone.
Call a family meeting.
What's the use of that?
They'll all object.
If something happens to him during surgery,
they'll hold you responsible.
Mr Gong's right. Call a family meeting.
Bring my father over here...
and call a meeting.
It's been a while, Soo Yeon.
Come with me.
Bok Shin.
Where am I?
Sir.
Do you feel better?
Why am I here?
What's going on?
Sir.
I need you...
to listen very carefully.
The chairman will join you shortly.
Why do we need a meeting?
I don't know.
Shin Young's all grown up.
Just one word from her...
and even Gun Woo came running.
He's here for a reason. Money.
Just look at him. He even brought his lawyer.
Watch your manners.
There are other people here.
Who?
Soo Yeon?
She might be special to you, but do we have to be polite?
Mum.
Don't you think...
Shin Young's too arrogant just because she's Dad's custodian?
She'll be a nobody once he dies.
Welcome.
Dad.
Why isn't he responding?
Do you want...
to keep it a secret from Shin Young, too?
I don't know...
whom exactly...
I can trust.
Who is really on my side?
I need to find that out.
He can't speak...
or understand a word.
Don't worry.
I will...
make you better.
Let's take him outside.
I gathered you here to make an important announcement.
What announcement?
You called a lawyer.
Is this about the inheritance?
There's a possibility that surgery will cure Dad completely.
What are you talking about?
Your dad...
was terminal.
Gun Woo lied.
Did you...
check your facts?
The success rate is 10 percent.
That means there's a 90-percent chance he'll die.
No doctor in Korea can operate on him.
Doctor Campbell will be flown in from America.
He's...
an expert in brain surgery.
Did you put her up to this?
It's not wrong to want...
the chairman to live.
Why won't you get rid of the bullet in your head?
You're afraid the surgery will kill you.
You can't subject my father to this.
The success rate of my surgery is zero.
It's zero percent.
If any doctor had given me a 10-percent success rate,
I'd have done it if only to get back...
the memories I lost.
This morning,
I spoke with Doctor Campbell.
The success rate isn't 10 percent.
It's over 30 percent.
I'm...
I'm against it.
Why?
The 30-percent success rate means...
there's a 70-percent chance it will fail.
Then...
do you want to let him die?
It's not my place to say, but...
since you're all here,
put it to a vote.
Whoever is against the surgery,
raise your hand.
Other than Shin Young,
everyone objects.
The surgery...
will not happen.
I'm his custodian.
Lawyer Oh.
The others don't have a legal say, do they?
No. They don't.
I don't care what you say.
I called you here...
to tell you that he's getting the surgery.
When did you start caring about him?
He said he'd give you half of his assets.
That's what this is about!
Are you going to kill Dad to take his money?
Why are you against the surgery?
You're afraid he'll recover and you'll end up without a penny!
Learn to give up when everyone says no.
What are you even doing here?
What do you think?
Don't you know my dad's the reason your family's so rich?
We own shares.
Stop it, all of you.
What would Soo Yeon think of us?
Don't act like you're so blameless.
You told us Dad was terminally ill because you were up to something!
I've had enough. Shut your mouth.
This is how I talk! It can't be helped!
May you all...
be struck by lightning!
(Monster)
Do Choong's secret safe?
I might be able to find proof that Il Jae killed your parents.
Don't visit me any more.
Are you going to betray me, too?
Look after Shin Young for me.
He died at 9:28am.
If the surgery's a success, it puts a dent in my plan.
He's already dead.
This dirty fight will end.
I won't die until I get what I want.