I think...
we might be able to find proof...
that Il Jae killed your parents.
(Il Jae, Dodo, the director's death, the secret's in Pandora's Box)
"Pandora's Box"?
The doctor who conducted the autopsy said...
he stored all information inside the Pandora's Box.
Do you mean the one who did Dong Soo's autopsy?
Yes. He was a researcher at Sudo Hospital...
back in 2005.
He used to work as an inspector with Guk Cheol's parents...
at Dodo Pharmaceutical for painkillers made...
with stem cells.
If you just close your eyes and take their side this once,
we'll get 20 million dollars.
Man Ok.
This is about handing over half of our management rights.
That's not closing our eyes just this once.
You know best about the finances of our hospital.
Man Ok.
You also know that...
we are currently inspecting Dodo Pharmaceutical's pills.
Asking us to work with them is...
to tamper with the inspection results.
Only if we find out where this Pandora's Box is,
we may be able to find the evidence...
of Il Jae's committing murder.
I'm sure...
it's among those who are related to Dodo Group.
- Open!
-  You can't go in.
Move!
You can't do this!
I thought I told you not to barge into my office.
Gun Woo, it's not late.
Hand me over the documents from Chairman Do's secret safe.
We already had this talk.
If you don't listen to me, I'll make sure you regret it.
I can't give it to you because I don't want to regret it.
Gun Woo, you...
What are you doing? Take him out of here!
Please leave.
Let go!
Gun Woo. You better think carefully...
about what I said.
Call the secretary's office...
and make sure they don't allow Il Jae in the building.
Yes, Sir.
Why did Il Jae come here?
You know it too, don't you? He's been threatening me...
He's been threatening me with my weakness.
Can't you tell me what that weakness is?
It's regarding my mother. I'll tell you everything later.
Anyway, why are you here?
We found something strange among the medical examiner's belongings.
What do you mean?
Pandora's Box?
Yes. If we find that,
we can get Il Jae arrested for murder.
I think Chairman Do might know.
But it's a little difficult to ask since Gwang Woo might be involved.
Father should know if it's something like that.
I'll ask him once the surgery is over.
Yes, Producer Choi. Did you get the files I sent you?
No, we're not sure who has the Pandora's Box yet.
We'll track it down as we record the show.
Okay, I'll come by the studio right now.
Bye.
Soo Yeon, I think it's too dangerous to air it on television.
I'll work on it and...
Don't worry, I'll be careful.
If that file gets into Lawyer Oh's hands,
Il Jae will take back the money we need for the matured bonds.
I know that.
Once the inheritance is sorted out and the company is stable again,
I'll hand these files to Soo Yeon.
I hear...
you're getting surgery tomorrow.
This...
might end up being my last meal.
I didn't expect you to invite me for such an occasion.
A couple may end their relationship by law,
but that's not the case for friends.
Friends?
We spent years together through conflicts.
If we're not friends, then what are we?
If you thought that way,
I should thank you.
Now that I'm knocking on my death's door,
life doesn't seem so complicated any more.
Your soup will get cold.
Please don't hesitate to talk about what you want to.
Dodo Group...
will support you for the election.
I might die.
I have no ulterior motives.
I'm thankful for your generosity,
but please do not bother helping me.
Listen, Congressman Hwang.
Did you...
change your mind...
now that I'm a strong candidate?
Friendship or partnership, they all depend on timing.
You're not helping me. It's the other way around.
Congressman Hwang.
Does it look like I'm asking you for a favour?
Then are you telling me...
that you're being sincere?
I don't have the power to save my life,
but I can easily...
control yours.
I'll save you a front row seat for my inaugural ceremony,
so please don't die.
I hope you get to see...
who the final winner is.
I was always treated by you,
so let me get this round.
This might be your last meal after all.
Take your time...
and enjoy it.
The winner?
Hwang Jae Man.
Money, wealth and honour...
are all but an empty dream.
I'll make sure...
I get...
to help you understand that.
Are you saying Chairman Do is involved...
in the murder of Chairman Kang's parents?
Chairman Do...
must have let Gwang Woo's crime slide.
If you look back at the T9 incident,
he could have concealed the truth on purpose.
That's why you're trying so hard to take over Dodo Group.
Did you say Gun Woo was able to open Do Choong's safe with a warrant?
Yes, that's what the bank teller said.
Do you think the Pandora's Box...
could be Chairman Do's secret safe?
Potentially.
That's a big problem.
Gun Woo already opened it.
These are all assumptions for now.
We'll figure things out now.
Welcome, Chairman Kang.
How are you feeling?
Very good. I'm of sound mind.
Thank you for bringing Dr Campbell, Gi Tan.
I thought you were against the surgery. Did you change your mind?
I'm relieved after meeting with Dr Campbell.
I think the surgery will go well tomorrow.
Could I ask you something, Sir?
What is it?
What's in your personal safe...
at Bando Bank?
Why are you asking me about that?
Gun Woo opened your safe...
with a warrant.
Did you really...
sign that warrant?
Don't you remember? You...
I remember.
It's true. I wrote him the warrant.
In the case...
that I die from the surgery,
someone has...
to open that safe.
I'm so tired.
I better sleep.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Did I...
really write...
that warrant?
Here's the warrant.
(I, Do Choong, allow Do Gun Woo the permission to access my safe.)
This is definitely your handwriting.
Then...
you must have seen what's inside.
It was something that no one else should see.
Gun Woo.
If...
I do not wake up after the surgery,
leave out the parts about Jae Man...
and burn the rest.
When you face...
difficulties as you run this company,
those documents about Jae Man's corruption...
will be of great help to you.
I understand.
How did you know I went to Bando Bank with that paper?
Have you been tailing me?
What was inside his secret safe?
Why do you want to know?
Because I think the Pandora's Box may lie in that safe.
If you're hiding it,
that means you've teamed up with Il Jae again.
You're wrong.
I'm going to find that Box and hand it to Soo Yeon.
How long do you think you can fool everyone?
I don't care if you fool everyone else.
But I won't forgive you...
if you fool Soo Yeon.
Soo Yeon is my fiancée.
Someone like you do not deserve to mention her name.
Listen closely, Gun Woo.
I will rip off your dirty mask...
in front of Soo Yeon very soon.
Are you all prepared to hide away Father?
Don't worry about it.
Have you ever seen me make a mistake?
Okay. I will trust you, Mr Yang.
Yes, okay.
Gun Woo probably won't stay quiet. Will this be okay?
Don't worry, Mum.
No one will find Father there.
Gwang Woo.
Only if we get our inheritance as it's written in his previous will,
we have nothing to worry about.
Gun Woo will not get...
a penny.
All of his work will go in vain.
You're so smart.
You're so good at these kind of stuff.
I'm not sure.
I think these kinds of things come...
whenever I get cornered.
These kind of wisdom just pops into my head out of nowhere.
Maybe this is an illness.
That's what people call a genius.
You've been gifted from above.
Only if Father had recognised me for who I am,
I wouldn't be doing such a thing.
My gosh.
Gwang Woo is completely fooled by me.
(Iris Identification)
(Transfer Confirmed)
(Your transfer has been successfully completed.)
I just sent you 100,000 dollars as front money.
You'll get the rest when everything is over.
Sure.
Sir.
One of my dreams as a child was to run a hotel.
Can you give me...
a bit of Dodo Hotel's shares?
You'll be getting all of Chairman Do's assets.
You can do that much for me.
I'll think about it.
Make sure you do.
If it wasn't for me, how would you receive such...
I said, I got it.
I trust you, Sir.
Dong Yi is such a pig.
He even wants Dodo Hotel.
As you know, talking about a crime does not make them guilty.
Let them make their move as planned.
When Dong Yi hands over Chairman Do to Gun Woo,
we'll get them.
That's the most effective way to let the world know...
about Gun Woo and Gwang Woo's crime.
I feel bad for Chairman Do.
All of his children except for Shin Young...
wishes that he dies.
He earned that.
He chased after money his entire life.
He has to go.
Dad.
Yes?
Don't worry.
I won't die easily.
I'm not worried. Things will all go well.
I believe you.
Shin Young.
Make sure Gwang Woo and your mum...
don't come...
near the hospital, please.
Okay.
Gun Woo.
Whatever happens,
you have to keep the company steady.
Yes, Father.
I will start the anaesthesia.
Anaesthesia is complete.
All right, then. Let's begin the operation.
Switch on the music, please.
Scalpel, please.
What is it, Mr Han?
I'm here at the annex parking lot with Mr Yang and his people.
Okay.
Yes, Mr Moon.
I'm at the parking lot in the annex.
Mr Han and Dong Yi are together.
You should greet them when the person arrives.
How many do we have?
I thought we may end up getting in a fight,
so I brought some strong ones.
Okay, then.
Goodness.
What's taking the surgery so long?
My gosh.
Hey.
How much longer do I have to wait?
Call the anaesthetist...
right now.
She's in the surgery room. I can't call her.
I'm waiting at the parking lot in the main building.
Give me a call as soon as she calls you.
All right, don't worry about it.
He's completely fooled.
My goodness.
(Doctor Kim)
What happened?
Chairman Do's surgery is finished.
Come to the recovery room in 20 minutes.
How is he?
Well, the operation was successful.
Then is the amnesia completely better?
Well, he probably won't suffer from amnesia.
However, he might have some problems with...
paralysis and speech problems.
But it can be overcome with therapy.
Okay, thanks. Thanks a lot.
Okay, you're welcome.
Where's Dad?
He's in the recovery room.
I'll call you once the patient is up.
I'm so relieved.
Ga Din, aren't you hungry?
I have to go somewhere.
You should eat with Mr Gong.
You must be starving. Let's go eat.
Patient Do is having a cardiac arrest!
Prepare for CPR.
200 joules.
Shoot.
300 joules.
9:28am. I pronounce Patient Do Choong...
dead.
What's this?
What happened?
Chairman Do disappeared.
What do you mean he's gone?
He should be in the recovery room, but he's not!
It's me.
Things have gone astray.
No, it's not that.
What's going on? Why did they just come out?
It's taking longer than I thought.
Yes. They should be here by now.
Who came from Gwang Woo's side?
We're keep a good eye on them. If someone arrives from their side,
we'll be informed.
Yes, Sir.
Things didn't work out. You should return to the office.
Mr Han is leaving.
Have someone follow him.
Follow the car that just exited.
Yes, Soo Tak. Go ahead.
What?
Okay.
What happened?
Dong Yi came out empty-handed.
- He didn't have Chairman Do?
-  No.
Chairman Do disappeared.
You said Dong Yi came out empty-handed.
It seems like someone else...
got there before he did.
- Check on Gwang Woo.
-  Yes, Sir.
You said the chairman died.
How can a dead man disappear?
I'm sorry. We're trying to figure it out,
so please calm down.
Shin Young.
Gi Tan. Dad...
I heard the news.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
I'm not myself right now.
I'll find out what happened. Go home and rest.
Mr Gong, please take Shin Young home.
We better do that.
Let's go, Shin Young.
Come on.
I have no leads.
If it's not Gwang Woo or Gun Woo, who could it be?
Go secure the CCTV footage.
Yes, Sir.
Why are you doing this to me?
I really have nothing to do with it.
If you don't, who does?
That's why this is so strange.
Did you side with Gwang Woo?
No way. Please trust me on this.
It's Gwang Woo.
- Put it on speaker.
-  Okay.
- Yes.
-  Hey!
Where did you take Dad?
I didn't take him.
When I got to the room, the chairman was already gone.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Who put you up to this?
Is it Gun Woo...
or Gi Tan?
Mr Kim. Talk to the hospital...
and make sure this news doesn't leak out.
Yes, Sir.
If you're trying to play tricks,
I'll kill you with my own hands.
I'll put my life on the line if you want me to.
Please trust me.
What a jerk.
That hurts.
Anyhow, this is getting complicated.
Pause it, please.
That's Father.
They covered him up, but I can tell.
Do you know that person?
I'm not sure.
He has a mask on, so it's hard to tell.
Please found out and let us know.
All right.
- Gun Woo.
-  Gi Tan.
Go ahead.
Did you take my father?
I think it has got to be someone around us.
I'm just curious.
I thought it would be you.
The only person...
who would benefit from this would be you.
There's the inheritance issue as well.
You should butt out of our family affairs.
I wish I could, but it's just so entertaining to watch you.
Entertaining? What did I do?
Do you want me to tell you?
Are you sure you want to hear it with Soo Yeon here?
No matter what you say, she won't believe you.
You know Yang Dong Yi, right?
You're...
a terrible human.
You're just as bad as Il Jae.
Gun Woo, do you know Dong Yi?
- Yes, I know him.
-  How?
He approached me as if he were a businessman,
but I only found out he's working for Gwang Woo later.
There's a lot I need to resolve.
I'll get going.
Your father's dead.
He didn't die. He disappeared.
There's no way he would have walked out on his two feet.
The surgery must have gone wrong and Gun Woo probably took him...
in order to hide the fact that he died.
Come to think of it, that sounds likely.
Why would Gun Woo hide him?
Because if the world finds out my husband is dead,
the inheritance will be divided according to the will.
That's no reason to hide a corpse.
It's his father after all.
You don't know anything.
Gwang Woo, pack up right away.
Are you going back home?
It's my house. Of course, I should.
I'm the owner now.
What are you doing? Pack up.
All right, Mum.
I need to be on my toes.
That's the only way I'll be able to take everything.
Let's call the police first.
We can't.
Why not?
If word gets out,
Dodo Group's shares will plummet.
Is that all you care about?
He asked me to take over the company.
You heard him.
What do you want to do?
Where is your father?
What do you mean?
As if tearing our family apart wasn't enough,
now you smuggled your father's body.
You're very brazen. It's your fault he's dead.
Shut your mouth.
I will plan his funeral.
Mum.
A funeral without a body?
Are you afraid you'll have nothing once his will is read?
Bring his body back then.
No one in this family is on your side now.
I'm against having the funeral, too.
That's just wrong.
Get a grip, you fool.
We have to get on with our lives.
Do you have the right to say that?
Shin Young.
Step aside.
I put up with you for Dad's sake,
but that's over now.
Won't news of the chairman's death...
work in your favour?
If his will is found in the secret safe...
Watch your tongue.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Let them do what they want for now.
If I am to avoid suspicion, the fake will...
must be found at the very end.
You're right.
Who do you think...
took the chairman from the hospital?
That bothers me.
Who could it be?
Thanks for making the time to come.
I heard his body is missing.
Will it be okay?
Nothing bad can happen.
He was pronounced dead.
I've never attended a funeral like this before.
Be quiet.
People might hear you.
What are you looking at?
I'm wondering if...
anyone here could've smuggled the chairman out.
Il Jae is here.
I'll wait for you outside.
Your approval rating has gone up.
I'm meeting members of the ruling party for dinner.
- I'll see you around.
-  Goodbye.
Mr Byun.
I'm the elder son. Don't bow to him.
You're nothing now that...
the chairman's gone.
This is a public place.
Please leave.
You will...
come back to me.
Very soon, Gun Woo.
I guess no one here...
welcomed you, Uncle.
Thanks to you,
I feel a bit lonely, but very much at ease.
Guess what?
Did you know that the coffin in that church...
is empty?
Is it?
That's news to me.
Be prepared.
Evidence of your crimes...
will come into my possession very soon.
No such thing...
even exists.
Don't waste your efforts.
Chairman Do...
is with me.
Once he wakes up,
the secret files you fear more than anything...
will be mine.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
No secret file can take me down.
What do you think?
I'm not sure.
I don't think he had anything to do with the chairman.
We got one thing out of him.
What, Sir?
The files we're looking for.
The chairman has them.
Then the Pandora's Box is...
It could be...
in the chairman's secret safe.
Hwang Jae Man, the ruling party's presidential candidate,
is gaining support.
In a telephone poll aimed at Hanguk Party's congressmen,
Mr Hwang's support rating is very close to that...
of Bang Hyung Joo's, who is currently in the lead.
Next up.
Dodo Group's Chairman Do Choong died in surgery...
and his funeral took place today at a cathedral in Seoul.
I am still...
alive and well.
How dare they hold a funeral?
Dodo Group hosted the funeral, but out of respect...
for the late Mr Do's wishes,
only close family and friends were invited.
It was a simple affair.
How dare they?
I can't move.
I can't speak.
Where's our legal counsel?
How dare they make us wait?
Sorry we're late.
Replacing you will be the first thing I do.
Read my father's will.
I will read the late Do Choong's final will and testament.
"I, Do Choong, will the following."
"50 percent of the shares I own..."
"will go to Do Gwang Woo."
"30 percent of the shares I own..."
"will go to Do Shin Young."
"The remaining 20 percent..."
"will go to Hwang Gwi Ja."
"How the remaining assets are split up..."
"is up to the family,"
"but Gwang Woo takes 50 percent, Shin Young takes 30..."
"and Gwi Ja takes 20 percent."
That's it.
You heard it all.
Lawyer Oh, execute the will.
- Mr Han.
-  Yes, Sir.
We'll host an extraordinary general meeting in two days.
What's the agenda?
Come on. Isn't it obvious?
We need to elect a temporary chairperson...
and fire Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo.
Yes, Sir.
(Chairman Do Choong)
Take this and throw it away in a garbage can.
Yes, Ma'am.
Gwang Woo, sit in the chairman's chair.
I'm fine. You should sit there.
You'll soon be the chairman. You should sit there.
I am going to make you the chairwoman...
in this next EGM.
Why?
I want you to be the temporary chairwoman.
I thought I should become...
the actual chairman at the next general meeting.
All right.
I guess that's another way to do it.
It's been so long.
After the EGM,
you should fire Mr Gong first.
We can't fire him yet.
Why not?
He knows all of the secrets about our household.
What if he decides to write an autobiography?
Not only will we be disgraced, but you'll be put in danger.
Oh, right.
Anyway, after this EGM,
I'm going to fire everyone...
from Gun Woo to the board.
I'll probably get fired after this EGM.
- Gun Woo.
-  I'm fine with everything.
But I feel sorry to you.
I didn't get engaged to you to show you a bad side of me.
I don't care what your position is.
All I care about is that you are an honest person.
I hope you won't get hurt as you go through this, Gun Woo.
Thank you, Soo Yeon.
Lawyer Oh!
I was so busy that I forgot to tell you.
Choong Dong gets discharged from jail thanks to a special pardon.
What time is that?
I think we'll make it if we leave now.
I have to run.
I'll call you.
I'm sorry.
Gwang Woo, Gwi Ja.
Are you trying to get rid of me?
(Korea Prison)
Mr Oh.
Congratulations on your parole.
This will probably be the most delicious thing...
Lawyer Oh has ever brought.
Here. Eat up.
You should think about your mum.
Don't ever return to prison ever again.
Come on.
Why did he throw this away? This is perfectly good.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Thanks for your work, Choong Dong.
I heard you took good care of my dear Choong Dong.
Thank you, Lawyer Oh.
You can forget about him now.
He'll continue to work for me.
Let's go, Choong Dong.
- I'll drive.
-  No, I'll drive. Get in.
He's on Il Jae's side to the end.
Everything we did went down the drain.
It's too early to give up.
You saw him, too.
Once Il Jae called him,
he ran over wagging his tail.
Choong Dong has been shaken.
I will make sure he gives in.
I got divorced and abandoned by Jae Man.
People give me such sad looks.
You still look fatigued.
For someone in the second place, first place is their enemy.
For third place, first and second places are their enemies.
Having fell through means I have a lot of people...
to get rid of.
Other than that, everything is the same.
It doesn't matter which place I'm in.
I only aim to come first place.
You'll be busy because we have so many enemies.
Be ready for it.
Yes.
Anyway, where are we headed?
You're here.
This is an anaesthetist of Dodo Hospital who's helping me.
Didn't you used to work at Sudo Hospital?
You're right. That's when he was a director there.
I'm surprised you remember me.
I thought the news reported Chairman Do dead.
If it wasn't for Doctor Kim, I would've never gotten him here.
Patient Do Choong has legally passed away as of 9:28am.
The guy who brought him out is...
Doctor Kim's younger brother.
If things go well, she'll become the director of Dodo Hospital.
I look forward to it, Lawyer Byun.
How is he doing?
He can't talk at all.
He also can't move well due to paralysis.
Can he hear?
His hearing is normal.
Chairman Do.
You've lived your life in vain.
Other than Shin Young,
there was no one who was sad about your death.
Do you know why you're here?
It's because you trusted Gun Woo.
He's a dangerous man.
You'll soon learn about Gun Woo for who he really is.
Great work, Son.
I'm sorry that I put you through this, Mum.
We don't even know where Dad is or what happened to him.
How can you do this?
Why do you wonder where he is?
He's probably dating Ja Young, Gun Woo's mum, in his afterlife.
Lawyer Oh is here.
What happened to his assets and inheritance?
It's being processed.
Process it quickly and run to Bando Bank tomorrow.
Bando Bank? Why?
We have to empty out the secret safe if we want to clear his articles.
A lawyer needs to be there,
so you can go over with Shin Young.
Why would I go there?
One of the heirs need to be there.
Why is that me?
Tomorrow is the EGM.
He'll be busy from the morning.
I'll write you a warrant, so go.
Tomorrow, Gun Woo will become penniless.
Soo Yeon.
What did I tell you?
I said I'd make you regret choosing Gun Woo.
At today's EGM,
Ms Hwang will be named temporary chairwoman.
Whoever it is,
it will be easier to deal with than Gun Woo.
Dodo Hotel will become the new holding company.
If I threaten them with the bonds,
they won't be able to refuse.
(Do Shin Young)
Isn't it a bit early?
I have to go to Bando Bank and I don't want to.
Bando Bank? What for?
We have to clear out his secret safe.
His secret safe?
Could you take Shin Young to Bando Bank?
Yes, Sir.
Why should he come along?
We need to check something.
Hello.
Do you have the documents?
- Here it is.
-  Thanks.
(Power of Attorney)
That's fine. Come with me.
Why are you here?
The Pandora's Box we're looking for...
may be in here.
If it is,
we'll ask Shin Young if we can take it.
Remember that.
Okay.
This is it. Please check.
What's this?
Is this the only thing inside?
What's wrong?
It's a will in the chairman's hand.
What?
There's another will?
This is dated most recently.
That means...
this is legally binding.
What does it say?
Lawyer Oh's party just left the bank.
They'll have found and read the will by now.
Gun Woo.
Are you here to resign?
I'd have tendered my resignation if I were you.
Do you want to get embarrassed in front of all our shareholders?
Where's your pride?
Say hello next time.
You look so calm.
Aren't you nervous?
Should I be?
We all know how this meeting will end.
I don't think we can be sure of anything.
I think he knows about...
the handwritten will.
He got into the safe already.
I smell...
something very fishy.
With your overwhelming support,
we now have a temporary chairperson.
I shall now let Chairwoman Hwang Gwi Ja take the stand...
and make a speech.
Mr Han.
I'll speak at the end. Deal with the next agenda first.
Yes, Ma'am.
We shall now vote on whether Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo...
must be dismissed.
Wait!
We found...
in Chairman Do's safety deposit box...
a handwritten will.
There's another will?
What's he talking about?
The date here is May 7 of this year.
It was written before the chairman was diagnosed with dementia.
That makes this a legally binding will...
that supersedes any other will the chairman...
wrote before this.
What?
Is that true?
As Dodo Group's legal counsel,
Lawyer Oh will read it out.
I shall now read Chairman Do Choong's will.
"This is my will."
"My wife and eldest son tried to harm me."
"They will not inherit anything."
"My daughter treated me with disrespect."
"I will leave her the house in Samseong-dong."
"My shares and assets..."
"will go to Yoon Ja Young's son."
"But Yoon Ja Young's son..."
"must uphold my spirit and make the company flourish."
That is all.
Who is Yoon Ja Young's son?
It's Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo.
Is that true?
Was that...
really found in your father's safe?
Yes.
Gun Woo.
Are you behind this?
Behind what?
Dad never said that he'd left...
a handwritten will.
I'd never heard of it either.
How dare you try to dupe me?
Come here.
You planned this!
I did not!
I've never seen it before!
I don't believe you!
Gwang Woo. Are you okay?
Leave my son alone.
- Ma'am.
-  Are you mad?
Calm down.
- Don't forget where you are!
-  Ma'am.
- Calm down.
-  Let me go.
You did it!
Calm down, Sir.
Calm down.
First your mother, now you!
I'd never heard about this will!
Don't do this in public!
Gwang Woo might be right.
The will could be fake.
Dodo Group's extraordinary general meeting...
ended in utter chaos.
Do Choong's handwritten will was revealed and read out,
and Vice Chairman Do Gun Woo was named temporary chairman.
Ex-CEO Do Gwang Woo insists on contesting the will...
and vowed he would sue.
(Byun Il Jae)
I sent the photos.
Lawyer Oh.
Where is Gun Woo?
In the chairman's office.
This is his phone. I picked it up earlier.
I'll take it to him.
You will sue for your share?
Did you think we'd just let you take it all?
You hid your father away so you could pull this off!
Sue me.
I will put you behind bars for attempted murder.
Attempted murder?
Have you forgotten?
You swapped my father's medication.
I have video evidence!
Sir.
Here's your phone.
Where did you find it?
(Byun Il Jae)
What is it?
Did you get the photo I sent?
What photo?
I'll send it again. Give me a call.
What is it?
My father.
Il Jae has him.
You know Yang Don Yi, right?
You're...
a terrible human.
Just as bad as Il Jae.
Chairman Do Gun Woo's here.
Come in.
Sit down.
Congratulations on becoming the chairman.
Tell me what happened.
It's me, Choong Dong.
Come in.
I can't let Gun Woo...
deceive you any longer.
(Monster)
Gun Woo's actions don't make sense.
Shin Young fell into the trap I set.
I beg of you.
Don't ever show up again.
I need to meet him.
Find a way.
I'm not stupid.
Of course I should get rid of everyone at once.
I will become President.
No one can stop me.
The stage is set. It's time to act.