(Episode 49)
Hello?
Is this Kang Gi Tan?
It is.
You want the Pandora's Box.
I have it.
Who is it?
Let's meet right now.
You said you would give me three million dollars.
Can you give me five million?
If you hand me that box,
I'll give you whatever you want.
I need some more time.
I'll call you again.
Wait. Hello? Hello?
Was that the informant?
Yes.
The two top presidential candidates for this election, Hwang Jae Man...
and Eo Gyeong Seok are revealing shocking stories about each other.
The nation is in deep shock over these scandals.
They both claim these scandals are false propaganda by the other,
and will not cease running for presidency.
On the other hand, the prosecution will...
conduct an investigation...
on Mr Eo and Mr Hwang's scandals...
after the presidential election is over.
Hence, there is much attention on the result of this election.
You have to go vote early tomorrow. Stop drinking, Father.
How's the public sentiment?
It looks like people will vote...
for the third in line instead of Mr Eo and you.
Il Jae.
I can't believe he stabbed me in the back at the last minute.
I told you to never trust him.
Everything depends...
on the result of the election tomorrow.
If I fail,
I probably can't avoid...
the prosecution investigation.
One good thing is that people are focused more...
on Mr Eo's sex scandal rather than your lobby.
Whether I get elected or not,
I will make sure...
to destroy Il Jae...
with my own hands.
If Mr Eo doesn't get elected, Gi Tan will take over the company.
Do you understand?
We have to wait for the result.
It's too early to feel defeated.
I can already see how it will go.
Are you blind?
That's too much, Gun Woo.
Shut it.
What? Are you kidding me?
What are you trying to do?
Choong Dong!
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Gun Woo dared to speak to you...
Apologise to Gun Woo. Be polite.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
Take Mr Kim and leave.
I understand you, Gun Woo.
Things aren't looking great, so you can be angry and you can blame me.
But Gun Woo,
what we need in a time like this is a peace of our mind.
Even if the world collapses, there is always a way out.
What if we don't find that way?
We will find a way.
(Mr Gong)
Speak.
Chairman is looking for you.
What is this about?
Gun Woo.
What Il Jae spread is...
all from Chairman's secret safe, right?
Gun Woo, are you listening to me?
Tell Father that I will visit him tomorrow to have a chat.
Okay.
He said he'll come tomorrow and tell you himself.
Wait. What is he saying?
Gun Woo must be crazy...
to give Il Jae everything in the Pandora's Box.
Let's stop thinking for tonight and just have a drink.
He's very drunk. Make sure he gets home safely.
Choong Dong.
What is this?
This is Gun Woo's fingerprint.
- Do you have a Dodo Group's card? - Yes.
Go to Chairman's room tonight...
and bring the Pandora's Box which Gun Woo is holding.
Yes, Sir.
(Dodo Group)
Safe unlocked.
(Moving 140 files from Desktop)
Did you bring it?
The safe was empty.
It was empty?
I think Gun Woo took everything out.
Did you try going through his computer?
Here you go.
Give it to me.
It's not here.
Gun Woo took it out already.
Why don't we just kidnap him and make him tell us?
What do you think I'll do now?
Are you saying you'll give Soo Yeon the evidence that I murdered?
Isn't that only fair?
I was ruined for trusting you.
He might have given it to Soo Yeon already.
Shadow her tomorrow and find out.
What if she already has it?
Why are you asking me?
Pardon?
In it are the evidence that I committed murder.
Kidnap or get rid of her.
We have to stop it from leaking to the media!
Yes, Sir.
What's your expectation for today's election?
Justice that cannot win...
is not justice.
I trust that our citizens...
will show us...
what justice exactly means.
You denied the secrets exposed by your ex-son-in-law, Byun Il Jae.
What do you mean, exposed?
If one makes up lies,
that's slandering.
A vicious slander.
Why do you think Byun Il Jae did such a thing?
We were arguing throughout our divorce.
I can only assume that...
it's a shameful revenge.
Please say one last word.
Sure.
Dear citizens.
If you want a world of justice and principle,
please head to a voting station right now.
Voting is the most political action...
you can take as citizens.
- Congressman Eo. - You must all be busy.
You claimed that Hong Hee Jin was bribed by Congressman Hwang...
when she reported she was sexually abused by you.
Do you have evidence?
I already stated my case.
Let's talk about something else.
Have you ever met with Byun Il Jae before?
He came to see me first...
and told me that he would expose Congressman Hwang's secrets.
I'd like to applause Byun Il Jae on his courage...
for revealing the truth despite all the dangers.
Oh Soo Yeon went to vote, and now she's going back to the office.
No, she's not doing anything out of the ordinary.
Yes. I'll keep watching.
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing? - What is it?
Did Il Jae tell you to tail Soo Yeon around?
This is a nice car.
Wow. How much does a car like this cost?
Have you had lunch yet?
Get off.
Sure. We all do different things to make a living.
We're going to order jjajangmyeon. Come join us.
I said, get off!
You're so rude.
You ate so well in jail.
It's just a meal. Why not just eat together?
Come on.
I'll order you something expensive. Come on.
When the informant shows up,
we'll be able to prove that Il Jae is a murderer.
Oh Choong Dong. You still have a chance.
What chance?
A chance to be forgiven...
for all the crimes you committed for him.
Enough nonsense. You can't fool me.
You need to wake up.
Il Jae will be pushed to the end of the cliff.
Do you plan on jumping off with him?
No, don't do that.
Your mother's still alive.
Is she well?
Why did Il Jae order you to shadow me?
It's not like that.
Then did he tell you to kidnap me?
No way, he wouldn't do that.
This is bad table manner.
Here, finish it. The noodles are getting cold.
I'm finished.
Choong Dong.
I have my trust in you.
I won't give up. I'll wait for you until the end.
Suit yourself.
Finish this before you go.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Gosh.
Are you okay?
Did you see those eyes? He gives me the chills.
Are you sure there's something we can get from him?
It'd be over if we can find the informant.
No one else would know...
better than him.
That's true. If he comes to our side,
Il Jae would spend the rest of his life in jail...
at the least.
He's like a VIP to us.
That's why I said we should have ordered something expensive.
How can we order it when we don't have money?
We can order with the business credit card.
Yes, Sir.
I'm certain Gun Woo hasn't given those files to Soo Yeon yet.
You can leave now.
Don't you need me to shadow them longer?
Dodo Group is still standing strong.
I won't make rash decisions for now.
Understood.
(Min and Oh Law Firm)
There are two hours left until voting closes.
The voting rate currently stands at 54.1 percent.
National Election Commission predicts...
the final rating to be around 60,
which is the least number of votes in history.
Great.
The chairman has been waiting for you.
What is it?
The announcement made by Il Jae regarding Jae Man.
Did that come from the chairman's secret safe?
That's right.
I gave it to Il Jae.
Why did you do that?
Even if it's for our company,
you should have never revealed it.
Does he know about what state the company is in?
Yes, I gave him an update.
It was the only way to help save the company.
If you wanted to save Dodo Group, you should have sided with Jae Man,
not Congressman Eo.
I won't let Gi Tan take over the company.
Don't worry, Father.
What are you doing?
Gun Woo.
Did you give Il Jae...
everything in the Pandora's Box?
Actually,
it would be better if you did.
I have the rest.
Why?
Are you scared you'll be found out about instigating murder?
Hey!
It doesn't have anything to do with you.
Why do you have that?
I have a feeling it'll come to good use later.
No. You'd never use it.
Just give it to me.
I'd rather burn it than do that.
No... Hold on.
You're not planning to give it to Soo Yeon, are you?
If that gets revealed,
it won't be just Il Jae and I that gets punished.
Dodo Group will be damaged. If you really are a chairman...
Mind your own business. I'll take care of it.
If Dodo Group...
gets eaten up by Gi Tan,
Do Gun Woo might go crazy and hand those over...
to Soo Yeon.
Mr Han.
Mr Han...
What is he doing? Is he even working?
We are about to find out who the next president of Korea is.
Here is the exit poll conducted by the three network TV stations.
(Exit poll, Hwang Jae Man has the safe seat.)
Candidate Hwang Jae Man with 41.3 percent of the votes,
and Candidate Eo Gyeong Seok with 29.6 percent of the votes.
The exit poll showed Candidate Hwang has...
about 11.7 percent more votes than Candidate Eo.
It's over.
Where are you going?
They only started counting. Go in and stay.
Everything is over.
The result is...
obvious.
The president is...
Hwang Jae Man.
It may not mean much to you,
but my life is at stake here.
- Are you insane? - What are you doing?
Let go of him.
Let go.
It's all over? It means I'll be dead.
Take your responsibility. Eo Gyeong Seok, take responsibility!
- Are you okay? - Let go.
He's completely insane.
Hwang Jae Man of the Hanguk Party won the election...
with 42.8 of the votes and became the next president of Korea.
- President Hwang Jae Man! - President Hwang Jae Man!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
- Great job, everyone. - President Hwang Jae Man!
- Father, congratulations. - Great job, Ji Soo.
Great job.
You will go in for a press conference.
Okay. Great job.
Good job.
Chairman Kang. Thank you.
Congratulations, President.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Welcome.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
Are you?
It's time for the press conference, President.
Sure.
I'll call you later.
See you later.
What's wrong? Are you going blind again?
No. I'm fine now.
We should go to a hospital and get a thorough checkup.
Before that,
I wonder how Il Jae is.
I'll look for him.
We told everyone about his corruption.
I can't believe over 40 percent of the people still voted for him.
They're probably indifferent because there are so many corruptions.
I hope this isn't a choice we will regret.
Let go of me.
How dare you talk back to me?
Do I look like an idiot to you?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Calm down.
Let go.
Do I look like an idiot to you, too?
What is with you, Sir?
I don't need any of you. If you want to leave, leave.
Please stop, Sir.
What brings you here?
Are you here to mock me?
I was, but I don't think that's necessary.
I don't need to name you anything when you've made a mess of yourself.
What?
I'm disappointed, Uncle.
I thought you'd be planning a revenge against me.
But look at you.
You're just a loser.
He is a loser, Chairman.
His slush fund is taken away, and the president despises him.
He's worse than a loser.
Fine.
You are amazing, Guk Cheol.
But...
getting a revenge won't bring your parents back alive.
You'll see your parents only once you die.
Do you understand?
That means you can't ever win...
no matter what you do.
Everyone you ever loved are all dead.
They are all rotting six feet under.
Sir.
You jerk.
Do you both want to die?
Come in.
You shouldn't play around with this.
If you do, you'll probably get ripped in pieces.
Listen carefully.
I will use all lawful means to give you a death penalty.
Remember what I said when you die on the gallows.
Death won't be the end for you.
You will drop down to a pit of fire when you die, Il Jae.
- Calm down... - Let go.
Let's see who will go...
down the pit, Guk Cheol.
Mr Moon.
Yes, Chairman.
Take out all matured bonds from Dodo Group tomorrow.
It must be Gun Woo's turn.
Call every single president of the banks...
that are doing business with Dodo Group right now.
Yes, Sir.
What has Mr Gong been doing?
Look at your toenails.
Isn't it great to have me cut your toenails?
No, it isn't.
Stop it, woman.
You used to pester me, asking to clip your nails...
and to clean your ears.
Back then,
we lived in a small house but those were the good times.
You never came back home empty-handed.
You always brought home my favourite street snacks.
I think those were the happiest days of my life.
I thought you'd love only me forever.
How did we end up like this?
You're right.
We lived a crazy life,
and what we lost wasn't just our time.
We still have a chance.
We can still go back to those times.
I won't be greedy.
I'll live the rest of my life taking care of you.
So please give Gwang Woo one of our subsidiaries.
For me, I'll be satisfied if you give me...
either Dodo Fashion or something in media.
We can be happy again like our old times, Honey.
This is why we have grown far away from each other.
Because of your greediness.
Your beard...
has grown quite a lot.
Do you want me to shave you?
What? No, thanks.
I never had a beard.
Gwi Ja, don't do this. Please.
Gwi Ja.
Why are you so stiffened up?
Are you afraid that I'll make a cut?
Don't worry.
I used...
to work at a barbershop before I met...
What are you talking about?
Did you also work at a barbershop and not just a factory?
I used to shave my father all the time when I was young.
Chairman, we're in trouble.
Dodo Group has gone bankrupt.
What do you mean it's bankrupt?
My goodness...
I'm so sorry, Honey.
Give me a tissue right now.
My goodness.
What do you mean bankrupt? What are you talking about?
Yes, this is the chairman's office.
Pardon?
How can you do this to us now?
What do you mean pay back the loan right now?
Excuse me, Sir!
Gosh.
I don't think this is something to discuss over the phone.
Let's meet in person.
Please hold on for a moment.
It's BC Bank.
If you won't meet, what do you expect me to do?
We'll give you a call back.
Do whatever you want.
BC Bank is requesting that we pay them back as well.
Yes, this is the chairman's office.
Although we're bankrupt,
it's strange that all of the banks are requesting to pay back.
It's Kang Gi Tan.
He's controlling it all.
An emergency creditors' meeting will be held this afternoon.
This is what we feared.
What happened to filing for legal management?
The documents are all ready.
- Get it registered at the court. - Yes, Sir.
Come if you dare, Kang Gi Tan.
I'll fight you until the end.
Gun Woo filed for legal management.
Then what happens now?
He's trying to stop us from exercising credit to earn time.
He wants to put up a fight?
Well,
we'll see how far he goes.
Dodo Group's secretary called and asked you...
to join for the creditors' meeting.
I understand how you feel,
but you must separate work from your personal life.
You're their legal advisor. You must go.
This is my resignation letter.
Are you going to quit being their legal advisor?
Please hand this in for me.
I want you to take over instead for the time being.
All right.
I'll be back.
Soo Yeon, is it over with Chairman Do?
What do you mean legal management?
Are you trying to avoid loan waiver?
That's a little harsh.
Please do not dishonour Dodo Group's name.
Dishonour?
You're bankrupt. Why does that matter right now?
I'll soon be announcing my plan to revive the company.
I'll pay all the creditors back, so please do not worry.
Chairman Do.
You forgot one thing.
Why are you hiding the fact...
that all of the banks requested you...
to pay back the loans at once?
Is this true?
Why don't you answer this question yourself...
since you're the one that persuaded the banks?
Instead of watering a rotten tree,
I prefer to pull it out and planting a new tree.
You're the one that made this tree rot.
So you agree that it's rotten?
Chairman Do Choong is here.
(Dodo Group)
Father.
Since the chairman is still ill,
I will be relaying his messages.
He's asking for you...
to put your trust in him once more...
and to extend the mature bonds.
I decline.
Even if the chairman asks me,
I cannot extend it any more.
He would like to...
speak to you in private.
Can we talk, Shin Young?
I'll be waiting in the lobby.
Why are you here? You're not a creditor.
What do you think...
Gi Tan will talk to Father about?
What's your intention behind this question?
What I mean is,
we should go listen to them.
In my opinion,
their conversation will really open up your ears.
Chairman knows...
that you're the son of the late director of Sudo Hospital.
And?
He's asking if you'd stop your attack against Dodo Group...
if he were to hand over the evidence of Il Jae committing murder.
You're mistaken.
It won't end with just revealing Il Jae's crimes.
Gwang Woo instigated the murder in order to be acknowledged by you.
Then you covered up his crime in order to save the company.
You all aren't much different from Il Jae to me.
Do you understand?
You're an accomplice of Il Jae that killed my parents!
The chairman...
trusts you enough to give Shin Young to you.
You should be thankful that she's your daughter.
If it wasn't for her,
I would have ripped Dodo Group to shreds.
Persuade Gun Woo...
to change the holding company to Dodo Hotel.
That's the only way to reduce the damages.
This is the last chance...
I'm giving to you.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Chairman. Chairman...
It's my fault.
Chairman...
I'm sorry,
but it's too late.
Dad.
I'm sorry,
Shin Young.
Dad.
What did he say?
Ask him yourself if you want to know.
Shall I tell you my plan?
Even if the company's torn apart,
I won't give it to you.
You got it all wrong.
You won't give it to me.
I'll take it from you.
You took Soo Yeon from me,
but I'll take everything from you.
Including Soo Yeon.
I told you not to talk about her!
Sir.
You can't have Soo Yeon or the company.
Do you think I'll give up if you file for legal management?
- Sir. - Oh dear.
- Sir. - What are you doing?
You can't fight here. Everyone's watching.
Talk it out. Mouths aren't just for eating with.
Stop it. Chairman Do's here.
- Mr Moon. - Yes?
Prepare to make a takeover bid on Dodo Group.
Gun Woo's...
trying to stall and...
I can't wait.
How much money can we pool together?
So Gil Du agreed to finance us.
How much can we borrow from Z Capital?
Name the amount. I'll get it for you.
Get the money.
Dodo Group...
is over.
- Yes, Boss. - Yes, Sir.
You heard...
what Gi Tan thinks of us.
Shall I explain everything for you?
I gave the order that Gi Tan's parents be killed...
and Dad knew about it but covered it up. Why?
He wanted Dodo Group to prosper.
Gi Tan knew all that...
and approached you on purpose.
Now... Do you finally get it?
Shin Young.
It's not too late.
If you and I think for ourselves and join forces,
we can crush Gi Tan...
Have you lost your mind? How dare you slap your big brother.
Get lost, you moron.
What? Moron?
I'm not the moron here. You are.
You're worse than a moron.
You heard what he said.
Gi Tan told our dad he can't forgive us.
Once he takes out Gun Woo,
you'll be next.
Do you get that?
Shin Young, my dear sister.
There's something called fate.
We're siblings. We're related.
I can't help but go against Gi Tan.
That is our fate and destiny.
That stupid brat.
How many times did she hit me?
You've had enough.
You're drunk.
Let go of me.
Go. Leave me alone.
- Shin Young. - Don't touch me.
You're drunk. I'll carry you.
I'm your enemy's daughter.
Forget about me.
Whether I'm in danger or not.
Shin Young.
My dad was your enemy.
You knew it all along.
Why didn't you tell me?
I fell for you and followed you around.
Did you enjoy that?
- I didn't. - Don't make excuses!
My dad and my brother did something terrible.
Why do I have to suffer along with them?
Why does my life have to be torn apart?
You did nothing wrong.
You won't know,
but you're the first man...
I ever really loved.
Because of you,
my heart...
beat so hard and fast.
Why did you do this to me?
Why?
You jerk. You scumbag. You dirtbag.
Do you know what...
the hardest part of my plan was?
It was you.
You made it so much harder.
You're a great woman.
You're too good for me.
I'm sorry, Ga Din.
This isn't why I got drunk.
I wanted to apologise to you.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
You can leave me any time you want.
Or you can stay.
You are...
the woman I trust the most.
You're my business partner.
I'll...
leave as soon as I find a great guy.
I'll marry a much better-looking man than you.
I'll make you jealous.
That's how happy...
I'll be with him.
Yes, Shin Young.
Gun Woo.
He says...
do what Gi Tan asks and change the holding company to Dodo Hotel.
Is that all he thought of after their chat?
Greed can become one's downfall.
That's what made me like this.
Father, I don't want to give in to Gi Tan.
You don't want to give in to Mr Hwang,
but look at you now while he became president.
Even if it means I go down with Gi Tan,
I will not be defeated like you were.
Goodbye.
I think you should revoke his ownership.
You just have to give the word and I'll...
No.
Sir.
Gun Woo...
Feel pity.
Are you waiting for the informant to call?
He's taking his time.
Do you think something happened since then?
The director of the lab, Jung Man Ok felt...
the need to receive that money.
Later, Man Ok became the director...
and tried to get that money again.
However, she failed because the late directors' son,
Lee Guk Cheol, declined.
I'm sure the informant...
worked at Dodo Pharmaceutical at the time.
Couldn't it be someone from Sudo Hospital?
I was there at the time.
Only the people on Jung Man Ok's team...
knew about the investment.
Gwang Woo was in charge of brokering the deal.
Who worked with him at the time?
Go Hae Sool, Chief Secretary of the Strategic Planning Department...
and Dodo Group's Han Sang Goo.
See what they've been up to.
I want to know about their work and private life.
Do you think 1 of those 2 men is the informant?
He asked me for some time.
There's a reason he can't give me...
the files right away.
I'll find out.
What's wrong?
Are you going blind again?
No.
I'm okay now.
This won't do. You need a checkup.
Let's go.
What did the doctor say?
It's temporary so I needn't worry.
You two can go ahead. I'll take a walk.
Did you ask the doctor?
He said the same. That it's temporary.
I will go blind?
Yes.
Is it because of the bullet in my head?
No.
Something went wrong with your transplanted cornea.
Will another transplant...
Your optic nerves are already damaged.
Your vision will not improve.
How long...
do I have until I lose...
my vision again?
Maybe three months.
You have six months at most.
I'll be on my way.
Soo Yeon.
I don't think I can go after you any more.
So...
before I go blind,
I want to see you a lot.
You are...
so beautiful, Soo Yeon.
After visiting the cemetery, presidential elect Hwang Jae Man...
headed to the press centre for the upcoming press conference.
Mr Hwang plans to share his plans...
to revive the economy and eradicate corruption...
while he is in office.
Turn it off.
(Appoint Byun Il Jae prime minister.)
(Prime minister)
It all went too wrong.
I don't know how to set things straight.
You've been drinking too much.
A little less drink...
Drinking is the least of my problems!
What's going on here?
Are you getting drunk already?
Why are you here?
Have you heard that Gi Tan's taking over Dodo Group?
What?
It's no time to be getting drunk.
If he loses the company,
Gun Woo will give Soo Yeon whatever the Pandora's Box is!
Where are you?
Let's meet up.
Why should I meet you?
What does that mean?
I don't have to see you ever again.
Don't call me.
I heard about the company.
I have a great idea, so...
It's all over.
Don't even dream of persuading me.
Gun Woo, what are you planning?
Gun Woo. Gun Woo.
Find out where Gun Woo is.
There's no need to.
I talked to Mr Han. The Pandora's Box...
is inside Gun Woo's safe.
I'll get my hands on it very soon. Just wait.
We checked the safe already.
It was empty. What are you talking about?
What? Wait... Mr Han...
Did he lie to me again?
Choong Dong, I need you to...
call the guys.
Yes, Sir.
Can we talk for a moment?
I have nothing to say to you.
I have something to say.
I thought about it...
and I don't know what I did wrong.
I did all I could to save the company.
And to win your heart.
What's wrong about that?
You deceived me.
I did not.
If you had given me time,
I'd have given you the proof...
to send Il Jae to prison.
You can say all you want, but I can't trust you any more.
I just can't.
I will give you...
what you want, Soo Yeon.
The Pandora's Box.
Are you the one who had that?
I won't give you up, Soo Yeon.
Did you find something?
Go Hae Sool moved to the US, but I'm suspicious of Han Sang Goo.
What do you mean?
He just put out his apartment for an urgent sale.
His wife and daughter suddenly moved to Canada a few days ago.
I think you're right, Boss.
We'll buy his apartment.
Pardon?
Oh, okay.
I want to be there, but I need to sell the place first.
I'll go over to Canada as soon as everything is settled.
Okay. I'll get five million dollars and leave.
I've had enough of this life.
Yes.
I'm the real estate agent.
Right, does someone want to buy my apartment?
They want to sign the papers today.
I see.
It'll take him about an hour.
We're fine.
They will wait.
Sure.
- Please, sit. - Sure.
Why are you so surprised?
Anyone would get surprised if you suddenly stand from behind.
Are you selling your apartment?
What?
Oh, yes.
You just moved there.
Mr Kim, I have an urgent business. I have to go right now.
Please tell the chairman for me.
Auxiliary power is on. Safe unlocked.
Do you still have the Pandora's Box?
Did you do this?
- What? - Did you steal it?
Han Sang Goo did steal it.
Are you sure he's at the office?
I checked in on him just now.
(Chairman)
Mr Han, wait.
Stop.
- Let's go. - Yes.
That's Han Sang Goo.
Follow him.
Chairman, that's Il Jae.
The car behind him is with him, too.
I don't care who it is. I won't let anyone take it away.
Get closer.
Yes, Chairman.
My goodness.
It's Gun Woo.
Chairman.
Hello?
I'm Han Sang Goo.
I am the informant behind the Pandora's Box.
Will you send me the money as promised?
Of course.
Il Jae and Gun Woo are chasing after me right now.
If you don't save me right now, they will take the Pandora's Box.
Please save me, Chairman Kang!
Where are you?