(Final Episode)
Chairman.
Hello?
I'm Han Sang Goo.
I am the informant behind the Pandora's Box.
Will you send me the money as promised?
Of course.
Il Jae and Gun Woo are chasing after me right now.
If you don't save me right now, they will take the Pandora's Box.
Please save me, Chairman Kang!
Where are you?
I am...
on the streets of the industrial park.
The streets of the industrial park?
We're on our way.
What's our mid-point?
Dongchon Farm.
I'll meet you at the entrance of Dongchon Farm.
Even if you get caught by Il Jae,
do not tell him where the Pandora's Box is.
Do you understand?
It's a red light.
- Just run it. - It's too dangerous.
Just run it.
Follow them.
Hey. It's over.
Get him. Get him.
My goodness.
Get him in the car.
Why are you doing this to me?
Hey.
What do you think? Don't you know?
- Get him in. - Yes, Sir.
Chairman. Chairman!
You can't take Mr Han.
Why not?
Will you find the Pandora's Box and give it to Soo Yeon?
Chairman, save me.
What are you doing? Take him away.
Hand him over.
Chairman.
- Chairman. - Save me, Chairman.
Chairman, save me. Chairman!
Beat him to the point of near death.
- Yes, Sir. - Byun Il Jae!
Chairman.
I will give you what you want, Soo Yeon.
The Pandora's Box.
Soo Yeon.
Let's go. Get in.
No.
Chairman, are you okay?
I'm sorry, Chairman.
This is bad. We need to go after them.
Chairman.
You can't leave like this. I have to get you to a hospital.
Soo Yeon is waiting for me. I have to keep my promise.
Chairman.
It's Gi Tan.
Where are you, Mr Han?
I'm already here. Why aren't you coming?
Il Jae...
took Mr Han away.
Gun Woo?
Gwang Woo is with Il Jae.
If you don't do something, Mr Han will tell everything.
Then the evidence to prove Il Jae's murder will be gone forever.
Which way did they go?
They went toward Incheon.
I'll call the police. You follow them.
Drive over to Incheon.
I'll take you to a hospital.
I will give you the Pandora's Box.
Are you the one who had it?
I'll give it to you tonight.
We'll talk again then.
(Do Gun Woo)
It's been two hours. We can't find him like this.
This is bad.
I don't think Han Sang Goo will hold out for long.
Don't you know where it is?
I know nothing.
Han Sang Goo.
Do you know how brutal and cruel these guys are?
How long do you think you can hold out for?
We haven't much time. Begin.
Yes, Sir.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm...
Who's calling?
It's an unknown number.
Let's not take weird phone calls.
Hello?
Do you need the Pandora's Box?
Who are you?
I'm the informant who called Lawyer Oh's TV show.
Have you seen the show?
Man Ok became the director and tried to get the 20 million dollars.
- However, she failed... - Who is this guy?
How can you prove that you have the Pandora's Box?
I see something like this.
"January 3, 2005."
"Murdered the directors of Sudo Hospital."
I also see names like these.
Lee Guk Cheol, Jung Man Ok and Go Joo Tae.
Do you need more proof?
What do you want?
Kang Gi Tan offered me three million for the file.
How much can you give me?
Are you trying to bargain with me...
using the file?
Based on what's written about you,
I'd say it's worth at least 10 million.
Let's say five million. What do you think?
I'll need some time to get...
that much cash together. Can you wait?
I don't have much time. I'll call you back.
Do you think Il Jae will buy it?
I'm not sure.
I should give him a little nudge.
Five million dollars?
That means he doesn't have it.
I really don't know where it is.
Believe me.
(Unknown number)
It's an unknown number.
It'll be him. Answer it.
- Hello? - Do you want...
the Pandora's Box?
Who are you?
I'll keep it short.
If you want the files,
bring me six million dollars.
He wants an extra million.
How do I know if you really have it?
The files say that...
you told Byun Il Jae to kill Sudo Hospital's director.
You're rich.
I'm sure you can get six million dollars just like that.
I can.
That much is chump change to me.
Where shall we meet?
No, no. Forget that.
You can come to us.
Are you insane? We can't trust him.
We can meet him somewhere else.
Where are you?
Mapo? You're quite far away, then.
We're at...
I know the place.
Sure.
Gwang Woo fell for it.
Go to the parking lot in Yeonsu-dong.
That's just 20 minutes away.
It'll take him at least an hour to get from Mapo to here.
I will go and wait for him there.
If I sense something's off, I'll get out.
Okay?
Which of you will go with him?
I'll go, Sir.
I think that's him.
Don't get out until we're sure.
I'll try to negotiate with him.
Attack from behind.
- Yes, Sir. - Good.
Don't you think we got here too soon?
It's him.
Hello. Where about are you?
The traffic's terrible. I might be late.
How much longer will you be?
About 40 minutes?
Do you have the money?
Of course I do.
Do you know how much cash I have lying around?
Six million dollars is...
Kang... Kang Gi Tan.
It's over, Gwang Woo.
Stop him. Get out and stop him.
Stop him!
Get him!
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm absolutely fine.
Shoot.
Tell me where...
Han Sang Goo is.
Do you think...
I'm crazy?
Why would I tell you that?
Turn yourself in...
and tell everyone what you did.
Me?
I'm giving you...
one last chance for poor Shin Young's sake.
Forget it.
Without those files,
no one can prove anything.
Instigating murder? Are there any witnesses?
Bring me one!
Gwang Woo.
Will you not give in?
Dodo Group's in pieces because of you.
Isn't that good enough?
Will this...
bring back the dead?
You're...
not even human.
Shut your mouth.
Fight me.
My parents are dead because of you.
It all started with you.
Sir!
That's enough.
He's out cold.
Sir!
Sir.
I checked his black box.
Mr Han's at an abandoned factory 10 minutes away.
Call...
the police.
Yes, Sir.
He's taking too long.
Your call has been forwarded to...
I think we should go somewhere else.
Bring him.
Get him.
It's the police. Get out of here.
- Stop! - Freeze!
Stop!
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Thank you for saving me.
Where's the file?
Don't worry. It's somewhere safe.
Mr Kim told us what happened.
You're lucky. It could've been worse.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise, Soo Yeon.
It's okay. I'm glad you're safe.
If Mr Han has been taken away by Il Jae,
that means the Pandora's Box is probably gone for good.
- Yes. - I found Mr Han, Soo Yeon.
Can you come now?
Where to?
Okay. I'll be there.
Gi Tan found Mr Han.
Then are we finally going to find the Pandora's Box?
I'll go over, Gun Woo.
- I'll be back. - Okay.
We will finally see the end of Il Jae.
I've had enough of him.
(Charged for the murder of Go Joo Tae)
Sir.
The police called, and they lost Il Jae.
Don't worry, Soo Yeon. He'll get caught soon.
First, we have to file a report to the police.
I have a live broadcast tomorrow.
I will reveal the truth...
to the world.
The truth behind the death of Sudo Hospital's directors was revealed.
Lawyer Oh, did you finally find the evidence to prove it?
Yes. We obtained a total of three voice recordings.
Please listen to the first recording.
All I will lose is just myself.
What about you?
People will find out Dodo Group's eldest son instigated murder.
You won't just destroy yourself. You'll destroy everything...
your father has spent his life to build.
Do you want me to make it easier for you?
Our position changed.
I will be the one to negotiate and threat,
- not you. - What is this about?
Can you tell us what the situation is, Lawyer Oh?
The person who instigated murder in this recording is...
the former vice-chairman of Dodo Group, Do Gwang Woo.
Honey.
Is she saying that Gwang Woo instigated murder?
He's currently being investigated for murder instigation.
The second voice recording holds more solid evidence.
Let's listen.
Don't worry, Choong Dong.
No one will find the evidence that I killed the directors.
Their son told the police about a possibility of a murder.
No one will believe a blind kid's words.
Also, Guk Cheol trusts me completely just because I'm his uncle.
He can never even imagine that I could've killed his parents.
The voice in this recording is...
the former Seoul mayor-elect who was charged with corruption.
It's Byun Il Jae.
This is very shocking.
It's very scary how someone like this was...
elected as the mayor of Seoul.
What's the last voice recording about?
It's about director Jung Man Ok, who shortly took over Sudo Hospital...
right after the directors' death.
Hasn't the real criminal already been caught?
You will see that the truth is different.
If Go Joo Tae falsely claims Guk Cheol is behind all this,
Sudo Hospital will be mine.
Because Hwang Ji Soo killed Jung Man Ok,
things just got better for us.
Father.
What is he talking about?
I got two things at once.
I became Sudo Hospital's director and Hwang Jae Man's son-in-law.
Did you really kill Jung Man Ok?
Wait, is this Hwang Ji Soo...
You're right.
She's the daughter of the president-elect Hwang Jae Man.
I was afraid this would happen.
I didn't know she would reveal everything.
What will I do, Father?
No wonder it was called the Pandora's Box. It's shocking.
Who and why did this person gather all these evidence?
There are shadow agents in Dodo Group's Secretary's Office.
These were recorded by them under the order of Chairman Do Choong.
Byun Il Jae and Oh Choong Dong are currently on the run.
If anyone sees them, please make a report to the number below.
Lastly, Lawyer Oh has a word to share with us.
One murder case of Byun Il Jae has not been revealed yet.
What is it?
Oh Choong Dong.
Turn yourself in.
You are the only one who can testify...
for my brother's wrongful death.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Please, I ask of you.
Turn yourself in and tell the world...
that Il Jae killed Dong Soo.
Turn off the TV.
I know who you are, Choong Dong.
Stop acting as evil Il Jae's dog.
Please live...
a new life.
Turn it off!
Wait.
Are you getting convinced by those meaningless words?
Why won't you answer?
The innkeeper knows our face. Let's get out of here.
- Great job today. - Great job.
Great job, Soo Yeon.
Thank you. It's all thanks to you, Gi Tan.
I'm sure Dong Soo and my parents...
can rest in peace now.
Don't cry any more.
Live a happy life for yourself.
You too, Gi Tan.
Thank you, Soo Yeon.
You should take care of Dodo Group now.
Get ready for a press conference.
KT Corporation decided...
to propose a take-over bid for the stock shares...
of Dodo Pharmaceutical.
Does this mean you are holding a hostile takeover process?
Yes.
Why are you so sure that you will gather 51 percent of the shares?
It's because Chairman Do Gun Woo is...
incompetent.
Things won't go your way, Gi Tan.
Dodo Pharmaceutical will be sold over...
to Geukdong Pharmaceutical, not KT Corporation.
Has this been decided?
I've been in contact with Geukdong Group's Chairman Yoon.
I believe you don't have much shares in Dodo Pharmaceutical, Chairman.
My father has entrusted me with everything about Dodo Group.
Chairman Do Choong's shares are my shares.
How can he give the holding company to Geukdong Group?
Gun Woo must be insane.
He's making a statement that he won't give it to you, Chairman.
Gun Woo.
Sir. Chairman Do Choong is here.
Dad, what brings you here?
Chairman Kang.
I will sell the shares...
I have in Dodo Pharmaceutical.
Dad.
So please...
forgive...
me...
and Gwang Woo.
I will revive...
Dodo Group once again.
Thank you.
What have you done?
Why did you sell your shares to Gi Tan?
Do you know...
how many people...
work for Dodo Group?
Including the suppliers...
and their families.
Tens of thousands of lives are at stake.
I just can't bear to...
let them down.
Father.
You can...
leave me...
now.
Are you...
abandoning me?
You are...
my son and will be forever.
But...
now,
I can only love you from afar.
(Pawn shop)
Thank you.
You appear on the news every day.
Shouldn't you be in hiding?
This is Oh Soo Yeon's car.
Open the door.
Are you going to kill her?
If Gi Tan didn't get in the way,
I'd have gotten everything I wanted.
Why don't you kill him instead?
This gun's loaded with two bullets.
I'll kill Soo Yeon first, and then Gi Tan.
Come to the junkyard when you're done.
We'll have to take care of Soo Yeon's body.
Move and I'll shoot.
(Unknown number)
(Oh Soo Yeon)
Gun Woo.
There's something I didn't tell you earlier.
I didn't feel it at first,
but...
I grew to like you.
Take care.
Where...
are you?
I love you, Father.
I mean it.
(Oh Soo Yeon)
(Unknown number)
Soo Yeon's in danger.
What do you mean she's in danger?
(Do Gun Woo)
What is it?
What?
How dare you think...
you could get away with ruining my life?
How dare we?
You're dying because of Gi Tan.
Don't blame me. Blame him.
Now I see what made you kill my brother.
- What? - You thought it would be fine.
You thought he's just a waste of space...
while the world needs someone like you.
You thought my brother should sacrifice his life...
for your lofty cause and ambition.
Am I wrong?
You got it right.
That's why you're a failure.
What?
You don't respect people or lives.
It's not me or Gi Tan.
It's your greed.
That's what took you down.
Shut your mouth!
Soo Yeon!
Gun Woo!
Run, Soo Yeon!
- Gun Woo. - Now!
My phone. My phone.
Die, Il Jae. Die!
Don't come over, Soo Yeon. Stay there.
Gun Woo!
Don't come here!
Gun Woo.
Stay with me.
Gun Woo. Wake up.
Don't die.
Gun Woo.
Sir!
Sir.
What did you do with Soo Yeon?
Don't you dream that this is the end, Guk Cheol.
Where's Soo Yeon?
Gun Woo, hold on. Hold on just a little more.
Don't let go of yourself.
I'm glad...
that I could...
protect you.
I wasn't late...
like I was to my mum.
Stop talking, Gun Woo.
Save your energy.
Gun Woo.
Forget...
everything.
Don't remember anything.
I don't...
want you to be hurt because of me.
Don't give up, Gun Woo.
You will live.
I can't let you go like this.
It's so cold.
Hold me.
You will live, Gun Woo.
You're warm.
Like...
my...
mum.
Gun Woo.
No.
Don't die, Gun Woo.
Soo Yeon.
You're wanted right now.
Go to the police station to turn yourself in, not here.
Let me...
stand as a witness for Dong Soo's murder case.
I'm very sorry.
I, Hwang Ji Soo,
accidently murdered...
the former director of Sudo Hospital...
Jung Man Ok back in 2006.
I deeply regret my action...
and I put down everything...
as the daughter of the president and as a congresswoman.
So, why did you want to see me?
Il Jae's final trial will be held soon.
He was already sentenced to life in prison.
His sentence won't be reduced. Do not worry.
Give him a death penalty.
The ruling will be given by the judge.
It's not for the president to interfere.
It's not fair for Il Jae to live. Both legally and morally.
I understand what you're saying.
There is one more thing.
You must execute him while you are still in your office.
This is the first and the last request I make to you, President.
Breaking news.
Byun Il Jae, the criminal behind death of Sudo Hospital's director,
Cha Dong Soo and Do Gun Woo was just sentenced with a death penalty.
Did you think I'd rot in prison forever? You're wrong, Guk Cheol.
You will be executed.
Nonsense.
No one has been executed over the last 20 years.
The president promised me.
He will execute you.
You must be scared of death.
I thought so. You've committed many crimes.
If you get meat in your soup,
that means it's your last meal.
Do not think about visiting me at the prison, Guk Cheol.
Don't repent.
That way, you'll be punished properly.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Isn't our party way too small?
Come on, this can't be the end.
Do we have something else?
I have...
something to tell you.
Mr Moon, what was your dream?
It wasn't anything big. I spent my youth in Dodo Group...
Dodo Group...
will be yours, Mr Moon.
- Pardon? - Please be the chairman.
That's your position.
I'm sure...
you'll do a much better job.
But still, Miss Do is here, too.
I don't care about the company. You can take care of it.
Chae Ryung.
Yes, Boss.
Huaping...
is yours.
Boss.
Don't call me boss. You're the boss from now on.
Why are you doing this, Sir?
All right.
Let's make a toast.
Soo Tak. What time did you say Soo Yeon's flight was?
Will you really never return to Korea?
Thank you for everything.
You too, Nan Jeong.
Can we visit you in Germany?
Of course. I'll call you often.
My goodness. Can you even speak German?
Bonjour?
Go on. You'll be late. Give us a call, okay?
- Sir, please give us a hand. - I'm fine.
- I can do it. - No. Sir, please take this.
Shouldn't you go and talk to her?
I can't...
hold her back.
Soo Yeon's face...
was the last thing...
I saw.
Dodo Group's Do Gwang Woo who was jailed for instigating murder...
was pardoned by the president after two years.
His sister Do Shin Young...
will receive the Swiss International Volunteer Award.
She has been travelling Africa for the past two years...
to care for orphans who lost parents in wars.
Sir.
Byun Il Jae will be hanged today.
If you get meat in your soup, that means it's your last meal.
4529, come out.
What for?
Come out.
No! Let me go!
Let go of me!
I'm sorry. Let me live.
Don't kill me. I want to live.
Honey, it's Gwang Woo's first meal at home.
You should do it.
Let's stick to the ritual.
You do it.
I want you to do it.
What... What are we going to do?
Okay.
I'll do it.
He...
has a lot to repent.
It will take some time.
What? Repent?
Bok Shin.
- Yes? - See if he opens his eyes.
Let's pray.
Thank you for the food you blessed us with.
Thank you.
Am... Amen.
You don't say that yet.
I pray that my family...
does not sin or commit a crime.
Dear God.
Please look down upon us.
I beg of you with all my heart.
The chairman is here.
Tell them not to greet me like this any more.
- It's old-fashioned. - Yes, Sir.
Sir. Soo Yeon just flew in today.
I think she flew back to mourn Gun Woo.
Where is she now?
(Do Gun Woo)
Why are you here?
Have you heard about Mr Kang?
I heard that he went blind.
He's scheduled for surgery to extract the bullet.
Surgery?
He'll live less than a year if he doesn't have the surgery.
Didn't you say the survival rate was very low?
It was two years ago.
Doctor Campbell said the success rate is 30 percent.
That means there's a 70-percent chance he'll die.
I was hoping you could stay with him until the surgery.
He doesn't say so,
but he still misses you.
Please, Lawyer Oh.
He can't go a day without painkillers.
I know him well.
He won't...
want me to see him like that.
That's what bothers me.
There is a way.
Welcome, Chairman Moon.
You're still the same.
Thanks for coming, Soo Yeon.
Where's Gi Tan?
This house used to be Guk Cheol's.
He bought it back.
Are you sure about this?
He's a tough man to cheat.
I'll be fine as long as he is.
I might die.
It'll hurt you more.
Why did you come back?
Hello, Sir.
Welcome, Chairman Moon.
Dodo Group's doing pretty well.
Thanks to you, Sir.
I hired you a new maid.
She's smart and hard-working.
Her name is Yeon Mi Jeong and she's...
I don't like her name.
Send her away.
She can't speak. She won't get on your nerves.
Ms Yeon.
I'm very picky.
Three warnings and you're out.
Ms Yeon.
Don't treat me like a patient.
That's one warning.
Don't touch me.
That's two warnings.
Gi Tan.
I'm sorry.
Move your face.
Three warnings.
You're fired.
It's time to leave for the hospital.
I just fired Ms Yeon.
Very well, Sir.
Come with me, Sir.
I'm sorry, Soo Yeon.
I don't want you...
to hurt because of me.
I'm sorry.
Jeong Eun.
You're so silly.
Did you think...
I wouldn't recognise you?
Guk Cheol.
I'll be waiting.
Come back alive.
I promise.
Okay.
Gi Tan.
(Thank you for watching Monster.)