Sub by VIKI
Ripped & Synced by @SULTAN KHILAF
Follow My IG
@sultan_khilaf_sub
Episode 7
We had a beer together just now,
Manager Shin is missing and she
doesn't answer the calls.
Yeon Hwa, what are you doing here?
And you are not reachable.
I'm not in the mood to talk.
Yeon Hwa.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Han Chul, why are you sorry for me?
I couldn't stop it.
So could I.
I am mad at myself who couldn't stop.
So don't feel sorry, Han Chul.
I know.
But still, it feels it's my mistake.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better now?
I cry so often in front of you.
Right.
I'm thankful that you were caring for me.
Why smile?
No worries.
Let's go!
Not yet. It doesn't feel right yet.
It's not 100%. There is one thing I still can't remember.
Excuse me, CEO. Ya Chae is on her way to pick you up.
I'm cold.
Hold on, get up. Let's wait inside.
Can you stay next to me, just like this?
Yeah?
I'm cold.
CEO, you seems drunk...
Stay here with me, mom.
I'm not your mom...
Don't go mom.
You son is well grown up.
No no no. I'm not the mom!
Oh no.
Yes, thank you.
Gently, please.
Wow you're full of energy, this is heavy.
Inside, put them inside.
Uh?
Hello!
You are here! What about other teams?
They will be here soon.
The stuffs are here early.
These are the first round, couple more times to come.
Hey, that should be out last.
I had no idea I would be doing an urban life I've dreamt of like this.
Tho it's better, we were worried.
Let's move first. We have a long day ahead us!
Wait what's this?
I mean the management team will use the upper level?
Are they gonna monitor us or what?
That's the random ping pong table in the middle of the office.
It's for employees' indoor sports activity.
Whenever you want, go enjoy!
Ah, the management team is working here,
in front of CEO's table, feel free to enjoy?
Feel free to!
Are you messing with us, this is non-sense!
Don't you think I've outdone myself with the tight budget I had to work with?
Yes, I do. You did good.
What is it?
What's that?
They are here to monitor us?
CEO's room, as well as the management department, and employees' beneficial facility
This is?
But can we do something about this wall?
It's so empty.
I feel like I'm working in the storage.
The outside looks good.
It's because of the budget, please understand.
CEO, this is ridiculous.
Think about the image of Gaming company.
Internal is more important, you gotta give up the exterior.
CEO, I'm the team lead for the design team.
You can't say that to someone who's in charge of exterior.
When you work, you can look at the monitor only.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Gosh, I can't take this.
Please purchase 10 cans of paint. We'll take care of it.
As the design team leader,
I can't accept having to work in a building where there's no sense of beauty.
Why don't you work during that time?
We won't let it interfere with our work.
We'll do it from time to time. So don't worry.
All right. Then I'll approve only five cans.
Fine, do that.
I'll purchase the rest with my own money.
I'm so sorry. I was going to watch your show last night...
Geez, forget it, man.
There's no need for us to stare at each other.
No one showed up?
Not even one?
There were some people who clicked wrong.
One or two.
They left after about 10 seconds or so.
You should've hung onto them, so they won't leave.
Oh, the Crazy One.
Crazy One?
You drink it.
I said you're dead if we run into each other again.
How will you do that?
Where are you going?
Please tell me how you're going to kill me before you go.
Don't follow me.
"Don't follow me."
Hey. What are you doing?
Give it.
You don't like 7-Up?
I was trying to make up.
All right, all right. I'll groom you.
You'll gain at least 500 audiences if you do the show with me.
Crazy One, is this fun for you?
You mean life?
Should we have a deep discussion sitting here?
Here. Hop on.
I don't know what you ate wrong.
Stop bothering me and go away!
Geez.
Hey, I don't smell anything.
My ex-boyfriend said even my fart smells like perfume.
But you know... you're enjoying me following you around, huh?
Aren't you happy to receive attention like this?
I know it, too. Attention seekers recognize each other.
You want me to continue to follow you around, huh?
Right. Who can stop a crazy person from thinking that?
You have no idea where you're going right now and you're just circling the field.
Isn't that asking for me to follow you around?
When my head is all mixed up, I just like to walk.
Why are you all mixed up in your head?
Is it the money I took from you?
I'll give back the 3 million won. Tell me your account number.
I won't fall for it again. Stop the bulls***.
Wow, you're quick.
I think I can get 6 million won out of you if I keep provoking.
Hey! You're really dead. I'm not kidding you.
Okay, okay, let's work harder.
I'll push for 6 million won!
You really want to die, huh?
Hey, this is how you make money.
You said you want to make money, didn't you?
Just be aggro like me. Whether you kill me or not, that's not important to me.
I just need the attention. I succeeded then.
Do you understand?
So what am I supposed to do?
Tell it to me straight if you're going to teach me! Hey!
Hey, Crazy One!
The Crazy One and the Lunatic combo...
It's a killer.
Right. That's definitely a watchtower.
Right? For some reason, I feel the stare in the back of my neck.
The budget... It's all done.
The cost of the paint and labor. It's all in here.
Then the interior walls. You didn't do it intentionally? That's not much of a savings.
- Move forward with the budget.
- What?
To spend money on amateur vendors when we have professionals. That's also a waste.
- What are you saying?
- Approve the cost of 10 cans of paint and use the labor cost as a bonus to the designers.
Use the same budget to utilize professionals and get all the credit.
It's not about taking the credit. It's a win-win situation.
Win-win? You're the only one who wins all the time.
CEO, where is the conference room? We have a shareholders meeting coming up.
Would they come all the way here? It's such a bother.
- But you never know. Shouldn't we still set it up?/- We can.
The conference room. Over there.
That ping pong table? How is that a conference room?
Mr. Song, you're right. It's a conference room.
Ping pong table (sounds like "grand conference room") conference room.
Ping pong table conference room?
Whoa. Daebak.
Unless they're part of the management team, there aren't any shareholders who'd come all the way here. Just do it here.
Our headquarter location is perfect!
We can get things done in a speedy manner.
What the heck?
Why is this here?
It's quite malicious.
What's going on?
Take a look here.
Someone posted the Joybuster
proposal on the game community site.
Do all the titles say, "Examples of game proposal failures?"
I think they intentionally spread it online
to prevent from anyone using a portion of it.
Can you trace it?
It's a one-time use username and the IP is overseas. It'd be tough.
Seeing how there's no hacking record from the outside, I think it's done by the Taesan insider.
Materials that Taesan stole?
Anyone you're suspicious of?
Half of the company quit. It's not like we can be suspicious of everyone.
First, look for ways to strengthen the security for the planning team internal system.
Will do.
- Bye.
- Good work.
- Sunbaenim, can I have a ride home?/- No, I don't want to.
- Please?
- Okay.
- Newbie.
- Yes.
How about some chicken?
I should take a break tonight. I don't feel too good.
What's with you? Being this weak when you're about to eat chicken?
- I'm really not feeling well. I'm sorry. Goodnight.
- Hey.
Hey, hey! Hey, Newbie!
Forget it then.
Timing and Subtitles by The Level Up Team @ Viki
Thank you. But I don't drink sweet drinks.
Me, too.
What in the world?
It's not sweet at all.
Tastes nutty.
What is this?
What's going on?
A rat, rat, rat!
A rat?
Do something.
How can I catch it?
Aren't you capable of doing anything?
Epidemic hemorrhagic fever, salmonella, leptospirosis, Black Plague, etc.
They all come from rats. I can't kill it.
What do we do then?
I'll call the pest control tomorrow. Let's leave for now.
Aren't you going home?
I will.
You go ahead.
I'll go in a moment.
You're really a scaredy-cat. I never thought you'd be like that.
I know that you'd be seeing me from a negative perspective.
At least, you know.
I'm asking just in case. When we drank together last time,
did I make a mistake with you that I can't recall?
Getting drunk would do that to you.
So I did make a mistake, that means.
I won't make an issue out of that. So don't worry.
I saw a saying in a bar overseas that say, "Alcohol doesn't make you a bad person.
It reveals the bad person in you."
Are you afraid you're a bad person?
I'm just concerned.
I'm sure I didn't mean to do what I did.
But if that means I revealed my true self,
that'd be a problem.
You're so sensitive. AAA type.
How did such a sensitive person decide to sell Pigwar?
I don't get it.
How did you know about me selling Pigwar?
What do you mean how do I know that? Don't you remember?
- Did I tell you?
- Are you still drunk?
Gosh, I got the chills.
I'm perfectly fine. Clear minded.
I'm asking you when did we talk about Pigwar?
What do you mean when? You told me everything in front of your house that night.
Who the heck are you?
Oh, telling you then. I thought you were talking about sucking your thumb.
Wait, wait...
You mean you didn't apologize that night because of Pigwar?
I have no reason to apologize over Pigwar. It was a management decision made by the decision-maker.
The sales cost is nothing compared to the new project we'll develop...
Emergency Ward
Yeon Hwa, what happened?
Mr. Park.
No matter how angry you are, how can you crack CEO's head?
I'm sorry. I lost my temper.
It's late. I'll stay with him. You go home.
No, I'll stay.
Both of you, go home.
Oh? You're awake?
I'll leave after I sleep for a bit. You guys, go home.
I'm really sorry. I didn't mean to.
You can say you meant it. You took out your anger on me. We're even now.
CEO...
Yeon Hwa, he's fine since he's talking just fine.
Let's go.
It's okay. Let's go. Your bag.
It's okay.
You're the fastest one to react, Yeon Hwa.
I was wondering what would happen in the morning at the office.
What's going on tomorrow?
Huh? Didn't you do that after checking his email?
What email?
CEO sent a companywide email after work.
The reason he sold Pigwar. He revealed his position on the matter.
When the company is gone, Pigwar is gone, too.
Instead of our future that is in dire straits, we should survive
and make a history of our own.
In our developing future, I won't have to make such a decision as I was forced to make.
I believe in your ability to develop the next generation and further and better Pigwar.
Dear Joybuster employees...
I didn't know.
Well, he was sharing his thoughts with us.
It's one of the two.
Either you empathized with the manager's feelings
or you said, "That's what you think!" and cracked his head.
It's not like that.
All right, I got it.
Should I drop you off there?
Yes.
Thank you for the ride. Go home safe.
Okay.
Yeon Hwa...
He loves his company more than you think.
So don't see him in such a negative light.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Goodnight.
Timing and Subtitles by The Level Up Team @ Viki
Countryside sure is nice even though it's far.
We took care of every corner. You won't have any problems now.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
CEO, good morning.
Newbie, you're here early.
CEO, what happened to your head? Did you get hurt?
- A rat bit me.
- A rat?
Good job. Makes me feel great.
Take your time and drink this as you work. Pear drinks are great for cooling off.
Wait, wait, that's not how it is...
Ms. Shin.
- I didn't...
- Team Leader!
This is crazy.
- You're a hero.
- Don't say that.
After reading the CEO's email last night, I hoped someone would hit him over the head.
I look up to you for hitting him over the head first.
Right? Right?
- I feel great.
- Fine. I'm glad you feel that way.
If he does that again next time, I'll break his legs. Happy?
But honestly, I do understand CEO.
It's not like he had room to make another choice.
That's why I hoped someone would hit him just once.
I see.
Let's get to work now.
Yes, ma'am.
The shareholders meeting is on Monday. Print out the performance report.
I already did. 10 copies.
That many? We won't have that many people.
What's that? Is that our tent?
I'm not sure.
What is it?
Why is it here? Oh, this is...
It's not mounted. Let's move it, so we can move the car.
Okay.
What the heck? There's a person in here. I'm coming out.
- You should knock or something.
- What the?
I fell asleep.
CEO Jo Tae Goo!
- Mr. Kang!/- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
CEO Ahn, how are you...
What's wrong with your head? Did you get hurt?
Why are you here?
What do you mean why? I got an invite.
I was going to come down on Monday, but thought I'd be late. So I came early.
Wow, nice scenery. It's perfect for camping.
By chance, did you send over abalone?
Did you enjoy them?
A friend of mine runs a sashimi place in Noryangjin. He gave me a deal.
Wasn't it fresh?
Move your tent. This is a parking lot.
I'm sorry. It was tough to set it up.
- Help me.
- Careful.
That sounds great.
Oh? Wait!
- CEO!
- Yeon Hwa!
- Hello.
- Wow.
It's great to see you guys like this.
Why did you lose so much weight?
How have you been?
Just taking a break, you know.
- Newbie, aren't we going?
- Coming.
- Do you want something to drink?
- What?
- Iced Americano for me.
- Iced carmel macchiato.
Geez, he's so mean.
What can you do? Geez, I had no idea he'd be like that.
But you know...
- Curious about who he is?
- Yes.
It's Jo Tae Goo. He was the former CEO of Joybuster.
- Former CEO?
- We fired him.
But why would be come here?
He sold off all his shares and kept only one share. Only one.
But the problem is he has the right to attend the shareholders meeting with that one share.
Seeing the way he is, I think he came to ruin the shareholders meeting.
I wondered why it was so easy to get rid of him.
- Have some.
- Here you go.
Thank you!
Oh, Soo Jung.
- Soo Jung.
- Yes?
Did you have your baby's first birthday party?
- Yes, we did.
- Aigoo...
Why didn't you invite me? I'm sad.
How can I? It was the day after you got fired.
I would've still gone crying.
Thank you.
I'm ashamed of coming here like this.
I feel so bad toward you all.
Oh, no. Don't say that. There's no other CEO like you.
We feel bad for staying behind.
It would've worked out if we held out a little longer.
I had no power.
You need more strength. Eat meat. It's burning.
- You guys eat. - Okay!
I'll just starve tomorrow.
What in the world?
Are you telling us to eat or not?
Eat watchfully.
Okay.
Bottoms up!
Cheers!
Joybuster
I should still look the part.
5/30/2019, Regular Shareholders Meeting
Here is our performance report.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
One, two, three. Okay.
Why is your office so far away?
And what's with the stairs?
Chairman, hello.
How can the major shareholder miss the meeting?
Hello, Chairman.
CEO Jo, it's good to see you!
Hello.
Why are you standing? Sit down.
Thank you for attending our meeting even though it's so far away.
All right, we'll begin...
Just a moment. There are more shareholders on their way.
They'll arrive soon. Let's wait for them before we begin.
Ah, okay. Sure.
Then we'll give a few more minutes...
The rules are rules.
Begin on time.
Okay. Then, to follow the rules...
we'll begin the meeting with those who are present.
The shareholders are here.
Joybuster
Hello.
- This way, please.
- Let's go.
Who are all those people?
Our company shareholders.
An innovative IT company shareholders are all old fogies?
Shareholder meeting thugs.
Shareholder meeting thugs?
One share or 10 shares at the most.
They purchase a bare minimum amount of shares to attend the meeting.
They disrupt the regular process of the meeting. Professional meeting disruptors.
They came determined.
It's going to get noisy.
Why did you hide your office out in the boonies?
Are you serving water only?
The way you serve your shareholders sucks.
The 2019...
Joybuster shareholders meeting is convened.
We'll pay respects to our country.
Please stand and face the flag.
At ease.
We'll skip singing the anthem due to time constraints.
I object. We have plenty of time. Let's sing the anthem.
As part of the game industry that contributes heavily to the national economics,
we have a duty to sing our national anthem with our own voices.
I agree!
Of course! We shouldn't skip the anthem as Koreans.
We're a huge contributor to the nation's industry. Sing all four verses.
What kind of nonsensical company runs a shareholders meeting like this from the get-go?
All right, all right. Let's do it!
We should keep the formality.
Okay.
Then we'll sing the anthem.
♪ Hibiscus and the vast land ♪
♪ Beautiful land of ours ♪
♪ Koreans in Korea ♪
♪ Long live Korea ♪
I'll conduct a roll call.
Based on the procedure of the meeting, we have a special agenda in place.
From the total shares of 11,256,210,
we have the majority which is 5,610,007 shares in attendance.
I declare this meeting is convened properly.
As for settlement of accounts report, please refer to the report we passed out to you.
We'll move onto the business strategic plan report.
For the growth of Joybuster,
thank you for coming all this way to
all of you, shareholders.
For mass revenue structural reorganization, we canceled the contract with the former publisher
in order to develop Joybuster's independent service platform.
This is an important proposal
and it's a decision we can't afford to postpone.
I have a question.
To establish independent service without a publisher, you need a huge amount of financial support.
Please tell us how you'll acquire the funds.
That's right! Tell us straight!
How would you acquire the funds?
Be straight with us!
With what money?
You're such a fraud! If you'll do it this way, forget about it!
Shareholders.
Please restrain from creating commotion for the smooth progress of the meeting.
How can I yell right now, huh?
Who the hell are you? How dare you shut us up?
That's right! You think you own the company? Aren't we the owners?
I'll address you all.
With the balance profit from the business and from the sales of the Pigwar IP,
we can obtain the funds.
Wait. Stop. Did you just say you're selling Pigwar IP?
I already did.
I canceled the contract by handing over the IP (Intellectual Property) to the publisher
and I obtained funds to develop new projects and an independent publisher.
That was a way to gain both independence and support.
Stop lying.
If you sell off the Pigwar IP, you don't have any game to service.
How will you raise revenue after you've run out of money?
We're developing a new game.
You don't own the Pigwar license.
Do you mean you'll repurchase the license and make Season 2?
Is that your plan?
We also shut down Season 2 of Pigwar that we were developing.
We're currently developing new IP project.
What did you say?
Doesn't this sound too familiar?
In the end, you'll take the money what's left of the business. You pull all funds pretending to develop new projects.
That sounds like you'll take the money and run.
That will never happen.
We're currently in development for the new game.
I can guarantee an effective increase in revenue once we release internationally.
You'll give up on stable income
and you'll risk it all on a dangerous bet. What is that new project anyway?
I can't tell you that.
It's connected to the management strategy. It's confidential.
Confidential? You don't have to keep it a secret from us shareholders.
Not long ago, we had an incident where our proposal was leaked.
Since then, we decided to have only the strategic planning team to share the proposals.
That is our policy.
You expect me to believe that? Are you sure you have a plan?
I apologize, but the only thing I can reveal to you is that we're currently developing new projects.
Let's be honest here, CEO Ahn!
It's only been a month since you started. You're telling me you're developing a new game that will turn the table?
You think that makes sense?
We're currently developing.
So, you should explain to us properly what you're currently developing!
I've never seen CEO Jo so angry like that.
It's understandable.
He was told that his baby Pigwar was fold off and we're holding someone else's baby.
But no matter how angry he gets, the agenda will pass regardless.
I just feel sorry for him.
No. CEO Jo already knows that he can't stop it.
That's not why he's getting so angry like that right now.
Then what?
They keep a record of the meeting in the minutes.
They have an obligation to record everything and share with everyone.
He wants to make the issue public.
Public? What's next then?
If you don't have any plans for the next product,
I charge CEO Ahn Dan Te with malicious and risky business management,
the outflow of funds by selling IP, and breach of duty.
We got sucked into this.
Delete it from the record.
Don't miss a word.
Yes.
Look, look, take it away and look.
Let's see if you recorded everything.
Aren't you an employee here?
I'm a new recruit.
You should have a professional transcriptionist.
You're in it together playing games with us?
Look at this terrible company. From the get-go,
how dare you try to mock the shareholders?
08A1907725.
Take it out.
Yes, sir.
For transparency in our records,
We hired a newbie who has
a national certification for transcription.
Everything is being recorded. So please don't worry.
Certification
Application
Certification: Transcriptionist
Are you sure it's legit?
We'll check everything in the end.
There's no point. How much longer do you think your lies will last?
You should know this, too.
What I say is also being recorded in the minutes.
CEO Jo Tae Goo, you were fired from Joybuster, right?
You want to damage my reputation?
Did you get fired for lying all the time?
I don't lie.
Then what is your standard for lying?
You don't know?
If you can't keep a promise, does that make it a lie?
A company always announces its plans for the future.
It just hasn't come to fruition yet.
You're saying you only laid out the plan?
Is it any different if I do it?
Did you manage to keep your plans well to drive it to the ground?
You can't take me down with you like that.
I am trying to get you to stand with me. But I'm not saying we should both go down.
I'm saying this because I believe you didn't intend to lie either.
A company's plan is a decision made for the company to survive.
This is the truth.
You asked what my standard for lying is, right?
It's simple. If none of the employees working here believe you, it means it's a lie.
Do you all believe CEO Ahn's words?
See?
You can't say a thing even if you're reported.
I'll say an honest word about the new product development.
Fine. Come clean if you got caught.
Shutting down the project, selling Pigwar, and the opposition from the shareholders for canceling the publisher.
I expected all that.
Of course, I considered the fact that you'll doubt the validity of the new product.
However, what's important to us is a platform for us to jump off of.
We'll work on that platform first...
Don't bother with all the spiel. Cut to the chase.
I thought you liked that.
Do you have a new product in mind or not?
Do you or don't you?
Currently...
Don't drag this out and just tell them.
It's so frustrating. What are you doing?
I'm Shin Yeon Hwa, Planning Team Leader.
Stay out of it.
Since developing new product is my job, I can speak to you myself, right?
Sure. You go ahead.
Please step aside.
That's right. The person in charge wants to reveal it herself.
CEO Ahn, step aside if you don't have anything to say.
That's right. Move. Step aside.
Take his mic away.
Okay, Yeon Hwa. Speak.
Do you or don't you?
We don't.
That's right.
There's no way you have it.
To come up with new product funds, he sold off Pigwar.
I had to stand back and watch since I'm just an employee. But I can't stand back any longer.
I'll tell you everything.
Good job!
Okay. Tell us everything now.
We have nothing here.
It's just an empty office.
So, it makes me think every morning when I come to work.
It must be difficult for you.
This is so fun.
Fun?
You're pissed off at the company and want to throw thinner (sounds like fun) at it, right?
The excitement of filling out the blanks one day at a time. Don't you know?
It sure is fun. Just like this storage walls.
Should I tell you about our new project? Nothing.
Of course, it's just not in a physical form yet.
But in the planning team's brain, including mine, it's already completed.
Bring me the proposal.
He already said it's confidential and we're working on it.
CEO Jo, aren't you aware of the importance of security more than anyone else?
Yeon Hwa, what are you doing?
Two years ago, a competitor of ours
released a similar item and we took the loss.
You had to give up on the development balance we were owed and shut it down.
Why? Objectively speaking, their game was upgraded better than ours.
In conclusion, I took all the responsibility and stepped down.
So CEO Ahn should also...
I'm not talking about your fault.
We just don't want to repeat the same mistake.
If you're trying to get past this by saying it's confidential...
No, if we pass this agenda and close the meeting,
I'll brief you on the new product separately without having to worry about the minutes.
What do you think?
You're on his team now.
We're on the same team.
Yeon Hwa.
Joybuster was always on the same team.
You too, CEO Jo, and also shareholders.
We're all on the same team, aren't we?
No, you can't.
What Ms. Shin is suggesting isn't what the company desires.
We can share the info with no one else except for the development team.
CEO!
We even had a proposal leak the other day. How can we trust him?
How can we? We've known him longer than you.
Much longer and much closer.
CEO Jo Tae Goo will never...
make the wrong decision.
Fine.
CEO Jo, would you like to hear our report before you leave?
CEO, we're busy people, too.
That's right, CEO Jo. Decide what you'll do.
Turn over the table with these kids and wake them up!
I'll pass this agenda.
Chairman, sir.
Do you agree to pass?
I agree.
- Agreed!
Agreed.
The agenda has passed with a unanimous vote from the shareholders present.
The 2019 Joybuster Regular Shareholders Meeting is adjourned.
It's a new innovative product that emphasizes camaraderie among the users.
We've pulled all the technical and design capabilities that developed and managed Pigwar.
It will be a relentless project.
That's all.
It's not our style.
That approach is intentional.
I hope the users also feel that it's different from the usual Joybuster style.
What's Joybuster's branding identity?
"Bringing happiness to the world."
It may be different from the style of the games we've produced thus far. But it doesn't mean we've changed.
Another words, our branding identity hasn't changed.
Whose idea is this?
Joybuster's idea.
Why didn't you work like this when I was here?
This is great!
Great! Great! Great!
Great!
Push this forward just like this.
If there's any shareholder who interferes with this, I'll roll up my sleeves
and convince them by showing up at their house.
Got it?
Great. That's it!
Great, great, great!
Great, great!
CEO.
Good job. You're good at your job!
You should've been a team leader sooner.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Were you sad because I didn't side with you?
No way.
I feel bad.
What's your real reason for coming here?
I got nothing to do at home.
You weren't dreaming of conquering?
Could be.
Selling the company at such a low price. Did you anticipate this situation?
I can't see the future that well.
I understand that NexViper showed greater interest with a better offer.
I wanted to know what your real reason is for handing over the company to us.
I was so angry.
Somehow, we became their subcontractor.
And the company faltered because we didn't follow their order.
That's not why I had started this company.
I started it to make the game I, I mean, we wanted to make.
I completely understand how you feel.
CEO Ahn.
I don't care what kind of position it is.
Can I continue to work here?
Prohibited to work in the same market within three years. Did you forget the contract?
I want to make games.
You're at fault for the past failed management.
You should stop working with games.
But instead, I'll ask you for a favor.
A favor?
You may have failed the company, but you've come all this way focused on games only all your life.
I don't think you're a failure at that.
At the least, I can tell that by looking at the employees who protect and follow you.
CEO Ahn.
If I lack anything, as a life sunbae who has lived in the world of games,
I ask for your uncensored advice and criticisms.
I ask of you.
Is it too much?
Yes.
Last time when you came by the monastery, I didn't tell you why I hired you, huh?
You said you just hired me trying to be cool.
I thought you'd fight well in my place.
For Joybuster. Just like today.
CEO...
She's fighting very well with me thanks to you who hired her.
Do I fight for no reason?
You make up reasons to fight.
See? How can I not get upset?
Just think he's expressing his interest in you.
Celebrities say malicious comments are better than no comments.
You two have great chemistry.
CEO!
Am I overdoing it here?
Yes.
Goodbye, CEO!
- Bye!
- Goodbye!
What's wrong with this?
What's with the warning all of a sudden?
Just you, Soo Jung?
Yes, it's acting weird!
I'm ruined.
I typed everything up.
Wait. Don't tough anything, everyone.
Warning
What's going on?
We have a problem. This is an emergency.
Warning!
Warning
Timing and Subtitles
by The Level Up Team @ Viki
Level Up
As of now, we can't use the Elephant engine.
Two steps forward, one step back.
Do you have even one person around you that you like, Dan Te?
Could you meet the development deadline with Joseph Lee?
It's more than possible.
Hello, oppa.
What are you looking at?
It's my sister.
Which website do you think the NG cut appeared on/
Listen to my request and you can ask me a favor, too.
You said you'd do me one more favor, right?